When Baobao said this news
Shocked me
The green grassland is about to be transformed into a high-tech city
Ah, I feel a little reluctant to see the green grassland now
No need not let it go
We’re making a time capsule now
As a memorable
Come on digging
You’re here to help
OK, the hole is ready
Then it’s…
The time capsule is ready
I’m going to put the sling in
I want to send a letter to myself for the future
Humph…
Then I’ll put some snacks in
Paddi
You can’t put your snacks in.
Then I’ll eat it now
Brother and sister
We want to put the painting in the time capsule
Wolffy
I thought you would let your invention go in
This is a little gray-painted
What we painted is our past adventure experience
It’s something more important than invention
dad
In the future, I will go to more places to venture with you
No problem son
Then let’s close the capsule
Wait a minute.
I have something I want to put in
Go to have a meal
The last one didn’t eat
ah
Ahhhhh…
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
It doesn’t matter to you. Paddi
What a big scent
Go and have a look
That thing hits the front
This is…
What a big pit
Let’s continue to check it out
Be careful
What’s there in…
Is this pit caused by this strange stone?
If I guess it’s right
This…I was the protagonist of the season
Sparky
Thunder summons
Invented me to create
No response
Since that’s the case
Why don’t you give the stone to the village chief to see
Yes, the village chief explained the question of opening the stone
I can be the protagonist
Wait for us
Why can’t I find results?
The village chief has big discoveries
We just snatched this strange rock
what
That’s just…
Again…no response
I have to study it carefully this time
Researched for so long
Now I only know this stone
Huge energy
And there is a certain connection between the stone and the robot
But the technology still has no way to read it now
I’m going to study it again
What are you doing
The ritual is about to begin. You are still here
Almost forgot
Let’s go quickly
Then continue to analyze the computer
Wow, so hot
Today is our green grassland
A classic of transformation to a science and technology city
Science and technology development is the first production force
The green grassland will definitely be better in the future
good…
To commemorate a new beginning
Let’s take a photo together
Stand ready
Everyone eat something
Wait for a smoky sermon
Science and Technology City
Really looking forward to it
What will the green grassland become in the future
What will we become again
I…will definitely be taller than dad
I’ll be fine if I’m with everyone
I will continue to protect the goat village in the future and protect everyone
I’ll eat more in the future
You’re not going to be at all
What about you, Weslie
I will…
Wolffy
They wanted to cook but forgot to cook the roast
Then let’s go to the test room to get it together
OK Let’s go
Dad, I’m going, too
Be good, eat an orange first and wait for dad
After eating, Dad will come back soon
dad
Let’s go, Big Gray Wolf
Wait for dad
Don’t look at me just a goat (wolf)
How did the door open
Let’s go and have a look
Who is it
Is that strange stone yours?
You haven’t answered my question yet
Who are you
I’m here to goat
not good
What kind of weapon is this
It can actually turn things into iron
Delivery door
Can’t let him take that stone
Let’s chase
ah
What is this place
look
If he continues to fight, he will run away
Chase
My swimming is not very good
careful
You’re fine
It’s OK
He’s about to escape
Weslie Let’s fly over
ah…
And me…
Don’t think about it
stop
Haven’t Weslie and Wolffy come back yet?
Yes, I’m going to get tired
Wow, so beautiful
It’s a pity that Weslie and Wolffy can’t see it
dad…
stop
ah…