ah
woke up
Ah Robot
What do you want to do
Let go of the Wolf
It’s hard to be with the mysterious
What do you want to do
Don’t miss it
We found you were in a coma in the wild
I’m going to take you to the hospital
ah…
How to untie the clothes
It’s easy to lie on the ground
So I put on your clothes
Don’t think I’ll trust you easily
Look at the trick
What happened last night
I don’t know either
There’s that mysterious person
Let’s go back and ask Mr. Slowy
What’s here?
It doesn’t feel like it’s back to Yang Village…
Wow
Very high-tech
Why didn’t I know there was this place
Is it difficult to…is it the next prairie?
It’s much better than our green grassland
All high-rise buildings
There are so many robots
Hello, please ask how to leave the Qingqing Grassland
Green grassland? That’s it here
ah
What we are talking about is the green grassland in the Goat Village
Goat Village, keep moving forward here
Just pass another river
This is the Goat Village
The door is still the same as before
Why is it different?
What exactly happened here
Who are they
I can no longer walk
Is it really a goat village here?
Why did this king get lost?
Let’s go there and ask the way
Is it really a goat village here?
I actually got to ask
Hello, please…
Come on Come on Come on Come on
Watch my tiger hit
Look at my leopard swallowing mountains
- Finally I saw something familiar
Children
You should be careful
OK Mr. Slowy
It’s Mr. Slowy. It’s great
Mr. Slowy
What’s up
What’s going on in the Goat Village
No matter how different it is
Happy…Weslie
Yes… It’s Weslie
Weslie is back
- Where is it
Where to
It’s Weslie and Wolffy
- Weslie is back
Uh…what’s the situation?
oops
Old Goat, are you doing
Am I dreaming?
What’s wrong
Why are you crying
Slowy You’re very abnormal
Mr. Slowy
Why did she get all night? Goat Village has changed
Fifteen years
- ah? Fifteen years?
what…
We are fifteen years later?
Based on your previous description
Only this explanation
So it was the night fifteen years ago
We chase the mysterious
I accidentally came to this time and space now
Who is that mysterious person
What exactly does he want to do
Don’t worry about any mysterious person
What should we do
We went out for one night
But for us
You’ve been gone for fifteen years
- We’ve disappeared for fifteen years
Then everyone will grow up
Didn’t Wolnie and Wilie lose my love for fifteen years?
Mr. Slowy
Go back fifteen years ago
We will not disappear in the future
Uh-huh
So what can I do to send us back
I don’t know how Wolnie and Wilie are doing
I have to think about how to open the time and space tunnel
Have to wait for a while
no
I have to go back to the Wolf Castle to see the red and small gray grey
Oh…
What’s going on
The outside is so beautiful… so big
I didn’t expect the plan to be so long
It’s actually quite good
But why did the Elephant Star Stone suddenly shatter
I also want to know why
Doctor, what should we do next
Collect all the fragments of the star stone back
yes
Run quickly
Is that our gyroscope?
Why did it suddenly become bigger
ah…
Get out of here quickly
Why did such a big gyro suddenly come out?
I don’t know either
Always move it to an empty place
It’s empty…I understand
Go to Xinqiao
There is no connection in the middle of the bridge
You can pull the top down to solve it
good
You will first evacuate nearby residents
Leave the job of attracting tops to me
good
If this continues, it will harm residents
careful
You’re fine
It must first attract its attention
attract? This king is the best
Look at mine
Isn’t it just a small gyro
I’m not afraid of you
Little gyro, come and chase me
Why did you stop?
Are you tired? Are you sucked?
Can’t turn around anymore
Come and chase me Lalala
Or you only have this ability
What to do next
It’s really you
what?
Nothing
Go here
This gyro is so big
With our strength, we can’t stop it
I’ll think about what’s the solution
The road to Xinqiao has been arranged
This sound…
Take this route to avoid crowds
We will support you on the road, too
receive
Let’s go
Right
Turning so fast
I’ll give you a lower temperature
What’s going on
It’s getting more violent
It’s just right
Here
Where is the bridge
Front
Are you planning to lead it down?
That’s right
But it won’t hear it like this
That’s not to let it go
Come
Tibbie Preparation
Um
arrive
Success
Hide away quickly
Have you done it?
What’s up
Hahahaha it’s done
Ahem…this water fog is too heavy
Such a big spiral
It must be heavy if it falls
Too
ah?
When did so many people come
Welcome… Go home
Ah…what is going on
- Hahaha finally…
It’s been forced to them
- Are you…Baiyangyang?
And the sound just now
You finally come back
I’ve been looking for you for a long time
Tibbie?
I thought I would never see you again
- How to beat
It’s fine if you’re fine
You are…
Warm…Jonie
The changes have been too big in the past fifteen years
Don’t cry, everyone
Hahaha, what did the man cry?
Haven’t you cried?
Um?
This is…
Coming from fifteen years ago?
That’s saying
Fifteen years ago they didn’t miss it
But…
Coming to the present
So it was still the same as a kid
I didn’t expect that we really came fifteen years later
I don’t know what happened to Wolnie and Wilie
This is the fragment of the star stone
Elephant Star Stone?
The Elephant Star Stone was fifteen years ago
The mysterious man’s energy stone
I’ve been searching for information over the years
I found out that the head of this stone is a star stone
And this film should be fragments produced by the explosion at that time
After this fragment is combined with the gyroscope
The gyro turned into a monster
It should be like this
A piece of fragments is so powerful
That complete star stone
Its energy must be unestimated
I feel
Use the huge energy of this elephant star stone
Maybe I can send you back fifteen years ago
- Really
Just a guess
So you have to retrieve all the fragments of the Elephant Star Stone
good
That mysterious person will definitely continue to snatch the elephant star stone
If the complete elephant star stone falls into his hands
He will definitely be unfavorable to the whole world
No matter what the mysterious person’s purpose
We won’t let him succeed
Then let us guardians of Yang Village together
Keep your home again
Um