Village chief, let’s come here to have sex
Identify success
Wow
Village Chief This is...
Welcome to our new base
The next task is
Find scattered fragments of star stones
This base has a shaped feature
It can facilitate our actions
Wow, the village chief is indeed a treasure troubling
A base was built so soon
Actually, you missed
The village chief built this base
Convenient to collect signals from different places
Come find you
Right
These are all for you by my hands
Tailored equipment
Wow, that’s great
This glove can detect
The approximate location of the star stone
But at this stage, it can only be done
The monsters attached to the Elephant Star Stone react
and…
This wasn’t the time when the gyro beasts were beaten yesterday
Did you get the card?
Yes
I found that the star stone fragments attached to the items
There will be special elements
Just insert the card into the gloves
Weapons will get the corresponding attributes of cards
Wow, so bad
Nothing to do
Let’s go find the fragments now
Um
That...I want to go home first
I want to go back and have a look
What happened to Wilie and Red Red
Well, let’s act separately
Wolffy
You wait
Some things I want to tell you
Fifteen years ago
You and Weslie suddenly missed
No Wolffy found yet
A few months later
Wolnie delegated Wilie to me
Son Mom has been back in a few days
You have to listen to the village chief obediently
I’ll be obedient
Then come to find you alone
It’s dad
Dad is back
dad…
Wilie It’s me
I’ll give you food
Thank you
Wilie has been waiting for you to come back
Dad said he would come back after I finished eating oranges
Dad will come back
Dad... Dad is cheating someone, how about it...
He’s been waiting for fifteen years
Wilie’s expectations from the beginning
Slowly turned into disappointment
Finally, I don’t even want to mention you
How about it... Son Dad is back
The changes around are so big
But the Wolf Castle has not changed at all
I’m back
Still a familiar feeling
Son
Mom, don’t ask me for any auntie
I can take care of myself
Yes OK
- See you again Mom
who?
Who is there
Swallow auntie
You...hello
I’m your mother looking for you
No, aunty
I can take good care of myself
I didn’t expect my son to become so independent
No, from now on
I want to compensate for his father’s love
Wow…
I didn’t expect that the green grassland will change so much now
It seems that I have missed a lot of things
yes
It’s been fifteen years since I finished
But at least you can come back to us
Um
ah…
- There are monsters
There is a card reaction
Let’s go
ah…
My moisturizer
Ahem...
Cough cough...it’s so hard
The visual is so fuzzy
Don’t panic, everyone
We’ll want to get everyone out safely
Tibbie...
Tibbie I’ll go to lead the monster
You’ll evacuate everyone
But...you are alone...
Don’t worry
This is not the first time we have been a guardian of the Goat Village
Yes, be careful
Everyone follows my lights
Blue Blue Sniper
Found you
ah
Hit it
ah…
That’s right
Come and chase me
Next
Only the second floor is left without sweeping
So clean
Wilie, you’re here
Swallow auntie
You eat some fruit first
Dinner is about to be ready
Come on, I’ll give the bag I’m going to pack
Auntie, why did you help me get started
Oops nothing
Is it a fight
The ginger I made is delicious
I’ll give you one...
Gloves in the closure
There is a star stone monster nearby
This is...
Shadow Blade
Wilie There is danger outside
You can hide quickly
Are you trying to sweep or protecting the glass?
Go and have a look
This monster
He actually let go of so much smoke and hide himself
Where did you go
Wolffy
Beware that there are monsters hidden in the fog
Weslie...Brother
Are you...Little Huihui?
It’s really you...Pleasant Brother Goat?
When did you come back
I’ll explain it to you later
There is a moisturizer monster nearby
Keep me in touch with you, I will protect you
Moisturizer... weird...
It’s OK to be careful
Wilie Be careful...
This sound...
Swallow auntie?
This is...
Wilie, don’t leave me
Um
Where have you gone
There
Stone?
This is not a way to go on
Right
I’ve seen you
Hey!
Aunt…
Wilie, you’re fine
Look at your clothes are wet
Let the aunt help you...
Don’t come
ah? What’s wrong with you?
Oh no, when is the mask...
It seems that I can’t fit it anymore
Son
Son...
Dad... is back...
How did it go
Just one last step