What’s wrong? Big Grey Wolf
Wilie still ignores me
And I’ll go to his room to find him
He also locked the door
He liked me so much when he was a kid
dad…
Dad, let’s go there
Is it hard to tell me if Wilie wants to talk to me?
The Wolf I know
Is this easy to give up?
Even if he’s talking to you now
I believe you have a way, too
Reconciled with Wilie
Don’t forget that you are the King of Wolffy
Holy, right
I’m Wolffy King
I... won’t give up
One day
Wilie will understand your intentions
Just like you and the Black Wolf
I have to cheer up
Let’s go find the cards
Um
Weslie
You are my best friend
Mom He’s back
Where to find a card
No
Ah...I can’t eat it anymore...
Paddi
Blue Blue Sniper
Weslie, don’t move
They are just hotel chefs
ah?
Thank you for saving us
What’s going on
Master Qingyangyang, we have improved the formula again
The dishes have been greatly upgraded
But I’ve already eaten the seventh day today
Really can’t eat it
How about...
Cough... I probably just moved and my stomach became hungry again
Master, please come, please
OK OK OK I’ll go I’ll go
Let’s come together
good…
Wow…Is the restaurants in the future so fashionable?
Please enter
Welcome to the bottom of the grass
Wow, it’s so popular inside
Serve the dishes
Rising
There are thirty dishes in total, and there are...
and?
Hello everyone, my name is Lao Zi
I will perform the grassland horse for everyone
Master
These dishes are newly developed by our restaurant
What do you think of
Vegetables fresh and refreshing
The soup is just right, no oil or fat
Really good
only…
Remember what the master said
yes
This salad is so sautéed
There is no deserving level for this group of bombers
The dessert is actually in front of you
The main dish is next to it
There are also problems with the dish being served
These errors are too low
And the tea cup mouth actually cracked
But I still like Laozi’s performance
Let’s see in a comprehensive way...
Four Stars
The Goat has become a professional gourmet
Very terrible
Looking forward to Master Qingyangyang to be proud of his resignation
Weslie, have you eaten it?
Uh-huh
Let’s take you to a good place
Do what we used to do
Things you said you haven’t done for a long time
Just lying on the grass
Hee Hee, everyone is growing up
I rarely enjoy this leisure hahaha
In the past, you always said you had to eat 700 meals a day
It’s over the mark now
I can eat some more
But I saw you really do
It really surprised me
Our Paddi have become so bad too
It’s so good that your ideal has come true
Can eat a lot of delicious food
Delicious is delicious
But fresh ingredients plus serious ingredients
Baking, steaming and cooking are just right
Nothing missed
Isn’t that good?
It’s very good
But it’s so perfect
I still miss the imperfect taste before.
Imperfect taste...
Let’s go bake sweet potatoes
OK OK OK
I haven’t eaten roasted sweet potatoes like this for a long time
Ah, this is...
It’s the future firearm
Click here to fire
I bought this firearm
Why can’t I beat it
Ah...I can’t eat roasted sweet potatoes...
Let me come
It turned out to be diamond wood to make fire
It seems that I can’t even eat roasted sweet potatoes in this dish
alright
Very fast
Weslie is still so darn
Yes, it smells so good
Yes
Wow I haven’t eaten roasted sweet potatoes for a long time
Can robots eat?
I’m not a robot
I’m just a robot lover
I’m the robot
I really can’t eat anything
It smells so good
Go and have a look
Very fragrant...
Ah, roasted sweet potatoes...
I didn’t expect that roasted sweet potatoes would be so popular
Don’t swear, everyone
Haha, the sweet potatoes are ready
Let’s eat together
OK
Thank you for your sweet potatoes
- Thank you
All sweet potatoes are divided
Then let’s bake a little more
Um
What kind of fire device
Always bad
Really useless
There are cards nearby
Ah Where is it
Click... click the firearm... turn into a monster
It’s going to be hot, right?
Give you a fire...ahhhhh
ah
A fire occurs urgently
I’m so useless
Floating cannon
The floating cannon is ineffective for it
It has a flame shield
Can’t hit it without extinguishing the flame
fire? Yes, use water to deal with it
Um
I’ll lead it to the river
You go to ambush first
Then use water to suck it
good
A fire pointer that cannot be fired
Not catching fire, slightly...
Who do you say doesn’t catch fire
Wow...you’re so dangerous that it’s going to be fire
That’s it
Let me extinguish it
Sparky
I’m on fire here. Come and put out the fire soon
I’m here right now
Arrive at the river
Why is Weslie not out yet
Quick, Weslie
Hehehe...I’m super useful
Monsters
Look here
Ah, the flame shield disappeared
Take advantage of the current floating cannon
- Success
The fire on the road is gone
Go back and repair it
Sweet potatoes are ready
Dried potatoes
Alas, it’s a little burnt
Difficult
Have eaten sweet potatoes
How can I eat the slept now
Do you think it’s so bitter and not delicious
You see, he’s about to cry
Delicious, but you haven’t changed Weslie at all
The technique of roasting sweet potatoes is still so poor
whee
Ah, I didn’t change at all
You’re not going to eat
I’m going to finish eating sweet potatoes
Ah, leave it to me...