We can finally sleep together again.
But will this cause some trouble
Why is it so I’m not fat
Why are you here again?
What’s the relationship here
We used to sleep together often
Think about it, I really thought about it before
It took fifteen years without thinking
To me, it was something that happened a few days ago
Yes
But…
You will change so much in fifteen years
The goat has become a foodie
Do your favorite things every day
Sparky  You have become a firefighter
Every day, I’m working hard to protect the grassland
Um
This Lumang Sparky
Really become a firefighter
Do you have any comments?
Do you want to compare
OK, just compare
But it’s better than this
I’m going to join too
OK
You two come here even though
Take the call
Look at mine
I’m here too
Hahahahaha
Today we are going to find more card lines
What’s wrong with you
I didn’t sleep well on my face
- It’s not because of you…
Hahaha I really…
That’s because…
Are they still kids
- Don’t run
Youth is just running fast
What are you laughing at
Nothing
Just remembering your first time playing basketball
Just a person’s picture
Hum, it’s better for us to play
I’ll let you see what it means to be a real person
- good
Sparky Your skills have become worse
I was going to go
But the earthquake suddenly broke out
- I don’t listen I don’t listen I don’t listen I don’t listen
Hahaha
you…
It’s so good to have ice cream on such a hot day
Sparky , let me take a bite of your taste
There are also Weslie, please go eat his
Weslie, just take a bite
OK…
…It’s strange
- Ha ha ha ha
My ice cream
Don’t run Weslie
I haven’t had such fun together for a long time
yes
We seem to have forgotten something important
card
Didn’t we come out to find the card?
Gloves have reaction
Wow, Cao Cao is here
Construction site
Will it be there?
Is it true that we sneak in?
- Um
You can’t go in
It’s a child
What about your parents
My dad works here
Then why are you standing here?
I’m the guardian here
My dad said
If the safety helmet is broken, you cannot enter the construction site.
Especially you
This one you wear is a fake
You can’t go in
Go quickly. You can’t go in. You can’t go in.
- Sorry, we’ll leave now
Let’s go now
Go quickly
What to do now
Only look around here
None here
None here either
earthquake
What happened? Is it an earthquake?
Not an earthquake
It feels more like a shock coming from the construction site
Let’s go and have a look
- good
An earthquake…
Run quickly…
It’s the shock coming from that side
careful
- Almost fell
Here is the tunnel
It has collapsed now
It’s very dangerous here
Let’s go there
Not good…
Don’t be shocked
Be careful, you see
Making machine
Must be attached to the fragments of the Elephant Star Stone
Evacuate the crowd first
Go here
Everyone, hurry away here
Son Where are you
dad…
Big brother…
It’s very dangerous here. Go quickly
My son doesn’t see it anymore
I want to go back to find him
It’s too dangerous here
I’ll go find you and leave here
But…
careful
Ahhhhhhhh
Please believe me
I’m a firefighter
I’ll bring your son back
Then… I’ll ask you
Yes, don’t worry
All evacuated
Let’s go deal with monsters
Trapped it in
Don’t let it go out and destroy the city
well
Each is in place…
Action
Floating cannon
What a powerful destructive force
Help me it’s too powerful
Come
Did it succeed?
Run quickly
Have you forgotten me and you two
You are worthy of being
The goat is so beautiful
Leave it to me
- come on
come on
Do you feel weaker
Yeah yeah
It’s okay, goat
It’s OK
But this stalemate continues
The floating cannon will be exhausted sooner
What do you think about different things
Hello…you two
Let’s go find a good location to discuss the war
You can keep up quickly
You two guys who are not optimistic
Very dangerous
Almost fell
Help, Weslie…
ah…
You’re fine
Something is wrong
My float seems to be incomplete
Floating cannon, please cheer up
- It seems nothing is wrong
The floating cannon is ruined
It seems that it will take some time for us to climb up
It’s OK
Let’s hand it over to me next
Wait, Sparky
Next
You use this top first
We’ll go up and help you
Thanks
We’ll climb up to help Sparky
Let’s try this next
ah…
That kid at noon
It’s okay
After…back
I’m so scared…
Don’t be afraid
You won’t have anything to do
I will definitely protect your safety
Take you home immediately
Because…I am a firefighter
Brother, you’re fine
It’s OK
Tried more than ten times
Finally came up
- Big Monster
- Come and receive punishment
- What about monsters
What about here
- Sparky
- You’re so bad
Son…
dad…
Dad, I’m so scared
Nothing is done
Thank you
Um
elder brother…
Thank you, brother firefighter
goodbye
dad
Can I be a firefighter when I grow up?
Of course
Dad supports you
This is collected today
Have tried it
This is an ice card
Very good how much did they collect
Currently there are four
We need to speed up the process