Fragments...
Where will the Elephant Star Stone fragments be...
oops
Tibbie, you’re fine
Are you looking for fragments of Elephant Star Stone nearby?
yes
What about my pen
It’s that one
Ah Yes
Um? What’s it?
That’s my pen
Sorry, I didn’t mean it
It doesn’t matter…
Fortunately, I didn’t step on it
Tibbie This pen must be very important
This pen is the time when I became a reporter
Everyone gave it to me
Tibbie Congratulations on becoming a reporter
Look at the gifts everyone in the Goat Village gives you
I’ve given two copies
I’ll do three
I’m four
What a beautiful steel pen
I kept bringing it around when I was a reporter
No wonder you cherish it so much
It has accompanied me a lot
I love it very much
There is a reaction of the elephant star stone nearby
Where is it
That uncle just now
Weslie
There
What’s up
Can’t turn red lights
It’s dangerous for you to run like this.
sorry…
Weslie
You’re fine
Look forward to your brother
OK I’m sorry
Sorry, I was too anxious
By the way that uncle...
Not good He’s on the car
Wait a moment
Don’t worry, I have a way
I know where he went
Come on together
This is a shared skateboard
Can’t I borrow one?
Your identity has been registered and cannot be borrowed
How do you know where he is going
Details
He is wearing a work clothes and holding a tool box
There is oil on the clothes
It should be related to maintenance work
He has a company logo on his car
And the repair company of this brand around
There are 4 companies in total
And when the car just left
This little flower fell
This is a unique variety in the suburbs of the northeast
So only this place meets the conditions
Tibbie, you’re so terrible
After all, I have been such a long reporter here
Of course I am more familiar with the surrounding environment
Have it
No one on the car
He’s there
Uncle, please wait a moment
Your box is dangerous
danger?
-Flashlight...
Did you report that I just stepped on the pen?
-Sorry, I’ll pack you up
Forget it
What’s up
What about my pen
Did you accidentally fall off on the way?
Go back and look for it first
Where is it
Tibbie...
What’s up
Tibbie You’ve changed
ah?
You used to be afraid of dirty things
When encountering problems, what is often said is
What to do? Weslie
But now it’s different
You are brave and good at observing
Become a very bad beauty
Let’s continue to search
Alas, it’s really
Do children nowadays need not go to work? Do they go to school?
Huh? This is not...
You stepped on me again
Ah Help
What happened
Run quickly
Then...what is that
What kind of monster is this
You dirty me You dirty me...
ah
Go away quickly
Save me...
what?
What’s up
You’re fine, Tibbie
I’m fine
I was careless just now. Sorry...
I’ll keep giving you trouble today
Boosting spirits to Weslie
We haven’t yet
You’re right
Right
Why did that monster suddenly stop attacking?
When talking to it
I have a familiar feeling
It...it should be the one I don’t see
what?
Let’s chase
Dirty me
-You’ve dirtyed me
I didn’t mean it
Come here
Uncle, go to a safe place
ah…
Stop it quickly
Tibbie...
Let me come
I’m Tibbie, do you still remember me?
It’s okay, look clean
You’ve been with me for so long
Have a look with me to witness such a special thing
You’re like my best friend
I’m sorry, you’ve been wronged
Regardless of what you become
I will always guard you with my heart
You’re still willing to stay with me
Have you seen more important moments together?
Tibbie...
Do you want to change back and stay with me?
Um
Success
Great, there is another card collected
It seems that it will be gathering soon
We should have a big treat
You know how to eat...
In fact, this time it’s all up to Tibbie
Only so conveniently collected
It’s weird
There is no problem with our reporter Tibbie
Yes, how did Tibbie become a reporter
Don’t you want to be a gardener?
Um…
I don’t remember
Frontline news reporters report for you
OK, the shot is finished
Thank you for accepting the interview
Could you please see this person?
Just be a reporter
I can visit everywhere
This way, it is easy to inquire about Weslie.
Whether it’s a gardener or a reporter
I want to be a good person
Tibbie You must be a very bad reporter
right
Thank you for sending me a letter and encourage me to hold on
Is this not what I gave it to you?
I only send snacks
I haven’t seen this pen, either
Not me, not
what…
…Who gave it to me