You’re not fighting
Wilie, let dad come and help
All said no
I’ll come
Need not
I’m here
Break… Break…
You’re here to help you
rest assured
There is nothing I can’t fix
You can hand it to me with confidence
Wait a minute.
Here is the concert of Sister Jonie
All made you mess up
Again…sorry…
I’ll definitely fix it here
Jonie, go and practice rehearsal
You are the brightest boy here tonight
- I searched for nothing in the morning
Best friend
Time together
Growing together
Go bravely
Light together
Smile exhibition together
Confidant is like sunlight
Very good to hear
A little embarrassed
I’m looking forward to tonight’s concert more and more
So do I thank you
Yes, what are you grateful for
Thank you for coming back to participate in my concert
Um
Concerts in each future
Neither of us will be absent
Nuanyang Goat Concert Don’t miss it if you have walked past
Come and have a look
Welcome
Is the Jonie talking about each other?
No, he is a little famous star
No
Jonie is a very hardworking and talented singer
Guaranteed not to disappoint you
Remember to support the scene
Weslie, let’s help us too
Everyone…
Bamboo wolf
Second uncle, it’s really you
I heard you are still alive but I didn’t expect it to be true
Huh? Weslie, are you alive?
It’s so good
Jiao Tailang Why haven’t you changed at all
You haven’t changed for fifteen years
Are you here to participate in the Jonie concert?
Of course
And I also picked some fat and big bananas
Replenish the energy of the Jonie
I bring so many bananas every time
How can I be so sorry
Have to eat this
That’s left for the Jonie
Don’t eat the goat
Let’s go and send a bill
I know
Hope the concert can be completed smoothly
It’s about to start
She’s the Hot Goat
- Nothing special
I don’t know how I sing
- Jonie Come on
- Come on, come on…
My son has become so outstanding
But I missed his growth
There are me and you in the blue sky
A confidant who is in the green grassland
- Wow, listen carefully
- Such a bad concert is still free
The same heaven and earth
We support each other when we fall on the road
- We don’t give up when we encounter difficulties
Good friend Feng Yu is not separated
Best friend
Time together
Growing together
Go bravely
Light together
- Smile exhibition together
- It must be that I sang so well, I couldn’t even see it directly
Do you think the light is getting brighter and brighter
Um
- Why did the light suddenly get completely washed
It’s not a show that is prepared for singing
Why are the lights completely damaged
What happened
It’s okay, Jonie
Jonie…
This is…
The detector has a reaction
I’m fine. Wilie is still on the stage.
Small gray
Son, Alas…
You’re injured
It’s nothing, it’s just a minor injury
Alas…
Don’t force yourself
Little Huihui, take Wolffy down
Um
It’s weird… strange…
Strange… monster
Go and protect everyone
I want to go, too
Jonie
No one is allowed to run
You’re fine
Find a place to hide
Nuanyang Goat You go and protect the citizens
I’ll cover it
Sparky  Tibbie
You must keep it up and create air
- Um
You come to give him the last shot
Don’t worry, hand it to me
superior
It’s an opportunity
- Knock it down
Knock it down
ah? It can still be
- How to shut down the power…
What’s going on
It sucks all the electricity in the city
Let’s stop it
Everyone…
Weslie
If you are injured, don’t go there if you are injured.
My body is paralyzed…I can’t move…
Abnormal…
Jonie…
It’s okay… I’m here…
No, its attack is too strong
I have to help them. Alas…
Second uncle
It’s hard for you to get close to that monster now
In the past, it only dragged them down
Jonie…
With me here… I will definitely protect you…
As long as you don’t give up
Hope is in our hands
As long as we are in a strong position
Then there is no difficulty…
It cannot be crossed
Go
Finally, I’ve defeated the monster
No one is okay
This time it’s all up to you. Jonie
but…
A concert that everyone has worked hard to hold
It’s also destroyed
The concert can’t be done at all
Nothing to do
It’s fine for everyone to be fine
As long as we are together
There are dances everywhere
Everyone…
There are me and you in the blue sky
A confidant who is in the green grassland
Good friends meet and know each other
- The same heaven and earth
It’s hard to say…the monster was defeated
We support each other when we fall on the road
- We don’t give up when we encounter difficulties
- Good friends
- The wind and rain are not separated
- Best friend
- Time together
- Growing together
- The stewards bravely go
- Light together
- Smile exhibition together
- Confidant is like sunlight
This is the most exciting concert
That’s right
As long as everyone is together
I’m the best dance hall everywhere