No, don’t want it
Or it’s apart
I always think it’s not great to live back to Wolf Castle like this
Why
Wolf Castle is your home
that is
And you are still Wilie’s father
Finally there is a chance for you to stay together
Don’t hesitate
Let it go
I’m not hurting
Hello Wilie
Weslie Brother
You’re...
Your dad’s injury relapsed...
Very serious, someone must take care of it
Oh, it hurts...
This is nutritional
These are medicines
Remember to change every day
Then Wolffy will hand it over to you. Little Big Big White
goodbye
Alas, it hurts...
Come in quickly
Son, you’re tired
Not enough
Dad will give you your favorite egg scrambled meal
You’re fine
Ahem...
I’m ready
Haven’t you been injured?
Oh my feet hurt so much
Alas
Wilie, you are so awesome
Do you want to watch the TV? I’ll accompany you
Son Your egg scrambled rice looks delicious
How to do it
Will you meet when you grow up?
Yes, it’s good to grow up
You’ve lost
Son
Do you remember we used to play with water guns together?
Not coming out yet
You actually discovered it
Stop slapping
Son is now
We’ve won
Ha ha ha ha
Ha ha ha ha…
Son, you are most afraid of thunder
Let’s sleep together tonight
Son, wait for me
Son, don’t be afraid, dad will accompany you
All right
Alas, how can I get along well with my son?
These are Wilie’s toys when she was a child
This light can still open
It’s really memorable
But I always feel that it’s a bit unfavorable
Maybe I’m thinking too much
Why did Wilie ignore me?
He’s just not tempted now
He’s so kind
I’ll accept yours very early
Nothing else
Wilie passed on me
The kind and kind tradition
Ha ha ha ha…
Hey, have you seen him?
Little Huihui?
He...what’s wrong with him
He moved my stuff
I’m looking for him
Move...your...things?
Oh, why is this happening
The son does not teach the father
I’ll definitely take him to find you to commit crimes
Wolffy Your wheel chair...
Let me go, I’m still in trouble
Let’s take you to apologize
What are you talking about
Is anyone
He...Brother Hema
Children do something wrong
Apologize definitely
All of these are blamed on me
I have not been with my child for the years
He will make mistakes, it’s mine.
What are you talking about
I’m here to thank him
ah…
I feel uncomfortable in the morning
He helped me carry the goods
I want to give him some candy as a reply
He doesn’t want it
Thank you only if you visit the door
That’s what it means
Sorry, son
It turns out that I was wronged you
sorry
thank you
- sorry
You’re almost the same
It’s going to rain
I’m going back to collect my clothes
It’s time to leave, too
I’ll just say it
My son has passed it
My righteous and kind tradition
Son, I’m tired of it, Dad gives you...
Why did the lights suddenly go out
What happened
It should be a star-like monster
You leave quickly
Leave it to me here
But aren’t you injured?
I’m fine
I also have gloves
Hand...set...
Oops I don’t know where to put the gloves
Ahem...
It’s so dark, Wilie, where are you
Wilie Wilie Wilie Wilie...
Small gray
Son...
This...what monster is this
Don’t worry, son
Dad will protect you
Have you injured your feet?
Light It’s afraid of light
We can use strong light to eliminate it
The second floor storefront
There was a stage light from the last time Jonie started her concert
You go up first
Why are you still doing me? Go quickly
Help me hold him up
Come on, Xiao Kei
Let this king accompany you to have a good time
ah
Oh…
Out... out
Where have you been hiding again
Why do I always think there is no match for the enemy?
My shadow is gone
This monster turns out to be my shadow
He actually sneaked into me
You are such a monster...
Want to steal me again
Not that easy
You know that this king’s wickedness is a disaster
My flashlight...
Don’t worry, Wilie
I’ll help you hold it
Little Gray Gray…
alright
Finally wait for you to say this
Son is now
good
So you remember
Say...your legs...
This leg... OK
Ha ha ha ha
Son, I’m done here
Son
I was tired of playing when I was a kid
Wilie also lies on the sofa and sleeps like this
It’s time to move