The Hantian system has been updated
Can go out anytime
very good
Your mission from now on
It is to collect pictogram fragments
If you encounter a person who is blocking the collection of pictogram fragments
Just call it online
Strictly all the pictogram pieces on their bodies
Yes Doctor
Hahahahahahahaha
My Rocket Model
How did you fly away
Hahahahahahahaha
I’m going to destroy everything
Wow
ah
Well
Hehehehehehehe…
Ah…Wow…
Hahahahaha
Huh… Huh?
Are you a toy model too?
Discover the target
Come and play with me
Huh? what?
Hum Come again
ah…
Begin recycling
Alas, wait a moment
I won’t play…
Oh no…
Quick engine
Target exceeds range
Run now
Correct distance
Lock the target
Start chasing
No…no…
The signal is nearby
What…what’s going on
It’s hard to say…
Wow, it’s so cold here
How did the signal disappear
Is this hand malfunctioning?
ah…
You’re fine
Thank you for saving me
Target appears
You’re all in a bad state
If you don’t mind
I’ll take you back to Yang Village to help you with treatment
Start cleaning the target
slow
Follow him to the lamb’s base first
Let them hit them all over again
yes
Let’s go
Mr. Slowy
Paddi
This is…
Mr. Slowy
It just suffered to save me
It’s another goal
Which robot is it
I don’t know either
I’ll help it check the damage
The shell is not severely damaged
It will be repaired soon
Wait for the base
Just report their position
yes
But it may also be an internal failure
Don’t be careless
Humph, let them take me back
Mr. Slowy What’s wrong with it
Don’t worry
I just connect to its host
Just enter the maintenance procedure
This robot structure is really complicated
Or bring back to the base
Use my super computer to check it
good
what? Has the cold sky lost its response?
Doctor: Someone invaded the host of cold sky
Immediately regain Hantian’s control
yes
The host that can actually get into the cold sky
A little capable
Haha, the structure is really complicated
Not like an ordinary robot at all
Hahaha, I’m so curious
Who designed it
Village President, it’s not the time to be curious now
Don’t worry
The repair procedure is working
Has returned to cold weather control
Huh? Where am I?
What’s going on
How to close the repair system
base…
Hum Start positioning
alright
Well?
What happened just now
Oh, is someone shaking something
Come again…
Mr. Slowy, why don’t you take a break?
I can
Uh… I might as well take it out for a break
See if anyone knows it
OK I’ll find a solution
Stop it
Could anyone know this robot?
Is anyone else going to kill robots
Stop
Robot…
I can’t tell that this old lady is the owner of the robot
Grandma Do you know it
Your robot hooked up my clothes
Sorry Sorry Sorry Sorry…
System startup
Location information is unknown
Preferred solution to goals
The lower body can’t move
Successfully retrieved some systems
Hantian restores upper body function
After searching for it for most of the day, I didn’t have any traces
This taste is…
Don’t walk here
I’ll pick some apples
Don’t try to escape
That’s so high I can’t pick it
Why did it suddenly become so big
Huh? It’s you
Have you come to help me pick apples?
Very good Thank you
Really fulfilled
Someone actually came here
Fast consumer goods project target
Enter the maintenance program
Ahhhhh…why can’t you stop…
Oh, you’re fine
Why did you protect me again
Oops ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Humph, I don’t believe that I can’t fight you
Look at me pull you out
snort
Alas, old
If I had been younger for fifteen years, I would never have gone
Successfully returned to Hantian Control
OK Don’t waste time
Let Hantian continue to execute the command
yes
The system has been reopened
Confirm the goal
Come
Execute the doctoral order
Oh, you can move, right?
Very good
Hehe, I should have a glass of juice and wish you a happy wish
This…this is…
Elephant Star Stone Card
Why do you have…
Is it iced?
How do you know I want to drink iced juice more
What a good brother who is thinking about me
Good brother, please drink iced juice
What happened? What happened…
This is…
You…what are you
Eliminate targets
Scratch of Elephant Star Stone