Beware of that robot
I had a mysterious force when I repaired it
Take control of it away
It’s too late it’s chasing me
what? Where are you
We have no grudges and no revenge
Why did you hit me
Floating cannon
You’ll force me again
Don’t blame me for being rude
Come on
Look at my fire ability card
It’s your star
fire…
Ah, so cold
How could you suddenly stumble
You’re playing tricks
Not good floating cannon
Chasing the enemy
Alas, I’m not doing anything again today
Hey hey hey let it open
Finally arrived
Hello, do you want to buy insurance?
ah…
Chasing the enemy
You have to remove the card soon
Well… so cold
ah…
Here is…
Paddi
This cold sky is really hard
Have to think about it
You’re in ambush
Have it
The location is just good
Floating cannon
Solved
You’re hiding outside
Hand over the Elephant Star Stone Card
You’re fine
You almost cheated
Wow…
Village Chief, I’ve been hurt by you
Why did I call me at this time
Oh
This is a tragedy…
Floating cannon
Haha…Big Head See you again
ah?
Wow…let me…
Help, Sparky
Give me the card
Wow…my hands…
My card…
never mind
Retreat first and then talk about it
Chasing the enemy
It’s coming soon
I’ve fought with you
Paddi…
Ahhhhhhhh
It’s you…Sparky…
You boy
He actually won’t tell me
Weslie
How did you come
The village chief asked us to help you
It’s okay
How about it…Weslie
It’s nothing
You’re so big
I also want Weslie to comfort you
Too scary
I was almost frozen into ice by that robot
What happened to that robot
I helped it repair it before
A mysterious force snatched away its control
I’ll recommend that
The mysterious person who has been competing with us on the Elephant Star Stone
It’s him
It’s hard to blame for snatching my flame card
You’ll remember it now
Um
Did they be stunned at that time
We’ll get it back
Thank you for your Weslie
You’re so big
Still rely on Weslie
Just like when I was a kid
That’s right
I’m still the boy before
No change in a single piece
You’re so kind
I don’t need you to help this time
I’ll get my card back.
I only have the most basic weapons
No card
But the other…
I definitely can’t beat it
But that’s what I’m going back…
I am not as good as Weslies and goats that are children
Yes, I’ll go first
Then go back
Just said that it was not found
I’m so lucky
I definitely didn’t encounter it so by chance
Ah…it’s it…
Hehe…The super trap is finally done
There was a reaction of the Elephant Star Stone fragments nearby
It will definitely come
It’s here
Let’s see the trick
Hand over the Elephant Star Stone card
Paddi
I’ll give you these few Elephant Star Stone cards
Hahahaha…I know I’m so sad
It turns out it was you
You…you haven’t fallen into the trap
I didn’t expect it to fly
I obviously did… a lot of traps…
I’ve made so many traps on the road
Do you think this can deal with me?
No…
Don’t come over
Ah Help…
What is it doing
I didn’t expect it to be a villain who loves flowers and plants
Keep going now…
Hehehe…it’s all up to that little flower to help me take off
Do you think you can escape?
You underestimate me too much
Help, is it finished
There is no way ahead…
Death
Don’t come over
Find the fragments
Small tricks of carving
Ah, what’s going on
My hands My feet…
Why did you move on your own
Hehehehehe…