What do you want
Don’t urge
You can also taste the taste of being controlled
ah…
Let me go…
Fun and fun
Not fun at all
ah
It hurts so much
Wow
It’s over
Not fun here
Paddi
This is…
There are fragmented reactions
Wow, where is the bubbles from? Very cute
what?
These bubbles are dangerous
Everyone, go quickly
There are so many bubbles that will explode
Double Butterfly Sword
There are so many bubbles
Where is the source
Very darn
Who is it
danger
Oh…
Wait a minute.
Welcome to visit again
Why are you here?
Didn’t you go looking for fragments?
Fragment Reaction
I’m so adults, and I’m still having fun
You’re so angry
Hahahahahaha…
Village Chief There are fragments reacting nearby
You’re coming just right
He is a little strange to the goat
Dance once you come back
This is a mantis fist
You’re fine
Fun and fun
What…what’s going on
There must be a problem
Blue Blue Sniper
Monsters come out soon
Not fun
I’ll chase the goat
Who are you
Why are you collecting cards
Feel sorry
The card can’t be given to you
You are also a mysterious organization
Don’t go
Wow, look
Is that person doing
Paddi
Why is he there
What happened to Tibbie goat
I know I’m nearby
Let’s discuss it first
Um
Weslie
What happened to the goat
I guess the goat was controlled by the fragmented monster
But I haven’t found the monster yet
Wow…
Wow, what happened above
Hahaha… It’s so fun
I’ll find the monsters
You find a chance to deal with it
Be careful
Wake up soon, goat
ah…
It’s fun to control others
This is not a solution
ah
The Goat must be controlled by these lines
Have to find a way to cut it off
Good chance to cut you off
what!
Found you
Oops
Finally found
It turns out there
Paddi…
Yes, here is…
Wow, what happened
Thank you for your Tibbie
Why can’t I catch
It’s you
Made me so bad
Let you taste my trauma
Come again!
whee…
If you don’t hit, there is no intention
Launch
ah…
When did my weapon become so bad
It’s time to you
Successfully I got the card
Three of us will definitely win you
Or surrender obediently
These petals…
It’s him…
These petals are dangerous. Be careful
Let him escape again
Who is he
It seems to be exhausted
Do you want to eat together?
- Still no
But goat
Why is that floating cannon so powerful
It should be my brave and strong will
Inspired its potential
Unfortunately, Hantian escaped
That mysterious person…
Are he the same as Han Tian?
Is it a mysterious person?
Have you come back?
ah? What’s wrong?
My beard hasn’t been opened yet
Village chief, I didn’t do it
What a mistake, the village chief…
Hehehehehe…