No signal No signal
Where are you?
careful
Have a signal
I’m going to see who is faster
Danger Stop
not good…
fortunately
Don’t run
Yes, it’s more powerful
I’m here to help
Monsters changed back to their original state
I helped you yesterday
You’re so kind to revenge
Help me? I haven’t seen you
It’s hard to say…
When I ate yesterday
More heart than others
You secretly gave it to me
The last move you took yesterday
It’s me who helped you
You said yesterday that my ability increased greatly because of you
No thanks to me
goodbye
Don’t want to leave
Do you want me?
You look pretty good
Then I will reward you myself
This drama has also developed too fast
Don’t want it
Then I want it
You look pretty strong, too
Or I’ll give myself to you
Wait a minute…
Didn’t you just say you rewarded me?
What should you do…you all want me
Who am I good to give
Why not compete for me
What is better than you are mine
stop
If you don’t compete for me…
No matter how your language changes
I just found a place to hide it and explode
Then you will always lack this piece of me
Ha ha ha ha…
Nope no
Who said we are not
You’re right?
Compare
Find Weslie and the others to help
You can’t find foreign players
Your competition is fair and just
All right
What is a competition
First game running
Let’s get started
what?
I’m not ready
I really miss this
The atmosphere of the competition for me
Humph, you are mine
No no no no
How can I compete with a high-priced competition
Just decide to get a degree by poop
It’s even better to compare
You’re such a monster that has a pursuit
Not comparable…
You know the consequences
whee…
Second game Swimming
Why is it a physical competition again
Come on
Everyone should be…
I’ve won
Give me the card
No no no no
You just used the card
This is illegal
So you can go
Really
That’s great
You say it again
You
You dare…
I’ll hide it and won’t find it for you
Don’t worry
And the last single car competition
Let me start quickly
But I’m tired
Why not take a day off
Let’s have a competition tomorrow
Where can I get my bike
Few people ride bicycles now
If only he could be found
It’s you, little guy
It’s you?
That’s how it is
So I can only practice temporarily with you by borrowing a bicycle
But the estimate is not big
Do you want to give up?
this…
If you give up now
Then everything is over
The opponent is so strong
How could it be rewarded
I’ve participated in this competition before
The competition that year was quite fierce
Um
Fortunately, I didn’t give up
Finally I got the prize
Hello, horrible
Alas, but it’s a pity
When I moved later, the prize cup accidentally broke it
ah
Little guy
Hold on for a while
Maybe it will win
Will it be
Success is only for those who are ready
Come on, little guy
I will work hard, thank you
You follow the route. Whoever rides back to the original point first will win.
Hum Speed War
The last one
Bike competition begins
Let’s goat
Persevere, work hard, work hard…
Ah it hurts
See you again
Not over yet
I won’t…
Give up…
Good feelings
Received
Win
Congratulations, you are the champion
This champion cup is yours
That’s great…no
Paddi
I want to give myself to you
- what
You just had the posture of being hindered
It’s exactly the same as when my master got me that year
I declare…you got me
You just said you have a master
Well… It’s a pity that the owner moved that year…
After opening
I’ve never seen my master again
Although you have this figure…
But you are like my master
Also a person who works hard to the end
So I chose you
But aren’t you supposed to be the winner?
Because I’m a comfort award cup
We will work hard for you in the game like this
The one who decided not to give up was ready
Come on, goat
Come and get the pieces
It’s enough
You can only be mine
ah…
I’ve been tolerating you for a long time
Don’t move it
Flame card
I’ll save you
Want to trap me with these broken wands
Think beautifully
Come on, goat
Enhancement card
Uncle Yun
I’m still working on it now
ah
I’ll be there for you to ride on your own and this one…
Did you find it for me?
I think you’re telling it
It’s very important
Welcome home Brother
Thank you for finding it back
It’s so good
I’ll take a lot of attention in the future