sorry
I failed
You’re useless
PhD
And it’s gone
It’s better to use it to the end
Maybe it can also play a role
Failed again
You know the consequences
Yes Doctor
I’m still worried
You go and have a look
OK
We are still very efficient in collecting fragments
What’s going on
Monsters
The cold weather is also here
Can’t harm plants
I didn’t expect you to protect a flower
Nothing to do with you
snort
When I don’t exist
Then another one
Then come together
Don’t hang your hands
- The fragments are mine
Who got the fragments a few times ago
Your fire melted my ice
I accidentally
I just want to eliminate monsters
I want to destroy you first
Help...
Ah, help, don’t chase me
- ah…
Dare not to ignore me
Come back to me
Weslie
Come and help me
I was blown by the cold sky
what?
You can hold on first
We’re here right now
good
Hand over the card, kid
ah…
Ah my card...
Hum, it’s my card now
who
Found you
You don’t want to ignore me
- Oops card
I can’t escape this time
Hahahahahaha
So dark
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh
Cold sky
Let it open
People without a card
Not worth my waste of energy
Not dead
What a thick wall
Let me try it
no
Why don’t we cooperate
I don’t need to cooperate
Paddi
What? Can’t connect to the phone number of the 海官网?
Don’t have anything to do
That person was the subordinate of a mysterious person
- what?
It is possible that it knows what inner story
We must not let it run away any more
You go and save the goat first
I’ll control it
Head-dividing action
You go and save the goat first
My husband and I went to help Tibbie
-good
superior!
Be careful
Your card will also be my
Don’t think about it!
The card of the goat
You really have a problem
Just surrender
It seems that I underestimated you
never mind
See you next time
Don’t run...
Let him run away
The goat stuck in its hand
It is very likely that Paddi are in danger
Then let’s go find him
- good
That’s too hard
Hahaha…
Don’t do slap in vain
You can’t escape
Who told you to ignore me
Why do you want to save me
Is this another reason?
I won’t see you never save me
Just like you’re going to save the flower
Ahhhhh…
The situation is getting more and more dangerous
And you’re hurting so much
Why not cooperate
good…
You finally answered
It’s funny, I won’t work with you
Hum, I want to cooperate with you
Go open, you don’t need to help
Humph, good intentions are not good
Even if you are not
I can also punch the wall
Close your mouth and disappear to me
Or...we will work together again
unnecessary
Ah, Oops, it’s over
Dead...
Sparky
You’re finally here
Paddi
Next
Take the call
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh
It’s okay, goat
It’s OK
Yes, it hurts very heavily in the cold days
Just in...
What about the cold weather?
Hantian will leave it to you for processing
Wait Doctor
I found that Hantian recorded the data of fighting with the lamb
These data will help deal with the lamb in the future
Then let it go
Enable me a new battle
Obey orders