Wilie Dad made a cake for you
Wilie Open the door
Don’t keep yourself in the room every day
oops…
Can you stop quarreling?
I’m busy
How long has it been since your room been cleaned
Miserable
You don’t have to worry about my business
OK OK OK Dad will help you clean up
Don’t quarrel with you
Oh, this…this mouse mark bites people
That’s a rat-shaped shaver
Cough cough cough…
Why do these shoes smell so smelly
That’s a shoe-type sponge
Why are there all the rooms strange things
Design diagram
Invention Competition
It turns out that my son has passed on my tomorrow
Son
Let Dad, the inventor, guide you
Your circuit is too complicated
Let’s simplify it
If the resistance value is too low, it will short circuit
Two more resistors
Or add a light
Where is there a problem
If the resistance value is too low, it will short circuit
Two more resistors
He really said it
Go
Help me sweep the Wolf Castle
Small gray
Have eaten
This is the invention of Wilie Competition
It’s not going to be rubbish
It’s smaller than garbage
What’s the use
no
Can’t let the son lose
I’ll help him win the competition
Ah, it’s coming
I’ll go with you
Need not
Son, come on
come on
Um
It’s now
The display time of the future Star Cup invention competition
Please make preparations
Please introduce and show your invention
This…This is the super swipe expert I invented
It has a bad function
It can be smaller
Run to a place that cannot be cleaned normally
oops
How did this happen
Hehe The celebration banquet is ready
When Wilie comes back, you can start to celebrate
Dad, you’re so terrible
I can only win the prize by your invention
Congratulations to son
How
Do you like your invention very much?
Did you stole my invention
What…what happened
You always think you are
I…
Do you think I’m happy like this?
Fifteen years have passed
You haven’t changed at all
How about it…Little Huihui complained to me
He said I always thought it was right
I’m just doing it for him
I know I know
Wilie probably just wanted to do it through his own efforts
Get the prize
Change it is you
You don’t want to win the championship by relying on others’ strength, right?
Wilie is no longer the child he used to be
Yes
I’m too self-righteous
I want to apologize
Don’t throw it away if you don’t want to
What’s the use of keeping it
What’s up
Monster beast
What’s going on
oops
You’re fine
Don’t slap
ah
You’re fine
Um
Um?
The sweeping robot I made?
You think you can fight
Am I the one who makes your master?
As long as it destroys your power core
You can’t move
You’re fine
I’m fine
You’ll escape to a safe place
And you
Of course I have taken on my own conspiracy
Aren’t you unable to break its outer armor?
How to clean it up
Let everyone deal with it together
Everyone went out to find the cards
It’s too late
As long as I want to attack it inside
dad…
Big block, I’ll deal with you
Oops…
Small gray
What are you doing here
Escape quickly
I’m here to help you attack its inside
Super Swallowing Experts
It’s up to you
no problem
See the big block again
- well done
Small gray
Remember it’s delicious
I’ll leave first
Could it be that I just got hurt?
Where to go
Don’t run away if your hands are injured
The hand is injured and it doesn’t affect walking
Just leave if you don’t come in
Don’t, I’ll come in here
Son…