Is this detector damaged?
I have been looking for it for so long but I haven’t reacted
Patient
Surely found
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Someone needs rescue
Everyone is ready for action
Sparky
It’s actually a scream from the park
Wow, Game Park
You’re such a big goat
I was so excited to see the game park
Look at the other person’s Weslie... what about the goat
Come back soon, we’re not here to play
There are fragments in the game park
Let’s go quickly, too
Um
Wow…
This is the future of the park...
Weslie
How do you want to play?
Hey... no no no...
Let’s go find the fragments
Weslie Show you something fun
What
That’s it
Wow...oh
Wow, this lens is amazing
Ha ha ha ha…
I’ll try it too
- Hahahahaha
There are more...hey...
What are we here to do
Haha... Let’s go now
Ah, they’re here
This is what we did when we were kids
I’m as cute as I was when I was a kid
When I was so young
We’re all doing
I remember
We were all turned into cats in the cat country
We played the ball together
There are many interesting things...
If I could grow up with you
How good that would it be
Although we are bigger than you now
But our friendship has always been
We can venture together now
This feels really good
Let’s go find the fragments
Grasp the time
good
This is what I will do in fifteen years
Huh
Don’t worry
Just look for pieces
We’ll send you back
Let’s go quickly
Um
go back…
I can grow up with them
kid
Play a circle game
Uh...this...
Which one in the set is given which one
Isn’t you really coming to try it?
No need, no need
I’m still in trouble
Wow…
kid
This circle is a gift, not a self
It obviously flew over and caught me
How is it possible
I’ll show you something
Have you seen it?
oops
That’s it just now
The detector has a reaction
It’s hard to tell...
Blue Blue Sniper
Wait... Wait... Wait
Wait a moment
What do you want to do
Don’t hurt my gifts
Hahahahahaha...Catch me, come and catch me
A little bit...
Stop me
Wow, no...my baby
You’ll bring me back
Stop and don’t run
Hehehe Come on, come on, hahahaha
Found
stop
It turned out to be a lens
A little bit...
It’s you...
whee…
what…
How about it...
It actually reversed my whirlwind
Any other tricks to use
If you can get hurt, I’ll count it
Oops, no way
Dad, I want to play that
Ah, so exciting
Have fun with the goat?
Uh-huh
Um?
ah? Sparky
Sorry...
Sparky , you hear me explain
What are you doing
I just came in and checked
Is there any card in the flying boat
Then the door suddenly closed
What...let me out...
And then when I asked for help...
Ah... I was swept to the seat
- ah
Ah...ahha
I didn’t expect it to be quite exciting
Hahaha, it’s really fun
Yes, right
Are you having fun?
- Ah...Tibbie
Tibbie, you heard me explain...
Wow, hahahaha... so exciting
Wow...hahaha...
Please answer everyone
ah…
So fun
Hello? Is Weslie?
How do you answer the phone...
Come and be surprised
There is a weird thing here...
Ah Weslie
Weslie
We’re here Where are you
who?
It turns out it’s a lens
I’ll go explore the way
I’ll go here
It’s like a maze here
Where is Weslie?
It’s too expensive to find
Have to think about it
I’m here...
Two and two groups Look for it in one place
Contact with a communications device
good
Don’t go...
Weslie Where are you
Weslie
Weslie Come Out soon
What’s up?
Is there any static on the wall?
Sparky
What are you doing
Attack of this level
It’s useless for me
Found you
Why do you know I’m here
Spiritual hearing is the basic skill of firefighters
Alas, wait a moment
what!
ah…
This is too bad
This time it’s a counter-surgery
Then how can we win it
Hehehehehe
Come and chase me
Can’t let it run away like that
We cover it with our heads
good
stop
Huh? Where have you gone?
ah
He is...
Who are you...
I can’t resist your attack
I’m here to take the fragments of you
Elephant Star Stone Fragments
He is the same as the mysterious man
Huhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
If you have the ability to catch me, please tell me
Wow
Hum, don’t try to escape