That person is called Heiji
That’s right
But what we can find
Only his name
Such a mystery
But since he also came with a card
He should be the subordinate of that mysterious person, too
A cold day
Another black diamond
How many subordinates does that mysterious person have?
Since that’s the case
Then we’re going to find the fragments before they
Um
No
After saying this for so long, my stomach is getting hungry
Let’s eat something first
Fierce
Hum, don’t wait for me
Wait for me
There was no reaction here either
ah!
Little sister, you’re fine
It hurts…
I’m fine
It’s a bit like BB Goat
I’ll help you up…
Thank you, brother
Wow…what is my doll
Dolls What about dolls
Where did you go
Is this your doll?
Great, the doll is still there
sorry
I just didn’t see the road hitting you
This doll must be very important to you
Yes
This doll was given to me by my brother
I’m going to go find my brother tightly
I won’t tell you
Alas, wait…
Be careful when passing the horse road
But brother…
Why? Where is the brother?
I just saw him there
Why didn’t you see it all at once?
Don’t see it again?
You tell me what he is like
I’ll find him
Um…
He has two eyes
A mouth
Two ears
What about the same thing as BB Goat
No effect at all
Is there anything else?
I just saw him wearing black clothes
Just saw it?
Did he not wear black clothes before?
Wow…
Run quickly and run quickly…
What happened
Black diamond? How could he be here?
Brother, wait for me…
Danger Don’t go past
Wow…
You’re fine
How did you get hurt
elder brother
Brother, where have you been
elder brother…
Oh…Brother
I finally found you
Why don’t you want Xiaoyu again
How about it…
The brother you said wouldn’t be a robot that was just now
How could he be your brother?
Do you think it’s wrong
He is my brother
I’m going to find him
it hurts…
Otherwise
I’ll help you deal with the injury first
You can tell me about your brother
Then I’ll help you find your brother
Really
Of course
Very good
OK, nothing is wrong
Thank you
Is this your home?
Yes, this is my secret base for my brother and I
My name is Weslie. What about you
Light rain
My brother’s name is Xiaolei
Can you tell me about your brother and you?
Um
this
This is…
It’s a photo of the brother’s competition
The champion of the martial arts competition
Your brother is so terrible
The tricks in this photo are my brother’s fame skills
Very nice
Wow, your brother is so terrible
Um? This doll…
It’s it
It was done by my brother
I’ll give it to you. Do you like it?
Like Thank you brother
But later my brother disappeared
Why didn’t your brother see it
One day
My brother said he was going to see a very bad person
Brother is going out now
You’re at home by yourself
Then never come back
Brother, come back soon…
Don’t worry
I’ll help you find your brother
Really
Yes, please wait at home
As long as there is news about your brother
I’ll notify you right away
Um
Say it
Don’t hide
You can’t escape
You’re really bullying
You forced me
Condensing reflected light a little
Scope Scope Shooting…
what
Ahhhhhh
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh
Black diamonds light rain
Impossible
Run quickly…
Everyone, I’m in love
receive
Black Diamond
Come just right
Hand over your card too
Don’t think about it
Blue Blue Sniper
Very fast
what?
Good opportunity
Are you Xiaoyu’s brother
I don’t know what you’re talking about
Ah ahem…
Rotary squirt
Hand over the card
impossible…
Then there’s nothing to do