Didn’t catch up
Weslie, you’re fine
It’s OK
That’s just the black diamond?
Um
The robots sent by mysterious people are getting more and more harmful
He is my brother
Is it a robot?
What do you mean
Uh…no
The power of black diamond is too strong
When looking for fragments of Elephant Star Stone, you must be careful
Um
Black diamonds are terrible
Now I can’t let Xiaoyu get close to him
Radda reacted
There are fragments of elephant star stones nearby
who?
elder brother
I finally found you
I’m not your brother
Don’t worry
I want to follow my brother
Hold it
Brother, what are you looking for
Are you looking for this one?
Are you unhappy?
You can enjoy the fun by eating candy
Still not happy
Then, can we play hide and seek?
Our favorite thing to play before
That’s it
I’ll hide it
Must find me
Things to do
Brother, I haven’t hid it yet
No peeking
Hidden here, I will definitely not find me
Brother, I’ve hidden it
Why didn’t my brother come to me yet
Brother, don’t you want me anymore
Brother, you found me
Weslie Brother
Xiaoyu What are you doing here
I play hide-and-seek with my brother
But my brother never came to me
Does he want me anymore
How did it happen
Your brother should have something to be busy
That’s why it can’t come
Really
If Hei Diamond is really Xiaoyu’s brother
How could he become like this?
Xiaoyu I’ll take you to find my brother, okay?
good
You can eat it slowly
Hahaha
Your eating habits have never changed as before
Still so unimportant
Um? I am me
This way it tastes good
Elephant star stone fragments
The debris should be nearby
Everyone, please open it quickly
It’s you
Unexpectedly, someone came to send fragments
I’ve accepted it
Be careful
What a powerful force
ah…
Be careful
Big Wolf behind you
what? How fast is it so fast
Wolffy, leave there quickly
Don’t think about it
It’s nothing
Is that skill?
Then it’s me
How could he be so
This is unscientific
The power of our six people
Can’t beat him
Your math is still so bad
There are five of us here
I can only delay the time
False
Go quickly
Hum, you can’t escape
What’s up
This street I used to come with my brother
Do you want to eat ice cream?
If possible, I want to eat candy
Do you like eating candy?
My brother said
Eat candy when you are unhappy
This will make you happy
But why is it now
No matter how much I eat, I can’t feel happy
Light rain…
My brother liked me very much before
My brother has been ignoring me now
He must have dismissed me
It won’t
There is no brother in the world who doesn’t like his sister
Believe me
Your brother will definitely come back to find you
Really
Yes, I’ll buy you more candy
By then you can eat candy with your brother
You have to stay here obediently
Yes, I’ll be good
Little bear
Do you think my brother will come to me?
elder brother
The fragments are nearby
Very good
My brother is really looking for me
Do you remember this bear doll?
You gave it to me
We’ve played with every family together
The little bear is here
The bear wants to eat candy
If you don’t have candy, you’ll be chaotic
Ha ha ha ha
Is it hard to be here?
Not at all?
Is it difficult to get nearby?
Discuss… Discuss
Why do you want to do this to her
She’s your sister
I don’t have a sister
Apologize
I’ll tell you
I’ll talk to you I’ll talk to you…
It’s a fragment of star stone
It actually attached to Xiaoyu’s body…
Worked
How did this happen
It turns out that the star stone fragments are on you
Then don’t blame me for being rude
You won’t let her hurt
I’m the most troublesome brother
Xiaoyu, stop now
It’s too late…
You must stop the light rain tightly