Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow w
Xiaoyu, stop now
Weslie
We’re here to help you
Come just right
stop
Wow ah ah ah ah ah…
Hey
You may not hurt her
Do you think the same trick will work for me?
Hey
ah…
You go and hang up with Xiaoyu first
I’ll hold him up
good
I’ll let you know
This is an incorrect decision
Is that right? Hum
Light rain
How can we stop her?
How to do it…
Right
This doll…
It’s done by my brother
Everyone, I understand
Be careful in front
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow w
Black Diamonds damaged Xiaoyu’s doll
It’s just that the light rain turned into this
I see
We took the dolls over and fixed them
That’s all
That’s right
The chief of the class, Tibbie
I’ll give it to you
We were responsible for attracting her attention for three of us
Take the opportunity to take the doll over
- good
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow w
Wolffy…
Ah, don’t touch my bear
ah…
Good opportunity
ah
Success
What happened just now
Please, please
OK Don’t worry
Um? Um? Where is my bear?
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow w
Light rain
Sparky
Ahem…
Quick…protect…light rain
Wow…
ah
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow w
Xiaoyu, wait for me
Let me open it
Success
what…
ah…
Rotary card
You’re fine
- Replenished
Very good
Xiaoyu, don’t cry
Look, the doll has been replenished
no
ah
Tibbie Jonie
You…you are cheating
Xiaoyu This is your little bear
ah
I just want the bear my brother gave me
Ah…ah…
Xiaoyu, please calm down
Light rain Light rain…
Little…rain?
Who is it
Well…wait…
elder brother
Don’t say it…
not good
Bear…
elder brother…
How about it…
How did it spread so quickly
We have to go out tight
How do we cross over?
Your floating cannon
The floating cannon was destroyed
I don’t know we really have no way
Oh no, the water is still rising
How to do where
How about it…
Brother…bad guy…
Stop shouting I’m not…
I…I…
Uh…that…what is that
I…
I…what am I doing
Why do I quit
Why…this thing…
like…
Have done it many times…
ah…
Wow
It’s going to slide down…
My ears…
You… don’t be upset
I can’t hold back…
The situation is urgent, this is the only way
Everyone is at ease
Stable
ah…
Sparky …
Then what do you do
Why am I still continuing…
Hey, you see
Your doll
Look at Xiaoyu What is this
My…doll
Brother, you’re finally back
Sparky , please hold on
Sparky …
I…I’m fine?
Is it hard to tell… it’s Xiaoyu?
Brother…Brother…
elder brother
Weslie
What happened to Xiaoyu
Nothing big anymore
But I haven’t woken up yet
Alas, put my hands…
Everyone
Something happened to my hand