Village Chief, have any results?
Although it spreads slowly
But your right hand has begun to become mechanical
what
Can cause such damage
There is only that mysterious person right now
Do you still remember how you got hurt?
Well…
Ah, it won’t be…
Will Wolffy become a robot in the future?
It’s hard to say now
Will I become a robot
Finally got a little more irrelevant with my son
But I haven’t seen any red
Don’t worry
You moved to Goat Village at a time
Let’s study the treatment together
But I’m afraid that one day I can’t control myself
Hurt you
Don’t worry
We will take care of you in all directions for 24 hours
They’re not monsters
Oh well
PhD
I’ve started adjusting the abnormal data of black diamonds
Um…
I’m very curious
Black Diamond is obviously a robot
Why do you still have feelings
And the fragments of star stones
It can also produce effects on the body
Fun… Fun…
Wilie, you are waiting for me here
dad
Wait a minute.
This is another
Son, you’re awake
I…
Just say if you have any
I have to move to Yangcun for a while
Yes
You have to take good care of yourself…
Just leave if you want
Anyway, I’m all ill
No I just…
Just leave if you want
Anyway, I’m all ill
Don’t worry, the village chief
I’m on the road
Weslie Brother
Wilie Why are you here
What about Wolffy
I heard that he was moving to Goat Village
What’s wrong with him
Big Wolf didn’t tell you
I really admire you
Dad catches the ball
Hahaha
Hey
Oh oh oh
Look at me…Oh
First…Sir…
You’re fine
Sorry
give
-Thank you -Thank you
Ah… Monster
monster?
Can’t I have become mechanical?
This…this is…
That’s how it is
He just likes to carry everything alone
Run quickly…
What happened
Weslie The fragments appear
Come to Central Park for support
receive
Wilie I’m going to help Big Wolf
You go and avoid the trouble first
Weslie Brother…
There are monsters, help…
Help
Ahhhhhh
You won’t have anything to do with me…
Ahhhhhhhh
It actually sneaked into me
I won’t let you go
I’m angry
Ahhhh
My hands…
Ah Hey
I know my trauma is not…
oops
This is… glue water
All of this can be restored
Still not talking
Help…
Ahhhhhh
Weslie
Wolffy
You’re fine
Don’t be careless
This water monster can recover
- Wilie
What did you come
It’s very dangerous here
Yes, hurry up and avoid the difficulties
Those who want to leave should be injured and strong people.
But…
What is that
This monster can recover
Could it be that is its core?
Little Huihui Big Wolf will hand it over to you
I’ll go over to help
no
You’ve been hurt
What kind of busyness can you help in the past
But Weslie can’t handle it alone
Danger
dad
not good
Wilie, please let go
You’ll be pulled in, too
I don’t want it
Little Gray Gray…
Ahhhh
Oops
Little Gray Gray Small Gray Gray
Don’t be afraid, Dad will come to save you immediately
Oops
Nothing is done…
Son, hold on
It’s not a way to hide like this
It’s necessary to find its core
The body cannot move at all…
Son
You have to hold on
Uh uh uh…
Don’t move your hand anymore…
no
I promise you will save you
Wait for dad
The cheating person…
Quit… Quit…
Don’t let things you do without ease
What will come back soon? Will definitely come back
Over the past fifteen years
I can live a very good life without you…
I always like to take all my responsibilities on my own
It appears if you like it. It disappears if you don’t like it.
Little Gray Gray…
Why
Have you ever thought about us?
Small gray
Alas
dad
Small gray
Wilie, you said it’s OK
Over the past fifteen years
I’ve never been with you
It’s natural for you to tell me
But…but…I…
Dad doesn’t cry or not
Wilie will wait for you to come back
Sorry Wilie Sorry…
dad…
You know…we have… miss you so much…
Small gray
Sorry, son
This time…
This is…
Wolffy
Son, I will definitely not leave you again
Found the core
good
This sun is really good
dad
Actually…you can do it without moving out
I’ll take care of you
Small gray
Don’t you blame me for leaving you back then?
Strange
but…
But haven’t you said it?
This time…
This time you won’t leave us again
Little Gray Gray…
Don’t hug you suddenly
I…I’m not a child again
But this time you have to say it
Um
and…
This is…
Hello