Big Wolf Where are you
Hello, what’s wrong My cute little gray
Red
I’m back...
Gray...Grey Wolf
Red Red Where are you now
When will you come back
Red Red Why don’t you talk anymore
You’re back
Yes, I’m back
Very good
Fifteen years, you’re still the same
Uh this...
Mom Sorry
I’ve been ignoring
I didn’t tell you about my father’s return
A lot of things have happened
Wait until you come back and we will slowly tell you
Go home red
Yes, I’ll go back now
wait for me…
Let’s go home and sweep it.
Wait for your mother to come back
Um
elder brother
This time, no mistakes are allowed
Black Diamond
Brother, don’t leave
It’s too late...
Can be vulnerable
Is it a spear or a shield or a shield?
Humph, it’s still necessary to say
It must be a spear
Benefit and frugal
Humph I think it’s still a little bit bad
After all, only good defense
Only by attacking better
Spear damage
Shield damage
- The spear is...
Hello, the museum is about to close. You leave quickly
Spear Spear
Who is more harmful
Thousands of years
Let us try again
Who is the strongest weapon
Of course it’s me
I have the most defensive supreme shield
Hahahahaha
The strongest defense
Just right
I also have the most powerful attacking spear
It depends on your God’s spear,
Or is my sacred shield hard
Hum, the Holy Shield
Take the call
Let my strongest spear break you
I
Hahaha
The strongest spear is just like this
Then let you see my true power
Come on
Look at my trick
I’m the worst
I’m the most harmful
Ahhhhhh
This was last night
The screen monitored outside the museum
What are the contradictions between these two contradictions?
The name of the most powerful weapon in the world
Since ancient times, it has been a contradiction between spear and shield
Don’t worry about their conflicts
We just need to find the spear and shield as soon as possible
It’s over
Stop talking about spears and shields
Everyone, go find conflicts
Finally finished swiping
Otherwise, please give me a swat next time
Wolffy
The monsters are missing
I’m here now
I’ll go too
You’re worried about something wrong with my arm, right?
Not
I’m afraid of you
Whenever you encounter danger
It’s so tiring that the little lamb brothers are not good
Can’t you leave yet
Come
Light rain
elder brother
How could I stay at home
What happened
Will it be nearby?
Must be there
Boy, I didn’t expect you to be a little capable
Next I’m going to take it seriously
Say nothing
Don’t disturb me from completing my mission
Let you see the attack power of the strongest weapon
Hehe, it’s not enough
what…
Good attack power
But the defense is too bad
Then I will crush you with attack
That’s it...
I only know how to avoid it. What a master
Solve you in one blow
Fewer look down on people
Pay for your arrogance
ah
Is this the most powerful attack weapon?
The spear can be cut off and not be humiliated
Take me with all my strength
ah…
Small tricks of carving
It’s my brother’s voice
Light rain...
Stupid
elder brother
Gloves reacted
The monster must be nearby
It’s hard to say it’s a monster
Don’t stay here
I’ll go see
What’s up
Nothing to go
It must be a monster
I’ll go see
Son
Actually, since I decided to come out and find monsters
Don’t be afraid of danger
So you don’t have to worry about me too much
I’ve said
I just don’t want to make you tired of the lamb brother
What are you doing
I didn’t expect to do my best
Flying us all so far
That’s...
Hum, wait for me
This time you must let you know that I am the most harmful
Found you
Wilie, what are you doing
Can’t go
Small gray
I know you’re afraid that your dad will be in danger
but…
Dad is one of the guardians of Yang Village
Encountering dangers and difficulties
How can you hide behind others
I don’t want to be a coward
I want to protect not only everyone
And where are you
and
If you can collect the fragments quickly
I’ll go back 15 years ago soon
This is…as a husband and a father’s responsibility
etc.
That... this time
No matter what, I’ll go with you
OK, we are going to be the father and son soldiers