Sparky
We didn’t find the monster here
Then find it and contact us
Um
Where will it be
Found
I’m here
I found a new restaurant
Ahhhhh…
Need to be tight when looking for cards
The monster is here
We’re here right now
It’s…
You’re OK with Jonie
I’m fine
Then let’s go quickly
I also collected a card for the doctor
It’s…
ah
Look forward to her and don’t let her run away
That’s too dangerous. You can’t get there
Believe in black diamonds
elder brother
I won’t win the same move for the second time
See you again
Oh…
Wolffy
Shield monster
Very hard to fight
Weslie Brother
Why are you here
We were beaten by the monsters there
Hahaha
Spear, you’re actually knocked down
No need to interfere…
It’s the same as many
Are you looking for me if you have something to do?
elder brother
not good
Wilie takes good care of Xiao Yu
Um
It’s okay
More carefree things
Ha… I’ve been beaten
The same to you
We’re going to make a quick decision
It’s really hard
They are so crowded that they are going to lose
Or we can cooperate at the right time
Hum, it’s just a while
Death piercing
dad
ah
elder brother
Don’t go past you will hinder their
They’re so terrible when they work together
- Watch the trick
elder brother…
Light rain
You don’t want to bully my brother
danger
Tell you… don’t run away…
elder brother
They actually ran away
There are no tools here
And his structure is so sophisticated
There is no way to practice the Dharma at all
elder brother…
elder brother
Who is the brother
Xiaoyu, please slow down
Who is he
Brother, turn faster
Does Xiaoyu like her brother?
Yes, my favorite brother
The brother will protect his sister
Wait a minute…
elder brother
younger sister
What exactly are these
And why does it appear in my memory
elder brother
Light rain
Brother, wake up
elder brother
- elder brother
Sister… Stop crying…
elder brother…
Just called Xiaoyu to call her sister
They came and we went out and led them out
This spear and this shield
One is indestructible, one is indestructible
How to deal with it
Yes, there is a way
No need to hide
Come out
Blue chase
We’re here
Come and catch us
Stealing and making a decision openly
Can’t escape
We won’t get
Alas, it’s so hard to fight
Haha…it’s up to us
Surrender
We were beaten by the Spear Monster
We have surrendered
Hahaha Do you know my widow is hurt?
Of course of course
Your attack is the most harmful
No one can attack you once you take action
The eyes of the crowd are bright
Are you right?
The shield monster is the most harmful
It’s all his body that is inaccessible to the sword
Stop our attack
We were just beaten
Hey…the eyes of the crowd are so bright
what
You mean you are worse than me
Isn’t this a bright one?
It’s not me who came to save you. You’ve already passed
So ugly, let’s compare
Come on
Master Spear Monster, let him see your ultimate move
Shield monster I’m going to do something
Lord Shield Monster, you can’t transfer it
- Just now
- Rotary Card
ah…
It turns out they’ve been doing it
Just wait for our chance to kill each other
Finally finished
Too tired
Don’t want to run, monster
You’re going to come late and it’s going to be broadcast at the end of the film
I don’t have to take my brother away…
Nothing allowed
Small gray
Light rain
I have a lot of questions to ask you
Why do you want to take the black diamond away
I want to recycle him because he belongs to Dr.
Today I will let you know that it is my martial arts
Or your machine is damaged
Come on
Brother Brother…
Hum, you still have some use
Hei Diamond is really Xiaoyu’s brother
Why did he become like this
Because the doctor chose him
Where is the smoke?
Cough cough cough…
Everyone is fine
It’s OK
My brother doesn’t see it
elder brother
Light rain
Where have you gone
The mood of the light rain is so exciting. It’s over
Who is it
Help her take away the black diamond
And I didn’t expect
Mysterious people have the ability to turn people into robots
Will it be cold weather?
Then will I become a robot in the end
Under the control of mythical people
Don’t worry, we will definitely defeat the mysterious
Let you recover and save Xiaoyu’s brother
Um
come on