Doctor Black Diamond System Has Crashed
Very heavy
Bu Lei
In PhD
Let’s see yours next
yes
Run quickly...
Ah...Run quickly, it’s a monster
Help
Help, help, help...
It’s nothing anymore
You leave here quickly
Thank you brother
Are you the firefighter Sparky?
Do you know me?
Of course you are my idol
Can I ask for your signature?
sign?
It’s not the time to say this
It’s very dangerous here. You can leave here quickly
- Sparky
The monster is indeed here
Let’s deal with it together
good
Come on, the great hero of Sparky
Why are you still here? Didn’t I tell you to leave?
I just want to see more idols, do you meet again?
Are you a fan of Sparky?
You go and hide first
Let’s come to you again soon
Go quickly
Thousand paper robe
Oops, it’s going to run away
Gravity War
Tibbie
Um
You bring me down
Leave it to me
Very good We have another card
It seems we are one step closer to the truth
Wow, you’re so terrible
Eliminate the monsters that hurt us
Why are you still here
Yes
It just exploded here, very dangerous
You shouldn’t follow us
Because I’ve seen an idol for the first time
Jonie, I am also your fan
Can I ask for your signature?
Also my fan?
All right
give
I’m saying how strange this person is
Always sign
I’m so lucky
Saved by idols and got a signature
Thank you
What a strange girl
Let’s go find the next card
Weslie in the West Region Weslie in the East Region
Let’s move in a different way too
- good
What’s wrong? Jonie
I’ve been followed
what? Could it be that the mystery was sent from?
Then there should be an alley ahead of you
Go in
We will cooperate with you to catch the carp in an actin
good
Huh? Where have you gone?
Eat me a stew
etc.
How
See clearly
ah?
Why are you again
Why are you following me
I just...want to take some photos of my idols back
I know this is not good
But I really like you
I’m really sorry for bringing you trouble
I’ve deleted the photo now
That’s because of this?
Forget it, it’s not a big deal
Let me tell you next time
Are you really not angry?
No anxiety
You’re so good
OK, we’re going to do the mission
goodbye
I always think there is no match for you
Tibbie, what do you think
suspicious
Take a look
Um
- Sure enough, there is a problem
Why do we follow her?
I think this person is a bit weird
At first I showed a very admiration for me
I don’t care much about it
I immediately showed admiration for the Jonie
This is intentionally approaching us
It’s definitely not against you
You’re thinking too much
Maybe
But her performance just now
I think it’s a bit suspicious, too
Yes, Tibbie said it right
All are related to mysterious people
She snatched up
I’m here
Go in
There is indeed a cat
Go and have a look
Nothing comes
Hand in hand... Delivery...
Hehehe, the Jonie...
card…
…weakness…
It must be the mysterious subordinate
Go in and take a look
Nothing allowed
You’re already enclosed
Old point, put down your hand...
This is...
How about it...
Now Fan Exchange Exchange Exchange Exchange Exchange Photos
Is that serious?
It seems to be... a mistake...
Uh, she seems to be a Jonie
Yes, it seems
She is the Hot Goat...
Jonie Jonie...
Wait a moment
What the hell is going on
We are all members of the support of the Hot Goat
It’s underway today
The exchange meeting between the warm Paddi
Surrounded?
comminicate?
No, no, no
Then you just said it was a little weaker. What’s the card?
What does it mean
ah?
oh
I mean, the card of this Jonie was a little weak
No big legs revealed
ah
So you...
As a fan of the Hot Goat
I’ve always wanted one
Nuanyang Goat Limited Doll
Then why are you all the way
Always sneaking around
No, no
I just can’t find the way
I almost missed the activity time
Fans’ First Article: Not allowed to arrive
It turns out...it’s like this...
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
-I got the signature of the Nuanyang Goat Clothing
I must let my family pass on for generations...
We love you, Jonie, forever
Thank you idol
No thanks
It’s our exchange meeting that will swear to everyone
This is a supplement to everyone
I also have the limited edition doll you want
I’ll give it to you
Really
Of course
But you need to go home with me to get it
go home? Still don’t want it
Compared to you sending me
I want to get it through my own efforts
Have brought you so much trouble
Can’t beat you anymore
Idol Goodbye
OK See you again
I always think she is not in a relationship
What’s up? Still doubting
My straightforward tells me that there is absolutely something wrong
Bu Lei also wants one
Nuanyang Goat Limited Edition Doll
- Look at the stars and look at the moon...
Everything is under control
Very good Don’t let me down
Guaranteed completion of the mission
The moon represents my heart. Dreams are sweet...