I’m really sorry that your audio machine is too old
No way to completely repair it
Nothing to do, thank you boss
And that...
Can you please help me sign a name?
Of course
Wow, isn’t this a Jonie?
Can you take a photo with me?
OK
Wow, thank you so much
Alas, I can’t hear it anyway
Is your favorite old record?
Lalala...Lalalala...
This song...
Who is singing
oops
Sorry, you’re fine...
Alas, isn’t this an idol?
I’m fine. You...you’re from last time...
I’m Bu Lei
Thank you Bu Lei
Hee Hee, it’s so exciting to help your idol
I have something to go first
Ah, Idol, you’re injured
Ah...when
Must be fine
Otherwise the wound will be infected
Can I go in?
Of course
Wow...
This is my studio
Wow, this bed is so beautiful
This electronic piano is also very beautiful
Let’s put things down first. It’s too heavy.
Not very heavy
Yes, where is your pharmacy?
There
What is this
This is an old audio machine
Only it can play
My favorite record when I was a kid
A record that idols like?
Can I listen?
OK
This song...
Very easy to hear
Alas...It’s a pity that this audio machine is too old
It’s always a jammed case when putting on the disc. No matter how hard it is to repair it
PhD
What do you plan to deal with this uninfected card
Don’t worry, I suddenly want to do a practical experience
Thank you today
No thanks
How many fans don’t have the chance to get close to their idols
Then I’ll leave first. Be careful not to get any wounds.
Uh-huh
There are cards nearby
Audio machine?
I’ve obviously turned off
What’s going on
careful
It’s a monster
Comet worm
Oops, let it run away
It’s very dangerous outside
Bu Lei You stay here
I’ll go and see it, too
It’s nearby
Wow
Found you
Blue Blue Sniper
What’s my pussy that can’t be beaten
It’s okay, Weslie
Yes, thank you, the class leader
The sound wave attack of this monster is very strong
Must let it stop playing
If you can directly hit the middle finger
Music can stop
clear
Since the normal attack does not work
Then you can only use this trick
Flying Spear Card
It hides
Success
- Look at the stars and the moon
- Look at my heart
-Wow, I listen to this song very well
Oh, it’s coming again...
Let me solve it
what…
Jonie...
Rotary card
Thank you, Weslie
- ah
Can’t let it run
Weslie We’re chasing
OK
Help
- It’s a monster
Help...
Run quickly... Run quickly...
ah…
Find the audio machine monster
Wow...
Rotary card
Audio machine monster beasts see where you can still run
Weslie Let’s attack it together
clear
Weslie, just take advantage of the situation
Class Manager
Jonie, you’re fine
Bu Lei I’m fine
Chief, we succeeded
The total solution has been concluded
- The class manager
Lalala...Lalala...
Xiao Xin
Chief, you finally wake up
How do you feel
I’m fine...
It’s great that you’re fine, we’re worried
Everyone is here
Strange That song just now was...
Am I dreaming?
- Lala...
Who is singing
Is it Bu Lei? She just left
Stepping?
Can’t she be Xiao Xin?
Lalala...Lalala...