Look at the stars and the moon Look at my heart
The singing of the two people is so similar to...
oops
Jonie
You’re fine
It’s OK…
Why do you feel so unpretentious all day long
I don’t know if I’m going to hit the glass
I…
If you have any troubles, say it
Maybe I can help
I think...
Bu Lei is my friend Xiao Xin when I was a child
We’re together all day...
I made it, please eat it
Wow, so cute
Hehe Hee As cute as we two
-Sing together...-The moon represents my heart
Later I moved to the green grassland
Xiao Xin also left the Goat clan later
We finally broke the contact
You’re because of that song
I think Bu Lei is Xiao Xin
Yes, Xiaoxin’s singing is unique
And few people know that song
Bu Lei, she can actually sing
Will this be just a coincidence
Bu Lei may just happen to be singing that song too
Is it a coincidence
Think about it seriously
Except for that song
Are there any other similarities between Bu Lei and Xiao Xin?
Tibbie, you’re right
Maybe I’m thinking too much
If Xiaoxin knew
You are still thinking about her good friend
Will be very happy too
-Fragment Reaction-Fragment Reaction
Help...
A high-altitude smash incident occurred in the city center
oops…
What’s going on
You guys always like to play with your phone with a low head
Don’t look at the road
See how I teach you
ah
ah…
Ah Thank you
Run to a safe place
Alas, help...
Blue Blue Sniper
What’s going on
ah…
Hum, you’re waiting
No more calm?
Escaped?
We’re fighting the air just now
It should be a tangible monster
Will be obscured
Then we can’t see it, how can we get the card?
Jonie
Xiao Xin…
Bu Lei, what happened to you
You were injured before, I came to see you
I also gave you some fun
Thank you
Wow, is there any food?
It’s the time
I can’t see you when I fight monsters
If you have food, you will appear
I’ve made a lot, let’s eat together
Very good
Bu Lei This...you did this...
Yes, what’s going on
How could you make this sensation?
I...I think it’s very cute
Bu Lei Where did you live when you were a child
Remember if you have any friends?
Uh I don’t have too many childhood memories
As for friends’ words...
I don’t remember it very much
I just vaguely remember
I should have a very good friend
But she seemed to move later
Jonie, hurry up
Thank you for your hard work so long
Of course you eat first
Then... I’m not polite
Yes, I’m really delicious
Looks delicious, I’m not polite
Sparky , don’t you try it?
So delicious
No, I don’t have much appetite
I’m leaving first
See you next time
Sparky  Do you don’t like thunder?
I think she has a problem
I don’t trust her
Is she... Xiao Xin?
Xiao Xin? Who is it
This is how things are…
So that’s how it is
That’s why you’re suspicious
Bu Lei is your good friend Xiao Xin
Is Xiaoxin a robot too?
No
Then how could Bu Lei be Xiao Xin?
But Bu Lei sang that song and had this slightest...
It’s really alike
If Bu Lei is Xiao Xin
Then there is only one possibility
She is the robot transformed by her
Mysterious
If Bu Lei was really transformed by a mysterious person
Then she deliberately approached you. It must be a pity.
I have to ask clearly
I must get an answer
Look at the stars and the moon
This song...
Look at my heart
Bu Lei Is it you
Idol, are you doing
You... are my friend Xiao Xin
What Xiaoxin, I am Bu Lei
Then I ask you if you were sent by a mysterious person
What are you tightening
Is that mysterious person threatening you
Turn you into a robot
What are you talking about
Who is the mysterious person
Nuanyang Goat You think it’s wrong
I’m not the Xiaoxin you said
But it’s fun to be a good friend by your idol.
Then why do you sing that song
Song?
Yes, a song I was in the time
Xiaoxin and I often sang when we were young
How do you sing
And why do you have that slightest mind
That’s the shape that Xiao Xin would make
I...I don’t know
Because you are not Bu Lei
You are my good friend Xiao Xin
You must have been exploited by a mysterious person
He’s not a good person
Come on, I’ll take you home
He wouldn’t be able to use me
I’m Bu Lei
Comet worm
Xiao Xin
You don’t remember when we were young
Have you been in the Goat tribe?
At that time, we played together and sang together
Stop talking
Let’s eat what you made together
Even though we lost contact
But I have never forgotten our friendship
Stop talking
I’m Bu Lei
We can’t be friends, either
We’re just enemies
Xiao Xin…
- We want to be good friends
I...who am I