Who am I…
You are Xiaoxin, we are friends
Catch the traitor
Xiaoxin I won’t let them catch you
Don’t hurt my friends
Xiao Xin
Xiaoxin I’ll take you back to treat you immediately
Can’t take her to our base
She is a mysterious subordinate
But Xiaoxin was injured
Village Chief Bu Lei How is she
OK, not seriously injured
That’s good
That village chief…
Can you restore Xiaoxin to her original appearance?
The body is not good, but the memory…
Maybe under certain circumstances
Under a certain situation…
At that time, Hei Diao put a danger on Xiaoyu.
Finally, Black Diamond even recognized the rain
Then I can try it too
Let Xiaoxin recall what happened before
But she is a mysterious subordinate
It’s very likely that I’m approaching you on purpose
But she really saved me when I was in danger
I want to try
Sparky’s worry is not unreasonable
Everyone should be vigilant and there will be no mistakes
Um
Come on, Jonie
If she is really Xiaoxin
You will surely wake her up
Yes, thank you for your Tibbie
Then we’ll go back first
OK See you tomorrow
Xiaoxin You’re awake
Am I… Xiaoxin?
Xiao Xin This is my diary of that year
You’ll see it later, maybe there will be an answer
Ha, Nuanyang, look
It’s a smoke
We will run together when we count down to 1
See who will arrive first
good
- 3 2…
There’s not a count to 1 yet, why did you run away
Of course I will run away too
Its wings were damaged
I’ll save it
Be careful
Good, I’ll save you
Ah, Jonie, be careful
ah…
You’re fine
We’re fine
Jonie, wait for me to save you
Um
Don’t be afraid, Xiao Xin won’t destroy ours
She will definitely come to save us
Have you been waiting for a long time
I know you’ll be back
Xiao Cui…
Have you remembered it?
I have no idea
It was just a sudden thought of it in my brain
Don’t be anxious
Let’s continue reading the diary and slowly recall it
Um
- Oops, no good…
There are monsters appearing
Warm Yangyang, come soon
good
Xiaoxin, you have a good rest at home
I’ll go back
It must be the monster yesterday again
careful
We can’t find where it is
Jonie…
Don’t know the trace of the monster
Still can’t catch it
ah…
Water … I can say this method can
disgusting
No wonder I can’t see it all the time
It turned out to be a glass monster
Hum, I won’t play with you anymore
It’s fine to see what’s going on
Don’t run
What other tricks do you have besides being invisible?
Jonie…
Hahahahaha
Your friends are in my hands
See how you deal with me
You’re so despicable
Despicable is a reward for this villain
Don’t hit me anymore
Then I’ll leave
Attack it now
It will definitely hurt the Jonie
What is this
It’s the ice card
It’s Bu Lei
What do you want to do
Don’t you be afraid of hurting your friends?
I’m a doctor’s subordinate
I only have one purpose
Just get the card on you
Bu Lei Stop
Xiao Xin…
I’ll launch a bubble card after a few strokes
3…
We will run together when we count down to 1
See who will arrive first
Don’t hurt the Hot Goat
2…
Ah, you’re cheating me
Jonie…
Jonie
You’re OK with the Jonie
I’m fine
Fortunately, Xiaoxin also remembers our tacit understanding when we were young
Sorry, because you have something to do with a mysterious person
So we didn’t believe you before
- sorry
Excuse me
No need to apologize
You don’t believe me, it’s right.
Because I am a doctor’s subordinate
Xiaoxin, can you take us to find a mysterious person
He may be doing something very dangerous
We need to find him and stop him
no
Why
What the doctor does is for everyone
I can’t take you to destroy the plan of Dr.
Yes, the doctor is kind to me
Are you kind?
The doctor saved me at my most difficult time
So no matter what
I won’t betray the Doctor
Is this the case?…
But if the doctor wants me to hurt you
I can’t do it, either
So sorry…
It seems we are too anxious
Wait one day
Xiaoxin knows how serious the things a mysterious person does
I believe she will stand here on our side
I see
Do you mind if I call you Xiaoxin
Don’t mind
You don’t seem to be happy
Will you betray the doctor because I don’t want to
Don’t like me
No, we all like you very much
real?
Um
Then I will give you a surprise tomorrow
surprise? What a surprise
You’ll know tomorrow
Wow, it turns out you’re surprised
Just made a cake for everyone by hand
The cake made by Xiaoxin is so delicious
Your hand is so good
I can eat two more
Eat more if you taste delicious
I’ll do it again if I don’t want it
Huh? Where is the village chief
Oh, he just said he had to be busy with something
I’ve sent him
How do I feel a little silly…
I also…
Xiao Xin…