Xiao Xin…you…
Ah he woke up…
What a big cake
It turns out to be a
I want to eat
ah…
It’s up to you
Another dreamer
Why is it so difficult
I knew you weren’t a good person
Why haven’t you been
Because I didn’t eat your food at all
I’m pretending to expose your true face
Hand over all the cards
Hum, you have been blocking my plan since the beginning
At the beginning, you should have dealt with it first.
Don’t run
Return the card back
Gravity War
Slide card
Hum, your lens card is useless to me
Run
Hum, the other cards will work for you
I’ll say it again last
Return the card
ah…
Just surrender
I have to find a safe and simple part-time job
A photo administrator in the museum
How about it…
The young man was thrown into the trash can
Behind all this
What kind of sad separation has happened
Who is so disrespectful to the elderly and has no public morality?
Based on the on-site search analysis…
Help me relax
I’ll tell you the truth?
Old man, tell me the truth now
I will remember your life-saving grace in my heart.
But I’m really in the middle of the day
There is also a chance to meet
I’ll tell you slowly
Wait for a moment to learn about personal accident insurance
I didn’t expect that the old man would take such a ruthless move.
Slowy How do you be here
Stop Bu Lei I know what you are doing
Ah, you discovered it
I made these amazing cakes by hand
Don’t tell everyone
I won’t let them eat it
You have been denying Xiaoxin’s identity on the surface
But you don’t know…
Ha ha ha ha…
Actually you…
Oh, it’s a pity
You have no luck with eating the cake I made
Let the lambs eat more for you
Bu Lei…
Huh…How come the old man runs so fast
Children
It’s okay, wake up
Well…Mura Chief…
You’re cheated by Bu Lei
She stole all the cards while you were
Xiao Xin…
I thought she had already remembered our friends
I’ll chase Xiaoxin
I want to ask clearly and take the card back
Don’t blame me for being rude if I don’t surrender
Don’t be civil, come here
This…this is the ability of the Goat Card
what?
Soil and whirlwind?
Did she use two cards at the same time?
How is this possible…
Of course it’s possible
My attack card
Haha…it’s mine now
Come back and don’t leave
Give me the card
Sparky , you’re fine
Jonie
Don’t worry, I’ll save you…
How can I not be in a hurry
Bu Lei snatched our card and walked there
You go chase me now, I can come out
You go first I’ll chase you soon
look
OK I’ll go chase her first
- Ah… monster…
Village Chief, what’s wrong
You’re hit by Bu Lei and there’s something wrong with the cake
So…Why did she do this
She is trying to steal all your cards
what?
It’s all our fault that we trust her too easily
Sparky  and Jonie have already chased
Hope they can get on
Sparky had clearly reminded us before
There is a problem with Bu Lei
Be careless
Sparky  What’s going on with you
Are everyone awake?
Come here in the forest, the thunder ran away
Sparky
Why do you want to talk to us from this angle?
Don’t care about these details
Anyway, you come and support it
You hold on, we’ll be there right away
Wake up, everyone
Xiao Xin…
Hum, why is there another one
Xiaoxin Why do you do this
Do you…have any hardships
You tell me
I will definitely help you Xiaoxin
Hum, don’t think you’re right
First I have no worries
Second, I am not Xiaoxin, my name is Bu Lei
Isn’t Bu Lei Xiao Xin?
That’s all my packaging
what…
I said…I’ve cheated on you
All are cheating on you…
You…really not Xiao Xin
How many times have you said
No, no, no…
At the beginning, I pretended to be a fan and planned to approach you slowly
I accidentally heard what you said about Xiaoxin
I specially collected all the information about her
Specially decorated as Xiaoxin to approach you
I didn’t expect you to be so terrible
Weiyi believed that I was Xiaoxin
But…
Stop following me
The card sent to the door… I collected you
It’s time to do nothing