Next, it’s you
What’s going on
-The body is a little uncontrolled - Bu Lei…
It’s hard to tell…
Bu Lei
Why did the monster start to move again
It also changed its shape
Quick… Let me go…
I’ll come to save you right away
Who wants…you save
ah…
Let me…release the thunder
Very hard
Do you actually use the metal adsorbed on your body as armor?
But the eyes are exposed
Bu Lei…
If this continues, she will not be able to hold back
Let me release the thunder
Stepping and Stepping and Stepping and Stepping…
Bu Lei Where are you
Bu Lei…
The doctor will definitely be happy this time
Mission…complete… the cards are all here… Come soon…
Bu Lei got the card
You bring the robot to get it back
yes
You… finally…
Bu Lei You don’t look very good
I…is nothing…
Card… card… handed over… to you…
The card has been obtained
But Bu Lei suffered a lot
She has no longer used the value
Just bring the card back
Know
Bu Lei Are you here?
Bu Lei
What’s going on
Is it you, the mysterious man?
Our cards…
Doctors no longer need you, never
Run away
I have to inform you very much
The mysterious subordinates were abandoning the construction site
He took all the cards
We’re here right now
Bu Lei, you hold on
I’ll take you back to the base now and let Mr. Slowy help you heal
insist
I’m not your friend
Why do you want to save me
Even if we are not friends now
But in the future we can also become good friends.
Return our cards
Look at mine
Don’t want to run
You can’t escape
Give us the card quickly
Hold them down
yes
what
What’s the good fortune
No way to leave
And me
Wolffy
Want to take everyone’s card away, ask me first
ah
Wolffy
I’m fine
Our cards…
Not finished yet
ah
Wolffy
You’re fine
I’m fine, what about my mysterious subordinates
Run away
Everyone is back
Yes, and got most of the cards back
most?
That’s right
I just cleared it
We only lack the enhancing card, acid rain card
Polkadot and slam cards
And it’s my only impact card
It’s okay, we can use it together
It’s all caused by the thunder
We still believe her so much
That…I…
Come with me
You’re back
It turns out that you are here, Mr. Slowy
Ah Bu Lei
Why is she here
Sorry, yes…I brought her back
She’s the one who stole everyone’s cards
Why did you bring her back?
She suffered a serious injury…and…
She was defeated by a mysterious person
Also attacked by companions
I really can’t bear it
Then she is dressed again
This time the injury is not ordinary serious
Then… can Mr. Slowy repair her?
Why…
She has never seen any designs or parts
It should have been created by that mysterious person
I have no way to repair her
I’ll look for information and study it
Everyone is tired today
Let’s take a break early
Um
I’m not allowed to take a shower first
Bu Lei…
Ah Bu Lei…
Doctor…I want to…go back…
Bu Lei
All the mysterious people abandon you
Why do you still have to go back
Bu Lei
You’re finally back
Doctor, I thought you didn’t want me anymore
How did it happen
Don’t be afraid, you’re safe now
PhD…
- Hehehehehe…
Oh
My name is Dr. Ti
Don’t be afraid, you’re safe now
Dr. Tie…Dr.
Bu Lei
Bo…Dr.
Overcoming machine stop…stop…motor…