After searching for two days, I still couldn’t find Bu Lei
Jonie
Is she really the friend you were a kid?
I...I don’t know, but I want to save her
No matter who she is
good
We want to find the mysterious
Then rescue everyone
That’s right
The mysterious man has sent out three robots
The fourth robot has probably appeared
When everyone is looking for cards
Be more careful
Um
What’s the matter? Goat
Hehehe, wasn’t your card stolen?
I’ll lend it to you
No need
It’s okay for me to have a few cards
Keep it and protect yourself
Sparky
A child at the station was stuck in a chair
OK I’ll go up right away
I have the task, let’s go first
Oh wow wow wow wow
I’m going to go out and suck
What happened to that kid
Go and have a look
Trouble everyone, let me
Let me thank you
Hello Sparky, please help my child
No problem, let me see what the child is doing
What to watch
Save me out quickly
Fortunately, I wasn’t injured. Please wait a moment
OK, let the children come out slowly
OK OK
Thank you so much
Thank you, brother
You are welcome
Be sure to pay more attention in the future
Don’t let children encounter dangerous things
Or tap the head to a narrow place
I will educate him well in the future
Children don’t want to be so naughty in the future
Oh wow, so terrible
Ah, what’s this sound
There are monsters nearby
I have other tasks, let’s go first
Dear passengers
The D206 train to Permanent City is about to enter the station
- Please carry your luggage and start checking
Alas
Oh
Very sorry, I’ll help you get it
Where are you going
Thank you, I’m going to get on the train behind you
Then let’s go quickly
There are cards
ah
Get off quickly
If this continues, your luggage will explode
There is danger here
Please leave the station immediately
Wow ah ah ah...
Help...
I’ll come... catch you
Do you catch me
But... thank you
Can’t destroy the station
I don’t have a broken station
The joke time has arrived
There was a bun since
ah
One day he got angry...
Hahaha
What buns...
What does it mean? What does it mean
It exploded outside, too
Ahhhh…
There is danger here
- Everyone, please leave
The suitcase exploded again
Come again...
The sound of clock... is strange
Why did all the items around start to explode
Where is the monster
How to beat
- How to beat...
Not good, the skateboard is ready to explode
Can’t let it explode here
Hahahahaha It’s so fun
Ha ha ha ha…
Found...you
Not wrong
Hey, this is the reward for finding me
You’ll explode together, too
Ha ha ha ha
What...what
It turns out that you are at the broken station
Ahhhhh…
dad
thank you
No thanks
The reaction disappeared
The monster that just now was defeated
Except for us
Only the mysterious people are still collecting cards. It’s hard to tell...
ah
Sorry
My photo...
It’s him
Red is us
Surprise or not
You’ve called five times today
I’m really anxious
Don’t worry, it should be here soon
mother
I’ve learned how to cook many dishes
I’ll make it for you
good
Red
We cleaned up the wolf castle
You come back to check
Uh-huh
good
Red Red I heard that there has been a meteor shower recently…
You come back and let’s go see it together
OK, it’s really exciting
We’ll be able to get together soon
The car is about to enter the tunnel, the signal is uncertain
Then I’ll quit first
Red and red again
See you again, mom
You’ve called a few phone calls
Are you ready to go home?
I must be seeing my family, aren’t you very anxious
Finally... I’m going to meet
Next…Next…Next…Next…
The system is stuck
Yes, then...just you
ah…
What? Mysterious sent robots out again
- ah….
Otherwise, who will solve the monster
Take the card away
Let’s have something to eat first
steamed stuffed bun…
There was a bun since then...
Huh? Isn’t one too small
I have it here
steamed stuffed bun…
puff…
Ah hahahahahaha
There is no problem with the bun
I’ll tell you a very funny joke
There was a bun since then...
Hahahahahahaha...
Why? Isn’t it funny? Hahaha...
What joke is so funny? Sparky
Hahahahahaha... It’s so funny...
It’s you
Yesterday’s jokes were so fun, hahaha...
Give it to me
Why so irritable
I’m not laughing at you
I just think that joke is so funny
Give it to me
Do you want to do
Cold and quiet
Um?
What do you want to do...
Give it to me
what?
ah…
What exactly do you want to do...
no
Give me a photo
Don’t go too far
I haven’t seen any photos
Huh? This is...
etc.
You’re looking for this photo
Yes Thanks
What happened to this person
Hitting someone is just to find photos
No
Don’t go...
Apologize to me...
Finally...come back...
Found you
Who is it?
ah…
Come on
Red...
Strange, why is there no one