Use astrological stone fragments to make biological experiments
Really looking forward to it
It’s really inexplicable
How did this do to me
How did I treat you
What’s wrong with you?
It’s okay, I’ll eat it
I’ll look for the card first
What happened to him in Sparky
It seems that Sparky has suffered a great grievance
Why is this said
Last night…
Last night I slept with Sparky
Suddenly I’m tired
Tell the point
Isn’t this just about to say
I’ve woken up
Sparky  What’s wrong with you
oops
How can you hit someone at will
Didn’t you hit me?
oops
Sparky  Grows Up
It’s been a long time since this has happened
So who happened to him yesterday
It’s okay, Sparky  is careless
It’s gone soon
Have you eaten it?
We’re going to find the card, too
- Um
I haven’t eaten yet
Sure enough, here again
You didn’t apologize to me yesterday about what happened to me?
How do you want to do it?
The elephant saw the passing
The stools are diamonded into the soil
Only one leg exposed
The rabbit asked him why he did this
后后后
I want to take revenge, he fell
Haha Haha Haha
Why did he joke again
I’m sorry to apologize. Do you hear jokes from me?
Just forget what happened yesterday
You’re a robot, I won’t consider it with you
Let’s shake hands and make peace
What do you mean
Have a signal
Discover target attack program start
What do you want to do
You took my way
Monsters
Gravity War
Too dangerous, please leave
I’ll deal with it
ah…
Who can’t stop my work, blow it up
You are not allowed to destroy this station
Why would he fight monsters if he doesn’t
This is a robot
He is a mysterious man’s subordinate
Owner
what
What’s wrong with him
No matter what, I’ll play with you next
Overestimate one’s ability, blow up
Oops
Go quickly
thank you
Everyone evacuates to a safe place
No one can stop my work.
stop
I searched for a long time but couldn’t find anything
My bun…
You’re fine
My buns…
Don’t eat the buns again
I’ll give you another one
steamed stuffed bun…
Ha ha ha ha
Mom…Is an uncle bullying me
You’ve got too much
What’s wrong with you, Yangyang
I didn’t mean it
I…I just saw the bun and figured it out
A joke that Sparky said yesterday
Hahaha… hiccup… I’ll tell you
There was a bun since before, and one day he sucked it
So funny…hahaha…
Is it so funny?
Forget it, you don’t understand. I’ll tell him Sparky
Have to find a time to come and unexpectedly
Sparky  I finally know why you laughed
So funny hahaha…
I can’t laugh anymore
Come here there are monsters
Oh no, the Sparky  now has no cards
You keep looking for it, we’re here to help
- Follow the order Weslie and Goat Chief
What’s up
Because Weslie is like a young official
Assign tasks to us
Doctor, you’re back
What’s up
Who are you
Let me go
Not a doctor…
Responsive to negative energy emotions Start the joke program
Have a stick on vacation in Northern Europe
Please ask what stick he is
The answer is pockmarks
Ha ha ha ha…
That’s your ability
Not his opponent at all
Let’s have fun again
Oops
Light and easy to carry
Who is it
You’re just here
Let me deal with you
No use
whee
not good
Thank you
Big Wolf You’re not doing well
Hahaha I’ve come and got a shot
Be careful about his pyrodisiac
Let me come and let him stop. Control card
Blasted
Hum, I have a flame card
No, his body is full of pyrodisiac
Once detonated, this area will become a sea of fire
Weslie, let him not move first
good
Sticky card
Success
Yes
Oops
We’re surrounded
You’re all too weak
Enjoy the blasting feast I prepared for you
Rotary card
It’s up to me…
Do you think I can’t get angry if I can’t move?
what…
Let’s change back to the original state
The darn boring goat
I’m a Sparky
Of course you don’t pay any more
Let’s go back
Um
Oh, it’s on fire…
Group photo? Who are these two people?
This is the robot at the station
Who is the other one