Um?
Why should I delete my memory
These things are too irritating to find fragments
It’s useless to keep
These are the memories of Dr. Fu
No one can touch
Don’t you want to find Dr. Fu?
Who helped you maintain and update your system these years
Who promised you to find Dr. Fu
And as a exchange you just need to help me find the fragments
If you don’t help me collect shreds
You don’t want to find Dr. Fu in the future
I understand I will definitely help you find the chips
You must help me find Dr. Fu.
Of course, only I can help you
Isn’t this Lao Fu and Oli?
It turns out that his name is Oli
Mr. Slowy, do you know them
Yes, it really makes people think of it
Say where did you find this photo
Say it’s long
Mr. Slowy should tell us first
What happened to Dr. Fu and Oli
Alas, this is also a long time…
That’s my representative to Goat Village
When I was attending the robot conference…
Look at the strange robots there
We can definitely make a big splash at the conference today
Hahaha…
My robot
It’s not time to participate in the competition
Old man…you’re fine…
Need help
My robot is broken
Your robot will be fine
Let us help you fix it
Is it OK
This robot has a good understanding with him
Fixed
Very good
Thank you, I am a Slowy, what about you
No need to be a polite person, I am Fu Yangyang
This is my partner Oli
Is the robot your…company?
Oli has been with me for many years
Make the most thoughtful robot
It’s my goal in life
Oli is the most successful invention of my
Doctor, you didn’t drink water today
Drink the water quickly or I will kill you
Hahaha obey the order
Is the most considerate robot?
Slowy
You’re also attending this robot conference
Let’s fight for the good results together
I…I still need to work hard
Then let’s work together
come on
Since then
I often go to various places to attend seminars with Dr. Fu
Every time Oli will be at the station
Wait for Dr. Fu to come back
Lao Fu made a robot like Oli
It actually left a deep impression on me
What about Dr. Fu now
Why haven’t you heard of this person
An explosion occurred at the Astronomy Institute in the suburbs last night
The fire has been destroyed
What is being studied is astrological movement
This explosion brought heavy blows to the scientific community…
At that time, Lao Fu was there
ah!
After that
Several times I’ve been to the station in the Science and Technology City
I’ve told him this
Don’t wait here
Dr. Fu is gone, go back
Will be back
Dr. Fu will definitely come back
I’ll wait for him here
Yes, he’ll come back
He never believed
The fact that Dr. Fu is no longer here
Dr. Fu…Oli…
Oli has been at the station
It turned out that I was waiting for Dr. Fu to come back
What a sentimental robot
But I didn’t see him later
I didn’t expect that he is back now
Oli…
This photo is important to him
It’s hard to find photos that day, like a crazy thing
I’ll give him the photo
We’ll go too
You wait…
Why don’t you see the photo again
The boulder…no one can hold…
If I don’t collect the chips
You don’t want to find Lao Fu in the future
Suffering
Who hit the rock
Rocket Card
You steal a huge rock
The boulder is going to be beaten
Alas, please hide
No, the station was destroyed
Dr. Fu can’t come back
Oh, the station cannot be destroyed
As long as you pass, you can’t attack the rock
Everyone, hurry up and leave the station, hurry up
Monster beast…
The boulders will be destroyed casually
Well
Can’t…
Dr. Fu has not come back yet
It cannot be destroyed here
Monsters
Gravity War
Take the call
Don’t worry about you
But… Oli, I’m helping you
You’ll destroy the station
Fu…Doctor has not come back yet
Oli…
Then be beaten by the huge rock
It’s quite awesome
You’ll destroy the station
You have something to do
The boulders are going to destroy you
Oli Oli Why are you watching the big bell all the time
Because you can tell how long does the doctor come back by looking at the clock
Very accurate
Oh, is that
It seems that I won’t be able to get away from now on
Why
Because the clock will be out of order
Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah
Not insulted
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Oli
Oli Are you okay
Can you still move?
The station…
The station…no more…
Oli Dr. Fu has…
photo
Oh, by the way, I’m going to give it to you
Dr. Fu…
I want…Dr. Fu is back
Cards Cards to the doctor
What doctor…
You wait a moment
Where is the card just now
Did the mysterious person ask you to find the card?
Hello, answer me
Just look for the card, Dr. Fu can come back
Just look for a card…
Impossible What are you talking about
Oli
Oli, you’re a little more awake
Dr. Fu…Dr. Fu has already…
Never come back
Oli…
Where are you going
Finally found
Give me
what
There are cards in your pocket, too
I won’t give it to you
Give me Give me
Even if you help the mysterious
Find all the cards in the world
Dr. Fu will not come back again
Dr. Fu is no longer here
Oli…
He wouldn’t have agreed to me
- Will definitely find Dr. Fu’s
Go back with me
We’ll help you repair Oli
Card…just get the card…
Oli
Give me
Have you been crazy? Stop it
Give me… Give me… Give me… Give me…
Give me… Give me… Give me… Give me… Give me…
There is no way to communicate. Retreat first