I tried to make a plan
Now I’ll try to remove mechanical transformation
Failed...
It seems that there is no hope for recovery
Don’t do that, there’s definitely something going on
I just worry if I’m really mechanical
You will be unable to control yourself and hurt you
It won’t
You’ve never caught us
I’ll definitely come back
So the chance of harming us is not high
Don’t worry, I’ll try other methods
Finally came back
Sparky , you’re injured
Just a little wound
What happened when I added the photos to Oli
I told you when I went to Oli...
I’m back
It’s bad
Um?
stop
You can’t play this pants
There are important mechanical components inside, so don’t touch them
This is a bad guy and you want to change a new one right away. Do you know
good
I’ll help you upgrade a batch of super solid bags
If it fails in the future, you must remember to change it in time
Um
Change the new one and the doctor will not get angry
Dr. Fu is no longer here
Old Fu is no longer here
The doctor will definitely come back
Have to wait a little longer
You have to listen
I’m back
Have called whom
mother
How to say red
No one answered the phone
But it was the same a few times before
Probably the signal is not good
Why not before our mother comes back
Clean up your home
good
What’s up
Dad, you’re fine
My robot is getting more and more difficult to control
No, this cabinet has been used for too long
It’s a damaging one’s force
So it’s not your problem
That’s great
real
Have a glutinous rice noodles yesterday
What’s the way to fry you today
Waited for a long time
This is my most successful egg scrambled meal
Is the quick-dry delicious?
OK
How
tasty
Very good
I’ve started eating, too
I’m so tired today, please give me yours
It’s good that you like it
Hahahahaha
Is it really delicious?
I’m going to do it too...
Oh, how many salts did I put
Small gray
It’s so hard to eat, don’t eat it
Now, even the amount of salt can’t be controlled well if you cook it
What should you do if this mechanical hand hurts you in the future
Then control it
What you said before
At that time, I accidentally ate fruit
My whole body is very weak...
Dad, mom, how crazy
Stop slapping, almost broken
But I can’t control it
Then control it
You are a man, Han man
Can’t you do this little thing?
But…
No, Dad, accompany you
Don’t eat it, that’s a fruit
Let’s control it together
Dad... OK
Dad, am I a man, Han?
Of course we are all
We held on for a day, didn’t we succeed in the end?
Little Gray Gray…
So I’ll accompany you
Son
You’re really grown up
Fried vegetables
Dad, did you wash the pot before cooking?
no…
We had noodles with sausage yesterday and there were sausages inside.
Oh, I fry it without washing it
So this fried rice is so delicious
So dad’s hand is fine
- Very good
Then let’s go buy food after finishing sanitation
Have a big meal tonight
Let’s start eating
Let’s take a photo and post it to your mother
Let her come back soon
Come back soon
Oh, Sparky
Even if you help the mysterious people find the zi card
Dr. Fu will not come back
- Dr. Fu is no longer here
What’s wrong with you?
Big Wolf, do you think I’m too far apart
what
Overscore
That’s right
I haven’t been to play for a long time
It’s time for me to play
Are you still traumatizing about Oli?
Um
I just went to find Oli
He’s not at the station
I’m very worried about him
What to do
Get up and get up
Always worried and afraid
Why not be more serious
Want to solve the problem
You’re not trying to help Oli
When encountering small setbacks, you must hold on to your beliefs
Don’t give up
OK I’ll go find Oli
Um
Ah, there is a fire police nearby
I have to go first, I’ll leave first
Go quickly
Who accidentally fell into fire
Fortunately, I was rescued in time
Must wait for the owner of this house to come back
Give him a good class
Oli and Dr. Fu
It’s hard to say that here is the home of Oli and Dr. Fu
I remember the village chief said that Dr. Fu often travels to other places on business trips
It seems that these are brought back by Dr. Fu
Dr. Fu has been away for so long
Oli also wiped the house so clean
Waiting for...
I was too pissed before
Huh? What’s it?
…Oli…
How does mud doll sound?
- It seems to be Dr. Fu’s voice
…Oli…
It turns out that the relationship between them is so deep
Alas, Oli hasn’t come back for so long
I’ll come again tomorrow
I believe...
We can definitely return to this kind of life