Oli
Why are you still here
Go home soon…
One day a horse fell into the river
It became a Hema
Haha Haha Haha
What jokes are you talking about
Your house is on fire
Go back and have a look
There are fragments nearby
Oli You finally come back
Don’t worry, the firefighters have already slammed the fire
Not good Dr. Fu’s items
who
Come out
Fu…Dr…
very good
Pay close attention to the situation around Oli
OK
It’s almost successful…
Dr. Fu
You finally come back
Where have you been there for so many years
I miss you so much
It’s about to crack
Dr. Fu, you’re fine
You look so weak
No… nothing, just a little tired
Dr. Fu, sit and rest, I’ll clean up
This robot is so terrifying. I have to find a way to throw him away.
You moved me to a wall
Shred the middle piece clean
yes
Finally I have the opportunity to replenish some energy
What sound
Oh, it’s my stomach’s sound
Dr. Fu, wait, I’ll cook for you
Always leave
Earth Energy My favorite Earth Energy
Dr. Fu The noodles are ready
Ah, so fast
Dr. Fu, I made your favorite ingredient oil noodles
Come and do it now
Don’t eat it, don’t want to eat it, it’s too oily
What do you want to eat
I’m not hungry, I’ll go out
Dr. Fu Where are you going
I’ll go with you
Alas, he still caught up with
Have to find a way to leave
Do you want to do
Say one day the sewer is in a bad mood
It said it couldn’t figure it out, so the sewer was blocked
What’s up
Is it funny
Not funny
I have other…
I’ve read all this book "Joker Collection"
Why don’t you buy a new joke book and listen to it to me
OK Dr. Fu
You wait, I’ll go back
There are fragments of elephant star stones nearby
Dr. Fu I bought "100,001 Jokes"
Dr. Fu
Where are you?
Ah…Oh
Dr. Fu, don’t leave me
It’s going to crack…
Dr. Fu, I won’t let go this time
You can’t leave my video
What, please let me go
Let me go
It’s Oli
That person looks so familiar
I seem to have seen it somewhere
I remembered that he is Dr. Fu
Wait a minute.
Didn’t Mr. Slowy say that Dr. Fu is no longer alive?
Oli
What’s going on
what? You saw Lao Fu
Yes, it’s on the street
I saw Oli and Dr. Fu together
This is impossible. The report must be correct
Are you dazzled
There are fragments of elephant star stones nearby
It’s hard…it’s hard…that…that Dr. Fu is fake
I’ll go to Dr. Fu’s house to see it right away
I don’t know if they’re back
The door is fine
When did the hole be empty here
How did it fall out? Only half of it is left
If you don’t have to find them soon
I’ve finally taken down that clingy robot
Haven’t you bought a new joke book?
Let me listen to it
One day, I went swimming with beef balls and suddenly got cramps
It turned into beef tendon pills
Have heard
One day I was walking on the road
As I walked, I felt sour in my feet
When I looked down, I found that I had stepped on a lemon
I heard it too
You go buy another new joke book
I’m waiting for you here
But…
Don’t worry, I won’t go anywhere
Dr. Fu, please wait for me here
Don’t come out, I’ll come back soon
OK I’ll wait for you
Haha, that’s it
There’s a little energy
I’ll suck the entire building
Don’t be afraid of that robot
There are fragments of elephant star stones nearby
Where to
Fu…Dr.
Is it really you?
You’re indeed fake
What exactly did you change
Dr. Fu
Walk open
Don’t hinder me from absorbing soil energy
Gravity War
soil?
Eat me a stew
Don’t come over, help
Dr. Fu
Oli, save me
stop