The 56th experiment…
Hello Oli
Can you hear me say
Unusual function, successful startup
Hello
…Is it successful?
Yeah
Successful, success hahahahahaha
My name is Dr. Fu
A scientist living in the Science and Technology City
DiDi Dr. Fu
You are the smart robot I have developed by myself.
Beep I’m Oli
That’s right. From now on, we’ll be a family
Family
Oli I’ll take you there
How about it? How about it? How about it? How about it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it? Was it
Doctor How is his eyes dripping
This is called crying
When people feel sad or moved
The eyes will flow down the water like this
Crying… shui…
Children, duck and crab want to eat cake
They decided to win the game, who would win, guess who won
Well…I don’t know
The answer is crab
Why
Because crabs can only produce scissors
The duck can only produce cloth
Oh hahahahahahaha…
Haha See you again
Doctor, why didn’t he cry
Because jokes make people happy
Happiness will make people smile
Then I will give you a joke every day
How about Oli
Have you felt the wonder of nature?
Detected many life reactions
Remove dirt
Wait…wait for a while
Oli, every life is precious
Don’t harm it
They are all trying to survive
Even if they are small and fragile
Have the right to survive
The view is great Oli
On the stars in this sky
Su contains many unknown materials and energy
I really want to study them
Oli I’m going on a business trip
Oli must wait for me to come back
knew
Finally came back
Go home and see Oli… Yes
What is this…
Welcome back Doctor
O’er…O’er
Have you not opened here?
Oh, silly kid…yes
Haha Oli Your gift
Oli I’ll teach you how to make oil noodles
Pay attention to maintaining balance
Try new parts
Oli is about to come out
knew
Oh…
Just pass this device
It can mechanicalize organic life bodies
It actually turned life into cold machinery…
Please ask the doctor
Mechanize life
What does this behavior mean?
Life is too fragile
But as long as it is mechanical
It will be able to eternally eliminate disease and death
And mechanization can also make us suck
Emotion is something that cannot be mastered
Let us use rationality to make the best choice
Complete further improvement
Thank you for your speech
Next, please…
With the advancement of technology
Our Science and Technology City is growing rapidly
It greatly improved our lives
But… I’ve encountered a big bottle now
The energy available on our planet is limited
Now we need to find new energy
From this I imagined the method of science
Induce energy-rich aurora to cities
This way, you can use the energy of stone
Please ask whether this solution has been verified through
The referenced device is almost completed
We will soon enter the experiment
Very wonderful speech
I wish you a successful experience
Thank you
Your research is interesting
Is this robot your assistant?
Maybe you can understand me Dr. Fu
I hope to use your research
Get energy that mechanizes the entire planet
This goes together
All living things on the planet will receive eternal life
Although life is fleeting…
But because it will disappear
Only beautiful and affordable
Your research is pretty good
But it should be used in more valuable places
In fact, it is constructed
Life is just a machine made of flesh and blood
Leave unnecessary emotional tragedies
Make the most correct choice with rationality
Isn’t it better?
If you are interested, you can come to me anytime
Dr. Fu’s experiment failed
The lime deviates from the pre-determined spiral
It hit the park in the city center
The park is hit by a huge impact
Have become completely different
Countering the crisis experience
And I’m safe in my home
- Anti-crisis experiments, and I’m safe in my home
How can you do such a dangerous experience in the city
That’s it
sorry
I’ll be responsible for this accident
Responsible for what you want to be
Fortunately, I just hit the open space this time
Who knows what the consequences will be if it hits the crowd
- Can you afford it?
Dr. Fu, you’re fine
Hum, you crazy scientist, leave here
Doctor Violent
Demonstration clearance immediately
Oli No…No harm to them
But…
Oli You are a listening child, you must be a kind robot
Um
Sorry, I can’t take you with me this experiment
Dr. Fu Your luggage
Thank you Oli, I’ll leave first
Dr. Fu…
What’s up
Pay attention to safety on the road
Yes, although this experiment will be far away from the Science and Technology City
But you don’t have to worry about it.
I’ll be back soon
You will be presented with a gift at that time
Oli will wait for the doctor to come back
The system… is severely damaged
It’s about to… stop running
Keep going like this
I… can’t wait…Dr. Fu comes back…
You want me to help you with repair
With my skills, I can do it
Since that’s the case… I’ll ask you…
But I have a condition
condition
You have to help me with your work
But I… have to wait for Dr. Fu…
You think it through yourself
This slowly decays
You can’t wait for Dr. Fu to come back
Dr. Fu…
Oli…Oli…Oli…Oli…
OK I’ll promise you…
This time… I won’t separate it with Dr. Fu again…
Oli…
You may not be able to attack Dr. Fu
ah
Oli
A little cold
This doctor is just a fake
He is the monster that the card depends on
The real Dr. Fu is no longer here
You’re nonsense… You’re nonsense… You’re nonsense… You’re nonsense
I won’t… let you hurt Dr. Fu