Oli, you’re sober
He is just the clay doll that Dr. Fu bought for you
Just put it with this clay doll
You will hear the recording that Dr. Fu left for you
What clay doll
I’ve never seen it
Oli
The ceremony is about to begin
Huh? Village chief?
-This view is...
That’s...
stop
Don’t want to run
oops…
Tibbie
Village Chief, you’re fine
I’ve sprained my feet. Alas...
I’ll take you to the hospital for a bag
No need, small question...
Why did she suddenly attack the village chief?
Alas, I’m not jealous of me, I want to catch me
To weaken our fighting power
Right
I’m going to attend the ceremony of the new building
Let’s go together
good
Don’t run around on the sidewalk and see the road
Dr. Fu
The central landmark building with the highest specifications of the building
Will be put into use in the Science and Technology City soon
With this building
Not only can the injury be cured
It can also increase its strength significantly
Mom is about to open
Welcome to the opening scene of the Central Building
Below is our Slowy
Announce the official opening of the Central Building
I won’t say much, let’s start immediately
Reaction of fragments of elephant star stone
danger
Oh no, no, no...
Village Chief, please hide. It’s too dangerous here
You have to be careful
Um
You should leave with everyone soon
Yes, thank you aunt
Call me sister
OK, see you again, sister
Sparky
That’s fake Dr. Fu, it’s getting bigger
It’s absorbing energy We have to stop it quickly
I want to absorb a little more and become more harmful
Stop it quickly
Let’s take care of you
You dare to come
You’re really crazy
All disappeared
While now
Success
who
- Oli
You don’t want to hurt Dr. Fu
Hehehe...you’re here just right
Take the call
You’ll be awake
It’s not Dr. Fu at all
Close your mouth
He is he is Dr. Fu
Sparky
Oli Dr. Fu... He has...
You shut my mouth for me
You can take a look at it yourself
Will Dr. Fu hurt everyone?
Will he destroy this city at will?
Not...No...
He is... He is Dr. Fu
Oli
PhD…
Oli Oli
Here is...
Dr. Fu…
Oli, every life is precious
Don’t hurt them
Dr. Fu...Dr. Fu...Dr. Fu
Dr. Fu Where have you been
I’ve been waiting for you so long, you won’t come back
I... haven’t come back? Hahaha
No
-don’t want…
You’re fine
ah...
The guy who is doing things
Let me return to the original mud doll
don’t want…
Don’t be in vain
I won’t hurt you...ah...
Sparky
This is not Dr. Fu at all
ah…
See how I deal with you
You are going to be dealt with
Oli What are you doing
Sparky
Oli
You’re injured. Go to a safe place with them
Leave it to me here
Oli
You actually fought with me
You’re not Dr. Fu at all
Oli…Why do you want to attack me
I’m Dr. Fu
No, you are not
Can’t you recognize me?
I’m right in front of you...
No
You’re just a clay man
whee
I never thought that robots would be interested
Oli
Go to waste
Dr. Fu’s son was damaged
Wait for me to get the clay doll you bought
Go home to repair
Oli will wait for you to come home
Can still
You are the clay man controlled by Elephant Star Stone
And I’m a clay doll
I’m Dr. Fu, you’re waiting for.
Dr. Fu is a kind, gentle and protects nature
Respect life Scientist who loves peace
Not yours
Only the clay man wearing Dr. Fu’s shell
Oli
- I am Dr. Fu
Oli Stop
I didn’t know why my heart hurts
It seems that I can get it now
Oli
You have to hold it
Oli’s injuries were too serious. I went to the village chief.
Sorry, Dr. Fu
The mud doll is dirty
And made myself like this...
You should be very angry
Oli is not afraid of slaughter
I’ll make you laugh, hahaha...
Come back soon
Dr. Fu Oli…I really want to see you again
Oli…
Oli gives you
This is
Oli...
PhD
Do you like this gift?
Like Like Like
Hehehehe, can you tell it’s us?
Yes...we
The city I visited this time is very good
Rich natural resources are very suitable for scientific research
The city here blends into nature
The environment is pleasant
Tell you good news
The new type of car is about to open
All robots can ride together
Hehehe, you won’t have to be alone in the future
- Waiting for me to come back at the station
Let’s go to different places to do scientific research together
OK
good…
Let’s go together
Wherever Dr. Fu goes, Oli goes
Oli will always be with Dr. Fu
We will never be separated and be together forever
thank you…
- Sparky ...
Stop it
Stop it Oli
The village chief will come soon
Oli Oli hold it
In the end, Oli was severely beaten
The village chief is unable to do anything...
Oli…Oli…