Fragment fusion is complete Next to eliminate the memory
Wait until the memory is eliminated
You can start card function testing
Red
Red is me, Big Grey Wolf
Why do you ignore me
oops
Mechanization…
Red and wait for me
No...
No
- Don’t have anything
It turns out to be a dream
Sorry, I fell asleep
I’m too tired to find cards recently
Are you just having a nightmare dream?
I’ve dreamed of red
Probably because I haven’t been able to contact her recently
I’m so worried
Wolffy
You asked me to investigate the behavior of Wolnie before
I found it
real
Where is the red red
Through the monitoring of the Science and Technology City
You can see that Wolnie has returned to the Science and Technology City
Look, these are all her activities
Where is the final event? When is it
Seven days ago Wolnie had returned to the neighborhood of Wolf Castle
But the activity tracks are closed nearby
Red Red returns to the Wolf Castle
Then why didn’t she go home?
Have you encountered danger?
No, I’m going to go out to find her
Wolffy
Wilie Let’s go find red red together
etc.
We’ll go with you
Yes, look for it separately
Um
Where is this
I...who am I
Doctor Her memory has not been completely eliminated
Need a test
Um
Is anyone
Answer me quickly
Who is the responsible person here?
Why did I suddenly keep me here
Come out soon
What is this
ah
What’s going on in this place
Start attacking others without saying a word
Response and agility marks Agent functions take effect
Isn’t this someone? Let me out quickly
Power level
Dare to hit me
Accuracy standards
Agent function test passed
Begin to conduct an intimate test
What tricks do you want to play
If I don’t let me out, I will call you...
Who do I want to call...
Who are they...
Who is it? I can’t remember
Red...
mother…
Who is it...
Not good, let her escape
- Robots are chasing
yes
Test Continue
Wait for me Hahaha
What’s going on
Who am I
Target person chase
Why do you want to catch me
Who can tell me...
Another batch
Why do you want to chase me
Catch it back
I actually jumped so high
Wilie, have you found it there?
no
I haven’t found this direction yet
Let’s go
Target disappears Continue search
They... didn’t find me
Ah I’m obsessed
Passed by the Invisible Test
This work is a bit interesting
Recycle now
yes
Can’t find it here either
Tianyan once again observed the activity traces of Wolnie
real
Where is it
Right near you
Let’s go quickly
- Um
Where did this force come from
I...
Who am I...
It seems to be around here
- Red Red…
mother…
Where are you
Very familiar sound
Red...who is it?
The head hurts so much...
Red I’m here
Who is he
Who are you
Red...I heard the red sound
Really, I heard it too
Is there any
Who is he
Red Red Where are you
Dad Mom, hurry up
- Come son
Son...
Red
mother
Little gray... Big gray wolf...
I remembered...
They are my husband and son
Wolffy I’m here
Red...
It’s a red sound
They’re still waiting for me to go home
I want to go home
It’s okay
Ah I’m sorry
What about red
Wolffy found it?
not…
Oh, my air ball has flew away
Red...