Red
What to do
Sorry, I’m wrong
I’ve recognized it
It’s okay, look for it again, don’t give up
Don’t give up
Mom Mom
Tibbie
What’s wrong with you in such a hurry to come to us
未分
You might as well want to ask us to visit the museum
No, I just got through here
Seeing the mysterious subordinates
Come out sneakily from the museum
She’s so casually going to visit the museum
I don’t think it’s that simple
I can’t keep up with her
But I don’t think she will appear in the museum at will.
Maybe…she will come back
Then we’re waiting here together
Do you want to eat a meal first and wait
Have been waiting for a long time
It’s been two hours
I’d known to eat something first
Maybe the mysterious subordinates will not appear
Do we want to have a meal first
What to eat
Iron board straw grill
Or a bunch of skewers
It appears
Why don’t you just go and catch her
Even if you catch her
I don’t think she’ll reveal any information.
Then what should I do
Follow her
Maybe you will find more information about mysterious people
What is the plan of a mysterious person
We haven’t known
Only the mysterious person is found
There is a chance to restore the normalcy of Wolffy
If you say it right, we will follow her
She went in
Walk
Alas, buy tickets first, line up, don’t be hustle
It’s you?
Why…
You want to ask why I’m here
I changed jobs
Because I want to take advantage of my youth to get a little more
When I’m old
Don’t regret it for being mediocre
I want to ask
Why don’t you fall in with the person you just came in?
Just keep us
Someone went in?
Impossible I am as loyal as I can here
I didn’t see anyone else coming in at all
Then give us five tickets
Please hurry up
Youth are so anxious
Oh, the ticket is broken
I’ll give you another one
No need to change this one
Remember not to make noise in the museum
Everyone go look for it separately
Be careful
Who is there
There are fragmented signals
Hum, it’s you
what…
There is a sound there
Go quickly
- ah
Rotary card
Don’t
You’ve lost
Now see where you want to run
You’ve been banging, it’s really noisy
Is it so difficult to sleep well?
Wow…
How did the dinosaur skeleton move
It’s a fragment of star stone
not good
stop
Everyone, hide
Don’t even want to escape
The Dragon Tail
Sorry, Brother Dino
Stop you to sleep, let’s go
You continue… and continue to sleep and look back
I want to eat you
Didn’t it mean that the museum should be kept peaceful?
Are you doing here because you’re so quarrel
The dinosaur… is alive…
ah…
Where do you want to go
Do you think you can escape?
The Dragon Tail
I dare to slap me to sleep
Don’t even think about leaving
The dinosaur is not powerful. You treat me as a little lizard
ah
- This is too strong
You just stay and play slowly
Don’t run
The Dragon Tail
ah…
Tibbie
Bone spur attack
Very darn
What about the double butterfly drama
Oops
I won’t let you run away
I clearly saw her running in
How could the empty disappear?
I always feel…what is there any unpleasant thing
I see
No reflection, that’s it
ah…
Wow, dinosaur
The dinosaur… is alive…
Bone spur attack
Everyone, let’s go
Know
Stinky dragon
The Dragon Tail
Stick to you
stop
Abnormal, easy to open
Let me relax
Everyone is now fighting against it
Everyone, come up with a move
Stinky Dragon Your sleep time is here
Weslie Send Me to the highest point
receive
What happened
The dinosaur dispersed…
What a perfect link
I just found the weapon of Tibbie on the ground
But her people don’t see it
what
It must be chasing the mysterious subordinates
That mysterious man’s subordinate is so strong
Tibbie has no weapons yet
I’m afraid she’s in danger
Then let’s go find her
Tibbie We’re here
Ahhhhh…
You must find this