What’s this place
Is it hard to tell that this is the base of the mysterious man?
Have to contact everyone quickly
Strange, there is a signal, why can’t it be connected
Unidentified signal appears behind
Find the source of the signal
Tibbie…
Where are you, Tibbie…
Let’s take a look there
I don’t seem to see it here either
Tibbie’s phone can’t be reached
Tibbie
Her signal finally disappeared here
There is no place to hide here
Tibbie, you must not be in trouble
ah?
Come quickly
This is Tibbie’s pen
Lost source of signal
Good luck, almost discovered
It seems that this is the base for the mysterious people
How come there are such multi-robots here
Shadow What’s going on
It turns out that her name is Shadow What are they doing
The progress of biological experiment data is very smooth
The progress has reached 98%
All data changes
All are in your calculations
Hahaha…it’s really exciting
Dr. Tie…Biology Experience…
What is his purpose
Oops, have you been discovered?
Bad hair…
What’s going on in this…
It’s them…
The progress has reached 98%
This should be their experience this time
I’m going to rescue them
what?
Police Police Intruders
Oops
It seems that a mouse has come in
But…you can’t escape
Catch the intruder Catch the intruder
This must be the line left by Tibbie
Next to this picture, I can’t tell you that there is a problem with this picture
There is nothing
There is another possibility that painting may be a channel
Let me come and try
Hey
It seems not
I can’t tell you that everyone’s guess is correct
There is no place to hide here
Let’s go to another place to find it
Weslie Have you discovered something
Have you noticed the direction of this pen?
ah
According to the depth of this pen insertion
It’s more like he passed away in desperation
So Tibbie is in danger
The unveiled pen
what?
If it is passed
The only suitable direction here is there
Try that picture quickly
Sure enough, it’s
Walk
Doctor: An invader came to the laboratory
Escape now
There is a ladder around the corner
ah
Oops
Not good, I’m about to lose my mind…
Take it down
Ah ah…
ah…
Have to leave here quickly
I didn’t expect there was a channel here
Go quickly. Tibbie must be very dangerous now
Give me a free
Boiling… Goat…
Tibbie
Still one step late
It’s still very dangerous here. Let’s take Tibbie back first
Um