What happened to Tibbie
What happened to Mr. Slowy
I… am I old?
Tibbie’s injury I actually…
It’s hard to say that she is Tibbie…
Tibbie…
It took me so long to cure it…
Mr. Slowy, can you say all your words at once
Why am I here…
Tibbie
I’m fine, don’t worry so much
Tibbie What happened yesterday
Yesterday I walked along the underground passage
Enter their base…
Doctor Tie’s biological experience progress is very smooth
All data changes
All are in your calculations
continue
clear
Knowing that Dr. Ti is still catching people to do biology experience
I want to rescue him, but…
That’s it
I ran into you after I escaped from the base
Too dangerous, luckily, you’re fine
It turns out that the mysterious man’s subordinate is called Shadow
And that mysterious person is Doctor Tie
It’s hard to say Hantian and they are the test products of Dr. Tie
It’s very possible
Being so many robots
Also collect debris energy
What does he want to do him?
It’s hard to tell that doctor
Mr. Slowy, you know him
Just by my invention
It can turn organic objects into machines
Then you can machine the organic life body
I’m afraid he’s doing something terrible
But I saw Dr.
Different from the Doctor on the screen
what
Whatever he is different
Let’s go and rush into his base now
Catch him and ask for an understanding
Then I’ll take you the way
No, you’re still hurt
Yes, you need to cure the wound first
I’m fine
If they don’t go back now, they might just leave
Let’s go, you stay here to take care of it
I’m fine
And I know the location of the base best
Don’t forget that I’m also a guardian of the Goat Village
Um
When I came yesterday, I had a login
Just follow it
ah…
arrive
What does it mean
It’s been so tacit understanding for so many years
You can’t understand this?
I said I’ll go ahead and explore the road
But Weslie said that their son is smaller
Not easy to find out, so he said he went
The experiment room is right in front
Big Wolf, what’s wrong with you
It’s OK
That’s it
There are many nutritious tanks with robots in it
Why is it empty…
It seems they have withdrawn
And it should have been moved for a long time
Still one step late
It’s hard to be so successful along the way
There was no one at all
No, it’s just too smooth
I think…he predicted that we would come
you mean…
This is a trap
Sure enough, everyone should be careful
Thank you
It’s so despicable. I know how to steal
Fortunately, I will
Let’s go with your partner
These robots again
I’m too underestimating us
Escape quickly
ah
Tibbie
Not good
I’ve arranged a new base
good
Really good
Fortunately, Wolffy used his skills
My hands…
Wolffy
ah…
Shadow Blade Zoom
Big Wolf Your arm is fine
It’s okay. The stone hit the mechanical arm just now
Sorry, it’s all my fault…
This is just a trap designed by the doctor
It doesn’t matter to you
Exit on top
As long as we smash a gap upwards
You can climb to the ground
No…
A collapse happened here
If there is another shock
More stones will fall down at any time
sorry
Your hair is blown by the wind
Weslie
Don’t care about my hair at this time
The point is not hair style, it’s style
It’s blown from here
Exits are generally available in places with wind
The hall opposite did not completely collapse
As long as we can get to the University
You can go out from the sewer exit as the same way
Then we’ll smash the wall and go over
…
What’s the meaning
It’s been so tacit understanding for so many years
You can’t understand this
Weslie said let us say something
Avoid a second collapse
It’s best to dig it out
Ah chi
Excuse me
Everyone should act quickly
Um
Going tight
Why are you getting fat again
I don’t want it either
It’s too late to move, now I can only take a try
Go quickly
Not good, the shock just now was too strong
I can’t hold it here anymore. Run to the exit
Let’s escape from there
Hurry up everyone
It’s really unexpected
Then continue to look forward to the situation