Where is this
You finally wake up
Who are you…
Have you forgotten
It seems that the memory is caused by encountering a fright
Encounter with a siege…
The head hurts so much…what is this…
It’s okay, the headache is just temporary
I’ll help you repair it
You’ve been beaten up during a mission
Ani
You are the robot I made by hand
You’ll be fine, Ani
Made me out…
I’m a robot…
And you are the one who made me the doctorate
That’s right
The damaged part has been fixed
Next, you can continue the mission
… Mission…
Install the transmitter in this place
Ani, have you seen those robots?
If we can’t complete the mission
It will become that way
yes
I won’t disappoint you
Doctor It seems that she believed the implanted memory
Yes, continue your mission
yes
Everyone has already gone to find Wolnie
Don’t worry
Thank you Weslie
I’ll get along with you right away
Ah, this is…
Red crown
Could you see this wolf?
Could anyone see this wolf?
Stop it
Could you see this wolf?
Ah my eyes…
You’re fine
What’s going on
Gloves have reaction
- Double Butterfly Sword
If this continues, your eyes will be damaged
Look at mine
Thunder card
Didn’t hit
The light is too dazzling
Let’s notify Sparky and others first
Sparky
We were hit by monsters
Ah, we also encountered monsters
what
Ahhh, what’s the smell? It smells so smelly
What’s going on with the sudden durian smell
Durite flavor
stop
Don’t run
Don’t destroy the city anymore… the city…
I can’t stand it anymore
And you, why didn’t it affect
This sweet smell
It must be a good dune before it becomes a monster
Just now
Control card
The old point
We won’t hurt you
ah…
Paddi
It’s finished, it’s finished
Wait, isn’t it better to just open the snail?
Huh, it’s safe
Wow…
who
What are you doing
Why ignore me…
Don’t…not to ignore my existence
Humph, you’ve seen me now
what…
Don’t worry
Do you still need to continue?
You, you, don’t be proud
I sent a signal and there were other monsters coming to help
There is the monster
What’s going on with it
Finally recognized
Huh, too tired
Wow
Run again…
Wait a minute.
Weslie I found the red crown
She must have been back
Maybe it’s nearby
Don’t worry, you will definitely find Wolnie
Uh, something happened
Wolffy, look
There are monsters
Let’s go and have a look
Um
Weslie
Tibbie, Jonie, What’s the matter with you
And we
The monster we encountered ran up
So are we
It seems that there is more than one tower
Let’s go up and take a look
good
Flying card Flying
whee
Let’s go quickly, too
Very…shen
Don’t be upset
Slow…slow, so high
Very high, very high…
Look, everyone
That’s…
Let’s go together
One to three, that’s too bad
Not finished yet
What a dazzling light…
Don’t open your eyes
You’ll be left with no way
We’re here
You owe me I want you to give me double
Wait a moment
Why take these cards
Are you a doctorate?
What’s up to you
This sound…
Hello, wait
Wolffy
Don’t think I’m bullying
Red… Red
Wolnie…
My cloak
Unforgivable
Too much…
Red
Finally found you
Where have you been
Wilie and I are looking for you
Red
Where are you going
Red and so on
Red…