Doctor I have already installed something, and I have this one
very good
Continue the mission This time it’s the museum. Go
yes
dad…
Dad hasn’t come back yet
Mom, where are you
That’s how it’s happening
Wolnie, did you find her?
Yes, but Wolnie doesn’t seem to know us
The strangest thing is that she is also collecting cards
It wouldn’t be that she’d been turned into a robot too
Yes, Tibbie
You said before that you saw Dr. Ti was doing biology experience
Will that person be too red and too wolf
I’m not sure I didn’t have time to see...
Just found out
What about Wolffy now
He’s still looking for it
I’m tired and I have to let us come back first
I don’t know if he found it
Hello, have you seen her?
Please think carefully
Big Wolf Have you found Big Wolf?
Not yet
Big Wolf, you’re fine
I’m fine
At least she appeared
Although she doesn’t remember me
Yes, you’re so unique
She can definitely remember you
The most important thing is that she is fine
I’ll be relieved if she’s fine
mother
It’s mom
Hello Is anyone there?
Dad, I saw my mother, come here
I’ll arrive right away
Who
Where is your mother
I’m following here
But I can’t see it once I turn my eyes
Don’t worry, let’s look for it
Um
Climb high and look far away. Go upstairs and take a look
That must be red. Wait for me
Install the instrument on the top of the museum pyramid
Under the crystal corner
who
Red, don’t you remember me?
Who are you…
The wolf that I beat down before
Forget those uneasy things
I’m Wolffy
I don’t know you
Red Red Where have you been here during this period
My son and I miss you very much
Is it okay to go home with me
Red Red What do you want to do
Red, look at me
Do you think it looks familiar? Very considerate
Don’t bother me
Look at it
This is our son, Wilie
How cute
Red, do you remember it?
Remembered...
I remembered to beat you up
Red Red Red
I’ll make you remember me
Last time I went to work during the day, I actually encountered a monster
Hum Now I’m going to work at night
The security system has been strengthened
This time it will definitely be fine
What sound
Start monitoring without humans
Have been discovered
What happened
Have a quick
what
Oh, my obscene is not available
There is a thief
All unmanned machines are activated
Hello…
…
Don’t open the door
Red Red How did you come here
Did you force me to do it?
I remember the museum used to
It’s his secret base
Close your mouth
Red, you see, this is our family portrait
I’ve got it done again
I’m Wolffy, you’re my wife
This is our son Wilie
We are a family
you…
Ah...thief...
don’t want
oops
It’s okay
Yep, I’ve lost my salary this month
I’ll get the red red back
How about it...
Red
What to do again
How can you hit someone randomly?
That security guard is innocent
More carefree things
Of course I have to take care of it
I won’t make you a cold-blooded person
Although you are missing now
But you can’t lose your kind heart
Come home with me
Ahem Red, I don’t want to yell at you either
It’s just if I don’t stop you
Wait until you recover your memory
Thinking of the wrong thing I’ve done
I’ll definitely regret it.
Come and go home with me
Ahem... Red I won’t give up
I’ll make you remember me