dad
Dad, what’s wrong with your hands
Don’t touch it
Ah, Wilie…
Wilie has something wrong with my hand. Don’t get close to me
I’ll help you hold it
No, don’t come
You…you’re fine…Little Huihui…
I’m fine, I’ll come to help you
No…cannot hurt Wilie anymore…
dad
I’ve lost control
Can Wilie even do it?
If you encounter red…
ah…
No, can’t hurt her
not good
Oops
Wolffy, don’t rush
Uh Weslie
Ah… Alas
Big Wolf, what are you doing
What to say
I’m going down to pick up a jar
Haha… So that’s the case… Hahahaha…
give
Why did you run out so late?
I also knew I was here
Wilie told me
I’ll come out to find you
I seem to be unable to control myself anymore
I really don’t know how long I can hold
If this continues, I will hurt you too
Let’s look for the village chief again. Maybe…
Have tried it several times
The Slowy also tried their best, but…
Then you can’t give up
It’s lost after giving up. Do you want to recognize it?
Weslie…
Not to mention us
If you become a robot
What should I do with Wilie and Wolnie
Little gray…Red red…
good
Village Chief, what happened
Mechanization in Wolffy’s body
It has begun to disintegrate
If this continues…
Wolffy, relax
My hand… is coming again
Slowy
How many negative locks do you help me lock my hand
Increase the burden of heavy locking or maybe
But that’s the case
Your hands can’t move normally
It doesn’t matter how much you add
I don’t want to hurt the people around me anymore
Yes, come here
alright
Um? Why isn’t it heavy at all
ah…
I guess one is enough
Another…
what
What, you’re crazy
Another…
This level
This robot will be suitable soon
Please, Slowy
Oh, I really can’t do anything about you
This time I lowered the value a little
This burden won’t be too heavy
Thank you for your Slowy
Weslie Let’s go find the card
Only in this way can we defeat the doctor as quickly as possible
Um
Where is the monster
Wolffy, don’t worry, I’m still
I’m afraid I won’t be able to help you, and I’ll be tired of you
What are the simple words
As long as we cooperate
Always invincible
The best in the world?
The first steel monster does not agree
Quickly split
Oops…hand…
Blue Blue Sniper
What is ineffective
Since you want to play with me so much…
Then I’ll play with you
ah…
No, my weapon won’t work for it
Weslie, catch it quickly
Smoke Card
Um?
Do you think you can escape this way?
What’s going on
- Wow…
Wolffy Beware…
Wolffy
- ah
Wolffy, you don’t…
ah…
Weslie My hands are out of control again
Hide away quickly
careful
Is this a sisters-in-law?
Stop me…
Wolffy…
Don’t worry about me. Defeat the monsters first
Um
Leave it to me
Just right, I’ve been bored
Weslie…
ah…
Weslie
No, I can’t drag down Weslie
But my hand…
Hahahahahahaha…
Weslie is fighting hard
How can I keep this arm in a limit
ah…
Can’t be tired of Weslie anymore
Then you can’t give up, do you want to recognize it?
My own body…
I’ve decided
That’s the end
Gray…Grey Wolf
Station farther away
Haha, that’s what it looks like
Shadow Blade
Very… so bad
This is impossible
You stop me
I can definitely control myself and defeat you
Weslie
Rotary squirt
Wolffy
You can control your robot
Yes Yes
Even if mechanicalization continues
I should be able to control myself, too…
Right…