- oops
Tibbie
- You’re fine
Excuse me
Why do I always hit you in the corner?
Do you want to find the Elephant Star Stone fragments together?
OK
careful
- We’re here to help you
- alright
- Thank you brother and sister
Weslie, look
There are frogs in the bird’s trunk
The people in the Science and Technology City are really interesting
Have been walking, don’t miss it
New goods are on the market. Take a look
No thanks
Let’s see
That’s our company’s new mobile phone
Very thin and can blow up
Really flying away...
Ah my phone...
It’s really thin
What a leisurely and peaceful day
If only this continues
No, it’s going to run away
ah…
It turns out to be a
-oops
Tibbie
You’re fine
It’s OK
Let’s go find the Elephant Star Stone Fragments together
OK
careful
Raising frogs in bird’s trunk
Have been walking, don’t miss it
New goods are on the market. Take a look
No thanks
Let’s see
That’s our company’s latest mobile phone
Very thin and can blow up
Really flying away
Ah my phone...
Weslie
Do you have a very familiar feeling?
You feel this way, too
No, it’s going to run away
It’s exactly the same as the dream
If I guess right...
We were trapped on the same day
Sure enough, I thought it was my fault
It seems to be about to find the real monster
Only by breaking this cycle
Or try to change this world
good
Have been walking past Don’t miss it...
It’s windy. Your phone is about to fly away
This is not a real monster
It seems that you have already noticed it
We’re trapped in the same day now
If you can’t find the monsters you’re sucking in secret
We will never go out
We need to find monsters that will replicate time and space
Defeat it
cooperate
Where is the monster hidden?
I want to kick off the ball
What’s Weslie
Do you feel
The little boy there was a bit strange sound
Any questions?
I always feel like I don’t want to be with the gangster... where is it...
careful
Wait a moment
Yes, that’s it
On my first day
It’s a middle-aged man who plays baseball by himself
But these two times were two children
It’s hard to tell... they...
etc.
Hum The modeling style...
No…
Why…Why…
Why stop us from playing
It’s indeed it
stop
You can’t escape
Hello, do you want to play with me?
I’m a newly moved neighborhood
Can we play together?
good
This is for you
I’ll play with you every afternoon at 4:00
Remember to adjust the time
Um
Hey, let’s go play
good
So after moving, I can’t play with you
That’s it, everyone left
I’m the only place left
Don’t waste your time and tighten the card...
What’s going on
Sorry, I can’t walk with you anymore
Time recovery…
Tibbie
Here is...
This is the first time I’ve met a monster
It seems that time has recovered
Oops Card...
The shadow is not there either
It seems that the card has been taken away by her
Weslie What do you want to do
Finally caught up. Thank you
It seems that time has recovered
Uncle is there
This sound...
Long time no see
Why are you here
We haven’t played baseball together for a long time