Dine
Thank you for your hard work lately. Let’s have a good meal
Yes, only after eating can you be strong and continue to look for cards
After everything has passed
Do you have any plans?
I’m ready to go to the mountain to be a volunteer
I think I’ll release a new song
I want to go to Xishi to see the spring sea of flowers
What about you
I’m more harmful than everyone else
I know
You want to sleep, right
Not
I want to publish an old food book
Teach everyone to make long-lost food
I’m going to open a sales
The top 100 people can get my ID signature
Who wants your signature
snort
Will you come
Of course
If I can go back
I’ll grow up with everyone
Then I can eat your food
Be a willful person with Sparky
Hear the new song of the Jonie
Go to see the sea of flowers with Tibbie
Wolffy, you’ll be together, right?
Yes, of course
Wolffy
You don’t have to eat it so urgent
I won’t kill you
It’s not that you eat slowly, I’ll go find red first
Weslie, why don’t you come and help me?
OK No problem
I’ll ask you to find the fragments. Eat slowly
Leave it to us
Ani
Previous museum launcher
Why don’t there be a signal
I was hampered by Wolffy when I installed it last time
So it failed
Can Wolffy hinder you?
Sorry me...I’m just careless
You have to remember it all the time
You are my best robot
Don’t let me down
Well, I’ll reinstall the stuff now
It is now the museum’s closing time
Please leave the venue in an orderly manner. Thank you for your cooperation
Just lock the door and get off work
Museum?
Didn’t you go find Wolnie?
…
Who is it
Strange
I just heard a sound here
Why come to the museum
Because two days ago
I’ve blocked red action here
I feel she will definitely come back
Besides, this was once the base of Dr. Ti
You should also find some spider horses
So have you been waiting for her here for the past two days?
Yes, I can’t think of a better way
It’s really here
Keep up
Red
How is everything taken?
Don’t worry, it’s all tidy
Haven’t been discovered
Of course not, let’s start to move
What are you doing? The lights are not open
Are you going to have a birthday party when you prepare these things?
Today is Weslie’s birthday
We are ready to give him a greeting
He is busy collecting cards
I forgot about my birthday
So we were ready to give him a surprise
You can arrange it quickly
Otherwise, Weslie will come back as soon as the meeting
very nice
I’ll help you too
What a pity
Red, please stop
Red, wake up, I’m really your best person
Humph, my name is Anni
It is a robot made by Dr. Ti
You don’t have to worry about cheating me
You’re not a robot
You will be happy, angry, and hurt
It’s a lovely wolf
ah
Weslie
I’m not
Red I won’t make you wrong again
Why does it seem like there is a sound
Let go
Red I won’t hurt you anymore
Then
I’ve always felt why there are some problems in the place
No one, please check it out
I almost forgot to lock the warehouse door
No humans seem to have found it
OK Get off work
- Ah Insurance
- Open the door quickly. We’re locked inside
Oops, it’s so cold
How can the insurance warehouse be so cold
Let me come Shadow Blade
It seems there is no way to come in
Oh, what should I do
Right, contact other people to save us
I tried it without a signal
It’s getting colder and colder, we can’t sit
Come and move
Red Red Red Red Stop you will be hurt
You see, your hands are made like this
Let’s think of a way to warm your body up first
Don’t worry, I’m not cold
I still feel a little hot after the exercise
Come and see
The cake is good too
Weslie must be very surprised
Village Chief
What gift do you want to give to Weslie
It’s very useful for Weslie
Learning information
He is still reading this year
Can’t fall behind
Why haven’t Weslie come back yet
This should be automatic
Single-to-entry delivery of collections
Just open the door and you can go out here
That’s great
Alas
Oh, this door...it’s too tight
Let’s pull together
Red
How did you become like this
I’m fine...
Don’t be strong
We need to go out quickly
Let’s pull together and let Wolnie go out first
Weslie...
Don’t be too slow, hurry up
thank you
- 123
Red Quick...
Red, are you happy?
Red, please ask someone to save us
Red Red Did you hear Red Red Red...
I need to install the transmitter quickly