Doctor Tie
The museum’s transmitter has been installed
Very good Annie, let’s continue the mission
yes
You’re not a robot
You will be happy, angry, and hurt
You are my Wolnie
A lovely wolf
Why…
Why do you always feel this weird feeling
Why do I always think of him
Red, please ask someone to save us
Don’t worry about them
I just need to perform the mission
Oops, the door can’t be opened
Don’t worry, we will definitely be able to go out. Don’t worry...
Sorry, I didn’t let you go out first
It doesn’t matter
If it’s my family
I’ll want to let her out first, too.
Let’s talk about Weslie…Today is your birthday
Is it...the eyelids are so heavy...
Weslie Don’t close your eyes
I’m asleep and can’t wake up
Weslie
Um…
I’ll open the door now
Open the door Open the door
Quick... Open the door...
Wolffy...
No, don’t close your eyes
I’m so cool
Weslie Weslie Weslie Weslie...
ah…
It’s already morning...
We actually waited until we fell asleep...
Yes, you are the only one who can sleep
Hehe, hehe, are they too rude
Weslie never came back all night
Didn’t call a single
Nothing will happen
It’s Weslie coming to the phone
It’s a little gray
Sister Tibbie is my dad there with you?
No, he didn’t come here
He has never come back since he went out yesterday
Weslie is also true, is there something wrong with them?
Their gloves don’t have a signal and can’t contact you
Everyone, go outside and look for them
good
Let me help you together, too
Um
Village Chief, please try again
Is there any way to contact them
Notify us if there is any news
I know, you’re careful
Could you please see these two people in the photo?
no
Huh? Aren’t you the Jonie?
I like yours very much. Can you help me sign a name?
My phone number is below
If you see those two people bother me to contact me
OK Thank you
Jonie
How did you find it?
No, I’m already in the city where I can play ads
All have been put into personal trouble
But no one has contacted me now
Let’s look for it again
Um
Have you seen them?
no
belch…
Please ask if you have seen the goat and wolf in the photo
no
Are you not Master Yangyang?
The Master of the Goat
Please give us some new dishes
no
Wilie runs quickly...
Master…
You go out with me
Please ask anyone in the photo
I said that you can’t find someone in the museum...
But we are really anxious to find them
Don’t let it go, go
Have been searching for a day
Still nothing was found
Sparky
Ah, maybe they are looking for us there too
Then maybe I’m tired and I’m tired
Maybe...where to rest
If...if they were like they were 15 years ago
It disappeared suddenly again
It won’t
It’s not dark yet, we can’t give up
That’s right, we must have found something missing
Let’s look for it again
good
How to warm up
My wolf wool plus your wool is the best cold protection
Wolffy...
Oh, I can’t run anymore
Can we finally make popsicles here?
Don’t worry, isn’t Wolnie going out?
She’ll find someone to save us
Do you think Red Red really asks someone to save us?
I believe red is too wolf
You have such deep feelings, you should believe her even more
Weslie...
Now I’ll give it to you
What to do
Not every time we are together
Do you want to bite me?
How long ago has it been
I’m vegetarian now
But everything seems to be what happened yesterday
Remember
At that time, every time you came to catch us
In the end, we ran away
You’re always worried
Live
- Ha ha ha ha…
Please ask if you have seen them
They are called Weslie and Wolffy
Please ask if you have seen them...
no
They are called Weslie and Wolffy
Hello
It’s hard to tell that they’re still in the insurance warehouse
Red, please ask someone to save us
Why did I remember him again
Please ask if you have seen them
no
Please... Please...
Why...is it...
Please ask if there is any...
No, no
no
Hello...
Please ask if you have seen them
no
- Please...have you seen them
- Haven’t seen it
no
dad…
Can’t find them anywhere
It won’t disappear like that
What are you talking about nonsense
If you can’t find it, please continue searching
Let’s be calm first
Weslie Where did you go
Tibbie
We can’t give up yet
It’s impossible for them to disappear
We will definitely find them
Whether it was 15 years ago or 15 years ago
It’s a meteor...
Please tell us where they are
It seems that something is really flying here
Yes, flow... meteor
There seems to be words on it
Very cold...
My feet don’t seem to feel...
Everyone has been worried for 15 years
This time we want to make everyone feel sad again
I miss them
Weslie Weslie Weslie
dad
Little River
- Come and open the door quickly
- Here is a low temperature warehouse
- Why would someone come in if it’s cold
It seems that we have had phantoms
It seems to be
You’re quick to move
Am I looking for a key
There are all collections inside, why does it have...
Someone...
dad
Weslie
Finally found you
dad
It seems that all the illusions appear
Dad cheer up, I’m here
dad…
Oh, move them out first
one two three…
Be careful
Yes Yes
Well...this is...
dad
You’re awake
You...have found us...
I thought I would be stuck in it all the time
Big Wolf We’re fine
Ha ha ha ha
By the way you...how did you find us
Of course I found you
Yes, it’s all up to him to knock down a meteor
I just found out about yours
meteor?
yes
The paper wrapped in the stone
Writing you in the warehouse
Must be...
Red
My stomach is getting hungry...
Don’t say that there are so many
Let’s go back and eat quickly
The birthday cake prepared for Weslie yesterday
Paddi
How did you tell the secret?
It turns out that you have a birthday cake
It was originally a surprise to you
Anyway, Weslie’s birthday is also over
Yes, it’s gone
It’s okay. Just pass it after your birthday
I can still show up here
I can see all of you
I’m very content and happy
Let’s go back to the base soon
Give Weslie birthday
good