Let’s continue to look for fragments
- OK
You…can let go
No, what if you disappear again
Yesterday was just an accident
We want to protect you well
Are you still a child
Speaking of it…
Haven’t seen it lately
Doctor’s robot is coming to get the card
Somewhat is wrong
There must be some plans
I remembered
Last time I saw the red red in the museum
She seemed to be performing some other mission
What are they doing
Don’t waste time
You must collect fragments of elephant star stones quickly
- good
Then let’s move separately. Be careful
Reaction of fragments of elephant star stone
Don’t try to escape
It’s a shadow
Disappeared
Behind
Have you found a monster?
Hum, what do you want to tell you
If you don’t want to get hurt, leave
ah…
It’s a Tibbie
Tibbie…
How do they be here? It’s hard to tell…
The weapon of Tibbie
Tibbie Where are you
happiness…
Wait a moment…
It’s us, Tibbie
Where has she gone
have no idea
When I came
Only Tibbie’s sword is left here
I just said that Dr. Ti hasn’t been chaotic to us recently
Something happened immediately
The gloves can’t be located in Tibbie
There are no strong fights around here,
By the way, Tibbie’s gloves should not be damaged
Will it be…Tibbie was locked up
Where signals will be blocked
There is no time to delay, please look for it
good
Where am I
Where is this
How is this wall so hard
We’re in the gecko monster’s belly
what? In the gecko monster’s belly?
Only by breaking its belly can you get out
belch…
Positioned to be Tibbie
Huh? Why don’t you see it again
I’ve recorded where she appeared
Northeast, valley direction
It seems that you can’t get out by relying solely on fire
ah…
Oops
Ah, your feet…
Stop attacking, stomach acid will increase
Things to do
shadow
What do you mean
The fragments can only be mine
It seems to be effective
You’ll only get worse and worse if you’re just doing alone
Let me down and let us work together
Hum, what do you want to do
Don’t underestimate me
It’s better to have one more person to do it than to fight alone
At least solve the crisis in front of you first
As for the others, let’s talk about it later
I don’t need you to help
Hum, what can I do
Then I’ll try to get out by myself
There is the gecko’s…
I’ve come up with the idea
I don’t believe that I can’t break you
ha…
Sorry…
Tibbie, what did you do
shadow…
Tibbie
Serial
Earth Card
- Tail is broken…
Oh my God, the tail will move even if it is broken
Gecko has the ability to survive with a tail
It’s normal for its tail to move
But this tail will still hit people…ah…
It seems to be protecting its tail
I see…
Everyone beats the tail
good
It’s true
The tail is where the fragments of the star stone depend on
Focus on attacking the tail
Tibbie Quick
Get it
ah…
Sparky
Card…no more…
That shadow again
OK But…
You have to remember
Making a machine is your primary task
I know
Go out
yes