You’re not a robot
You will be happy, angry, and hurt
You are my Wolnie
A lovely wolf
How to open the door
who?
Are you doing? stop
Huh? Where is the person
What do you want to do
etc.
ah…
Don’t run Don’t run...
Small gray
Your performance in this inventorial competition is pretty good
Your first try to convert light energy to heat energy
It’s so terrible
Thank you
However, there are still some places that need to be adjusted
OK, Baoba, where do you want to go next
I’ll think about it...
Well...I want to go to the park
OK
Then Dad will take you there
Hahahahaha
Little Gray Gray Small Gray Gray
What’s wrong with you
Nothing to do, maybe just tired
Then go back and have a break...
Help...
Wow, then...what is that
Ah...it’s past
Let’s try it
Find a place to hide
What’s going on
It’s hard to say that it’s a fragment of star stone
Ahhhh…
Target confirmation
- Target cleared
Begin recycling of fragments
ah?
Will it...rebirth?
It’s still spikes
Uh...what is going on...
Not sure... Injury...
My mother
Humph, let me remember
It seems it has run away
Mom Mom
Mom, what’s wrong with you
Mom, you’re awake
Hmm...
Mom, don’t
I’m helping you with the injury
you…
Mom, this is for you
Mom, do you still remember
I was injured when I was a kid and you will give me candy
I won’t feel any more pain in this way
Wow, so beautiful
Well...wow, it hurts very much
Well...wow, it hurts...
Wilie, be good, don’t cry
Let mother see
Wilie Look
It’s candy
Wilie is the bravest
After taking candy, it doesn’t hurt if we take medicine
Ahhh
Come, mother, look at your hands
The wound hurts more because my family cares
I’ll feel unparalleled happiness
happiness?
Well, happy... to me...
It’s when my mother is around me
The bag is ready
Mom, do you still feel pain?
Why do I feel pain?
Mom Leave a reminder last time
You are the one who found my dad
Feel less self-righteous
I’m a robot, it won’t hurt at all
will not
mother
The poison in your body has not been cleaned yet
You must come tomorrow
I’ll wait for you here
dad
Where did you go
oops…
dad
What happened
Wait, don’t come in first
Dad is doing a practical experiment
The foot...why...why it hurts...
Dad, I saw my mother today
Really
Yes, but she’s gone
But I’ll make an appointment with her to meet at the river tomorrow
That’s great
Uh, Dad will go with you tomorrow
You have a rest first
OK Dad, you have a good rest, too
Why haven’t my mother come yet
Don’t worry, I believe your mother will come back
Um
Mom, I’ll wait for you
- Red
What is this
Be careful, dad
These thorns are poisonous
It was also his mother’s injuries before
Wilie, hand it to me here. You can hurry up...
dad…
Let’s fight together
Wilie Be careful behind
Drink...uh
Small gray
Ah, at this time...
Ah...Mom
Don’t mislead, I’m just here to get the pieces
I can’t catch you yet
You’re fine
Be careful, this guy likes stealing
ah…
Protect your child’s work
How can I hand it all over to red
I’ll help, too
Shadow Blade
Want to hold on
This is...
Dad, this is great
It has miraculous effects on vines
If you careless this time, you will remember it for me again
Don’t run
Red, let’s go chase
Ah...uh...
Red...Don’t worry about me first. Chase
You’re nowhere to escape
You’re not the same person too
Fight with you...
Very fast
Oops...
The toxicity works
See how I deal with you
Yes
what?
Who will allow you...
The red that hurt my family...
Wilie, you see your mother and me
Have you cooperated without any wits?
See it, see it
Hehehehehehehehe
You said yes
Red...
Don’t worry, our family will definitely be able to gather together
Yes, we can definitely
Um?
dad…
Your face...