How did this happen
Wolffy...
What are you doing
Don’t you think I’m getting too angry now?
Look at the skin of this mysterious mechanical
How many people dream of it
Look at this mechanical arm full of power
Can you still use a single hand sofa
Stop being rude Dad
How to do this
Oh, don’t worry, Wilie
Your dad, I will never become a robot
So do you
It’s getting late, hurry up and go back and rest
But…
Dad, I’m still worried about you
Why don’t I stay with you tonight
Haha How
This big guy is afraid of the dark
Not
Hehehe... Let’s take a shower first
Otherwise, the smell on you will be too heavy
I don’t want to have insomnia
There is no smell, obviously it doesn’t
Hahaha, done well
If nothing else, I’ll go out first
Slow down
Go and help me catch someone and come back
Who to catch
It’s him
Wilie... Why is it him
Um? Any questions?
Don’t dare I go out immediately
Ani, don’t let me down
learn
No harvest today
Big Wolf, aren’t you tired?
I’ve been running for only one day and said I’m tired
Paddi
- You have to train more
Big Wolf What are you shooting
Yes, I’m shooting once I come back
Ah I want to take some pictures for red
Why
Oh, look, Red Red doesn’t remember me now
I didn’t know if I could think of you when I saw this
Then I have to go and change the suit first
Haha No need
Just like usual
Then I’ll start shooting
Then take a photo like this
Hello everyone, I am Tibbie
What we want to introduce now is the popular professional foodie
Paddi
Alas, what exactly should you do with the Goat?
Orange juice is still good
The goat or the same thing, you know how to eat it
Next, we will introduce the brave firefighter
Sparky
Do more exercise while you are young
Sparky, you are just good at training muscles
Only by exercising your body will you be healthy
- My brand new album is about to be in two weeks
- Online on all major platforms
Please don’t miss it
Wow, a new album is coming
Yes, I’ve been ready for a long time
The cover design looks good
Wolffy, are you shooting these...
Yes, where will we go to find fragments tomorrow
Why don’t you go to the suburbs and have a look
Nothing has been found there
good
Then let’s go to see the sunrise together tomorrow morning
- ah…
Let’s take a group photo together
ah…
What to do if you don’t get up
- All shots are now
Only red leaves
Ah Found it
Dad is really
How can I forget to bring a long-focused lens
It turns out you are hiding here
It’s really confusing
Right
This may make my mother remember us
Ah, I have to be out of here
Hahaha... What a big marshmallow...
ah…
Ah, it’s coming
Hahahaha I’m sorry everyone...
It’s okay
Look, Wolffy is right in front of you
Let’s go over
Everyone…
What’s wrong? Weslie
Actually... Wolffy...
I have been asking everyone to make videos because...
It’s because I’m afraid of forgetting us. Yes
Really...we knew this early in the morning
Don’t forget
I’m the goat with the most hot baths in Wolfburg
I know Wolffy very well
And it is also the goat that has been rescued the most
Hahaha…
But I really think about it
- At that time, I could get a lot of food when I took a bath.
- We need to face it with a smile now
You’re here
Sorry, we’re late
Alas, it’s a pity that you didn’t see the sunrise
It’s okay. You’ve definitely taken it very well
Hehehe...that’s for sure
Wolffy Little Huihui
Didn’t he come with you?
Um? He went back to help me get something
It should be coming soon
Yes, wait a little longer
Don’t worry, this kid has grown a lot
Let’s take a group photo when someone is over
The scenery here is really too...
Beautiful
Wolffy Be careful
Catch you
I saw the red below...
what
She also carried a little gray
Everyone, hurry up
Wolnie Where do you want to take Wilie?
This is the order of Doctor Tie, it has nothing to do with you
what
Red Red This is our son
Why do you want to catch him
Don’t worry
Captured
well done
The doctor can’t get...
Don’t think about it, either
Red, no...
ah
Little Gray Gray…
Wilie wake up and don’t scare me
Wake up quickly...
Son, wake up quickly...
Wilie, wake up
Son...
Small gray
Dad...Dad, what’s wrong
Son, you’re fine
Very good
But Wilie...
It’s okay for you to be attacked by that kind of attack
Attack?
Yes, it hurts a little here
It turned out that this sling held the attack
What happened
I seem to see my mother
You’re fine... It’s really great
But why are you...
Doctor Sorry, my mission failed
I won’t blame you this time. Let’s go down first
yes
It’s so cruel to start
I also discovered something interesting
Ha ha ha ha…
It’s so early, Wilie
Dad, are you doing
I want to take a picture of my cute little gray
Dad, be careful
oops…
I thought it was
Red Red has accepted Wilie and me
but…
How did this section be recorded
No...
She deliberately hit the position of the hanging wall
It’s a monitor
Red Thank you...
Hey, you must have forgotten who you called now
Remember, your name is Big Wolf