Not too quick to have breakfast
Come
See what delicious food today...
Why is it still bread...
Have the same breakfast every day, I have eaten it
I obviously have water every day
Why did this flower die
Impossible I have water every day
So, I’ve been three times a day
So am I...
Drinking this watery every day is so strange
It seems there is no way to save it
Finally taken care of
Village Chief, why hasn’t you seen this computer before
This is the new supercomputer of the Tech Museum
Director, please ask me to help it detect and maintain it
It’s hard to tell that
Can predict future supercomputers
That’s right
Predicting the future
Let you see it
Let your computer predict
What happens here next
The Goat Apple Village Manager
The goat are not there
So hungry, what to eat for breakfast today
Why did you eat these again...
This Apple is pretty good
The taste of this apple is so...it’s so hard to eat
How long has this apple been left?
It’s all gone
I accidentally let it go for three weeks
Can you really predict the future? Is this magic?
Not magic
A massive amount of data is stored in a super computer
It is through analysis of the character of the Goat
For example, love is so bad and the bad of this Apple
It was only reasonable to draw a
That can predict several months
Or something a few years later
It’s theoretically OK
But the predicted time span is longer
The lower the accuracy
I’m going to go back and rest first, too
You’ll send your computer back to the tech museum later
good
Hehe...I’ll try what to eat for breakfast tomorrow
I won’t eat bread tomorrow
It won’t be released for three weeks
This computer...can really predict the future
Of course it’s true
Don’t miss the time
Big Wolf and I first sent the super computer back to the technology library
Everyone else will look for the card first
Say... are they familiar with the path of the tech museum?
Why not predict it
See when can we go back fifteen years ago
It’s okay for a computer
Ah, look ahead
- ah
I don’t know if they have sent it
My robot...why is it not controlled by...
No...good...
You’re fine
We’re fine...
It’s all my fault for the robot. The super computer has dropped
Let’s go and look for it
Look there
Ah, what about computers
There are fragmented reactions
You’ve gotten too far
Don’t you know if you want to Aixi Electronics
My fragile screen has broken
Can you afford it?
Super computer has become a monster
Comet worm
Double Butterfly Sword
Gravity War
Shadow Blade
Blue Blue Sniper
Floating cannon
Sure enough, the first one was a whirlwind card
Hehehehehe...
Ah, I’ve been hiding
Weslie
Next...
Spear card and fire medicine card
The attack range of fire medicine cards is limited
Just take a few steps back
The spear stuck behind the smoke
Just grab the machine when you are optimistic
what
Comet worm
Thunder card, let’s solve you first
It’s not me who took action
Ahhh
Oops Oops...
- Jonie Grey Wolf
What other moves do you have even
Anyway, I can follow your actions and attitudes
Predict your moves easily
ah…
Tibbie
Computer monster tricks
it hurts
ah
Ah, I won’t beat you anymore
It’s just a matter of being beaten
Any tricks used will be predicted
How to hit
Want to use a cyclone card for me again
ah…
My screen...
Wow, cool...
We exchange cards for use
Just surprise it can defeat it
Wolffy We’ll hold it
Hum I have all your data
Start with you who have shadow cards
what
Wolffy follows
This is the Shadow Card When…
How about it...
Sparky follow
ah…
Now you win me
But a month later...
You can’t win at all
Have you seen it
This is your future
You can’t stop the world from ruin
Our future...
Ahhhhh...It’s over
Just like yesterday’s...
The prophecy...is true
In one month, the Science and Technology City will really...
Ha ha…
New breakfast is good
Ah Who are you
It’s us, village chief
oh
What’s wrong? Is the breakfast not delicious?
You said the breakfast was not delicious before
I just changed a flower
Don’t put on your face
We didn’t collect so many cards
Let’s go find the card
Haven’t eaten breakfast yet
Is the breakfast that bad today?
He didn’t eat a bite
Didn’t you look for fragments?
How did Weslie ask us to come here to gather
I’m not waiting, I’m going to find a card
What to do? Weslie
Everyone still remembers
Did we participate in the basketball cup?
Just as the weak goat played the ball
Wolf and Goat Team Competition
It’s an impossible task
But have we been here again and again?
And the obstacles and setbacks faced by the wolves and goat peace
Did you defeat us?
no
We’ve never been knocked down
As long as we have hope
It can be like this pot of flowers that have withered in the end
Grow young buds and grow to the sun
This flower...
It’s your pot of flowers
But didn’t he wither yesterday?
Yes, I obviously remember the computer predicted screen
It shows that this pot of flowers has withered
The village chief said before
Computers are not 100% accurate
That is to say, the end of the world may not necessarily come
Yes, but even if it arrives
We can also enjoy the hard work and courage
Change the future
Said it right, we won’t be knocked down
Dare to come to a competition...and the future
Come on
Watch the ball