Done well
I didn’t expect that they had collected 29 cards
Then you continue to perform your mission
Shadow Is there anything wrong with it?
Sorry, PhD, I don’t know you’re busy
I’ll step down right away
Come in
The progress of the instrument has been completed.
Please...please see
Yes, very good
Let’s prepare for the experiment
yes
A new card
I’ll have one too
We are three of us in the
Two
Yes, it’s very done
Recently, our taxi has increased significantly
Keep working hard
come on
Children
Village Chief
There is a situation
This is...
Another monster appears
On the contrary, fragments of the star stone can be collected again
Let’s go over
The location has been released to you
Let’s go
clear
Doctor, route inspection has been completed, and the test can be started
Let’s get started
yes
The trial begins
Charging completed optical emission
Qu
What’s going on
Scheduling the system is being conducted
It is the capacitor that is loaded and operated
Causes a short circuit in the system
The trial must be terminated immediately...
ah…
shadow
Well...yes
You’d better explain it
Why did this accident happen
yes
I have an error in calculating the capacitor power required by the device
Runtime value
Far exceeds the upper limit of our existing capacitors
This leads to the overload operation of capacitors
Then what
Need to find a larger capacitor
Go up right now
yes
you…
Follow her
It can actually push my attack
Who are you
Why do you disturb me
Hum, useless
This rubber wheel is so flexible
But since it’s a wheel...
Everyone, I have thought of a way
It’s a fragment of star stone
Don’t run hahahahaha...
Wow…
It’s you again
I’ll accept the fragments of the star stone
What do you say
Disappear
Uh, I just tried to get hurt from the explosion...
what…
ah
Let’s start acting
ah…
Hehe, can’t run anymore
Hahahaha…you don’t think…
Hide away quickly
That’s how you can... catch me
No use, no use, no use, no use, no use...
ah…
I didn’t expect it to have a hand
Shadow Lord
What should I do here
There is also a weakness in the tire
Give up and resist
Flame card
Do you think this level of attack will work for me?
what
Hey, look at the trick
ah
The most feared thing about wheel tires
Break you
what
impossible…
How to deal with her
How about taking her back
She’s an enemy, don’t worry about her
She is a doctoral student, and she may be able to get some information
ah
But... I want to bring the enemy back to our base
I finally felt bad
What’s going on when I bring it back to our laboratory
Well... OK
Then let’s take her back to find the village chief
Is it dressed?
- Don’t be
It’s so bad. Let’s wake her up first.
Wait for the village chief
I still think it’s inappropriate
What if she suddenly gets into trouble when she wakes up
Will there be some danger?
But if she doesn’t wake her up
How do we ask about the situation where Dr. Tie?
Well... I’ll save it or save it
But some insurance measures are needed
What is this
I’ll feel relieved
Ha ha ha ha……
You all let me wait outside
Is the village chief asleep? It’s so slow
You think the village chief is you
It’s a bit long
Don’t think too much, wait
Alas...
What’s up
Oops, the shadow ran away
Where is the village chief
Miss
Chase quickly
Alas...
Village Chief
You go chase us here
Paddi
Come
Really awesome
One step ahead
Reporting Dr. All the transmitters are installed
Hmm...
ah…
Sorry Doctor
Unable to complete the mission
Hum not only did I not get the capacitor
Almost caught
Very...I’m sorry
It really disappoints people...
Keep her in the laboratory and continue to repair the appliance
yes
Ani
exist
There are new tasks to hand over to you next
yes
Go and find the maximum power capacitor for me
Obey orders