That’s an important part we’ve developed
Be sure to retrieve it
Hum, so stupid
Alas, where has the red red gone
Let it open…so quickly
ah…
Help
Oops
Shadow Blade
Help
Wow…
Red
Help
You’re fine
Bao Bao scared me to death
Thank you for saving us mother and son
Uh, it’s fine if you’re fine
Bao Bao is thanking you too
Red
I’ve found you
Red, I’ve been looking for you so hard
Red…
Hmm…
You’re very noisy
I miss this feeling so much
oops
Wow ah ah wow ah…
Baby, baby, baby, don’t cry
Red Red You still like it so much when you bother children
You see how much he can’t let you go
I’m just a robot
I don’t understand what you’re talking about
Of course you are not a robot, you just saved someone
Red, wait for me
Hero Thank you for saving my old pig’s life
- Red Red Red Red Red…
Red Red Stop working on doctoral jobs
He’s a bad person
Let us go out
- Let us out quickly
Let me go…
What is this to do
Report These are trials of doctoral designs
Plan? What plan
Exceeded the answer range
Dad, you’re fine
Please let us go
dad
dad…
You bad guys, don’t bully my dad anymore
I…I don’t know what you’re going to do
But he’s just a child
Please don’t hurt him
Dad, I want to go home…
You finally come back
How could this be…
Dr. Jenny is waiting for you
very good
With it, the instrument will be completed soon
A device?
Yes, a machine that can make everyone machine
But…can this really be done?
Don’t worry
The emitter you installed
It can allow signals to cover every corner of the Science and Technology City
But why… we need to turn people into robots
Ha ha ha ha…
I can’t think you
Is robot the most perfect existence on this planet?
No harm, no pain, no birth, old age, sickness and death
And the most important thing…
No feelings
But no feelings…
Annie, you’re talking a lot today
Yes…I’m sorry
Go and hand over the parts to the shadow
Start the experiment immediately after the instrument is completed
yes
How do you feel now
Are you OK
You saved me
- If it’s not you…
Baobao, why did he cry again
Wow wow wow wow…
Let me come
I’m the most experienced coaxing kids
How to beat
Ah hahaha…
That’s great, Bao Bao laughed
I’ve failed for several seasons of ghost faces and actually…
It actually succeeded
Thank you and that sister for saving us
No, no, just a handful
That sister is so nice
One foot kicked the light box
Just now? What lamp box?
Ah, that’s it
Oh no
Wow, so terrible
That’s how it is
Red actually saved me
She still cares about me
Thank you for being in search of Red Red. See you again
These robots
Are humans used as test products?
That’s right, but they’re useless
Handle those waste irons
Waste iron?
handle?
How to deal with it
Become a material for making new robots
They have also paid a lot for the doctorate
That’s how you handled it
They no longer use the value
Once there is no utilization value
They’re just a wasteland
What a pity that the doctor gave him an opportunity
But he recovered his useless relationship
Turning people into robots is to use them
Otherwise
Be able to complete the doctoral mission…
It’s our value
Dad, I want to go home…
What about their will
They don’t want to
Who cares
It is our blessing to pay homage to the doctor
No, absolutely no, right
This plan is really too absurd
I can’t accept it
Annie ran away with parts. Chase
I really should have a red color
I can’t find her now
What’s going on
Lock
Hand over the parts Hand over the parts
Hand over the parts
Red, you’re fine
More carefree things
Stop resistance Stop resistance
Red Red Why do they want to chase you
Just verbose
Leave it to me here
Give me…let me go
It seems that I can only use the ultimate move
Look at that
I’m just a lively atmosphere hahaha…
Come with me quickly
Smoke Card
Turn on night mode
They’re leaving
Why did those robots suddenly catch you
Leave it easy
That won’t work. I said I want to protect you.
Because I took this
This is…
Listen
Purpose of doctoral
It turns all the people in the technology city into machines
what? Did he get crazy?
That’s why he took away the fragments of the Elephant Heart Stone
In order to turn people… into robots…
Yes, it’s only a short time before this piece of part, he succeeded
This plan must be blocked
Red…I knew you wouldn’t help him
You are my favorite
Kind and beautiful red