This plan is really too absurd
I can’t accept it
How love is such a thing
Leading the era toward a more advanced civilization
It will be done by me
It’s time to do it
Wouldn’t it be enough to do it for me?
Why do you betray me
- Dr. Tie
Now I’ll give you another chance
Hand over the parts
Doctor Title, you finally reveal your face
It was you who made me and my family separate for 15 years
Wolnie is in trouble
It made me become like this
We have to do a good job today
I’ll let you do nothing
Red, run away, I’ll deal with him
but…
Run quickly and can’t let him get the parts
You have to be careful
There was no scar at all
Zoom card
Not overestimating one’s ability
Everyone is here to help. Doctor Tie appears
- what
How
Hand over the parts...
Here
I won’t let your plan succeed
traitor
ah
Go and squeeze the parts on
yes
You ruined my plan
Red, you’re fine
I haven’t seen it for a long time...Dr.
You’ve been hindering me
Is this the doctoral chess?
But is Dr. Ti a robot?
No matter what he is
He let Weslie and Wolffy disappear for 15 years
Hahahahahahahaha…there is a limit to human body
And machinery never changes
15 years...
My attack didn’t work
It’s time for me
Hunyang Goat Thank you
Don’t bully...Tibbie...
And me
- And we
Let’s go and help them
Um
Tibbie...
Did it succeed?
Hairless
Why doesn’t everyone’s attack work for him
Are you the only level?
Let’s go together
Um
ah…
He’s too strong
Everyone takes advantage of the situation
drink…
Ani
Did it succeed?
It is said that machinery is eternal
Why are our strength still getting worse
It doesn’t cause any harm to him
maybe…
As long as I use three cards at a time
what
You can’t bear it
Let’s try it. Now this is the only way to do it
Please distract him
Understood
superior
What are your ideas
Weslie
Exclude the most troublesome ones first
Wake up quickly
Card...card...
Let me come
We cover you up
- Paddi
Stop him
Don’t miss me
Give some rewards to the brave you
ah…
Wolffy
Ah, it succeeded
oh? Yes?
Congratulations on your success in challenging the limit
drink…
what
Injuring my companions
No...but...or...
This energy...
Doctor Tie...I really...I defeated him
Ahhhh…Doctor was beaten
Weslie
Sparky , have we won?
Win, Dr. Ti has been defeated
I’ll just say this season I’ll be the protagonist
Dr. Tie’s Elephant Star Stone Card has also been recycled
It’s finally over
Very good
What happened
What about the doctor
The doctor was defeated by the flock of goat and wolf
Take all the cards
Just say it
Doctor Tie was defeated
Had been beaten
Defeated...