Very good
The crisis in Science and Technology City was finally lifted
Now just find the remaining cards
You can restore the star stone
Then there is a chance to help Weslie and others go back
- Very good
After eating, let’s go play
OK
Uh, Wolffy
He’s busy
Come on for red
Red We have defeated Dr. Tie
Now I finally have time to have a good conversation
No need
It’s okay. You want to talk after you’ve recovered your memory
Come and take a look at this first
This is our family portrait
You’re as beautiful as you were back then
I’m the same as I did back then
Dad, you were like that year
Red Red Come here soon
This is your favorite queen
Do you still remember this banana peel?
There is also the smell of the chair...
mother
Do you remember the package you bought online before?
Red, you’re remembering our home now
no
It’s okay, I have it
This is my big move
What is this
look
This is your favorite stir-fry for me before
You come and taste it and remember it
Never seen such a bad stir-fry
This trick doesn’t work either
You don’t like this, I have other ones
It won’t be this thing again
Red Red You just believe me
Red eat more, this is what you love the most
This is also your favorite food
And this and this...
Oh, he accidentally got too much
You’ve got it all for me
What are you eating
I...I...
I’ll eat the coriander you don’t eat
Red You haven’t eaten well in these fifteen years
From now on, I will let you eat every one of them
Red, you can see
There is nothing special
yes
Because the most special thing is in front of me
dad
Dad, I didn’t see anything
I originally wanted to
Give you the tickets for these two games
come on
Red, let’s go to the park to play
I…
Let’s go
Have a great day at the park and red
Ahhhhhh
This is not good at all
You’re afraid
How is it possible that I, Big Wolf King, are afraid of
Red, don’t be nervous, it’s only a few ten seconds
Oh, I don’t want to play for a second
Still have to take action
Don’t worry, Father, I won’t hurt myself
That’s just...
The future of the game is terrible
Red, let’s go and play other things
Don’t play anymore No more...
This is the game
Fame
There is a gift in the set
Let’s play this
This security
Safety
no
I mean this game requires insight
Quick judgment and decisive movement
Dad, this circle game is too boring and won’t play
kid
Don’t play, boring
All are here, let’s have fun
Red, you’re afraid of being transferred to me
I didn’t expect you to be very skilled
I have no confidence in this little game
Do you think I’ll get your motivation?
I’m just a little bit leisurely
Seen
whee
I haven’t finished yet
whee...
Finally got this doll
It’s a boring game. Let’s go
Red
Do it
This doll is given to you
ah
I don’t want it
But I’m concocting this doll for you
what
I can’t remember who you are
You don’t remember me before
Then you can just re-recognize me now
As long as we are together
There is no need to recall
Doll, are you right?
Right
Your performance just now is too stupid
I don’t want it
Ah, don’t do that
Red, let’s go to the time corridor to play
That’s a red spot on the internet
Look, red, we are old
That’s it...
Red, you’re waiting for me here
The feeling of discomfort that just started
What exactly is...
It’s hard to say it’s my fault
Ani
Not wrong
Annie Annie…
The person who can call out this name
Only one
But how
Red I’ll give you a ball to surprise you
I didn’t expect to scare you
Yes...I’m sorry
Why does red look so uneasy
How can I eliminate the uneasiness of red
Ah... You were just in amazement and protecting others
They feel very secure
There is a way
If red is scared in the house
I want to show my heroic side to protect her
They feel very secure
Nothing is wrong
Red, let’s go to the surprise house
Let’s go I’ll protect you
Red, don’t be afraid, I’m right beside you
ah…
Help
So terrible
Just a tourist
Of course I know, just want to warm up the atmosphere
How to beat
Everything here is props
It can also scare the child...
ah…
Oh, red, I’m afraid
You come and protect me
As long as you can be with Red
So what about changing the strategy
Just a prop
You’ll come down first
Appeared
Red Where are you going
Oh, don’t go so fast
Red, you wait for me
Stop running...
Red let me take a breath
What kind of red do you want...
Red...
Oh, let’s go quickly...
Holding red hands will make you feel much more at ease
The surprise is not that scary
I really hope this shocking house will never be as good as possible
Finally came out
Red Red What do you think
Feeling bad
Why do I have to pull me out? I still have to work
You will pay after the salary is deducted
It’s not the time to fall
Red is still in the shocking house
Who is he
what
ah
You...who are you
Red... Where are you
Have you ever seen a female wolf like an agent
no…
And you
Red... Red
ah
Is it you who just kept following me?
I’m not there, you have fun
But I’m not happy
You betray me again and again
Who are you
Well
How do you know...my moves
Tell me who are you
I said...
Mission failed I will make you pay
Ani
It’s impossible that you are not already...
ah…
card…
snort
Where are you
Red Red What’s wrong with you?
Wolffy...
It’s me, red... red...