Red
How do you feel
The Elephant Star Stone Card in Wolnie’s Body was pulled away
Red Red What happened at that time
Ah…Ni…
Wow ah ah
- Red
The love of Wolnie is very unstable
Let’s let her rest first
Red Red No matter what happens
I’ll always be with you
So don’t be afraid
I stay here to accompany the red
You all go out first
Doctor Tie… has not been eliminated
Didn’t he be solved by me?
That’s right
I saw him broken into pieces
You should have misread it
Who did we defeat before
It’s hard to make a mistake
Impossible
Red
… Let’s go out first
The lock…unopened
Lord Shadow, please come with me
Shadow How is the instrument repaired
Naturally everything is ready
Welcome the doctoral return
- Welcome the doctoral return - Welcome the doctoral return
Ha ha ha ha…
Ahem, you heard it too
This can be achieved with the ability of Wolnie
Everyone’s situation will become very dangerous
Wow, what should I do
Weslie, why not save the card
no
Isn’t Weslie even more dangerous if you do?
Then what should I do
Why not… let’s keep the card for the village chief
Um
Village Chief
But…Isn’t this Slowy dangerous?
Just leave it to me for custody
The village chief is…
Don’t worry, the card will be very safe in my hands
Hey, I remember the last time the village chief
I was knocked down by Bu Lei at once
Humph, the last time it was outside
But this time it’s different
When you usually look for cards
I’ve strengthened the defense of the base
No outsider can step into this base
Is it really okay?
I believe in the village chief
What we have to do now is to continue looking for fragments
If you carry a card
It is likely that he will be directly attacked by the doctor
I’ll leave it to you. Village Chief
But we have no cards
Will it be difficult to deal with monsters
Village Chief, then I’ll think about it again
Have you forgotten?
We didn’t have any cards before
Everyone is fighting with all their heart
It can also defeat monsters
That’s true, however…
I agree
Tibbie said it right
Now in a tight situation
Let’s put the card in a safe place first
So the card can only be handed over to the Slowy
Rest assured everyone
Our base, Doctor Tie will never be able to break through
OK Then decide like this
Um
We can’t give the chance to succeed to the doctor
I’ve handed over to you Village Chief
Don’t worry
Then I’ll send the red red back to rest first
Um
Wolffy
Be careful if you have something to contact
Um
That’s all
Come on
Come and open the meal
I can eat it myself
No, you are injured now, can’t be troubled
Mom, just taste it
The dishes made by dad are delicious
ah…
Wilie When I met your mother back then…
There are also desserts, I’ll get them
Wolffy
Can you not go
Doctor Tie is very strong, I’m afraid of you…
It’s okay I’ll be back soon
Actually, I enjoyed this meal
Really happy
I think I’ll be like this every day from now on
Have a happy meal together
Chat and fight…
You said you would be back soon that year
What’s the result
This is already enough now
I don’t want to eat alone anymore
Aren’t you waiting for me?
Of course I want to stay with you all the time
But I don’t want you to lose me
This time…must come back
must
Doctor, I heard you last time…
Haha, I was defeated
They’re just my stand-in
Hum, but it’s good to let them be alert
I have the chance to go out and do a lot of things
Go and do what you should do
yes
ah…
Why didn’t you see it
Village Chief What happened
Children, all the cards are missing
what
Village Chief, have you put it somewhere else
Forgot
No, who did you take it
If we take it, we will definitely tell you
I was careless
I thought someone outside wanted to secretly take our cards
I didn’t expect the bottom of the penis to be in your place
Bottom
That’s right
I’ve checked it out
There are no traces of outsiders invading the base
Then you are the only one who is suspicious
Wait a moment, it’s stuck in your hand and you don’t see it
You’re suspicious, too
I? How could I possibly
Why do I steal cards?
Maybe you have directed and acted in a self-conducted role
Wait, let’s not be chaotic
The most important thing is to find the card quickly
Yes, the card fell on the hands of the doctor
Then it’s all over
That…
I have one here
I just found it leaked when I went back to my room yesterday
Don’t look at me like that, I’m very stressful
The bottom will definitely come and steal this last card
You should hold this important thing
Now it’s only me and the Goat
Most likely not the bottom
I’ll hold it
Wait a minute.
Here, you are obviously the most suspicious of village chief
That’s right, it can’t be given to the village manager
The kids don’t believe me
Want to go
Only hand over the card to me who is upright
It’s the safest
Wait a minute.
The village chief is the most suspected
But besides goat
It seems that others have no choice but to prove their innocence.
Tibbie said it right
Since we have no doubts about slandering
The card is still held by the goat
OK, this is also a good way
Only the safest one is the
Why are you back here?