Look at mine...
Paddi
Uh...you are so doing standing
It won’t be...
careful
Weslie Thank you...
Thank you...
Are you in trouble with Weslie?
I have a plan that leads to the bottom
But you need to cooperate
You are not suspicious of scrubbing
I don’t listen
I’ve definitely not done a way to prove that I’m not a good person
And it’s more doubtful to come to you at this time
But since I came to the future world, I met everyone
I know that everyone has been worried because of my disappearance
I’m also very sorry I didn’t grow up with everyone
Work hard together
So I don’t want to miss you anymore
Now I want to find the Elephant Star Stone
Back to the past
I…
Then...what do I need to do
Paddi...
The plan is like this
First we need to prepare a fake card
Then deliberately reveal the location it hides to everyone
Then the bottom of the body will definitely steal that fake card
- Oh, then we’ll catch him on the spot
What if the real card is done
You’d better keep it
Only on the body is the safest
What if you hide in your butt pocket
No, no, I can’t afford it if I get hurt
Hidden here
That hurts my hair
No, no
Here no, no, no, no...
Good morning
Why did you get up so late?
Sorry, I didn’t sleep well last night
Is it because I worry about the card?
Of course, don’t worry
I’ve hidden it in one
Nowhere can be found
Hidden?
Are you sure the hidden place is safe?
Don’t worry, it’s absolutely safe
I feel so uncomfortable on the top of the card
Haven’t had a good night’s sleep
This...you won’t hide in...
I think you’ll hide it if you change another place.
You’re so concerned about the card, it’s hard to tell...you’re the bottom of the body
The last hope is all here for you
Isn’t it normal to care?
Normal and normal...
snort
Could it be that my prompt is not obvious yet?
It shouldn’t be true. Everyone is usually very smart
Come on, come on the bottom
Let me see who you are
Sparky ... It turns out that you are the bottom of the body
It’s all this time, where are you going
Really, we’re looking for a bottom
It’s really worrying
Leave
Not a Sparky
Great, who would be
Another...
Are you there
No
The bottom of the neck is a gentle and kind class leader
I can’t accept it
Really, I don’t know where to go to play again
No clothes are collected
Not a class manager
Who else is this?
Who are you
Don’t run
The bottom of the squid appears
What happened to Tibbie
I just saw a strange black shadow
Then he suddenly disappeared
Black shadow
Bad card...
Go and have a look
Hu is still there...
Fortunately, it’s still there
What’s up
Paddi
This important thing
You’re just hiding here
This is too bad
When having breakfast
I guess you hid the card here
What if it is stolen
Don’t be motivated first
You are so beautiful...
Don’t worry, the card is fake
What’s going on
Weslie, come and tell me
This is the trap set by me and Yuyangyang
Tell everyone that fake cards are hidden here
I just hope to bring out the bottom
Unfortunately, the bottom is not good
You’re scared
That’s a real card
Don’t worry, I just checked it
The card is also hidden in a safe place in the hall
No one can find it
What...you’re hiding
Didn’t I let you carry it?
Hahahaha I think it’s still what Tibbie said
It’s easy to get rid of it on your body
It’s best to hide it
Tibbie...
Who was shouting
Tibbie
What about Tibbie
It seems to be gone just now
Not good, go and have a look
I’ve just finished checking
You go quickly
Oh, don’t worry, it’s okay
It’s just staying under the chair
Miss it...
I’ve just seen it...
Why didn’t there be no more...
If you look for something, are you remembering the wrong place?
Keep the change, please
The card was taken away by Tibbie
Impossible
Tibbie and us fought so long
There is no sign of any problem with Tibbie
She can’t be an undercover
But that’s true
Now the greatest possibility is her
But I can’t figure it out
How could she know I hid the card here
You told her yourself
At that time, only Tibbie was in the passage
Then I heard her shouting "Don’t run."
Didn’t you really see the black shadow
Instead, I want to cause the worry of the slaughter of the slaughter.
Everyone is anxious to go to the Goat House
When looking at fake cards
Goat who worry about the real card lost
Didn’t go
His first time
I’ll definitely check the security of the real card first
There was still no one who went there at this time
That’s Tibbie
Her goal is to goat
So she watched from the side
The entire process of checking cards by the Goat
While the Paddi are leaving
Just took the card
It turned out to be like this...
Why don’t you hear Weslie?
Put the card on it
In fact, Tibbie went to me before Weslie came...
Tibbie...
You hear me first
Now anyone can be an undercover
So no matter who comes to you next
Don’t believe anything you say
The safest way
Just put this card in one beside you
Something that no one knows
Do you understand
Why did Tibbie suddenly talk to me about these
But she said it was quite right, I had to hide the card
Uh...what is the person
Forget it, don’t care
Have it
Paddi...
That’s it
Unexpectedly, Tibbie actually calculated everything
Tibbie, Body Bottom...Is it really you?
I still don’t understand
Why does Tibbie need to help Doctor Tie?
All the cards on the Slowy have been obtained
Will it be when fighting with the shadow
Being controlled
If the time of the single fight
I don’t think it’s possible
When Tibbie is looking for a card
They are all with us
And it’s been communicating
She...why...
It’s a surprise
Tibbie has actually been controlled by me
Become a secret chess step for me
Tibbie
Go and bring your partners to bury them
Escape quickly
ah…
Tibbie...
It’s hard to say that Tibbie was already under control at that time
With you two, my plan will be successful soon
I hope you can cooperate happily in the future
- Yes Doctor
These are just our guesses
You will know when you find Tibbie
But we don’t know where she is
Yes, I’ll know right away
Waited for a long time
Don’t forget
Wolnie escaped from Dr. Ti’s base
Let’s start the battle meeting soon
good
The base is here
You’ll be here
Dad, please wait and see
We’ll be on the way tomorrow. Everyone is ready
yes