Go out for a walk
OK
You can’t sleep, either
Yes, I think that tomorrow will end all
A little complicated
Just beat Doctor Tie
Your body will recover
Hope it, but after watching it for a long time, it’s pretty good
- Hahahahahahaha
Weslie
Um
If we go back
What do they do here
They will definitely meet us better
and…
Isn’t anyone waiting for us?
yes…
Look at the stars and the moon Look at my heart
The moon represents my heart. Dreams are sweet and sweet
The road to pursuit is never over, but how far away it is
I won’t lose my way I have starlight
Red…
- If I come back, can I make me fried eggs?
The future emerges
Finally one year
- One day
- Don’t you send them?
- Please ask for the stars and the moon
- Listen to my heart
They’ve already realized
- Even if they pay for the price
It will definitely defeat Doctor
- Happiness never changes
We’re here
It must be safe and irresistible
Can it be…
Go again someday
What’s wrong? Are you scared
I’m not afraid I’m just…
It’s just… I just don’t want to fight with Tibbie
I don’t want to hurt my friends
Don’t want to see her get hurt
There are monsters
Look, it’s like this
ah…
Tibbie
Tibbie, you’re fine
Don’t disturb me
What happened to Tibbie
We can help you
Mission continues
Found…you…
Tibbie You were just flew by this thing
This thing doesn’t look so strong
And it looks soft and should be delicious
Tibbie We can deal with this together…
Wonderful
Hahahahahahahaha…
But you don’t remember very well
I’ve just seen this trick
If you can’t cut two blocks, just four blocks
If four blocks don’t work, just eight blocks
If the eight blocks don’t work, they will be broken up
Things to do
You’re going to try it
Get it easy
yeah
No
If the monster is defeated, the card will appear
Ha ha ha ha
You’re already surrounded by me
What’s the use of siegeing us
See I’ll break you up
What…what happened
Breathing… becomes difficult…
Doesn’t it feel uncomfortable
Because the oxygen here will become thinner
You just snatch it as much as you want
Oh hehehe…
Why are you not affected
Have you seen a robot breathe?
Really awesome
Not yet…I can’t fall
Draw…to put the barrier to…
It’s almost there
Break…
I want to… save everyone…
For your efforts…
I’ll give you more rewards
It’s okay I’ll be back soon
This time…must come back
Isn’t anyone waiting for us?
I’ll definitely go back
Just the last one
Wolffy
Why do I do such a strange thing
Not a strange thing
Red egg scrambled
It’s the best food in the world
OK? Red
You come back and tell me
OK OK OK
Then we’ll say
Red… Red…
What about red
Red
Big Wolf, let’s play ball together
you…
Who is it…
Don’t go
Who are you
Big Wolf Why are you hurt again
Dad is having a meal
- Who are you again
No…
Wolffy
- Wolffy
Who am I…
Dare to hurt me
Unforgivable
Wolffy…
Forever
impossible
Ha ha ha ha…
Although it’s a bit bad…
But you’re really a surprise and unexpected harvest
Bring the card back
Yes Doctor Tie