Scanned
Doctor Big Wolf is already a robot
Very good I didn’t expect this unexpected harvest to be so good
Do your best for me in the future
yes
Haha, God helps me too
I got the last card
Continuous integration and no neglect
- yes
yes
That’s one last step
Village Chief Big Wolf has become a robot
Alas, but I don’t have time to hurt
Since that’s the case
It is even more necessary to destroy Dr. Ti’s plan to save everyone
Um
Then follow the original plan
In addition to being careful about the robot patrol
There is also red external monitoring
Weslie, you need to install a silencer
First time shooting monitoring
There is a sound
According to the village chief
This is the door to the laboratory
Let’s go
That…this is such a coincidence
have…
Oops
Floating cannon
Get out of here quickly
Some enemies invade
what
Alert Police
There are intruders There are intruders
Big Wolf, what are you going to see
yes
Here
Catch the enemy Catch the enemy
Capture the enemy
Only hard
We’re here
We’ve been
Someone must have come to save us
- Help
We’re here
Help… Help…
Help…
He actually caught so many people
We have to rescue them first
We’re here
Help Help
Don’t want to escape
Wolffy
You save someone first, I’ll deal with him
Yes, I’ve handed it to you
Be careful
Then don’t hurt Wolffy
snort
Are you insulting me to be able to beat a little brat?
Uh…it doesn’t mean that
Thank you for saving us
Go quickly and leave here first
Let’s go while there’s no one guarding you now
Let me open it
Wolffy Wake up, we are our best friends
Say nothing
Can’t continue to get along with him
Wait…wait for a while
I don’t want to hit me
snort
Good opportunity
Hum, I’ll complain about you
- And we
Give me in
And me
Sorry, Wolffy
We’ll come back to save you later
You’ll wait for me
It’s about to succeed
Doctor Tie Let me deal with them
Doctor Tie
The last time I defeated it was your substitute
Hum, I thought Wolffy could be useful
How does it feel to kill a companion?
Look, that’s the Elephant Star Stone
99% have been synthesized
Hey your opponent is me
Look at the trick
Prepare
what
There is a protective cover outside the star stone
Weslie
Star Stone is like your future
Weslie, you’re fine
You never have a chance to touch it
It’s time to end you
Finally, the Elephant Star Stone returned to my hands
Is it successful?
Hum The overall situation is decided
In the future…we can’t really touch it?
Village Chief This is…
This is the strength I made for you
Can break anything
But there is only one
The Elephant Star Stone Protective Cover has been destroyed
Start repairing now
Countdown time 10 seconds
10 seconds…
You’re too cunning
Good things you hurt me again and again
This time it’s not that easy
Quick, let’s sweep
Weslie Come on
- Don’t think about it
Must…
Failed to repair the protective cover
Shadow took it to me
I… didn’t have this plan
Do you want to do
What is this doing
Didn’t understand
He was anxious, he was anxious
When did you start to wake up
It’s from the beginning
You were the one who broke the Elephant Star Stone before
what
Who is the shadow
That’s right. This time I won’t let you harm everyone
Shadow Don’t forget that your daughter is still in my hands
I didn’t want to do that
Tibbie
But you disappointed me
So the shadow is the mother of Tibbie
daughter…
Hand over the Elephant Star Stone Otherwise I will kill her
Tibbie, wake up
This is something that can destroy the world
Cannot exist
Sorry, Tibbie
Mom, I’m so scared…
Mom, save me…
You’ve lost
Your biggest weakness is ultimately emotion
Let me go if you have the ability and fight openly
See you again, no, it’s forever
What to do? It’s hard to tell that this is the end
Ha ha ha ha
This soon became a
It’s all a robot world