The explosion outside stopped
We’re safe at the moment
But here is also shocked
Hey, why are there so many mechanical parts here?
Be careful
actually
This is a secret base built by Dr. Ti
Secret base
Um
I’ve been working on ways to remove mechanization here
Unfortunately, I haven’t done any research yet…
Then… what happened to Bu Lei and the others now
They’re not at the base
I’ve moved them to a safe place
That…
Except for the thunder…
Since that mission, he has been missing
The class leader…
Then why did you become a robot
Can you still stay awake
Things will begin from that day…
The seedlings have begun to change
The barrier is ready
OK, let’s start the experiment
Wow, we succeeded
Dr. Qian, Dr. Yan, long-awaited Daming
My name is Dr. Ti
I have something important to discuss with you
Dr. Tie The important thing you said is…
Actually, I have a scientific research project
Hope both join
Especially the top experts in biotechnology
Dr. Qian, you
Winning the prize
The content of that project is…
Please visit two doctors
Machinery…Plant
Mechanical frog
This project is through technology
Mechanize fragile life
From then on, you can gain true eternity
Sorry, I’m sorry for refusing
oh…
I think life is fragile but it is also impoverished
We cannot cure disease and death
But it’s also because of this
We cherish each other more and cherish the present
So you still need to go back
Alas, since that’s the case…
Take them away
Qianqian, let’s go quickly
good
Brother Jian…
Brother Yan, please cheer up
How did this happen
Qian…Qianqian Quick…Go away…
ah…
I have to turn you into robots
Is it better to have an answer earlier
And it happened to be the drug we studied at that time
Let me retain human consciousness
You mean… this can inhibit mechanicalization
right
Unfortunately, it cannot transform mechanized people back
And this was originally developed for plants
If you are not careful, it will cause great harm to the human body
I just happened to succeed last time
If it fails, I may lose my life
That’s so dangerous
Let’s stop Dr. Ti
Not much time, let’s talk
Why is the doctor so enforced that star stone?
Global mechanized instruments
Needs a lot of energy to start
When he struggles with energy supply problems
It is discovered that the star stone has great energy
But when he got it
Because of time problems
The energy of the Elephant Star Stone has been greatly reduced to nothing
So I’m going back fifteen years ago
Go and grab that energy-filled elephant star stone back
When he returned here
I took advantage of the situation and destroyed the Elephant Star Stone
But it was just delayed for a while
So that’s how it is
You should tell us early
In this way, we can work with you
No
He is a person with a close mind and a very suspicious person
I can’t take it easy
Yes
Sparky, you have such a big mouth, can you believe it
You’re just a big mouth
I’m a foodie job
Don’t be too worried
Actually, I’ve been in contact with Slowy
Village Chief
That’s right
Although he has always been very strict in my supervision
But there are many goat and cold weather
Only then can I successfully get in touch with the Slowy
A goat?
I?
Why don’t I remember it?
Just last time…
When the control is in a cold weather…
I was swaying him and made a message
And secretly sent the Slowy
This is…
Hum, meet and discuss
Who is it
Let me see your true face
What a do, busy
ah…
You, who are you
How did you come in
Village chief, it’s me
Is she okay with Tibbie?
You are… Qian Yangyang
The child is suffering
As long as you can crush the doctor’s traits
Everything is worth it
Must stop him, not let him succeed
I’ll do my best to help you
After that, I and Slowy secretly contacted each other many times
Bu Lei is a subordinate of Dr. Ti
You need to be more careful
I understand, you should also pay attention to safety
Oh, Slowy, Why are you here
Village Chief
Then let’s take her back to find the village chief
Wait outside
Village chief…
Goat Village may have a bottom
Bottom of the bed?
Please pay more attention to the people around you
I should leave, I can’t make him suspicious of me
Wait, you can’t just go out like that
That’s it, I have an idea…
I don’t know the last card
The village chief insisted that he had a bottom
After that, I was trapped at the base
Completely broke up with the village chief
We finally came out
You have to find Dr. Tie quickly
Let me tell you the village chief about the current situation
Doctor picking is about to start the instrument
Must find and stop him as soon as possible
Um
Jonie, Sparky, binge goat
You’re fine
Village Chief, we’re fine, it makes you worry
Duomei Goat’s mother saved us
I’ll bring you out just now and be ready to contact you
It seems that you all know about Qianyangyang
What about Big Big Werewolf
Wolffy… controlled by Dr. Cut and left
Still couldn’t save him
Wolffy, you are such a big cheat
Didn’t you say you’d come back?
I really don’t know how long I can hold…
Then you can’t give up…
Can’t give up
We can’t let Dr. Tie succeed
Everyone is very committed to stop him
-Yeah, go all out -Yeah, go all out
Children…
Out
Still no trace of Dr. Tie
Me too
How to do it? There is not much time left
Doctor Tie may start the machine at any time
There must be something we didn’t notice
Doctor’s instrument
To use these transmitters to radiate the surrounding
You have to go to the highest place to start the machine
But we have looked for all the high floors
Oops It’s too difficult
He can’t shoot at our base
Goat Village Base
Hello, Slowy
Hum What is the ability to bully an elderly woman?
Don’t be excited, I just borrowed local private matters
Wolffy…
I plan to use your base as the startup center
Isn’t it a blessing
You…you don’t want to move my base
Village Chief Village Chief Quickly connect to the phone
Oh, he’s still alive
village…
This is…
Ha ha ha ha
Congratulations
I’m lucky to witness the great miracle I created
Dr. Tie…