Wolffy, wake up
Let us go
I’ve planned it for so long, just for today
Let you witness this historic moment
- Hahaha
Is this the transmitter?
Father, I won’t disappoint you
Father
Um
Look, I’ve succeeded again
This is my latest robot
This robot is really good and is as darn like you
Thank you father
I’ll keep working hard
Be careful
Father…
Don’t hurt yourself
Be sure to protect yourself
Thank you father
My father is so good to me
A helping waste
It really disappointed me
Father…
Son, you will not disappoint me
It will definitely not
Doctor’s equipment has been ready
Very good My plan is finally finished
Open it
stop
- You’re here
Oh, you finally arrived
Mr. Slowy and Wolnie are about to be released
We will never let your plan succeed
Tibbie, you’ll be awake
It’s useless that her current consciousness is not controlled by her
How to do it
We can’t hurt Tibbie
Let’s go
ah
what
If you become a robot, you won’t be afraid of you getting hurt
ah…
Tibbie
Tibbie has also become a robot
We won’t let you go
Don’t worry, you’re here soon
As long as I press the button
The transmitter will radiate the entire city
By then everyone will be the same as her
Become a robot
Including you
My father’s will be done by me.
Your father?
My Father, you know it too
He’s the wolf’s head
Wolf Head…
The leader of the wolf clan is going to give us a salary increase
Are you helping him?
It turned out to be him…
For the Father’s Heart
I’ll take action on you in the Basketball Game
But Zi Tailang disappointed me too much
It turns out that you are the post-scene doctor who is said by Zi Tailang
Not bad, it was a pity that I didn’t get the hope that time
But this time I won’t fail again
Just turn you all into robots
This world will be controlled by me
Realize my father’s heart
Stop, Doctor Tips, this will only make you repeat it
Is that right? Then try it
Hahahahahaha
What are you laughing at
If everyone becomes
A robot without feelings
Then what can you do if you control the entire world
A lot of feelings will only make things complicated
What I need is complete control
No feelings, no happiness
Then what’s the meaning?
What do you mean by me?
Do you think I am the villain who died a lot?
Don’t be too busy, no one can stop me
No…
- What’s going on
What is that
- Something happened
Oh my God
What’s going on
- You see
Mom, look…ah
ah…
Run fast
Don’t miss the way
mother…
How about mom…
daughter…
Everyone…is going to become robots
The range of the device is constantly narrowing
Don’t destroy it as soon as possible
All residents will become robots
Let’s work together to destroy it
Uh…Grey Wolf
Fast brings Slowy to leave here
You’re careful
Um
Please…save Wolffy
Success
Can residents come back
That’s it?
I want to destroy my plan with such ability
Don’t think about it
Don’t slap, surrender
Not overestimating one’s ability
Look at the trick
Do you know what the power gap is?
ah…
Paddi…
Do you still have time to care about others?
We haven’t yet
Without cards, your fighting power is not that great
Then add me
Traitors, you’ll disappear for me
Paddi
The game is over
what…
We’re here
Dr. Tie…
Stopped
Stopped Stopped…
Doctor Tie, you’re injured
What do you say
You’ve been injured
Why…Why can’t I feel the pain…
How did this happen
Mechanical arm
He’s also a robot
No… won’t…
What a joke
This is impossible
No…
Don’t hurt yourself
Be sure to protect yourself
Thank you father
My father is so good to me
If you are injured…
It’s easy to find out that you’re a robot
You, I’ve finally gotten
The work that was successfully created
I…is not a father’s child…
I’m a robot
Hahahahahahahahaha…
What a thorn
Machine calculations are as good as possible, want to turn others into robot control
I found out that I was a robot that lets me wear
So that’s the case?
So am I just a chess piece you made?
So, do you care about me? Are you performing?
So is my whole world fake?
Did he get crazy?
Haha Since that’s the case
I’ll create my world
What’s going on…
What does he want to do
Auntie, catch me
Wolffy
All the robots were sucked in