Since that’s the case…
I’ll create… belong to…My world
Hiding… is useless
Go quickly
dad
Give me daddy
I’ll help you
It’s so carefree
- ah…
dad…
Help Dad…
My floating cannon
Wilie, you’re fine
It’s OK
It’s you
They actually ran away
How to do it
It’s really turned into a ruin on the predictor
Sure enough…the future is…unchanged
Brother, have you seen my mother?
she…
Ah…I want dad, I want mom…
How to beat…
Although the current science and technology city has been predicted
Turned into a ruin
But what about the future after that
We can’t just give up like that
But that big robot is incapable of gunfire
Then we will destroy him from the inside
Inside
- Just when Wilie shouted
The big robot stopped attacking for a moment
Maybe… everyone still has their own ideas
Think of black diamonds…
He was crying at Xiaoyu
Finally, my memory was restored
Then what should we do
We can use our precious replies
To disintegrate the robot
I believe that feelings are not so easily eliminated
The collected images are uploaded
The power supply on the building has also been restored
He’s almost at the screen
Received Data Send
It seems…
It is effective
It seems he stopped
It turns out you are here
Run quickly
Hahahaha… See where you run
Weslie What are you doing
You… don’t worry
I’ll bring you all… back…
Weslie…
This is the body of a large robot
I’m going to save Weslie
Sparky  I’m fine
Your body…
How do you stay sane
Because I used the blocker in advance
I plan to release a memo clip in it to wake everyone up
Please ask you outside
good
Oh wow wow wow…
You need to find everyone quickly
Hello everyone, I am Tibbie
Weslie, please rest assured
We will definitely protect the outside…
- Wait for you to come back
- Brave Firefighter Sparky
She’s not
- Sparky, you don’t like it the same…
- Tibbie
- My brand new album is about to be in two weeks
- Online on major platforms
- Please don’t miss it
- Orange juice is still fresh
It’s so early, Wilie
Dad, are you doing
I want to take a picture of my cute little gray
Tibbie
Wolffy
I’m definitely taller than dad
Ah, will that be…
Look at Sparky
dad…
Wolffy Wolffy Wolffy, wake up
Everyone is ready
Connect
Wolffy
Wake up quickly Wake up
Everyone is waiting for us to go back
You finally got together with them
Now they’re ruined
Do you want them to wait for you for another fifteen years?
Still thirty years
Don’t do slap in vain
Run away, everyone
ah…
ah
Wolffy…
Have you heard what I said?
Split them two
Tibbie and auntie…
Let me go
Wolffy
Wake up quickly
Don’t give up yet?
Let’s come again
Mom, come back soon
Mom, do you want to go to the game park?
Hahaha, it’s Bao, you want to go
Haha, go, go
We’re always good friends
Congratulations on graduating
Dad, I’ll give you half of it
- Dad, wake up
- Everyone wake up
We…go…back to fifteen years ago
Keep watching with everyone…the smoke that hasn’t been finished
Wolffy…
come on
- We will definitely win the sports club
Welcome home Children
Mr. Slowy
happy birthday
Red I’m back
Dad, I’m tall
We can also be good friends
It’s so early, Wilie
dad…
- I want to take a picture of my cute little gray
Stopped
Impossible Why can I still wake up
Here is…
Tibbie
mother
dad…
dad
Wolffy
I’m back
Welcome back
whee…
Done well
I can’t beat this little goat
You underestimate our relationship too much
Feelings Hahahahahahaha…
What is love? It’s ridiculous
Not ridiculous at all
You have feelings for yourself, right?
You long to get your father’s praise
You want to help your father complete his dream
I felt angry after knowing the truth
Could it be that these are not feelings
Feelings bring us happiness and sorrow
It may also influence our judgment
But because of these…
That’s why we have people who want to cherish and protect
Thank you father
I’ll keep working hard
It turns out…this is love
Unfortunately, everything is over
Not finished yet
There is also a chance to start over
- You want to apologize to everyone. Be punished
Rebuild here with us
Mission failed Self-destruction program started