Fry…fry…
Let go of Weslie
Can’t move…
I can’t control myself anymore
I’ll help you
My hands can’t move, either
- We’re here too
No, don’t come over
- What to do now
Dr. Tie…
It’s hard to say…this is the meaning of my existence…
- Dr. Tie
Doctor Tie to hold
The self-destructing program will be started after clearing all data
- Clear
It seems there is no chance
Memory data has been cleared
Doctor Tie
He had no idea at all
Self-destruction program starts, three minutes to count down
Want to remove the blow-off
Once it explodes, the entire city center will be destroyed
I’ll try to crack it
Don’t be nervous first
You go quickly and evacuate residents in nearby streets first
good
Village chief…
We have a way
Really
Hey where are you going
You give me…back
Everyone walks to that place
Weslie
Go here
Go slowly
- Weslie…
Stop now
Stop
Dad, where are you going
Wolffy
Red Red Little Huihui…Don’t chase after you
This is the final solution
Weslie
Don’t do this
You finally came back
Don’t chase after me anymore
Wolffy, don’t leave…
You are my most important friends
Even though you can’t grow up with you
But I’ve participated in your future
I’m very happy to see you again
Weslie Wolffy…
Wolffy
What is the future
No matter what happens in the future
We’re here, we can definitely solve it
Dad is really
Don’t take the stuff yourself
I’ve taken so much
When will it be used
Not on my own
Hear it all
Young people need to exercise more
It’s so much to take this thing
This is what?
Your dad said it right
Finally, I want to introduce my latest invention…
Mechanical goat
It has many bionic functions
Can show handstand splits and eat grass
Are these actions very simple
Then will he be able to do Chinese martial arts?
Chinese martial arts…
This idea is great. You can try it
I’ll continue to change to the mechanical goat
Besides martial arts, you may also learn feelings
Everyone is looking forward to it
Tibbie, the child, came to help
Where did you go?
Aunt Qianyangyang
Have you ever seen Tibbie?
no
Finally finished today’s work hiccup…
Have you seen Tibbie?
Yes, there is
Tibbie…
Uncle Yangyang…
Uncle Yangyang
- Ah I heard it
Hahahaha OK Tibbie
Um
Let’s go, everyone is waiting for us to set off
Come on
What about Weslie
Weslie…
Up, beat him down
Get on now
Defeat him
Fall him down
Brother Come on
good…
marvelous…
Hello, I’ll be there soon
There was a bun since before. One day it was hungry and sucking…
Then there’s no more
That’s it
Uh-huh
Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
Oli
Dr. Fu…
I’m back
Dr. Fu Welcome home
Thank you, Jiao Tailang
Not polite, remember to give the help of Jonie
- One, two, two, one…
Sorry, I’m late
So slow, Weslie
Find a place to sit down
ah…
Thank you for coming to my concert today
- Jonie, Jonie, Jonie,…
good…
Thank you everyone, I was really happy today
Quick and quick
Everyone is waiting for us in front. Quick
There will be tens of thousands of future
Tibbie Run Slowly
- We only went to one of them
And the road to these future
That’s what we choose now
No one can define our own future
- Our future…
- We decided on it ourselves
Hey, why haven’t Weslie and Wolffy come back yet
Yes, Dad has been there for a long time
My oranges have already been finished
Or I’ll find them
Red Red Son
Weslie, are you doing
Weslie, why are you crying
What’s wrong with Big Wolf? Nothing is wrong
Good Daddy doesn’t cry
Don’t cry, you’ll never see it
Such a beautiful smoke will be gone if you don’t look at it
Ha ha ha ha…