Marching to the New Wonderland
The Energy Seed
Thunderbolt!
Morning Sun!
Lightning Angel!
Hurricane!
Rainbow!
Speeding up!
If only these trains were real.
Then we could ride in them as we save the world!
You don’t even know how to protect insects,
yet you want to save the world?
Sirius, enter!
Wolnie, don’t worry!
With my newly invented Sirius to protect you,
no one will dare to harm you!
Oh no...
I’ve got yet another wrinkle in the corner of my eye.
Wolnie, I can harvest the stars and the Moon for you,
but I can’t help you get rid of wrinkles.
I don’t care! I want to look young!
I found a solution!
What is it?
There’s this magical “Energy Seed.”
It’s a source of unlimited vital energy.
If we get it,
you can stay young forever, and I’ll have unlimited power!
Then go find it now.
I can’t.
This type of seed is extremely small; we can’t find them.
But that’s still fine, because I’ve made a transformation gun.
I can look for it if I make myself small.
Then hurry up!
Wolffy, don’t be long!
Wolnie!
Just you wait!
Let me help.
Thanks, Wolnie!
Don’t be long!
A big train!
Wilie!
The big train is just like our house on the inside!
This is your dad’s stuff; don’t touch it!
He’s awake.
What is he saying?
He says
that his “Energy Seed” is missing,
and he needs to find it right away.
What?
“Energy Seed?”
Being small is actually quite difficult.
Mr. Slowy, it’s not over here.
It’s not over here, either.
Keep searching.
Alright.
I found it!
Great!
The Energy Seed is in the goats’ hands.
It won’t take much effort to get it!
So this is the Energy Seed!
It looks just like a gem!
How tiny.
Wolffy!
Hand over the Energy Seed right now!
No way!
I’ll have you taste my wrath!
Sirius!
What... What the...?
This is my own super epic tank invention,
Sirius!
Hand over the Energy Seed right now!
I just so happened to have transformed our toy trains into tanks as well.
Really, Mr. Slowy?
Of course! Come summon them with me.
Yes!
Daybreak!
Rainbow!
Lightning Angel!
Hurricane!
Morning Sun!
Come on out, Thunderbolt!
Wolffy, how do you like our Magic Trains?
I’m going to make you all shrink.
We’ll see how much your Magic Trains can really handle!
You’re quick, huh?
Darn it, my train doesn’t have defense abilities!
Rainbow Shield!
You dodged it?
Now’s my chance!
Watch my last hit!
Sparky, your train is a mechanic train.
It’s not for attacking.
That can’t be!
Now’s my chance.
The Magic Trains aren’t really much at all!
Uh-oh.
What is this place?
The plants here are huge.
Grandpa Beetle, how’d you get bigger?
I didn’t get bigger; you all shrunk.
What?
Shrunk?
We really did shrink.
What now?
I won’t be able to eat many things if I’m this small!
Don’t worry.
I have a spray to transform us bigger.
We can return whenever.
Great!
You can’t leave!
Grandpa Beetle, we still have to go home and do homework today.
We have to go home and eat, too!
Professor Beetle, we’ve already found the Energy Seed for you,
so we’ll be on our way.
But you guys are the new hopes to save the Big Tree World!
Save the world?
Yes. The Energy Seed is the Sun’s life essence.
My job is to collect these essences
and send them to the Big Tree’s Summit.
If I can’t send the Energy Seed to the Summit
within three months,
the Big Tree World will die and all of the insects will go extinct.
But now, I’m old and not as fast as I used to be.
I might not be able to make it.
Grandpa Beetle, let us go and save the Big Tree World!
Right, we have to do something!
Alright.
Traveling the world also counts as education.
Professor Beetle,
you can leave this great mission to us.
The Big Tree World’s entrance is up front.
Right now, we have to quickly deliver the Energy Seed
to the Big Tree’s Summit,
Isn’t it just from the bottom of the tree to the top? How hard can it be?
Is the tree we know really this big?
Through the eyes of insects, the world is really just this big.
So how long will it take us to get the seed up there?
Wouldn’t it be easier if we transformed back into our regular sizes?
You can’t do that.
Delivering the seed is a tradition.
We must do it from the perspective of the insects,
nothing else.
The Energy Seed is mine now!
Mr. Slowy, what now?
Don’t worry; watch this.
Magic Trains, assemble!
Assemble?
Kids, follow me.
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
We look so cool while assembled!
We now have more abilities!
We have more power, too!
We’re also faster than before!
Watch this!
Guess who I am!
Son?
Why are you here?
You’re asking?
Wolnie?
I went on the train to find Wilie.
Suddenly, the train flew over here.
Take us back right now!
Goodbye, Mr. Wolffy!
Trying to run?
Wolnie, I’ve already found the Energy Seed
that’ll let you stay young forever!
The goats have it!
Awesome! Get them!
Let’s go!
Yay! We’re going out!
END