Marching to the New Wonderland
Driving Exchange
Thunderbolt, speed up!
Hurricane, find the closest path!
Rainbow, bring out the shield!
Mr. Slowy!
These trains are so good!
Each train has been specifically made by me
to ensure that you’ll all like them.
Look out!
Tibbie,
don’t worry! I’ll help you!
Mr. Slowy, I don’t want to drive Lightning Angel anymore!
It’s too scary!
I don’t want to drive Morning Sun anymore, either!
Morning Sun is way too weak.
It doesn’t suit me one bit!
Morning Sun isn’t weak at all.
It’s the greatest mechanic train.
Try out the repair button.
But I don’t want to be a mechanic.
I want to be on the frontlines.
I want to handle logistics.
Attacking doesn’t fit me.
I set this up for you two.
Sparky, you have to learn how to watch after your friends.
Tibbie, you also have to learn how to protect everyone else.
But—
Alright. Let’s camp here for today.
These trains can also turn into a house;
awesome!
Incredible!
We’ll rest for tonight.
Tibbie,
give the Energy Seed to Weslie for safekeeping.
What’s the matter?
The Energy Seed is missing!
What?
Now what do we do?
We don’t need to worry.
Remember how I put the Energy Seed inside a safe box?
My high-tech safe box is completely break-proof
and environmentally friendly.
It can only be opened with our six handprints.
So even if Wolffy takes it, it’s okay.
No!
Just because we have the safe box
doesn’t mean it’s safe to leave the Energy Seed outside.
Paddi,
use Hurricane to locate where the Energy Seed is.
According to Hurricane’s searches,
the Energy Seed is most likely to be at one of these places.
You guys split up and search immediately.
I’ll remain here and wait.
Okay!
But this train…
Why don’t we swap?
Sure!
Lightning Angel is incredible!
Watch this!
Swapping is so much fun!
What is that?
Found it!
It’s the Energy Seed!
Let’s get it now!
What?
I saw it first!
Oh no! Wolffy!
Tibbie, don’t worry!
This is the perfect time to test out Lightning Angel’s true power.
It’s so strong!
You’re so done!
Tibbie, help repair the train now!
Yes!
What’s going on?
I’m sorry!
I didn’t mean to!
Perfect!
Oh no!
This is perfect!
Now that we have the Energy Seed,
I can now get my strength and youth back!
I can catch all the goats I want, whenever I want!
Awesome!
What kind of stupid box is this?
It’s no use.
This is Mr. Slowy’s specially invented safe box.
There’s no way for you to open it.
So you say!
I get it now!
I just need to collect all six of the goats’ handprints
in order to get to the Energy Seed!
Wolffy, you’re brilliant!
We have been surrounded…
This is perfect!
It’s my fault.
It’s okay. There’s still Paddi and Jonie.
Only Jonie is left.
What?
Jonie disappeared?
Good job, Jonie!
I found you!
Now all that’s left is that old goat’s handprint.
I’ll be able to get the Energy Seed!
It’s all my fault.
If I hadn’t used Lightning Angel to destroy the grass,
you guys wouldn’t have had all those obstacles.
It’s my fault.
It was my wrong usage of Morning Sun that made everyone get caught.
Found you.
Old goat,
here I come!
Don’t hurt Mr. Slowy!
More yelling won’t do anything!
Stupid weeds, how dare you block my path!
Watch this.
And he still calls himself powerful.
What are you doing?
Let me go!
Help!
Unless you want to watch them get braised, steamed, and fried,
go clear the road and fix my train!
Don’t hurt them!
We’ll help you!
Then hurry up.
Mr. Slowy is right.
I need to learn how to protect everyone with courage.
I also need to learn how to watch over everyone with patience.
You’re not too bad.
But…
Is Tibbie really going to be okay clearing the road?
She’s just a teeny little girl.
Don’t underestimate Tibbie.
Lightning Angel is her signature train.
Finally finished!
Incredible!
I’ve finished repairing as well.
Finally done fixing!
Slowy, here I come!
What is going on?
I rescued all of my friends
while I was repairing Sirius.
And he also took back the Energy Seed!
I hate you guys!
I’ll get rid of you all!
Go!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Goodbye, Mr. Wolffy!
I’ll be back!
Look!
We’ve arrived on the Big Tree!
There’s a branch up front blocking our road.
Let me clear the road.
Tibbie,
let me do some maintenance on your Lightning Angel.
Thank you, Sparky!
It looks like they understand my aim now.
END