Marching to the New Wonderland
The Devil, Justice Spider
We’re currently delivering the extremely important Energy Seed,
but the kids are so unvigilant.
I need an idea.
Kids, be careful!
I’ve heard that there is a big, dangerous devil on the Big Tree!
He’s very scary!
Big devil?
They believe it.
The devil is coming!
Everyone, run!
There really is a devil!
Let’s get out of here!
But to get to the Big Tree’s Summit,
we have to use this road!
What a massive spider web!
Spider web?
Does that mean…
The—
The devil!
Do you need any help?
Why haven’t you eaten yet?
Hurry and eat!
It won’t be good if it goes cold.
Who are you?
Why are you helping us?
I’m the Big Tree’s jumping spider.
My name is Justice Spider.
I’m the personification of justice.
Helping others is my favorite thing.
So you aren’t the big devil?
That’s great!
But the Big Tree World is still dangerous.
We still have to be careful.
We still have a long way to travel.
What do we do?
Don’t worry; I’ll protect you as you go!
Once you’ve eaten, we’ll set out immediately.
Great!
Hot!
Sorry, I added too much pepper!
Stop!
What’s the matter?
Don’t worry!
Watch this!
Who ruined my plan?
That was dangerous.
But don’t you worry;
with me around, you’ll be safe!
Thank you, Justice Spider.
What an incredible goat-catching move!
But I, with years of goat-catching experience, won’t lose!
You can’t run this time!
This road isn’t safe!
I’ll help you find a different path!
This guy is really good at catching goats!
If he and I worked together, we’d be invincible!
Is everyone okay?
Why do I feel like we always get messed up
whenever Justice Spider helps us?
Exactly.
Is everyone okay?
I’m here to help!
Again?
No thanks!
Don’t run!
Didn’t I tell you guys not to run?
Looks like Justice Spider is, in fact, the big devil they speak of.
We can’t stay by his side any longer!
Kids,
Justice Spider meant well in helping us.
We shouldn’t treat him like this.
True, however—
Chatting in such a dark room will hurt your eyes.
Let me help you turn the lights on. Where’s the switch?
That’s my face!
That’s my ear!
We finally have light!
Mr. Slowy, what’s the matter?
I’m… I’m fine.
You guys go on.
Weslie, I agree with you.
This is my collected list
of insects that need your help.
You better go and help them out.
Do they really need me?
They do!
Right now, they’re in dire crises.
They need you more than we do.
Okay, I’ll go right now!
Wait a minute!
If I leave, then who’s going to protect you all?
We can take care of ourselves; you rest assured and go on now.
Goodbye, everybody!
Goodbye, Justice Spider!
They didn’t tell me the locations.
Justice Spider is finally gone.
But isn’t this a bit mean of us to do?
Well,
Justice Spider put us through so much trouble,
and he’s quite clumsy.
He also made us get hurt.
But… he…
Justice—
So, all along, you guys have hated me?
We’re sorry! Actually, what we wanted to say was—
You don’t have to say anything!
I’ll just leave!
Mr. Slowy, what now?
This time, we were in the wrong.
Let’s hurry and apologize to him.
As long as I win over Justice Spider,
I can catch goats without worry!
Watch this.
Somebody help me!
Can you help me out?
Come on up.
Never mind; all I do is hurt others.
I better leave.
Don’t leave!
I’ve already waited for three days and three nights!
Only you can save me!
Can I really help you?
I believe that you’re the personification of justice!
Personification of justice?
Okay, I’ll help you!
Finished.
The wood scraps are placed well; nobody will fall in again.
Can you get me out first?
I told you I just bring trouble.
How is that possible?
Look at your just face,
and your set of just skills.
The most valuable of all is that you have a heart of justice.
You speak quite sincerely.
You must be a good person.
Everyone says that about me.
However,
that group of little goats is always harassing me!
Little goats?
I wholeheartedly helped them deliver things.
Not only did they not thank me,
they also left me in the pit as revenge!
Look, my finger’s even been hurt!
So they’re that type of goats!
No wonder they hate the just me!
Then can you help me capture those goats?
Of course! Let’s go!
Mr. Slowy, we couldn’t find Justice Spider.
If you find him, we must apologize to him face to face.
You terrible goats! Hands behind your back!
Justice Spider!
We’re sorry; we want to apologize.
Don’t be fooled!
They love to play the victim.
Wolffy!
You want to fool me?
I’m going to capture you all!
Everyone, get on the trains!
Don’t let them get away!
They used acorns as a block!
Watch this!
There’s no block now.
Could you throw them elsewhere?
Sorry, I forgot about you!
The goats have run away.
It’s okay; I set up a massive web up ahead
They can’t run!
Warning, warning. Danger is ahead.
It’s the goats’ screaming.
They must have been ambushed!
Is everyone okay?
We’re okay.
It looks like Justice Spider believes Wolffy.
Let’s just hurry and get out of here.
Don’t let them catch up to us.
Did I just hear Wolffy and Justice Spider screaming just now?
I’ll be back!
END