Marching to the New Wonderland
Ant Express
Delivering the Energy Seed is actually quite tiring.
Need to send a package? Come here!
We are Ant Express!
No matter what is delivered, no matter where it’s delivered,
we will deliver it for you quickly and safely!
If you need a delivery, please contact us!
Our purpose is: every mission must be done!
These commercials are just for scamming little kids, yet you trust them?
Who’s that?
Your parcels are here.
Our parcels are here!
My ice cream didn’t even melt during delivery!
How fast!
My wooden tower didn’t even fall during delivery!
How stable!
Even my spiderweb hair clip didn’t break!
Ant Express is incredible!
Aha!
I can just send the Energy Seed to be delivered to the Big Tree’s Summit!
Hello, how can I help you?
I need to deliver something.
But I’m worried you won’t be able to send it there.
Don’t worry! As long as you can say the name of the place,
we here at Ant Express will definitely be able to deliver it there!
Awesome!
Please deliver this to the Big Tree’s Summit for me.
I’m sorry; we can’t deliver anything to the Big Tree’s Summit.
Why not?
Don’t your ads say that you can deliver to any place?
That place is very dangerous.
Our Ant Express regulations state that we must never go there.
Ant Express really does just scam young kids.
Do you need a delivery?
Are you really willing to help me send it?
They say that ants can’t go there.
I’ve never heard of a place
where we ants can’t go.
I will deliver it for you.
Can I trust you?
This delivery is extremely important.
Don’t worry; Ant Express will fulfill every mission.
My name is Andy. This is my work ID.
Then Andy, I’ll hand it to you.
My name is Paddi. Remember to tell me once you’ve delivered it!
Just you wait!
How professional! Now I don’t need to worry.
Once my boss gets to see my skills,
I’ll become a permanent Ant Express courier!
I’ll get promoted to general manager!
I’ll get to the pinnacle of life!
Let me fill my stomach before I continue.
—Andy?　—Paddi?
Weren’t you helping me deliver my parcel?
What are you doing here?
Um… uh…
I get it.
You have to eat before you can work, right?
Right, right.
Here, eat a bunch.
Thank you!
I’ll head out now.
I’m so full.
I’ll sleep a bit before continuing.
Andy?
Weren’t you delivering my parcel?
Why are you sleeping here?
Uh… uh…
I get it.
You’re sleeping to refresh your energy, right?
Right, exactly.
Then I won’t bother your rest.
I’ll head back first.
I’m waiting to hear from you!
Where’s my parcel?
Paddi!
Andy?
Did you already deliver the Energy Seed
to the Big Tree’s Summit that quickly?
You people at Ant Express are truly incredible!
I still haven’t delivered it yet.
What?
Why have you still not delivered it yet?
Then where’s the Energy Seed?
I lost it?
What?
Aren’t you a master courier?
How did you lose it?
Actually, I’m just an intern.
I haven’t had a chance to deliver a parcel yet.
Then, your parcel didn’t have anyone willing to deliver it,
so I decided to try it out.
And so…
This is not good.
I need to find the Energy Seed!
Paddi.
Listen to me.
Don’t disturb me!
Please listen to me!
I won’t! I will never trust you again!
Okay.
I just wanted to tell you that there’s a cliff up ahead.
Why didn’t you say so?
We’ve found signs of the Energy Seed!
Paddi,
I’ll definitely help you find it again.
I’m not trusting you.
Where’d Paddi go?
What the heck happened to Sirius?
Who dropped this litter?
The Energy Seed?
Awesome! This was too easy!
Oh no.
We can’t let the Energy Seed be in Wolffy’s hands!
I’ll ask for it back.
Don’t cause chaos. I’ll think of something myself.
Am I really unable to open it without the goats’ handprints?
I refuse to believe
that I can’t open you without the goats’ handprints.
What’s the matter?
Don’t disturb me. I’m thinking of a solution.
What the heck is this safe box made out of?
I can’t think of an idea.
If only Weslie were here, then it’d be alright!
I’ll help you get it back.
Don’t go! It’s dangerous!
Give back my parcel!
I found it, so it’s mine! Let go right now!
No way; I’m never going to lose the parcel again.
Let go, or no?
Danger, Andy!
Paddi, you’re here as well!
Let him go!
Mr. Ant, let’s not fight!
How do I use this thing?
What’s this button for?
I’ll be back!
Andy,
why didn’t you let go even in such danger?
Because I’ve always dreamed of
becoming a dedicated Ant Express courier.
For the sake of Ant Express,
I can’t lose a parcel again.
But before, I also didn’t trust you.
I did you wrong.
Actually,
I really wanted to help deliver your parcel to the Big Tree’s Summit.
But I almost got it lost.
I’m sorry.
I’m a failed courier.
But didn’t you bring it back to me again anyway?
In my heart,
you’re already an outstanding courier!
Paddi, thank you!
No one has ever commended me like this!
I actually think we’re quite similar.
I really hope I can see you again.
We have branch offices all throughout the Big Tree.
We’ll definitely meet again.
Definitely!
There you are, Paddi!
It’s time to get going!
I’m coming!
See you next time, Andy!
It’s Auntie Ant calling.
Hello, Auntie Ant?
Andy,
congratulations on becoming a permanent Ant Express courier!
From now on, you may deliver parcels!
END