Marching to the New Wonderland
Her Highness Comes
Today I helped an elderly ant cross the road
and earned yet another pennant!
I want a pennant, too!
Why don’t I give you mine, then?
No, that’s not my own.
I want to use my own power to get a pennant.
But what should I do to get a pennant?
Sparky,
as long as you keep helping others,
the day that you get a pennant will always come!
Right, I’ll go find people that need help right now!
What happened?
I’ll get off and see.
Where are they?
Have you seen our bee princess?
Uh… I haven’t.
If you see her, please notify us immediately.
We will reward you generously.
Then could I get a pennant?
What are you doing?
Leave it to me
to find the princess!
I must find the bee princess!
Bee princess, where are you?
Help me!
It’s the princess!
Thank you.
You’re welcome, Your Highness.
How could the bee princess be this dirty?
I’m sorry. Wrong person.
Where are you going? Can I come with you?
Little girl, stop following me.
I still have an important task to complete.
I’ve set up dragnets.
There’s no way that the goats can avoid falling into my trap!
It worked!
Delivery pipe, activate!
Fat goat, fat goat, come on in to my train!
Have you seen our bee princess?
What princess?
I haven’t even seen a bee.
Help me!
I can explain!
I told you not to follow, and you didn’t listen?
See? Now you’re hungry.
Here, eat.
I don’t want what you’ve already eaten!
You don’t want it? Fine!
Don’t find me if you’re starving.
I haven’t bitten this part.
Don’t worry, I haven’t touched this cherry!
I only eat peeled cherries.
If I turn the cherry into juice,
she can’t tell if it’s peeled or not!
Here.
Drink it.
The cotton on this bed is high on one side and lower on the other!
How am I supposed to sleep on it?
This is all we have here; take it or leave it!
Don’t leave!
I want to hear a bedtime story!
Once upon a time, there was a big hero.
He defeated the big, evil dragon
and rescued the princess.
Then, he earned the pennant he’d dreamed of.
You aren’t a hero.
You—
Don’t chase me! No!
Careful!
You’re always running off and causing me trouble!
Don’t follow me anymore.
I just wanted to make a cup of strawberry juice to thank you.
I hate you, big brother!
Stupid bees!
I’m coming right now to get revenge!
Who is it?
Where am I?
A bee that’s been left behind!
Come on home with me.
Help me!
Let my friend go!
Big brother!
Little goat, you delivered yourself to my door.
Don’t blame me for having no mercy.
Come on out, Morning Sun!
Come on out, Sirius!
Go, Morning Sun!
Morning Sun!
I forgot again that you don’t have attack abilities!
Big brother, look out!
What a great day!
Mutton to eat and bees to vent my anger at!
How perfect!
Sparky!
I won’t let you hurt her!
Big brother…
She…
She’s not a bee! You’ve got it wrong!
I can confirm whether or not she’s a bee, no?
Let me see who you really are.
What’s happening? It’s blinding!
She’s so cute!
However, why does she look a bit familiar?
I feel like I’ve seen her somewhere.
Could she…
She’s the bee princess!
Security!
Your Highness, are you okay?
It was he who captured me!
Let me explain!
How dare you mistreat Her Highness!
What is there to explain?
Your Highness, spare me!
Little girl—
Princess Vivi,
take care.
Big brother,
I almost forgot to give you this.
I hope you’ll like it.
Sparky, hurry up and open it!
It just might be a pennant!
A lollipop?
A thick honey flavor! So good!
Look!
It’s my pennant!
END