Marching to the New Wonderland
An Unexpected Disaster
How many times have I told you, Paddi?
No eating while driving!
You have to focus on the road!
I still have a bunch right here!
I knew you’d do this.
If you ever eat while driving again, I’ll throw out all of your candy!
No, don’t!
It’s a sweet-tooth aphid!
No, I can’t give this last one to you.
Don’t take my candy!
Weslie!
I’m coming down to rescue you!
We’ve arrived, little goats!
Oh no!
I’ve finally gotten the Energy Seed!
Wolnie and I can keep our eternal youth!
Oh, come on!
I surely won’t tell you
about how Weslie fell out of the train and got dragged away by an aphid.
Please stop talking, Paddi.
So that’s what happened! I’m going to find him right now.
Good thing I didn’t tell him
that the safe box’s locks have a time limit.
If the palm prints turn dark,
then we have to put our hands on it again.
So that’s how it works!
Then I’ll take the Energy Seed with me,
and I’ll make Weslie open the lock as soon as I find him!
Justice Spider, take the goats back to Sirius
and watch them closely.
Yes, sir!
Give back my lollipop!
There you are!
Wolffy!
The Energy Seed? Why is it with you?
That’s right. I’m only missing your hand print.
Give me your hand right now!
Here comes a honey fruit!
Another one!
Open the Energy Seed box for me now!
I will not!
Yes, you will!
No, I won’t!
He’s sleeping; now’s our chance. When I count down from three,
we’ll run in five different directions
so he won’t be able to catch us.
Everyone, get ready.
Three, two, one!
You want to run?
It won’t be easy!
If you dare, let me go! We’ll fight one-on-one!
Okay! Who’s scared of who?
Don’t think that you can bully me just because you’re tall!
Although I’m short—
Although… Although I’m short…
Do you think I want to be short?
Do you want to get taller?
Yes, yes! I do!
I have a quick fix.
What’s the matter?
Wrong hand.
What?
Weslie’s hand is mine; no one can bite it!
I shower every single day! Do you have to act so repulsed?
Hurry, run!
One thousand one hundred and eleven!
One thousand one hundred and twelve!
One thousand one hundred and thirteen!
You’ll grow taller very soon!
Keep going!
I’m too tired. I just can’t jump anymore.
This is what you’ll look like when you’re tall!
How handsome!
Persistence is important!
As long as you persist in jumping rope,
you’ll look like this very soon!
Tell me, can you do it?
I can!
What’s that? I can’t hear you!
Wonderful!
Then we’ll head out and not bother your exercise!
Keep going, Justice Spider!
Okay!
Maintain your speed!
Yes!
Keep it up! Don’t stop!
Now, are you ready?
Bring it!
Looks like it didn’t work.
Can we try something else?
Look over there.
Can we?
Of course!
This fruit sap is way too sticky.
Give it some more time, and it’ll get even softer.
Can we try something else?
No.
Why not?
Wonderful, my hand is out!
Your hand is free, but the honey is still on my face!
Come on,
let’s hurry and run!
My leg is stuck!
Hold on, Wolffy!
I’m going to help you!
Yes, yes! The aphid is finally gone!
Thank you for saving me, Weslie.
You’re welcome.
And thank you for helping me open this box!
I’ve finally gotten the Energy Seed!
Wait, what?
That’s because the other goats’ hand prints have already expired.
I’m so done!
Justice Spider?
I’m… over… here!
Two thousand and fifteen,
two thousand and sixteen,
two thousand and seventeen,
two thousand and eighteen,
two thousand and nineteen…
Where are the goats?
Two thousand—
How… How the heck would I know?
I’m busy jumping rope to get taller!
Two thousand and—
Darn it, I forgot how many times I’ve jumped!
Don’t… disturb… me!
Wolffy, you should just give up.
As long as I have the Energy Seed, I’ll just start over and catch you!
Come get us, Wolffy!
Watch this!
Start up, Sirius!
This is our present for you.
Do you like it, Wolffy?
If you run away, that’s still fine.
The Energy Seed is still in my hands right now!
Look, what’s this?
When you were carrying me just now,
I stole it back from you!
I hate you guys!
Trying to run? I don’t think so!
I forgot to tell you.
We added a boomerang system to your missiles.
Where’s Wolffy?
I, Wolffy, can’t be struck down by just a missile!
I’ve actually grown taller!
Wolffy, Justice Spider, goodbye!
Goodbye! Thank you guys for your height fix!
END