Marching to the New Wonderland
The Importance of Logistics
Which path do we take?
Why don’t we just try each path to see?
Let me do it!
This task is better suited for Paddi.
Watch my Hurricane’s power!
Begin search!
I found the right path!
Great job!
Do we just go through?
It’s so scary!
Don’t worry!
I’ll lead the way!
Jonie should go.
Great job as well, Jonie!
It’s just a broken branch; Lightning Angel, you’re up.
Sparky!
Let me do it this time.
Morning Sun!
It’s fixed so sturdily; Morning Sun never disappoints!
It really is super sturdy.
Right.
Now it’s even harder to get past.
I’m sorry.
I forgot yet again that Morning Sun only has mechanical abilities.
It’s fine.
Lightning Angel, break away the branch!
Darn it, I don’t have enough power!
Don’t worry.
The battery we ordered is probably coming very soon.
Ordered battery?
I’m sorry.
It’s okay; let’s think of how to move the branch.
Right, right!
Aren’t we only losing a little, little bit of time?
Weslie.
I’m here!
You…
You quickly go
and see if there are nearby insects that can help.
Paddi, take Hurricane and go find food.
Jonie, in a bit, go camouflage our trains.
Tibbie, save Lightning Angel’s power.
We’ll need it later to push away the branch.
Sparky…
Is there anything you need me to do?
You…
How about you just rest for a bit?
Why can my Morning Sun only help with logistics?
Every day, it’s just fixing things.
Why did you take my pebble?
So you guys are also miserable mechanics.
How are we miserable?
Look, carrier ants perform an incredibly important task.
You guys can only fix things. Is that not miserable?
Repairing is also a very important job.
Where there is injustice, there is me!
Hand over your loot!
Loot?
These are all our clients’ parcels, not loot!
How stubborn.
Don’t steal other peoples’ packages!
Everyone, run!
Go away!
Thank you guys!
Let’s get started, Tibbie.
Wait.
Sparky’s not here.
Oh no, it’s Wolffy!
Everyone, run!
I can’t; my train is already out of power!
Why hasn’t the battery been delivered yet?
The battery will never arrive!
Justice Spider!
You can’t steal this stuff!
No one can stop my justice!
In that case, don’t beg me for mercy!
Morning Sun!
It can’t be this powerful, right?
You’re scared, aren’t you?
Darn it, why isn’t it working?
So it’s a paper tiger! It’s my turn now!
Stop!
What can a group of mechanics do?
Are you here to fix my shoes?
You guys can’t defeat him! Run!
I won’t let you get out alive!
Keep it up!
Great job,
mechanics!
I’m out of spider silk!
Don’t get ahead of yourselves; I shall justly retreat!
I’m going to be back!
You guys are incredible!
Great job, mechanics!
Mechanics may be the logistics force,
but when needed, they can do a lot!
The train has been worn out to its limit!
If Wolffy attacks us one more time,
we might…
This is bad!
What happened?
Those ant mechanics ruined the plan!
Mechanics?
That’s us!
Sparky!
The battery!
Just keep it up for a bit;
I’ll get some spider silk and then be back!
Morning Sun!
Wolffy!
You destroyed all of our trains!
Watch this!
Automatic repairing, activate!
Sparky,
did you think I’d give you time to do repairs?
When will it be over?
What?
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
It’s our turn to attack!
What happened?
We’ve already conducted a big change
to your cannon!
A silly mechanic can’t ruin my life!
I’m going to tell you once.
Us mechanics are
incredibly important!
I’ll be back!
Great job!
Sparky, come help!
Yep!
All fixed!
I meant for you to help move the rocks.
I’m sorry.
My Morning Sun can only do repairing and maintenance.
END