Marching to the New Wonderland
Indecisive
Tibbie, are you almost done?
Almost.
It’s been three hours and food still isn’t ready yet!
My stomach is so empty.
Let’s go see.
Tibbie, you still haven’t started cooking?
There’s too many ingredients!
Should I make mushroom soup first
or green grass cake first?
Tibbie,
I’m going to use the bathroom.
Please turn off the stove for me if the water boils.
No problem!
Everyone, let’s have a meeting.
Mr. Slowy,
I’m sorry.
It’s all my fault.
You are indeed responsible here.
But I called you all over for something more important.
That is, choosing the head train.
Head train?
Then that’s definitely Weslie!
Weslie’s Thunderbolt needs maintenance,
so we need to choose someone new,
a head train with abilities.
Right.
The new head train is Lightning Angel!
Lightning Angel?
That’s what I said.
You’ve all been head trains before.
Only Tibbie hasn’t.
No, no!
I… I can’t be the head train.
Tibbie, you have to believe in yourself.
I’m going to do some experiments.
Don’t bother me unless needed.
Tibbie,
be more confident!
Mr. Slowy says you can do it, so you definitely can!
I hope today goes smoothly.
Tibbie, the road up ahead is blocked by spiderwebs!
What now?
Tibbie, extend the mechanical arm to cut down the spiderweb!
The mechanical arm’s point of contact is a little small.
The diamond drill is better!
This time, you guys are done for!
So is it better to use the mechanical arm or the diamond drill?
Use the mechanical arm!
Get out the diamond drill!
What did you guys hit the brakes for?
Wolffy!
What happened?
Thank goodness you hit the brakes so that we’d escaped!
But I didn’t hit the brakes.
Mr. Slowy!
Who is it?
Mr. Slowy, it was so scary just now!
It scared me so bad that for dinner,
I only ate five plates!
Thank goodness the train stopped; otherwise, we’d be in danger.
I hit the brakes.
What?
I’m in charge of the train’s emergency controls.
Don’t worry.
I get it!
Mr. Slowy wanted Tibbie to be the head train
so he could train her.
She’ll be able to get rid of her bad habit of indecision.
So that’s it!
Rest assured, Mr. Slowy!
We’ll do everything we can to help Tibbie.
I’ll help too.
Which path do we take?
Tibbie,
you’re the head train.
It’s your decision.
Let me teach you a decision-making strategy.
Great! How do I do it?
Here’s a map.
As long as you memorize the roads,
you’ll know where to go,
and you won’t need to decide again.
It’s such a big map.
I can’t memorize it all in one go.
Have you memorized it?
I’m still working on it.
Memorizing the roads is too hard.
Tibbie,
let me help you.
Everyone, please answer this poll for which road to take!
Paddi, is there a result yet?
Almost!
Once I count it out, I’ll have it!
I’ve finally counted them all!
What’s the result?
It’s a tie.
I can’t make a decision, Mr. Slowy.
I just can’t be the head train.
I’m sorry, Mr. Slowy.
It’s my fault for not helping Tibbie.
No, this time it was my fault.
Don’t blame Tibbie.
Everyone cares about me that much?
I must get rid of my bad habit of indecision!
I have to live up to their expectations!
Rest assured, everyone! I’ve already found a way to make decisions!
Flower petals!
Mr. Slowy says we can’t just pick flowers.
Don’t worry.
I’m using flowers that have already fallen from the trees.
It’s very sustainable!
But is it reliable?
I’ll know if I try it.
Mechanical arm, diamond drill, mechanical arm,
diamond drill, mechanical arm…
Left, right, left, right,
right!
Have you missed me, little goats?
Tibbie, do we charge forward or take a U-turn?
Make a decision!
U-turn!
Tibbie, great job!
Oh no!
Hurricane has discovered a split path up ahead!
It’s likely that a landmine has been set up!
And Wolffy has caught up from behind!
Let’s see how you’ll run this time!
Don’t worry!
Oh no, I’ve used up all my flowers!
Tibbie, stay calm!
Right now, you have to rely on yourself, Tibbie!
Make a decision!
Both roads are dead ends; let’s see how you decide!
I can’t let everyone down.
I’ve got it!
You little goats, I will get you!
Good job, Tibbie!
She can finally make her own decisions.
What’s the matter?
Help me!
Tibbie, hurry back up here!
Tibbie!
Come out!
Hurry!
Give me your hand!
Tibbie!
Your hand!
It’s too late.
I can’t drag everyone down.
Tibbie!
Goodbye, everyone.
No!
You’re safe.
Why didn’t you take it out earlier?
Why did you choose to drop into the abyss, Tibbie?
Right, Tibbie.
That was a very dangerous decision this time.
Why didn’t you hesitate at all?
Why would I hesitate saving everyone?
Tibbie, you’ve finally grown.
So touching!
You made so much good food!
Tibbie,
you didn’t make a month’s worth of food, did you?
I wanted to thank everybody,
but I also didn’t know what everyone wanted to eat.
So I just decided to make everything!
END