Marching to the New Wonderland
A Difficult Choice
What are you howling for at midnight?
Can you let me sleep?
Wolnie, the goats’ only route is through this intersection.
I’m staying up all night to catch them!
You’ve finally arrived!
You can’t run from me now, little goats!
Oh no, it’s Wolffy!
Speed up, Weslie!
Watch this!
Oh no, it’s a dead end!
It’s over; Wolffy’s caught up!
You can’t run!
You little goats…
What’s going on with Wolffy?
Who cares? Let’s run!
I’m… I’m sorry, Mr. Slowy.
You guys are so unvigilant.
What if Wolffy arrives?
But Wolffy hasn’t appeared for several days now.
Even if Wolffy does come, it’s fine.
We’ve already set up traps.
What traps?
Help me!
He’s fallen into our trap; let’s go see!
Why is it you guys?
What in the world happened?
Brother Weslie, my dad came down with a strange and serious illness.
Mommy has used every idea she has,
but nothing has cured Daddy!
Please help him!
Could this be another one of Wolffy’s plans to capture us?
It could be.
But Wilie wouldn’t lie.
Then let’s go and test Wolffy first.
Wolffy’s heartbeat is normal.
But it’s accompanied by a loud gurgling sound.
It’s very weird.
It’s as if it’s his stomach.
Right, how did you know?
See for yourself.
Since he’s been sick, he hasn’t really eaten much.
He must be very hungry.
I’ll make some porridge for him.
I’m helping, too!
What kind of illness is this?
Could Wolffy be faking his illness?
We’ll test him and see.
What if he’s actually sick?
Look, he’s awake.
Wolnie?
Why’d you get fat?
Wolnie, why do I feel like you smell like mutton?
Just now, I wanted to bite you.
I’m just so illness-addled.
It looks like Wolffy is actually very sick.
Is there a cure, Mr. Slowy?
I seem to have seen this illness before.
What is it?
Why are there so many Wolnies?
I’m so dizzy.
Extra sunlight helps you get better.
We’ve found some stuff.
See if it can help Wolffy.
Paddi, what medicine did you give to him?
Hawthorn berries. They help with digestion.
He’s already super hungry.
There’s nothing in his stomach to digest!
You’re such a mess, Paddi.
Here, try my dit da jow.
Try my slimming cream!
Wait!
Wolffy seems to be even more sick.
It seems that he’s going to die soon.
Am I… going to die soon?
Weslie, what are you thinking about?
I’m thinking…
I disagree!
I disagree, too!
Wolffy’s an evil wolf!
How could we possibly use the Energy Seed to save him?
Wolffy is indeed evil,
but he has a life, too.
But the Energy Seed is for saving the Big Tree!
If we use it, then what will we use to save the Big Tree?
But it would be terrible for Wilie to not have a dad.
—Weslie, what do you think?　　—Weslie, it’s up to you!
Let’s ask Mr. Slowy’s opinion.
What in the world is Wolffy’s illness?
Brothers, sisters!
Please save my dad!
Daddy is feeling more and more unwell!
Please save him!
Wilie.
Daddy!
Daddy, how do you feel now?
Daddy is okay.
Little goats,
please help me with one last thing.
What is it?
I have a photo.
Please help me edit it so I look more energetic.
Make my eyes bigger,
my nose higher,
my teeth whiter,
and myself overall more handsome.
Mr. Wolffy, the photo is finished.
Thank you.
Wilie,
when Daddy’s not by your side,
you have to be strong.
You must be a man and protect your mom.
—Wolffy!　—Daddy!
Daddy, you’ll be okay!
Son.
Wolnie.
Let’s take a family portrait.
So, do we really have to watch Wilie lose his dad
with our own eyes?
Let’s head to Sirius first.
Okay.
What’s the matter?
Look up ahead.
Everyone, get together to move the branch!
Okay!
Let us go!
It isn’t Wolffy, is it?
Correct.
It is… King Wolffy.
So you were pretending to be sick, Wolffy!
You’re despicable!
Catch goats…
You’re already this sick, yet you still want to catch goats?
Wolnie.
I’m useless. I’ve never let my family eat mutton before.
I wanted to use my last strength
to let them eat a meal of mutton.
I agree!
Sparky, you—
You agree to be eaten?
What the heck are you guys thinking?
I’m saying that I agree with using the Energy Seed to save Wolffy!
Awesome!
Let’s send Wolffy back first.
Okay.
We just need Mr. Slowy.
Where is Mr. Slowy?
What in the world is Wolffy’s illness?
I’ve almost got it.
Who says I’m sick?
You… Weren’t you about to die?
I took a nap, and now I feel much more energetic.
Watch this!
I know!
Wolffy has altitude hypoxic vertigo!
Altitude hypoxic vertigo?
What kind of illness is that?
Although the Big Tree is only a few meters tall,
us shrinking down makes it seem as though we climbed several kilometers.
Then why did only Wolffy get this type of illness?
If you’re tired, or if you lack rest,
then getting this illness is very likely.
Only proper rest
can cure altitude hypoxic vertigo.
Mr. Slowy, you’re incredible!
Give me the Energy Seed!
You guys can’t run today!
Wolffy!
You’re finally awake!
Let go of me, Wolnie!
I’ll get the Seed and capture goats for you!
I don’t want to eat mutton! I just want you to be healthy
and safe and sound!
Daddy!
Lighter, I can’t breathe!
Wolffy!
Daddy!
END