Marching to the New Wonderland
The Approaching Storm
We’re moving slower than a snail!
Go faster, Weslie!
Mr. Slowy, it’d be a waste to just keep driving
in weather as good as this!
We should go and have a picnic
and enjoy a warm sunbath!
This week, you guys have already had seven picnics,
and have already sunbathed fifteen times!
Don’t just relax; we have to cover distance!
Alright, I’ll go faster.
Hurricane has just detected that a storm is arriving in the next half hour!
How is that possible? The weather is so clear.
Look!
The Magic Trains are so strong.
We don’t need to fear the weather, no matter how bad it gets!
No matter how advanced technology is, it can’t conquer nature.
What do we do if the rain is this heavy?
Don’t worry, I’ve already found a way.
Which is…
To find shelter from the rain.
Someone tell me where to go!
What kind of place are we looking for?
Let’s go find Andy!
This is the right place for storm shelter!
In fact, our branch has the title of “Lots of Three!”
“Lots of Three?”
That’s right!
Lots of ants,
lots of parcels,
and…
Lots of dust!
Are there any other rooms?
No. This is the only utility room left that still has space.
This isn’t too bad.
We can still stay here as long as we clean it up a little.
We’ve finally finished cleaning!
Brother Goat,
it’s about to rain soon.
Can my family and I also come in and take shelter here?
It’s only a few people.
They can come in.
Of course you can!
Thank you, Brother Goat!
Thank you…
My last 923rd aunt is in here now.
Thank you!
Never mind. You guys can stay here instead.
You’re all so kind; thank you!
—It’s starting to rain! What do we do?　　—Aha!
The Bee Hotel!
Welcome.
You are my distinguished guests.
Choose whichever room you would like to stay in!
This place isn’t so bad!
No!
There’s a hole up there.
Rain will leak through.
Then we’ll switch rooms.
We’ve looked at all of the rooms.
Only the first one has the least problems.
We’ll stay in the first one, then.
I’m sorry, I thought you didn’t want to stay here anymore,
so I’ve already given the rooms to other people.
All of the rooms are full now.
Then let’s go to the lobby for a moment!
Since there aren’t any rooms,
we’ll just go to the lobby.
The lobby is already filled with people; what now?
There’s nothing we can do.
We can only go searching for another shelter.
There’s a tree cave up ahead; we can hide in there!
Let’s go somewhere else instead.
A branch dropped!
There’re giant insects!
A fruit broke the branch!
Go that way!
How are you, Brother Goats?
We’re fine…
Are you tired?
Come have some hot chocolate!
A storm is coming,
yet you’re still in the mood for hot chocolate?
Everyone’s drinking hot chocolate!
My dad made an emergency refuge.
Everyone can avoid the storm here!
You guys come over and play with me, too!
Can we trust Wolffy?
No, it must be a trap.
I’ll send the map to you right now.
See you soon!
Mr. Slowy, what do we do?
We absolutely cannot go to Wolffy’s emergency refuge.
Let’s go look for another shelter instead.
The water is rising, Mr. Slowy.
What now?
Power through!
Thank goodness the storm paused so that we could be saved.
Paddi, report the train’s current location.
Positioning.
This place looks familiar.
Oh no, it’s Wolffy’s refuge!
I’ve been waiting for so long; you’re finally here.
You… What are you trying to do?
Since you’re here now,
just come on and rest here.
In the face of a disaster, we’re all in the same boat.
Did I see that correctly?
He’s right; we’re all in the same boat.
We should overcome this together.
Sparky,
begin the rescue operation
and let injured insects come inside for help.
Yes!
We will help the others.
Wolffy, we’ve come to help!
Finally, I’ve lured you out!
Oh no, we fell for it!
What are you doing?
How could you treat the goats like that?
Exactly!
Quiet! Quiet!
If you don’t be quiet, I’ll eat you guys too!
Wolffy,
the storm is here.
There’s no way you can handle this by yourself!
Release us so we can all work together!
As long as I get the Energy Seed,
I won’t need to worry about storms, will I?
Oh no!
Wolffy,
unless you want to die with us, release us so we can help!
Nope.
Wolffy, help!
Son!
Wolnie!
Wolffy, release us right now!
Fine.
Have the insects get on the train for shelter!
Raise the shield function to the highest power!
Got it!
You guys…
We told you, we’re all in the same boat!
Oh no, we’re about to get blown over by the wind!
Reciprocated.
This is actually quite difficult!
Ugh!
Everyone’s clearly working so hard.
Why is it still not enough?
I can’t hold it down anymore!
The lever is bouncing back!
Keep going; don’t give up!
We can pass through this!
You’re right.
Keep it up, everyone!
We will definitely get through it!
If I can pass this,
then I will never catch goats again!
Keep it up!
We’ve got this!
Yay!
Now, I can eat mutton again!
Look, another storm is here!
Where?
I’m going to get you guys one day!
END