Marching to the New Wonderland
Overprotective
We’re departing!
Come on back!
Yep, got it!
Let’s have a race to see who can get to Mr. Slowy the fastest!
Ready, set,
go!
Thank goodness my train didn’t get dirty.
Wait for me!
I won!
Jonie is the slowest!
I’m not the slowest!
Tibbie is still back there!
Good thing my train didn’t get dirty.
Tibbie,
if we keep going this slow, we won’t make it in time.
But…
Paddi told me
that there’s a very beautiful dew pond up ahead.
It’d be a shame to miss it!
My dear Wolnie, I introduce to you
the upgraded Sirius!
It looks terrible!
Change it back right now!
Don’t look at its ugliness, Wolnie.
Now, it’s a mountain-spitting super weapon.
Are you sure you want to change it back, Wolnie?
This isn’t a scenic spot at all.
The road ahead has been blocked by a tree branch.
It’s up to you, Tibbie!
No worries!
Oh no!
That’ll scratch my train!
My train!
I’m sorry!
I just knew
that you’d change your mind!
That train is so beautiful!
It’s of a bright shade of pink
with such a shiny, glowy body!
It’s simply standing in front of all the trends!
Since Wolnie likes it,
I’ll go and snatch the train for her!
Sparky?
Is it fixable?
Fixable, yes,
but it will take me several hours to do it.
I’m sorry.
It’s all my fault.
It’s not just you.
Don’t blame yourself too much.
The good news is that, according to the map,
we’ll be fine after crossing this path!
Who says you’re “fine?”
Wolffy!
My train is so dirty!
Tibbie!
You want to save her?
It won’t be easy!
Careful!
It’s game over!
Jonie has also been caught!
It’s your turn, Weslie!
Weslie!
How brave!
However,
the more you struggle, the dirtier and uglier your train will get!
Gross!
Tibbie!
Weslie, run!
Mr. Slowy!
Don’t worry about us! Get away!
Weslie, you won’t escape my grasp!
Don’t hurt my friends!
Tibbie, go rescue Weslie first!
The Seed is with him!
We can’t let Wolffy get it!
I’ll come back to save you guys in a moment!
Running away won’t be that easy!
Oh no…
Even Weslie…
I have to rescue everyone!
Don’t touch the Energy Seed!
Don’t worry.
As long as Tibbie doesn’t get caught,
Wolffy can’t get the Seed.
I’ve already trapped her in a cage!
I’ll come bring her over here right now!
Hold this for me, Paddi.
Trivial.
What’s all this about?
Tibbie!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
I’ll be back!
Our survival this time
is all thanks to Tibbie!
It was all my fault.
From now on, I promise that…
I won’t be so overprotective of my train anymore.
To celebrate getting rid of this bad habit,
I’m treating you to some ice cream!
I’m sorry, Tibbie!
It’s okay!
Wow, Tibbie!
You’ve really changed!
My train!
END