Marching to the New Wonderland
Courageously Responsible
The juice that Andy sent is super refreshing.
Sadly, he only sent one.
Paddi, hurry and help move these branches!
I…
I can’t really handle these big tasks.
Come on!
The slumber fruit is very powerful.
It releases a hypnotic aroma that,
if smelled, without the antidote,
you will fall asleep forever after two hours!
Of course I have to be careful!
If I catch you secretly eating again, I’ll tell Mr. Slowy!
Fine.
I won’t anymore.
Uh… I didn’t!
What the…?
Why do the leaves of this fruit look so weird?
What kind of fruit is this?
It looks so strange!
Mr. Slowy, come take a look.
What is this? It smells so good!
You’ve all been poisoned!
What exactly did they come here for?
Don’t worry; none of you are showing symptoms of poisoning.
Wolffy was likely just trying to scare us.
Now, we’re going to determine the new route for delivering the Seed.
Pay attention and listen.
Paddi!
That wasn’t me!
I’m sorry, that was me.
That wasn’t me, either!
We’re sorry, Mr. Slowy; we’re just too sleepy.
Sleepy for what? Why aren’t I sleepy?
You guys are just…
Wake up, Mr. Slowy!
Something’s not right.
Bring that weird fruit over here,
along with my encyclopedia.
Oh no, this is the slumber fruit!
We’ve really been poisoned!
What in the world is the slumber fruit?
What happens if you’re poisoned by it?
Once poisoned, you could fall asleep at any time.
If you don’t take the antidote within two hours,
you’ll never wake up!
Never wake up?
No wonder Wolffy just disappeared without saying a word.
He was actually waiting for us to all fall asleep
so he could catch us easily!
Why don’t I feel anything?
The book says that we’ll be fine
if we quickly drink the juice from the juice pond.
So the juice was actually from the juice pond?
Then let’s hurry up and go to the juice pond!
Being poisoned, we could all fall asleep at any time.
Therefore, the goats who are awake must look after everybody.
Look after everybody?
I can’t handle such an important task!
What should I do?
Oh right, I can just pretend to sleep!
Guys,
Paddi has already fallen asleep from the poison!
The rest of us have to be more alert!
Great, everyone is very alert!
I can keep sleeping!
Turn on the camouflage setting right now, Jonie!
What now? Jonie fell asleep!
Tibbie, get on top!
We made it!
You’re amazing, Tibbie!
Sparky, too?
Tibbie and Sparky both fell asleep!
What now?
Oh no!
Watch this!
Weslie is still the most reliable one.
The train is coming! Why aren’t you getting out of the way?
In three seconds, the slumber fruit’s poison will hit its peak.
The train will automatically stop—
Let’s go, Weslie!
Weslie, what happened?
Weslie, is this how you’ve kept going?
Weslie, you can’t sleep!
Wake up, wake up!
If you don’t take the antidote within two hours,
you’ll never wake up!
The goats who are awake must look after everybody.
I’m still awake.
I need to have courage in taking on responsibilities
and looking after everybody!
Magic Trains,
go!
I, Paddi, can still look after everyone on my own!
Why isn’t the train moving?
What now?
Don’t move!
Put your hands in the air and surrender!
All done!
Paddi is missing!
Paddi is such a scaredy-cat.
He even left behind his friends and ran away by himself!
Now, all I have to do is to capture Paddi,
and the Energy Seed will be mine!
Why’d they wake up?
That’s not possible!
If poisoned by the slumber fruit, they can’t wake up without the antidote!
What’s going on?
Where’s Paddi?
Paddi has already left you guys behind and run away!
Nonsense! Paddi would never do that!
Believe it or don’t, your choice.
That must be Paddi coming to save us!
I’ll capture him!
Careful!
It might be a trap; wait for a moment.
Is no one here to receive the parcel?
Aren’t these the fruits that Madam Wolnie bought?
No one’s home.
Wait!
It smells so good; try it!
Not bad!
Let’s see what kind of fruits our Wolnie bought.
Wolffy!
Paddi!
I’m here to surrender.
So you’ve sent yourself to my door!
What’s this?
Are these the fruits that Madam Wolnie bought to eat with mutton?
Of course!
My Wolnie loves to eat that!
A slumber fruit!
Get back here, little goats!
Chasing us will delay you getting the antidote!
You’re amazing, Paddi!
Thank you!
You’re a hero!
You’re such a good kid!
You—
Hey, don’t sleep!
Paddi’s very tired; let’s let him sleep for a while.
END