Marching to the New Wonderland
Motion Sickness
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Tibbie, just wait and see!
We did it! Wasn’t that amazing?
Tibbie, you’re incredible!
Aww, thank you…
Stop messing around! Wolffy’s about to catch up to us!
I’ll get rid of you!
Watch this!
Wolffy’s caught up to us!
Now’s my chance!
Goodbye, Wolffy!
We’re safe now!
Why is everyone motion sick?
Why did you hit the emergency brake, Wolnie?
I was just about to catch the goats!
How can you care about catching goats when our son is this sick?
I don’t want to ride a train ever again, Daddy.
Son!
I don’t want to ride the train!
These symptoms…
It seems to me that…
Wilie…
is sick.
Is that not obvious?
From what I see,
he’s suffering from a paralysis
of the nerve center due to an excessive release of bioelectric currents
from the ear vestibule balance receptors.
What kind of illness is that? Is it serious?
It’s not serious; he’s just motion sick.
I already knew that! I don’t need you to tell me!
In order to cure motion sickness,
just use the shimmerfruit from the nine-turn spiraling branch.
Son, Daddy is going to grab it for you!
No!
I don’t want to ride the train!
Okay, okay… Mommy will take you elsewhere to play.
We won’t ride the train.
Hurry up, Wolffy!
Also, shimmerfruits…
only work if two are used together.
Mr. Slowy’s encyclopedia must have a fix.
Only the shimmerfruit can cure everyone’s motion sickness?
This terrain is so hard to get past.
Even Sirius can’t handle it.
If only I had a vehicle that was better suited for cleaning up the way.
Hear me out, Tibbie!
Truth is, I just want to capture you!
I’d like to collaborate with you!
Wait, Tibbie!
Tibbie, I’m begging you!
I sincerely ask you for your help!
Please see the honesty in my eyes!
Don’t go!
Wolffy!
Our son is getting more and more motion sick!
Daddy…
Son,
no matter what,
Daddy is going to get a shimmerfruit for you!
Wolffy.
I… I’ll collaborate with you,
so we can get shimmerfruits.
I must get shimmerfruits as fast as I can!
Daddy won’t be long, Wilie!
Tibbie, if you’re making the road, why aren’t you driving faster?
Can’t you drive slower?
So now you’re arguing with me!
Go, Lightning Angel!
Stop!
Let me make the road instead!
Wolffy!
Do you know how to drive or not?
What are you talking about?
You’re the one being clumsy!
It’s all your fault
that after all this time,
I still haven’t been able to get shimmerfruits to save my friends!
You’re the one being so slow!
Lightning Angel!
Alright, alright, don’t cry.
I’ll go fix Lightning Angel for you.
Thank you.
The trains are all fixed!
Now, let’s get on our way!
Okay!
Darn, I can’t dodge it!
Tibbie…
You…
We said we’d help each other out.
Alright! Then King Wolffy shall help you out as well!
We’re finally here!
Shimmerfruits!
I’ve got a shimmerfruit, Tibbie.
I’m going back to save my son!
Wait!
Son, you won’t be motion sick anymore
once you eat this shimmerfruit.
What in the world did you make our son eat?
Just a shimmerfruit!
Maybe he didn’t eat enough?
Son, have a few more bites.
Give Wilie back to me!
Son!
Wolffy, wait!
Don’t mistake me for a dog
if I don’t show off my wolf powers!
Careful, cannonballs! Activate the shield!
Give me back my son right now!
He’s motion sick and can’t ride trains!
Give back my son!
Otherwise, I won’t be sorry!
Daddy!
Son?
Son, are you okay now?
What are you wearing?
Shimmerfruits!
Sister Tibbie gave them to me.
Mr. Slowy’s encyclopedia states
that shimmerfruits are worn on the ears,
and two are required to work.
If it’s eaten, it’ll make the symptoms worse.
So you were just trying to help Wilie when…
Tibbie, I misunderstood.
You can’t run from me!
Daddy!
Look, Daddy! I won’t get motion sick anymore!
Look, Mommy, look!
I’m giving you guys ten minutes to run away.
Counting down now!
Ten minutes? That’s not enough.
How about an hour?
I think we should get at least a day.
Three days isn’t so bad!
Stop fooling around! Delivering the Seed is our priority!
Depart now!
Yes.
Wolffy’s actually quite a good dad.
END