Marching to the New Wonderland
General Manager’s Good Friday
You can’t win with just one train!
Not so fast!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Together, we’re six!
It’s not too late for you to give up!
This isn’t fair!
I only have one train, but you guys have six!
Wolffy, I’m coming!
Daddy!
Where there’s family, there is love!
I have helpers now, too!
Cake!
My parcel is here; I’ll go receive it.
So this is the price of love?
Now’s our chance! Attack!
To commemorate our one hundredth time of defeating Wolffy,
I’m treating everybody to sour prune drinks!
Sour prune drinks are my favorite!
Where is it?
Here.
Well, actually, the parcel hasn’t arrived yet.
I’ll help you urge for it!
Thank goodness the train didn’t roll over.
Do not
block
the path of the general manager!
How rude! If you keep it up, I’ll—
I’ll—
I’ll treat you all to candy.
The general manager is here!
If only I had that many followers.
Then I’d definitely be able to catch all of the goats.
General manager,
this cell phone is the symbol of your supreme power.
You better not lose it.
The cell phone is the symbol of supreme power?
Aha!
Hand over your cell phone!
You’re alone right now, so don’t even think about resisting!
I’m just kidding!
Hold on.
This is the cell phone you want, right?
I… I really was just joking.
Joking is not allowed!
From now on, Wolffy is the general manager.
What?
Where are you going?
I’ve been wanting to take a vacation for so long.
I’m going to vacation at the Bee Hotel!
Goodbye!
Don’t go!
General manager, the goats are here to expedite their parcel.
Out of my way!
Wait…
What did you call me?
General manager.
According to the regulations, whoever possesses the golden cellphone
is the general manager.
I’ve finally done it!
Who did you just say was coming to expedite their parcel?
The goats.
This is perfect!!
Give it to him good!
I meant for you to show him your true colors!
Yes, sir!
Here are different colors of parcel notes; take a look.
Thank you!
But I’m here today because I want to expedite my parcel.
No problem!
We’ll help you follow up.
I’ll do it myself!
General manager, these are all expedited express parcels.
According to the regulations,
you must sort all of them out by the end of today.
Being the general manager is so hard!
Why are you on my train?
General manager, I wanted to chat with you.
According to the regulations,
the general manager has the responsibility
of channeling the employees’ mental stress.
Leave me alone!
Work has been more and more boring recently.
I just do the same stuff every day,
day after day,
year after year,
one day bleeds into another,
slowly… slowly losing feeling.
I’m unable to feel even the littlest warmth.
This is how my life passes by.
Chatting with you felt so good, general manager!
Thank you!
You’re welcome. Can I sleep now?
Of course!
Please rest.
What now?
It’s time to go to work, general manager.
I just knew you’d be here!
General manager, something happened at the firm.
Please return immediately.
I’m not your general manager!
Your general manager is over there!
No, you’re our general manager now!
Auntie Ant, I’ve finally found you!
How long until my parcel will arrive?
Right now, I just want to take my vacation peacefully.
Put on some exciting music!
I’ll just go to the headquarters to complain.
Would you like any more services?
Do you guys have any files for me to sort out?
I’m very sorry; we don’t have files that need to be sorted out.
I actually feel quite uncomfortable not having files to finish.
My parcel! My parcel!
Oh my goodness!
How did it get this bad?
When work efficiency is low, the parcels pile up.
But I finished every last thing before leaving yesterday!
Yeah, that was yesterday’s work.
—Who’s in charge?　—Who’s the manager?
I have a complaint!
Wolffy?
Where’s my weight loss medicine?
I was so worried that I only ate five bowls of rice for lunch!
Where’s my parcel also?
Mine, too!
And my sour prune drink!
Wolffy!
I’m busy right now, Wolnie.
Can we talk about catching goats later?
Forget the goats!
Get my parcel back home by today,
or else!
My parcel! My parcel!
My parcel! Where’s my parcel?
Fine!
There’s nothing in this world that I, Wolffy, cannot do!
You’re incredible, general manager!
Incredible!
Amazing!
In that case, no one minds working an extra shift for me, do they?
Let’s go catch some goats!
Okay!
I’ve got so many ants now, Weslie.
There’s still time for you to hand over the Energy Seed!
Why hasn’t Paddi come back from getting the package yet?
Without him, the Magic Trains can’t assemble!
I’ve got thousands of men!
Are you even comparable?
Being the general manager is so cool!
Thank you for your hard work!
I’ve decided that I don’t actually like the vacation life.
Return and process parcels!
Yes, ma’am!
Let me be the general manager for just one more second!
I’ll be back!
I got the sour prune drink!
My sour prune drink!
END