Marching to the New Wonderland
The Father–Son Bond
Why am I shorter than I was yesterday?
Justice Spider!
Justice Spider, the goats are up to no good again!
Come teach them a lesson with me!
I don’t feel like it today. Let’s do it another day.
But they’re making fun of you being short everywhere.
Short?
I wanted to stop them,
but I got bullied instead!
How dare they talk about someone behind their back!
Disgusting!
Daddy!
Come play with me!
Wilie?
Are you the one Daddy talks about?
Uncle Justice “Shorty” Spider?
You’re not actually that short!
Don’t blame Wilie; he doesn’t know better.
So it was you, Wolffy, who was talking about me behind my back!
I won’t forgive you!
Daddy!
Wilie!
“The Greatest Love.”
How should I write this essay?
Where’d this cocoon come from?
Let me out! Let me out!
Wilie?
Daddy, I’m coming to save you!
Wilie,
what are you doing here?
Where’s your dad?
Sister Tibbie,
Justice Spider captured my dad!
I have to go rescue him!
Wolffy’s been captured?
It’s too dangerous for you to go alone.
Let’s think of another way.
I’m going to go save Daddy right now!
Give me the map; I’ll go save him for you.
Really?
I’ll… I’ll look around.
Trying to keep me tied up?
Justice Spider, release Wolffy!
If not… If not, I’ll—
You broke down my door!
Don’t… Don’t come near me!
Since you’re here now, don’t even think about leaving!
Daddy!
You’re home!
Of course I am!
I’m the world’s greatest hero!
Daddy,
did you see sister Tibbie at all?
Uh…
No, I… I didn’t.
She promised to help me find you.
I’ll go save him for you.
What if she’s only just found the spider den?
I’m going to go find her!
Wilie!
Let Daddy do these kinds of dangerous tasks instead.
Oh, right!
Put this on, Daddy!
Now, Daddy is truly the greatest hero!
The greatest hero must rescue sister Tibbie!
It’s too dangerous; I shouldn’t go.
Besides, no one will know.
Excuse me, please!
If you’re not going in, don’t block the path.
What are you—
Be quiet. Just say that you haven’t seen me.
You should be gentler when feeding pine nuts to others.
Thank goodness Wilie isn’t here.
I’ve got you!
Daddy,
did you rescue sister Tibbie?
Of… Of course I did!
Daddy is the greatest hero!
When I grow up, I want to be just like Daddy!
I want to be a real hero, too!
Justice Spider is always “helping.”
You’d better be careful if you ever see him.
Exactly.
He doesn’t apologize for his “help,” not to mention how mean he is!
Who would dare disturb him?
My dad, the world’s greatest hero,
is never afraid of him!
He just saved Tibbie from his hands a while ago!
For real?
Justice Spider is so strong.
Can Wolffy defeat him?
Of course! Daddy wouldn’t lie to me!
Daddy, Daddy!
Tell them how you defeated Justice Spider!
The situation was very urgent.
Justice Spider wanted to harm Tibbie.
So, I jumped onto him,
and I held down his pair of legs!
Hold on!
Justice Spider has so many pairs of legs.
Which pair did you hold down?
Which pair?
I forgot.
Don’t get too hung up on the details.
After that, I used a frying pan!
Is a frying pan useful?
Justice Spider has practiced iron head Kung Fu.
You don’t even know that fact,
yet you say that you defeated Justice Spider?
It seems to me that you haven’t even gone to the spider den.
I can confirm that Wolffy did, in fact, go to the spider den.
Did he really defeat Justice Spider?
You know what you should say, Andy.
What happened back there?
I have a lot of pine nuts!
I saw Wolffy…
run away from the spider den.
Didn’t you say that we shouldn’t lie to people, Daddy!
You don’t mean what you say!
Daddy’s a liar!
I just knew that you weren’t telling the truth!
Liar! Liar!
Pants on fire!
Wilie? Wilie!
Your son is much braver than you.
He’s gone to the spider den himself.
Son!
Where in the world is sister Tibbie?
Isn’t that…
It’s Tibbie’s bow!
Complete!
What’s that sound?
Justice Spider, show yourself!
Release my son right now,
or else!
Or else what?
Or else I…
Or else I won’t get up!
Son?
Now you see how powerful I am, no?
Son!
Are you scared now? Don’t anger me next time!
Son, I’m glad that you’re okay.
I don’t want to talk to Daddy the liar.
Alright, alright. I promise I won’t lie ever again.
Wilie, your dad is promising to never lie again.
Don’t be mad anymore.
Right, right. I’ll never tell a lie again.
Daddy!
Son!
Look, Wolffy!
I just bought these new elevator shoes.
Don’t I look so much taller and more majestic when wearing them?
Yes, yes…
—very tall.　—Daddy,
you’re not lying again this time, are you?
Taller… but how tall can you be?
You’ve gone too far, Wolffy!
Have a taste of my great gymnastics swing!
Help me!
It turns out that a good parent
will do anything for their child!
I know what to write for “The Greatest Love” now!
END