Marching to the New Wonderland
No More Passengers
The only route to the Big Tree’s Summit
contains a bottomless chasm.
Every year, at noon on the fifth of May,
a beautiful flower blooms in the chasm,
bridging the two ends.
This is the story of the Mayflower Bridge.
On this day,
the Tree World’s insects will gather here
to celebrate this annual event.
The Mayflower’s blooming period is very short,
so we must get to the Mayflower Bridge as fast as possible.
The festival is going to be so much fun!
And there’ll be lots of food to eat!
We’re crossing the bridge to get to the Summit,
not to participate in the festival!
What happens if we don’t cross the bridge?
We’ll have to wait another year to cross.
Then let’s pick up our speed!
Yes, full speed!
Do not stop the train!
Jonie, what did you stop the train for?
Thank you for giving me a ride.
Goodbye!
Jonie!
We have priorities!
Right now, our priority is going as fast as we can!
Do not stop the train to pick up more passengers!
I understand.
Let me be the head train!
The Mayflower Bridge that only appears once a year?
How romantic!
Sadly, it only blooms for half a day.
I don’t think I’ll get to see it.
Don’t you worry, Wolnie.
I’ll make sure that you get to see the Mayflower Bridge!
But the traffic jam is this bad.
Watch this!
Sit tight, Wolnie!
Pay for my damages right now—
You’re brilliant, Wolffy!
In this world, there are some things you can’t imagine,
but nothing that I can’t do for you!
I want to see the Mayflower!
Don’t worry, I’m finding a solution!
Jonie, come here for a second.
Could you give me a ride?
For the sake of our progress, I can’t carry more passengers.
Fine.
Mr. Slowy only said that we can’t stop the train.
He didn’t say that I can’t pick up others.
Thank you!
You’ve got a lot of luggage,
but it shouldn’t be a problem.
Mr. Slowy?
To help speed up the train,
we’re traveling lightweight!
Dump all of your unnecessary things!
Alright.
Jonie, do you have any more—
No, no, I don’t!
What’s the matter, Jonie?
I’ve been eating a lot recently.
I need to exercise!
I saw it already!
Look up here!
I told you that we have to travel lightweight,
yet you guys hid so much stuff behind my back!
Mr. Slowy is right.
I’ll go throw this stuff out.
Hold on.
Have I been caught?
I trust you, Jonie.
Dump out this clutter, too.
Mr. Slowy won’t let us carry others.
Just stay here.
You must not wander around, okay?
Jonie, you’re so kind!
Could we also pick up my little brother on the way?
I really can’t.
We can’t add any more weight here.
My brother is very light. Please help us out!
Fine.
Yay!
My brothers will definitely thank you!
Brother… s?
Hold on!
How many brothers do you have?
Not many, just one hundred or so.
One hundred or so?
Are you finished yet?
The Mayflower is blooming soon.
It’s fixed!
We’re missing a screw. No matter what, it can’t be fixed.
Wolnie, we might not be able to see the Mayflower.
Mayflower…
If I can’t see the Mayflower,
perhaps the moonflower diamond ring can make it up for me.
Wolnie, don’t rush!
There’ll be a way!
Awesome! Our big brother found us a ride!
Come with me!
Why are people still giving rides at this time?
Could it be the goats?
Wolnie, I have a solution!
We’ll catch goats and see the Mayflower at the same time!
Hello, please get in line.
Do you, little bug, know who I am?
Who are you?
Go on.
Actually, I’m a model young man who loves to follow rules and queue up!
Goodbye!
Come on in.
Don’t leave me behind!
We’re too full! We can’t carry any more people!
I’m sorry!
It’s alright.
All of my brothers have already gotten on board.
I don’t recognize that ladybug.
I’m sorry, we really don’t have any more room!
Wait for another ride!
The screw!
66th brother, is that you?
What a coincidence, 55th brother!
Are we at full power, Weslie?
We’re already at the highest power.
Why are we going even slower than before?
What in the world is wrong, Jonie?
I…
My foot is itchy! Can you scratch it for me?
Jonie, did you—
I’m sorry! I saw that they were struggling,
so I decided to help them!
You’re right.
If we dismiss other peoples’ needs
for the purpose of going faster,
then we might as well not deserve to deliver the Energy Seed at all.
But, Mr. Slowy…
It’s okay. There’ll always be a way.
Sit tight, everyone. We’re still traveling!
We’re home!
Thank you all!
Goodbye!
Goodbye, everybody!
The Mayflower…
already wilted.
We can’t cross the bridge all because I slowed us down.
I’m sorry.
Don’t worry. There must be another path we can take.
Hurricane’s detection abilities are top-notch.
I should definitely be able to help!
Us, too!
You guys…
There’s no time to lose; let’s hurry and find a new route.
Okay!
We still didn’t make it on time.
Wolnie, don’t be upset!
I’ll catch some goats for you; that’s just as romantic!
Get on the trains!
Hurry, get in!
I’ll put down a dragnet.
We’ll see if you can escape!
Mr. Slowy, what do we do now?
Sister Jonie,
let us help you this time.
They’re making a bridge so we can cross!
Thank you guys!
Alright! Magic Trains, onward!
Stop!
Hey, I haven’t crossed yet!
Thank you all! Goodbye!
Goodbye, everyone!
END