Marching to the New Wonderland
Staying at the Hotel
How in the world am I supposed to get the Energy Seed?
My necklace!
I’ll clean it for you!
Absolutely not!
This is very valuable!
Waiter, keep this safe for me.
Right, I can get the Energy Seed this way!
But without collecting the goats’ handprints,
I can’t open the safe box.
Madam, if you are satisfied with our services,
please give us a positive review.
Alright.
This way, I can open the box!
What is this?
The bill? Is it this much?
I’d like this… and this, too…
We’re very happy with your services,
so I’d like to thank all of your employees
face-to-face!
May I?
Sure.
In order to thank all of you,
I’ll treat all of you to a good nap!
I’m so sleepy…
This hotel is now mine!
Luxury five-star hotel!
Five-star hotel, 50% off!
50% off!
Five-star hotel!
Complimentary stay!
Three meals included!
Is it really complimentary? We’ll stay, we’ll stay!
Get away from me!
It’s only complimentary for goats!
What? It’s only complimentary for goats?
How come?
Is a stay actually free?
Of course it is!
Then let’s check in; we should charge the Magic Trains, too.
No problem! Thank you for coming!
Why is this waiter acting so weird?
Let me help carry your luggage!
No thanks, we’ve got it already.
It’s fine; I can get the handprints first.
I’ve finally done it!
Dear guests,
our food is complimentary.
No thanks. We already have food.
You carry luggage yourselves and bring food yourselves?
Then I, a waiter, have no job!
We still have some luggage that you can help us carry.
Plus, there’s a lot of it, and it’s very heavy!
Not a problem! No matter how much, I’ll carry it!
This is too much!
I’ve finished. Would you mind giving a positive review?
I’m so hungry; do you have any food?
There’s no food! Go away!
Don’t be upset; I didn’t mean it that way.
Our hotel is already out of ingredients,
so you better go to a different place to eat.
Why run a hotel if there’s nothing to eat?
If they don’t take the easy way, I’ll give them the hard way!
The goats are all asleep.
Now’s my chance to get their handprints and steal the Seed!
Just a minor trick.
Who’d have thought I’d get caught the moment I come in?
Thank goodness you’re here.
Have the pillow fight with them for me, would you?
My poor waist can’t take it any more.
No problem! Accompanying eating and playing
are also within our job responsibilities.
I’ll capture all of you during the pillow fight!
Pillows don’t have eyes! Don’t blame me if you get hurt!
I haven’t had this much fun in a long time!
While this waiter is kind of weird,
his services aren’t too bad!
Since everyone is satisfied,
could you guys give me a good review?
Sure!
Finally, I have the handprints—
I mean, positive reviews!
Thank you guys!
But I still can’t do anything if I can’t get the seed!
I can’t believe it!
If that’s all, I’ll head out for now. Enjoy your time here!
What a wonderful waiter!
After this step,
I’ll get to access the Energy Seed with unlimited vital energy!
Little goats, you’ve bullied me for so many episodes.
It’s time for revenge!
Out of my way!
You guys are so annoying!
Can’t you let me get stronger in peace?
It’s you guys?
That’s right.
It’s our time for revenge.
Uh… Guys, I can explain.
Do you think explaining is going to help?
I’d better get out of here!
He’s over there!
Help me!
The Seed was just here yesterday; why is it gone now?
Search carefully, guys.
Dear guests,
it’s time to check out.
Please pack your items.
Yay! Here it is!
Thank you!
You must stay and compensate for your actions.
Seriously?
You’re truly a wonderful waiter; keep it up!
We’re leaving now; goodbye!
Don’t leave!
Next time, prepare some more food,
so customers won’t leave.
My food is you!
Since you’ve gone AWOL, you’re punished for three more days.
I’ll be back!
END