Marching to the New Wonderland
Born To Be Useful
Paddi has been gathering food for such a long time.
Why isn’t he back yet?
Let me go check.
Mr. Slowy, I—
Forget it.
Just be in charge of watching the Energy Seed today.
The rest of us will quickly go and gather food.
Let’s start.
Alright, Mr. Slowy.
I just overslept, is all.
I smell chocolate!
This time, I’ll definitely gather a lot of food!
There’re so many fruits!
They’re choco-fruits!
There’s no food over here, Mr. Slowy.
Let’s go back and search somewhere else.
When it comes to gathering food, I’m the best!
The Energy Seed?
Paddi!
I forgot to bring the Energy Seed with me.
The Energy Seed is so important.
How could I forget about it?
I’m useless.
But you’re very useful to me!
Wolffy!
Trying to run?
This is outrageous! Parking on a highway?
That wasn’t so hard!
Why has Paddi been out there for so long?
We have to leave soon!
He just got told off,
so he might be reflecting on himself.
Fixing mistakes is correct.
I think I should go look for him, Mr. Slowy.
You have a parcel!
Please sign for it, Weslie.
It’s for me?
“Exchange the Energy Seed for Paddi.
“—Wolffy.”
Paddi’s been captured!
Let’s hurry and rescue Paddi!
Hold on.
Without Paddi’s Hurricane,
the Magic Trains’ fighting power
can’t defeat Wolffy’s Sirius.
Does that mean…
Does that mean we have to trade the Energy Seed for Paddi?
But...
we promised Grandpa Beetle
that we would deliver the Energy Seed to save the Big Tree World.
But we can’t not save Paddi!
It’s what we’ve got to do.
Where’s the ransom?
It’s here.
Where’s Paddi?
He’s here.
Are you okay, Paddi?
Paddi can really fall asleep wherever.
Cut the nonsense. Give me the Energy Seed!
I’ve finally gotten the Energy Seed!
Wolffy, release Paddi right now!
Why would I release a goat I’ve caught?
Is that Wolnie?
Wolnie?
Weslie!
Officer Snail?
How dare you attack me, Wolffy!
You are a terrible person!
What are you guys doing here?
Where’s Wolffy?
What happened?
This is what happened…
You illegally parked in the middle of the highway.
I’m just parking for a little bit.
Just let it slide this time.
No!
You two keep chatting! I have to go!
Come back here!
You may not leave. Move your vehicle immediately!
Good thing I have a spare!
Help me!
What are you going to do?
You ruined my plan.
Now, I must use you to trade for the Energy Seed!
If I see Wolffy again,
I’m going to teach him a big lesson!
What? Did you say that Paddi fell off of the branch?
That’s not good!
Let’s hurry and find him!
That was so dangerous. Thank goodness…
Sirius?
Why am I this unlucky?
Outrageous!
They traded me a juice ball in exchange for Paddi!
I can’t hold on anymore!
Paddi, what a coincidence!
Where are you, Paddi?
Paddi!
Paddi is in my hands!
Hand over the real Energy Seed, now!
We’re not falling for this again!
Don’t pay attention to him; just look for Paddi!
Look, who’s this?
Help me! Help me!
Wolffy actually captured Paddi this time!
What do you want, Wolffy?
Hand over the actual Energy Seed,
and I’ll release him immediately!
Alright.
Give him the Energy Seed, Weslie.
The Energy Seed is right here!
Let Paddi go!
The Energy Seed is gone. I’m sorry!
It’s alright; we’re glad that you’re okay.
I’ve finally gotten the Energy Seed!
Wolnie will get to stay young forever,
and I’ll get to rule the world!
Mr. Wolffy, have you forgotten?
Without our handprints,
you can’t open the Energy Seed’s safe box!
Oh, you’re right!
Then I’ll capture every single one of you!
What do we do?
Assemble!
Just forget it and give your handprints
to the safe box!
What now?
Run!
What do I do? Everyone’s been captured!
Is that a…? Aha!
Let’s see if you can escape!
The Energy Seed is mine and so are the goats!
Mr. Wolffy,
have you forgotten about Paddi?
That little fatso?
You think he can save you guys?
Fatso?
What are you doing?
Paddi!
I’ll be back!
The Energy Seed!
We couldn’t find the Energy Seed.
How do we explain to Professor Beetle
that we lost the Energy Seed?
I’m sorry. It’s all my fault.
Wait a minute, I smell fruit juice!
We found the Seed!
Thank you, Paddi!
It turns out that I am kind of useful!
Paddi, you’re amazing!
There you are! Come with me right this instant!
END