Marching to the New Wonderland
The Magical Snail Shell
Looks like Mr. Slowy and the others should be here soon.
Why isn’t Mr. Slowy here yet?
If I delivered the Seed by myself, I’d be at the Summit already.
You have vandalized our traffic facilities.
I didn’t, Officer Snail!
Look at the traffic lights.
Now come inside with me to get educated.
Inside?
It’s so small here.
So this is the inside of the snail shell?
Stay here and reflect on your mistakes.
This place is so fun!
Please exit.
Already? I haven’t even started reflecting yet.
Let me stay for a little longer!
No. As the traffic captain,
I always abide by the law.
Fine. I’ll head out, then.
Thunderbolt!
You park recklessly and vandalize buildings?
You must be educated deeply and discreetly!
Okay! I’m willing to be educated!
This lesson will last for one year!
One year?
How can I help deliver the Energy Seed
if my lesson lasts for that long?
What do I do now?
Mr. Slowy will worry if he can’t find me.
I have to get out of here!
Who knew it’d be this simple?
Trying to hold me down? I’ll just drag it with me.
It’s so heavy.
It’s Mr. Slowy and the others!
If they were to see me like this…
I can’t let anyone see me like this!
What are you sitting here for, Weslie?
What took you guys so long?
You drive too fast; we can’t keep up with you.
Then this time, you guys drive first, and I’ll rest for a bit.
I’ll catch up soon!
Weslie, why are you carrying a snail shell?
Uh… I feel like I always run too fast,
so I got a snail shell to slow me down!
But are you even able to run still?
Of course I am! Watch closely!
Don’t worry, guys; I’m usually on my train, anyway.
I won’t be walking.
Weslie, just tell us what the deal is with your snail shell.
I broke the rules, and Officer Snail is making me self-reflect in the shell.
Breaking the rules does indeed require self-reflection afterwards.
How long do you need to reflect for?
A year.
That long?
That’s why you guys should just go ahead.
Delivering the Energy Seed is a lot more important!
Weslie…
Everyone must have departed by now.
The dolls can speak?
It’s me! This entrance is way too small.
So the shell’s inside is really this big!
You guys…
Missed us?
How could we leave you behind?
We’re all united!
Correct. We’re all in one family.
No matter what, we stick together!
The wind up here is way too strong!
Wolffy is getting closer to us!
How far away is he?
He’s right in front of us!
Hand over the Energy Seed!
Otherwise, you’ll get a taste of my laser cannonballs!
My ammunition needs changing?
Now’s our chance! Run!
What just happened?
Wolffy?
I’m over here!
Let me help you!
What a hard shell!
Come and get me!
You darn Weslie!
I’ll deal with you later.
I’m going to chase the rest of the goats first!
Oh no, Mr. Slowy and the others are in danger!
I have to go save them!
I’m way too slow. What should I do?
Wolffy, you’re speeding!
Who knew that the snail shell could be used like that?
Grandma, I’ll help you cross the road.
Yes, thank you!
Thank goodness we’ve outrun Wolffy.
Oh no!
Mr. Slowy, Weslie is missing!
What should we do, Mr. Slowy?
Oh no!
It’s Wolffy!
Hand over the Energy Seed right now!
Get on the trains!
Activate the shield!
Watch this!
The shield… isn’t strong enough!
Scared, huh?
Start up the Magic Trains’ highest power!
Mr. Slowy,
without Weslie,
there’s no way to activate the Magic Trains’ highest power!
I’ll have you taste an even stronger power!
Weslie?
Weslie’s done it!
Why is it you again?
We’ll see how much you can really take!
That’s if you can strike me!
Well, you’re quick!
Watch my last hit!
Darn it, I’m out of cannonballs!
Then it’s our turn to attack!
Just you wait!
I’ll be back!
I want to go back on Thunderbolt.
Why… Why are you guys here?
Mr. Slowy decided.
Since you can’t get on the train,
then we won’t, either.
We’ll bring all our luggage in,
and we’ll live together with you in the snail shell,
delivering the Seed on foot.
In short, we’ll always stick together!
It’s all my fault!
I’ve trapped the rest of you in this shell with me!
It seems that you already understand your mistakes.
You have completed the goal of this education.
I suppose I’ll let you go early.
Yay!
Thank you!
Don’t hug me.
I still have to chase Wolffy!
I missed catching him last time, as I was helping a grandma cross the road!
He won’t be so lucky this time!
Wolffy’s in trouble!
END