Marching to the New Wonderland
Soaring Over the Waterfall
Mr. Slowy, what should we do now?
Tibbie,
use your Lightning Angel and create a tunnel
that we can cross though.
Got it!
Mr. Slowy, Lightning Angel can’t get through!
I don’t have enough power!
I know!
What now?
Don’t worry. I’ll definitely think of something.
Grandpa Beetle!
Weslie, what do you need?
We accidentally broke a dew pool
while we were clearing the branch.
The water escaped from the inside
and turned into a huge waterfall.
How do we cross the waterfall?
Cross the waterfall?
I was once plagued by this question as well.
How did you end up resolving it?
At that time, I stayed up ten days and ten nights analyzing.
I came up with 81 different ways to cross the falls.
That’s incredible!
But all of them failed.
Now, hold on. If you can’t cross the falls,
you can patch the hole.
But the hole is so big.
How can we patch it?
With honey.
Honey?
They’re looking for honey?
As long as we’re sincere,
they’ll definitely lend us some honey!
I’m not so sure about that.
Calm down; we have good intentions!
Brother Weslie,
why did you crash into our hotel?
I’m sorry! I’ll fix it.
Oh, yeah.
We accidentally punctured a dew pool,
and we’d like to borrow some of your honey to patch the hole.
I see.
My mom says that protecting nature
is everyone’s responsibility.
You can back off and let them get some honey.
Thank you, Your Highness!
Stop them!
They want to steal our honey!
No, we don’t!
What’s going on?
What now, Weslie?
Your Highness, we don’t have much time.
I’ll explain to you later!
Come on!
Look, Weslie!
That bee is Wolffy in disguise!
Let’s get out of here first!
I’m sorry!
I’ve got it!
If we use honey to fix the hole,
we can pass through!
Weslie and Paddi have already gone to get it.
We found honey!
That fast?
Bring out the honey, Paddi!
Wasn’t the honey with you?
What?
We lost the honey.
There’s honey on the wheels!
It must have gotten stuck when we were at the Bee Hotel!
We can fix the hole now!
Not yet!
Why not?
Honey is just the glue.
We also need other materials.
What other materials?
Petals, leaves, and brushes.
That’s easy!
Let’s hurry and gather materials!
Hold on!
It’s important that we stop the water flow
before we can continue repairing the pool.
However, it seems that this is not quite feasible…
Mr. Slowy, why didn’t you say so earlier?
Aha!
Don’t worry, everyone!
I have an idea!
Are you all ready?
We’re ready, Mr. Slowy!
Good.
Begin!
Go ahead, Sparky!
You guys have got to hold on.
Oh no, we’re flooding!
All fixed!
We did it! We did it!
This time, we lost a lot of time.
Let’s hurry and leave.
Brother Weslie,
I can’t believe that you’re a honey-stealing goat!
Your Highness, please let me explain!
Do you really think
that our own Mighty would frame you?
Within our bee colony,
he’s the most, most trustworthy bee of us all!
They just want to steal our honey!
Work together to capture them right now!
Don’t trust him, Your Highness!
He’s Wolffy in disguise!
They’re framing me!
Your Highness…
Why is there another Mighty?
Earlier…
I saw a strange-looking flower.
I didn’t realize until later
that it was a trap.
Stop right there!
That’s right!
I am Wolffy!
No matter what,
Weslie,
you guys cannot escape my grasp!
Sirius!
I’ll be back!
Your Highness!
Thank you, brother Weslie!
What do we do now, Mr. Slowy?
Brother Weslie…
All of us bees will help you repair the dew pool!
Your Highness,
thank you for helping us patch the dew pool.
We must leave now.
Wait.
You haven’t fixed our damaged hotel yet.
I’ll do it immediately!
END