Marching to the New Wonderland
Rescuing Justice Spider
Wait!
You have to be careful to not step on flowers.
Jonie is so careful.
She even notices that kind of stuff!
From now on, I also want to protect flowers.
Then you’ll have to cherish me well!
Me, too!
We’ve been surrounded!
I’m going to finish you, evil goats!
We’ll definitely capture you all today!
Looks like Sparky is more specialized in emergency treatment.
Sparky, Justice Spider is—
This spider is far too despicable! I’ll get rid of him next time!
He hates Justice Spider that much?
He definitely won’t help me!
Oh, it’s Jonie? Did you need anything?
Never mind!
Don’t mind me…
What’s up with Jonie?
The spiders are appearing!
It’s up to you to defeat them!
Got it!
Right, I can ask Weslie for help!
I’ll help, too!
Let’s smack the spiders together!
Okay!
Looks like I have to rely on myself.
What is this place?
Who tied me up?
It’s the group of evil goats.
I can’t believe she captured other spiders, too!
This eight-legged herb looks a lot like a spider.
She’s cooking the spider?
These eight-legged herbs will help his injuries.
What should I do?
You’ll heal up after eating this bowl of soup.
What now?
Goodness, she’s making me eat spider soup!
Help me!
It’s so bitter!
Aha!
You must not like bitter tastes.
Here, you don’t have to worry anymore.
Thank goodness I escaped. That was terrifying!
My injuries…
…are all healed?
Could it be… that Jonie helped me?
Justice Spider, I was just about to go rescue you!
I guess you’ve already escaped!
Rescue me?
I saw Jonie capture you.
She did, in fact, capture me,
but she also helped treat me.
She—?
Treating your injuries must have been for her to injure you again,
then treat you again, injure you again,
and then treat you again, and then injure you again!
This is how she’ll obscenely torture you!
Outrageous! I can’t believe she’s that evil!
Put this on the Magic Train.
Once the clock ticks…
Alright!
No rush!
I must teach her a lesson this time!
Justice Spider?
How familiar…
Why am I here again?
Take it. Your body will heal quickly once you do.
How dare you feed me this kind of stuff!
You’re so—
Did… Did you burn yourself while making medicine?
It’s no big deal.
I’ll get another bowl for you.
I guess I misunderstood.
Justice Spider, have you placed the bomb?
But…
Jonie made medicine for me and burned her hand during it.
Don’t think of her as so sincere.
Truth is, she often steals little kids’ lollipops,
and she doesn’t let old people cross the road first!
She’s too evil! I know what to do now!
You’re going to explode!
Where’s my bomb?
Are you looking for this?
I’ll keep your things safe for now
and give them back when you’ve eaten the soup.
This medicine must have something in it.
But to get back the bomb…
I can only endure it.
Here.
So sweet!
What… What are you doing?
Didn’t I promise you
that once you ate the soup, I’d return this to you?
She truly is very sincere; she’s not evil at all.
She’s a good goat.
Oh no!
Careful!
The most beautiful fireworks are about to go off.
I’ll be back!
I…
…have just done another act of justice!
Jonie, you’re a good goat.
From now on, I’ll be the one to protect you.
Jonie, come play with us!
Justice Spider, you—
Why did you tie up Jonie?
Jonie, don’t be afraid!
We’re here to save you!
Wait, I can explain!
It turns out that you guys really are evil goats!
I’ll make sure to justly teach you guys a lesson!
END