Marching to the New Wonderland
An Unwanted Guest
I just came to check on the Seed’s safety.
Am I interrupting?
No, you’re not. The kids were in class, is all.
Mr. Slowy,
what kind of fruits are those?
Are they edible?
Those are called four-season fruits.
They’re pretty good.
Any other questions?
I have one.
What do I do if the control lever breaks?
What should we do?
We’re completely stuck in the spider webs!
How do we unravel it, Mr. Slowy?
Unraveling it isn’t easy.
Yes, it is! Just use water and vinegar.
I’ve got it!
You never finish listening, Weslie!
What’s next after water and vinegar, Professor Beetle?
Nothing else. Weslie is very smart.
But he’s quite impatient.
I’m back!
I told you to not be so impatient!
Now, hold on.
Look.
The spider webs are dissolving already. He’s okay.
Look, Mr. Slowy!
Grandpa Beetle’s solution actually worked!
It’s alright this time,
but you need to learn more patience.
Based on the scene,
the goats must have parked over here.
What’s with these spider webs, though?
What are you doing here?
I don’t know who destroyed my webs.
So, you’d like to—
So, I’d like to stay a few days on your train!
May I?
You may not!
Goodbye, then.
I won’t be able to uphold justice with you anymore.
What?
Does that mean that I won’t have anyone to help me catch goats?
Don’t leave; we’ll talk about it!
Keep studying, kids!
These are mimosa plants.
They’re so shy that when they’re touched, they fold their leaves in.
That’s so interesting!
Your education would be better
if you learn by having fun instead.
Okay!
Professor Beetle, I’m teaching the kids botany.
Don’t mess it up.
Brother Slowy,
what’s the point of making the kids learn about
this useless flower-grass stuff?
Then what are they supposed to learn?
They should be learning the things that will be useful to them in life.
Kids,
would you like for me to take you outside
and show you what the Big Tree is really like?
Yes!
I’m their teacher! This is my classroom!
You’ve already checked on the Seed, Professor Beetle.
When are you thinking of heading out to handle other things?
I’ll head out after having a going-away lunch with the kids.
Kids, this is the four-season fruit.
Non-toxic and very tasty!
Understood?
Eat slowly; we’ll find other fruits when you’re done.
You have to eat to get energy!
Here, have a four-season fruit.
No thanks.
I’ll just eat this.
This isn’t bad, either!
Kids, come eat some mushrooms!
No! If the kids eat these, they’ll get stomach aches!
Stomach aches?
Then won’t I get a stomach ache now, too?
My stomach…
…doesn’t hurt at all.
You’re fine; don’t worry.
You say I’m not fine, and then you say that I am!
So which of them is it?
These mushrooms are completely alright.
Don’t use food to joke with me, Brother Beetle.
Mr. Slowy, these mushrooms are so tasty!
Don’t eat them! Don’t eat them!
Don’t eat them!
If you don’t eat some, there’ll be no more.
Ouch! My stomach really hurts!
How can this be?
I’m perfectly fine!
These tasty mushrooms are fine to eat alone.
But eating them together with four-season fruits causes stomach aches!
You’re so beautiful today, Wolnie!
You’re acting so sweet! Is there something you want from me?
Wolnie is so smart!
I have a friend who wants to stay here for a day or two.
Can he?
Sure,
as long as it isn’t Justice Spider.
I hate spider webs.
What’s this smell? It’s so familiar.
I used some air freshener.
Hide!
Who used up all of my new, branded perfume?
Wolnie, I can explain—
Fine. It was me!
I’m going to buy you another big bottle of perfume!
Thank goodness she didn’t find out.
What did you eat?
I don’t know, although it tasted a little weird.
Where are you, Wolffy?
Where’s my beauty-wellness soup that I made?
I… ate it.
I’ll make some more for you.
It’s made specifically for women!
If a man eats it, he’ll get sick and extremely dizzy!
Are you okay?
Wolnie, I feel dizzy!
Could you help me out?
You’re so ravenous. Watch your step.
Professor Beetle, thank you for helping the kids.
I hope that next time we meet,
you’ll be able to teach us even more!
Why look forward to next time? I’ll stay for a few more days,
and teach you all more knowledge about the Big Tree.
What a beautiful day!
Wolnie, let me explain!
This is only because I haven’t cleaned the place in so long.
It’s definitely not because I brought Justice Spider home!
Are you guys talking about me?
Get rid of this unwanted guest immediately,
or else…
I’ll buy, buy, and buy!
Wolnie, please don’t!
You’ve already bought a lot of things this month!
What’s wrong with her?
You made her mad.
There’s goats. Go help me capture them!
Now!
Okay.
I haven’t gotten back on yet!
Stop!
Today, I’ll teach you all how to fly kites!
Yay!
Professor Beetle,
there’s no need to stay behind just for the sake of us.
I don’t want to waste all of your time.
It’s alright; I can stay as long as you’re all happy!
I haven’t gotten on… on the train yet!
How dare he chase us!
Stop!
Help!
Oh no!
Justice Spider,
don’t you know that chasing vehicles is very dangerous?
You can stay here; no need to bring us gifts!
Be our guest and have some fruits.
Now, we only need that old goat to open the box!
Professor Beetle, you’re so knowledgeable.
Do something!
I can’t; I don’t have practical knowledge with this!
I know what to do!
But I need something from you.
What do you need? Make your choice!
I just need some food, that’s all. Help me gather them, would you?
I’m here to surrender!
I want to be with the kids!
Mr. Slowy!
This was too easy!
What are these?
These are my tasty mushrooms!
Then we’ve got to try them!
What if there’s something wrong with them?
Don’t worry, I eat these mushrooms all the time!
They’re very good!
It’s so good!
My stomach hurts!
I knew it was toxic!
How… How is this possible?
Ouch!
I’ve eaten these mushrooms for so many years!
How could it be—
Ouch!
Eating them alone is perfectly fine.
But eating them together with four-season fruits
is bound to give you a stomach ache!
We got tricked!
Slowy, your strategy worked so well!
How admirable!
I have to thank your knowledge and teaching as well.
Don’t be so humble. Together,
the two of you are invincible!
END