Marching to the New Wonderland
Careful Driving
Weslie, slow down!
This is too dangerous!
I can’t! If I drive slower, Wolffy will capture us!
You can’t run from me, Weslie!
Speeding!
You two trains up ahead, pull over!
Let’s see who’s faster, you or my cannonball!
Weslie, just wait and see!
You were speeding; now, you must—
Open the door!
Let me try my newly installed accelerator!
So you want to run away? Watch this!
Stop right there, Wolffy!
This is the new acceleration mode you talked about?
Powerful, is it not?
Yeah, right.
Even a snail is faster than you.
Stop the train! You were speeding!
You can’t catch up now, can you?
Stop the train! Stop right this instant!
Goodbye!
Haven’t we already escaped Wolffy?
Why are we still driving so fast?
I’m sorry, I’m used to it!
I’ll slow down right now.
Wolffy must have caught up to us. Watch this!
You’re in violation for speeding!
Why is it you guys?
However, you were also speeding.
You must study the Big Tree’s regulations.
Slow and steady wins the race.
I’m sorry.
First, I’ll discuss the Big Tree’s traffic rules.
I’ll study the contents of this book thoroughly!
That’s just the table of contents.
This is what you will be learning today.
Alright, we’re finished.
Do you understand now?
Where are you going?
Didn’t I already finish learning?
Hands-on learning comes afterwards.
Do you know what you must do before driving?
Activate the switch!
No. Open the windows.
Let the air flow.
Do you know what you must do next?
Activate the switch!
No. Put on your seatbelt. Your safety comes first.
Do you know what to do next?
I don’t.
Well, of course it’s activating the switch!
Since you don’t know anything,
it looks like you’ll need to start from the beginner’s course.
Too fast! Slow down!
Even slower!
The train will stop if I get any slower.
We won’t be able to run away if Wolffy comes.
It is never okay to drive anxiously.
You must relax in order to see the beautiful scenery.
What scenery?
Look!
Why don’t we typically get to see this stuff?
This is the luminous flower’s pollen.
We normally drive so fast
that we blow away all of the pollen.
It’s so beautiful!
Don’t get distracted. No matter how slow your speed is,
you must keep an eye on the road in front.
I understand; drive carefully!
Looks like you finally understand the point of careful driving.
Be more careful from now on.
I understand!
Feel free to monitor us!
I’ll definitely catch you this time, you little goats!
Weslie, it’s Wolffy!
You… You have to drive faster!
I can’t; this is a speed limit highway!
This is the fastest we can go!
But Wolffy has already caught up to us!
I promised Officer Snail that I’d drive carefully.
You have to keep a promise that you made.
Both the goats and the Seed are mine now!
Stop right now, Wolffy!
I won’t let you get away this time!
Stop!
You must relearn the Big Tree’s regulations!
Stop
right
now!
What a nuisance! Get out of my way!
It’s all your fault that I couldn’t catch the goats!
Have a taste of a cannonball!
Wolffy, not only did you speed,
you also vandalized a highway!
You must stop your vehicle and receive more education!
Wolffy, stop right there!
Wolffy,
stop! Stop right now!
Scared, aren’t you?
Why is there such a huge pit?
Charge past it, Sirius!
First, I’ll discuss the Big Tree’s traffic regulations.
I already know!
That’s just the table of contents.
This is what you will be learning today.
I’ll be back!
END