Marching to the New Wonderland
The Evil Wolf’s Tricks
It’s getting late; I have to go home.
Princess Vivi is so cute!
I just want to protect her!
Princess Vivi, here’s a gift from me.
It’s for you!
This is for you!
This is our gratitude; we hope Your Highness will come here again.
Thank you for your gifts!
Your Highness, be wary of bad guys on your way home!
In this beautiful world,
how could there be bad guys?
Her Highness is adorable!
How in the world am I supposed to get the Energy Seed?
Do you need help?
Thank you!
You’re such a bad guy!
Thanks for the compliment!
Do you need help?
Thank you!
You’re so kind.
You’re a bad guy!
The bee princess!
I’ll take care of you!
Do you need help?
Thank you!
You’re welcome!
She’s so cute!
Thank you. You’re so kind!
Did I really just do a good deed?
Why is there only one gift left?
I have to keep this one close to me.
The Energy Seed?
I’m too lucky!
I can’t let her recognize me.
Do we really not need to accompany Her Highness?
What if Her Highness actually encounters a bad guy?
Don’t worry.
I was worried she’d be in danger,
so I put a tracker on one of the gifts.
Mr. Slowy, why does it say that she’s still on our train?
Mr. Slowy, is this the gift you’re talking about?
It is! Then what did we give to Her Highness?
The Energy Seed!
What are you doing?
You’ve walked a lot; have some food.
Thank you!
Watch this!
Give me your stuff!
Was it this easy?
Thank you for holding it for me!
I can’t be a good wolf anymore!
This time, I must get the Seed into my hands!
I must be cruel this time around!
Wo…
Wolffy!
Darn it, I’ve been caught!
You saved me! You’re actually a good wolf all along!
Thank you! Goodbye!
Since being a bad guy didn’t work,
I’ll just be a good wolf from now on!
There’s footprints from Wolffy.
Oh no!
Wolffy doesn’t eat bees, though. What’s the worry?
If Wolffy wants to get the Energy Seed from the bee princess,
it’ll be easy for him!
We can’t let Wolffy succeed!
Magic Trains, speed up!
Your Highness!
The road is dangerous; let me walk you home!
Thank you, Wolffy! You’re so kind.
Your bag looks so heavy; let me carry it for you.
These are the gifts that the goats gave me.
I can carry it myself.
Now’s my chance.
I’ll snatch her bag while she’s distracted!
Now!
Careful!
Wolffy, you’re too kind.
You got hurt so badly just trying to save me.
It’s the least I can do.
It’s him!
Right! He bullies the old, the weak, the sick, and the young.
He’s evil!
You evil wolf!
We’ll teach you a lesson!
I’m not afraid of you!
Wait, if she finds out that I’m a bad guy,
it’ll be difficult for me to get the Energy Seed.
I’m a good wolf! Is there some kind of misunderstanding?
Stop it! Wolffy is a good wolf!
He’s been helping me all this time; how could he be a bad wolf?
There must be some misunderstanding!
Right, right!
Just a misunderstanding!
He seems to be truthful.
Did we really get it wrong?
Yes, you must have!
Grandma, I’ve made you a new wheelchair!
How about I blow up another balloon for you?
Here, I’ll treat you guys to candy!
There we go; the misunderstanding has been cleared up!
You truly are a good wolf!
Goodbye!
Finally, it’s resolved.
Wolffy, my home is up ahead.
If I don’t act now, it’ll be too late!
Wolffy, what’s the matter?
I still can’t do it.
Who am I?
What is this?
That flower causes amnesia?
That’s it! I can give the princess amnesia.
This way, I can get the Energy Seed,
and I won’t have to hurt her!
Your Highness, look at how pretty this bud is.
It’s for you!
Thank you, Wolffy!
I’ll head home now.
I just need to open the bud, and I’ll be done!
Thank you for walking me home.
I will always remember you.
You’re the best wolf I’ve ever met!
Wolffy, didn’t you give that to me?
This flower isn’t pretty enough.
How about I give you even prettier ones later?
Really?
Pinky promise!
Okay.
Now, why don’t you go home? I’ll stop here.
Okay. Thank you, Wolffy!
I’ll head home now. Goodbye!
Never mind; I’ll think of some other way later.
Wolffy, this is for you.
This is for me?
This is the gift that the goats gave to me.
You’re a good wolf, so they won’t mind!
I can’t believe it!
Good deeds really are rewarded!
This is bad!
Wolffy is taking the Seed!
Speed up!
Put down the Seed!
Wolffy!
I’ll be back!
Is this the even prettier flower that Wolffy is giving to me?
Why am I here?
Your Highness!
You just ran into Wolffy. Are you okay?
Yep!
Wolffy?
How familiar.
You’d better go home.
Okay, I’m going home.
Goodbye, goats!
END