Marching to the New Wonderland
Aromatic Sparky
That smells so good!
I just picked these! Don’t they smell good?
What’s that smell? It stinks!
The trains are all fixed!
You’re covered in sweat, Sparky.
It must be that I sweat too much while fixing the train.
Go ahead and take a bath.
Okay.
If you don’t, you’ll smell worse than I do after not showering for ten days.
That’s alright!
Even if you stink,
you’re still my favorite, Paddi!
Don’t hurt Paddi!
Then I’ll capture you first!
Let go of me! Help!
When was the last time you showered? You stink!
You’re so dirty, bad kids!
We’re safe.
You really do stink.
Don’t get too close.
Go shower now.
Those little goats. How could they be so unhygienic?
Wolffy, I purchased a very, very expensive bottle of perfume!
Perfume? Perfect!
How come… there’s only one drop?
But it works pretty well.
That bottle of perfume was very, very expensive!
Even I didn’t have the heart to use it,
yet you used it all up?
Isn’t it just a bottle of perfume?
How expensive can it be? I’ll buy more for you.
Then build another Sirius to trade for them.
Isn’t it just Sirius—
Sirius?
Is Sirius actually gone?
Yes.
My Sirius!
What are you crying for? All you need to do is summon it,
and it’ll come back, won’t it?
That’s right!
So why don’t you hurry up and trade for another bottle of perfume?
On it!
This is so much better! You’re all clean!
Let’s gather our things and prepare to depart!
Okay!
Let me help you!
Thank you, young goat.
You’re welcome!
Awesome job, Sparky!
It’s the least I can do.
But you just took a bath, and now you’re all dirty again.
Then what should I do?
How about another bath?
You really like taking baths, don’t you?
Uncle Dung Beetle?
Oh, it’s not like that.
I sweat all the time, so I have to wash myself.
I have a bottle of ancestral perfume with me.
One drop lasts for ten days.
I’ll give you one!
Dad!
I used ancestral perfume to trade for this moving house!
What?
What’s the point of using our perfume to trade for this garbage?
Uncle Dung Beetle is right!
This Sirius’ owner is a bad guy!
He can summon Sirius back to him whenever he wants to.
When he does, you guys will end up with nothing.
Then what should we do?
I removed the summoning hardware,
so he can’t summon Sirius anymore!
Thank you so much!
You’re sweating again.
Use the perfume that I just gave to you!
It’s the only ancestral perfume that’s left.
For the next ten days,
no matter how much you sweat, you’ll still smell very good!
It smells so good!
Thank you, Uncle Dung Beetle!
We have to be on our way to deliver the Seed.
What’s taking Sparky so long?
Exactly. He’s been gone a long while.
What smells so good?
It smells just like…
Just like jasmine!
Like fresh fruits!
Like freshly baked cakes!
I’m back!
Sparky!
Sparky got so aromatic!
The handsomest Sparky is a clean one!
This perfume is so strong!
Alright, we’ve got to get going.
Let’s go!
Mmm!
He smells so good!
Don’t you guys think it’s rather rude to keep following other people?
We’re sorry.
When we smelled such a good scent, we unconsciously followed it.
This is our instinct.
Aha!
Now there won’t be a scent!
Where did he go?
The scent is gone.
The same scent is over there!
Besides me, who else could possibly have this kind of perfume?
You can’t be serious!
Smells so good!
Even more aromatic than flowers! So good!
Sparky has suddenly become very popular.
Mr. Slowy, with all of these insects surrounding us,
we can’t get through.
This isn’t good; I need to talk to them.
You guys are blocking our road.
My idol, can I get an autograph?
There’s still so many. How long is this going to take?
At this rate, we can’t deliver the Seed, Mr. Slowy!
Then leave it to me! How about I help you?
Get on the trains, now!
It’s Wolffy! Let me out of here!
Darn it; with so many people surrounding us, we can’t get out!
Now’s my chance!
Come on out, Sirius!
Sirius? Sirius! Sirius!
Attack!
Sirius, why aren’t you listening to me?
This trashy house of yours isn’t one bit good to live in!
I’ll actually trade this back to you for the perfume.
Trading perfume for a house?
I’ll teach you a lesson today, profiteer!
Uncle Dung Beetle, be careful!
You’re no match for Wolffy!
Old man,
I’ll let you go if you give me another bottle of perfume.
Do you think that the strength we build
from pushing dung balls every day is for nothing?
We can talk about this!
So you say!
In that case, I’ll trade you perfume for your clothes!
Why is my scent even stronger now?
Mmm!
Over there!
How about an autograph?
Autographs are fine, but don’t crowd me!
Wear this cloak,
and your scent won’t get out.
Thank you, Uncle Dung Beetle!
But I don’t have anything to trade with you.
No need to trade. This is a reward for good kids only!
Thank you, Uncle Dung Beetle!
Goodbye!
I’ve finally escaped them.
The feeling of coming back home is so amazing!
First, I can sit on my own couch,
and then have a cup of lovely coffee.
Why is it so messy in here?
Dung Beetle, I won’t let this slide!
END