Marching to the New Wonderland
Wilie Goes Missing
Why are there only pictures?
We finished all our food already; for now, choose what you want to eat.
When your mom comes back from shopping with Sirius,
I’ll cook a big feast for you!
That’s right!
I still have a blissfruit.
It’s so sweet!
Of course it is! This type of blissfruit is very rare.
I searched all around here, and I only found one!
Daddy, I will collect a lot of blissfruits for you!
I won’t eat this half.
What a lovely child!
No, this is for brother Paddi.
Today is our acquaintance anniversary.
In a bit, he’s going to come and swap gifts with me.
Paddi is coming?
A great opportunity to catch goats!
Daddy!
Play “Red Light, Green Light” with me!
Okay!
Are you ready? I’m starting!
Green light… Red light!
Wilie?
Where’d he go?
He must be hiding in here!
Sorry!
Wilie?
Daddy is going to be angry if you don’t come out!
Son, don’t scare me!
Oh no!
Danger! Level one alert!
Nothing’s happening.
Paddi, what in the world happened?
Oh, nothing.
I almost forgot
that today is Wilie and I’s acquaintance anniversary.
We planned to swap gifts!
Wilie and I plan to meet in the forest.
Paddi!
I’ll come back after giving him my gift!
I’ll give these blissfruits to Wilie.
I think he’ll really like them!
Wilie, I’m here!
Where are you?
Not here… Not here…
Not here… Not here!
What’s Wolffy doing here?
Not here!
This place is too dangerous!
At least I’m safe.
Not here…
Why isn’t he anywhere?
Paddi?
Stay away!
Help me find Wilie!
What did you say?
Wilie’s disappeared!
Your train has a detection system; help me find him!
What are you waiting for?
We’re going to find Wilie!
Once I find my son,
I’ll have him eat mutton to celebrate!
What’s the matter?
Hurricane’s controls have an identification system installed.
Only I can start it.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
You tied me up! Of course I wouldn’t tell you!
Come on, I was just kidding!
We’re friends; don’t mind me, okay?
Detectors, activate! Locate Wilie!
Found him! Let’s go!
Let’s go!
Awesome job, Paddi!
Keep it up!
Drive faster! Even a turtle can go faster than you!
Hurry!
You’re supposed to turn right here! Do you even know what a shortcut is?
Why can’t your detectors locate Wilie anymore?
Get our son on the phone; I’m buying clothes for him,
and I want to ask which color he likes.
Uh…
What’s wrong?
What are you thinking?
Son, your mother wants to talk to you.
Mom…
Why do you sound so strange?
You kind of sound like Paddi.
I ate too many fries and… got a bit sick.
Son, what color of clothes do you like?
I don’t like clothes. I only like to eat snacks!
The signal isn’t good here; later!
How dare they hang up on me!
We’re running out of time. Find Wilie!
Alright, but don’t interfere with my driving again.
Fine, fine. Whatever you say.
Now Daddy has blissfruits to eat!
I can’t do this anymore.
Yes, you can!
I can’t.
As a goat, who is your worst enemy?
You.
Incorrect!
It’s your own self!
You can only find Wilie if you win over yourself!
Do you have the confidence?
I do!
Our goal is?
To find Wilie!
Our slogan is?
If we don’t find Wilie, we won’t eat!
Use your food-finding abilities to find the wolf!
Alright!
Found it!
I meant for you to use your food-finding abilities,
not for you to find actual food!
Look closer.
That’s my son’s backpack!
Check where it is!
Son, I failed you!
Wilie must be okay.
We’ll definitely find him!
Using the evidence from the chasm,
Wilie is inside the cave.
I sent a scouting satellite in there.
We’ll know what’s going on very soon.
What happened last time? Get our son on the phone.
Uh…
What’s with the hesitation? Is our son in trouble?
I can see inside!
Son!
Wait for me!
What happened to our son?
Hello? Hello?
Let go of my son!
Let go of my friend!
Hand over my son right now, or else—
For my son, I’m risking it all!
Daddy!
Son!
Daddy, I—
Don’t be scared; Daddy is here to save you!
Watch out!
Don’t hurt my friend!
He likes to eat blissfruits?
I’ll distract him, Wolffy!
Take Wilie and get out of here!
Big guy, do you want more blissfruits?
I’ve got a lot here! Come and get it!
Thank you, Paddi!
Son, let’s get out of here!
No, I want to play with Uncle Tree Frog.
Didn’t you get attacked by the tree frog?
No.
While playing hide and seek,
I saw a lot of blissfruits,
so I went to pick some.
After that, I ran into Uncle Tree Frog,
and we started to play!
So after all this time, it was just a misunderstanding.
You could have said so earlier.
I’m sorry; I won’t wander off again from now on.
Brother Paddi, I saved this for you!
Thank you, Wilie!
You playing with me is the best gift ever!
We’re friends forever!
Wolffy!
Where’s our son?
He’s playing over there.
What’s Paddi doing here?
Wolnie, let’s just let our son spend a day with his friend.
END