Marching to the New Wonderland
The Adventures of the Elderly Duo
Grandpa Beetle!
Kids, I’m here to check on the Energy Seed!
Brother Slowy,
are you making progress?
Yeah!
At your age, you should be at home resting.
Don’t keep on running outside.
Wolffy has already attacked us several days in a row.
We have to go faster.
I already have a solution.
If we’re attacked, we’ll run in different directions,
so Wolffy won’t know who to chase.
But as long as he captures one of us,
he’ll lure the rest of us back in.
Then do you have a better idea?
I do!
Look, I’ve found some smoking fruits!
Get down, everyone!
Why is it not working?
This one has to work!
Enough, enough!
Little goats, you can’t run away from me!
It’s Wolffy again!
As originally planned, we’ll meet at the juice pond!
Look at how well my plan worked!
This is bad!
I can lure out all of the goats just by catching you!
Where…?
Do you know the way?
Would you like
for me to help?
What are you talking about? Of course I know!
Daybreak!
Darn it.
We’re too far away; I can’t summon it.
I can’t let him underestimate me.
I’ll just ask for directions when I see other people.
Excuse me!
Wo… Wolffy!
I’ve found you at last, old goat!
What…
…do you want?
Not much!
I’m lost; could you please help me out of here?
Why hasn’t Mr. Slowy arrived yet?
What if something happened to him?
Why don’t we go search?
Paddi, detect Mr. Slowy’s location.
Finding things?
I’m the best at that!
I’ve already detected it without you telling me!
Let’s go!
So you meant that what you detected was food?
I’m sorry, I got too hungry.
If Wolffy finds out that the Seed is in my hands,
it’s game over.
I’ll say, can you two hurry up?
What did you say?
I’m old and can’t hear very clearly.
I said, can the two of you hurry up?
I’m not cold!
What a nuisance.
I’m hungry; I can’t stand anymore.
Eat.
The grass is so tough that it’s breaking my teeth!
How am I supposed to eat that?
We can’t lead the way without energy.
Alright, alright. I’ll just get some more for you.
Once you’re full, hurry and keep walking!
Wait a minute.
Why must I also take this old beetle with me?
All I need to take is Slowy!
Professor Beetle, you’re awake?
Then why don’t you go over there and pick some fruits?
What are you doing?
Be quiet!
I’m so thirsty.
If only I could eat some fruit right now.
Here!
Thank you.
Good, is it not?
Plan B.
Professor Beetle, you may need to use the bathroom now.
But I can wait.
You’re slower to react physically than mentally.
Now’s the time to go.
We can’t leave, Professor Beetle is—
Shut up!
You were right; it turns out that I did need to use the bathroom.
Mr. Slowy and Grandpa Beetle aren’t in there.
They must have been captured by Wolffy.
Mr. Slowy must be in a very dangerous situation right now.
We have to go rescue them!
Why do I feel like we’ve been here before?
Are you sure it’s this way, Slowy?
Sooner or later, Wolffy will figure out that I don’t know the way!
And the Energy Seed is with me.
I need to think of a way to put it somewhere safe.
What—
What do you want?
You’re walking way too slow!
You’re slowing us down!
Don’t follow us anymore!
It should have been that way from the start.
But it’s always been me who is walking faster than you!
Enough!
Keep this dried green grass.
We’ll head off first.
Come on, come on!
Safe at last.
Slowy!
You got it wrong!
The box doesn’t have green grass in it!
It has the
En—
er—
gy
Seed!
How dare you try to fool me, old goat!
What’s this?
Smoking fruit!
This is the power of the smoking fruit!
Where’s the Seed?
I hid it already; just run!
The exit is over there!
So you did know the way out?
Big thanks to you two!
No need to thank me; we’re all friends.
If it weren’t for you leading the way,
I really couldn’t have escaped the maze!
Give me the Seed now!
This time, it’s my turn to attack!
Professor Beetle, take the Seed and go!
I’ll see you later, then!
Let go of me, old goat!
If you won’t, then don’t blame me for having no mercy!
What… What are you thinking?
I want to…
Stop it!
Don’t harm Mr. Slowy, Wolffy!
What are you doing?
I’ll be back!
Are you okay, Mr. Slowy?
How did you guys get here?
Grandpa Beetle was the one who took us here.
Professor Beetle?
Do you want to say “thank you” to me?
What, no!
I just wanted to say…
What?
Alright. Thank you.
END