Marching to the New Wonderland
Saving the Big Tree
We’ve already gone through five tunnels.
Why is the landscape still the same?
What happened, Mr. Slowy?
I think we’re lost.
We make markings on the roads
to ensure that we don’t walk the same path again.
We’ll make markings, too!
No graffiti!
And with this type of toxic paint,
you’re going to harm the Big Tree!
We’re sorry; we did wrong.
You must admit it when you do something wrong.
As punishment, revert the Big Tree back to its original state!
Better to have them reflect in my stomach instead as punishment!
I can’t believe we’re out of power at this hour!
What’s going on?
Thank goodness we’re okay.
Why have all of the leaves here turned yellow?
Sparky, check to see what’s the matter with the Big Tree.
You shall be penalized for unauthorized parking.
Oh no!
What in the world happened?
The Big Tree is sick.
Recharging Sirius is such a hassle.
Daddy!
Play with me!
Dear Wilie, how about Mommy taking you to look at flowers?
Okay!
Back already?
You have damaged the environment. You shall be penalized.
Apologies; let me get ready first.
Get ready for what?
Getting ready to catch goats!
Hand over the Energy Seed right now!
I’ve got you this time!
Where’d they go?
Don’t even think about running!
Wolffy, stop!
Now you have nowhere to run!
Oh no!
Wolnie!
Jonie, go!
Son!
It’s all your fault!
If it weren’t for you pulling and burning bark to generate electricity,
the Big Tree wouldn’t have gotten sick!
Go and save the Big Tree, you guys!
I’ll stay here to look after Wolnie and Willie!
I caused it,
so I’ll fix it!
Just wait!
Syringe!
Bioactivator!
All done!
I’ve done everything at this point!
Why isn’t it working?
Everybody, run!
What in the world is going on?
There’s danger over there; you guys better run!
This is too strange; let’s go have a look.
The problem spot is over there!
Hurry there now!
Wolnie!
Son!
Who did this?
Who painted graffiti?
It severed the veins that carry the Big Tree’s sap!
The veins carry nutrients for the Big Tree,
but now that it’s clogged,
the Big Tree is nutrient deficient,
and this branch is about to wilt!
Be careful!
It was our fault all along.
We
have
to
save the Big Tree!
The branch is breaking!
Darn it!
Get across!
Without Jonie,
we don’t have enough power
to get across!
There’s still me!
We’re running out of time!
I’ll help you guys cross!
You must revive the Big Tree!
We must!
Go!
Save
the
Big
Tree!
END