Marching to the New Wonderland
Old Is Better Than New
Marshmallows! My greatest love!
The candy here is so tasty!
Help me!
It’s all this bed’s fault for ruining my sweet dream.
My foot!
I want a new bed!
What… What are you doing here?
My bed is broken.
May I sleep on your bed for a night?
Of course.
Why did you wake me up, Sparky?
You move a little too much in your sleep.
I’m sorry.
I don’t think this bed is that comfortable for me.
I’ll go find a different bed to sleep in!
Are there really no beds that I can sleep in?
No!
I can’t give up!
I must find a bed where I can sleep deeply!
Here is the grand introduction of
the “Pudding Bed!”
I spent all night working on this new bed!
Now we’ll be able to sleep well!
But I’m very satisfied with my own bed.
This isn’t any ordinary bed, though!
This is a high-tech bed.
It can adapt to individual circumstances
to provide the most comfortable sleeping environment!
Satisfaction guaranteed!
If you have time to make these boring things,
why don’t you have time to go get the Energy Seed?
What a waste of time.
I like my previous bed more.
Why…
Why don’t you guys care about your sleeping environment?
We’ve all worked very hard traveling for the last few days.
Today, we’ll rest and do maintenance.
Where’s Paddi?
I heard that he has a very important thing to do.
Very important thing?
Right now is meal time, though.
Isn’t that also very important to Paddi?
What could be more important than eating?
Alright.
Let’s eat first.
I must find a bed that suits me!
Cotton candy!
Cotton candy bed, here I come!
Too bouncy!
This flower bed should be safe.
Safe and comfortable!
What are you doing here?
This is our honey factory.
I’m sorry.
I just wanted to find a bed to sleep in, that’s all!
Why isn’t anyone interested in my bed?
Why isn’t anyone interested in my talent?
Found something!
What a pity!
Who threw out such a good bed?
Finally, someone is interested in my bed!
Paddi?
Not to mention he really likes the Pudding Bed I made!
How lucky!
Hey, kid!
I’m the favorite green grass fairy.
Cute, am I not?
Excuse me,
did you throw out this bed?
That’s not mine.
What about this one?
That’s not mine, either.
I didn’t throw out any of the beds here.
You’re so honest, kid!
As a reward,
I’ll give this amazing Pudding Bed to you!
From now on, it belongs to you!
Really?
The massaging is so relaxing!
This is the bed I’ve been looking for!
I almost forgot to put on the jammer.
Beautiful!
Kid, it’s very dangerous to sleep outdoors!
You better take your bed back home with you.
Oh, right!
Thank you!
Goodbye!
We’ll meet very soon, Paddi!
Have you missed me?
Paddi!
Scan the roads up ahead!
I can’t believe you’re sleeping at this hour!
It’s time for my jammer’s big moment!
Why did the Magic Trains stop?
Little goats, here I come!
There’s one more.
I have to stay awake…!
The new bed is incredible; even my dreams are so sweet!
You have nowhere to run, Paddi!
No!
This can’t be real!
This has to be a nightmare!
I want to wake up!
This is real?
What do I do? Oh, what do I do?
Weslie!
This time, it’s all thanks to Paddi!
Paddi, you’re incredible!
How did you defeat Wolffy so that you could come rescue us?
I didn’t defeat Wolffy.
Right now, he’s sleeping inside my train.
What now?
Don’t disturb me; I’m eating mutton right now!
Wake up!
How dare you sleep on the highway!
That’s so dangerous!
You’re going to cause trouble for a lot of people!
So…
So what?
So you shall be educated for one day!
What in the world is going on?
I’ll be back!
We’ve made a new bed for you, Paddi!
Really?
Do you like it?
We know that you like sleeping on this bed the most,
so we made another one for you.
But this bed makes me dream about Wolffy!
I’d rather sleep on my old bed instead!
END