Marching to the New Wonderland
Egg Hatching
Tasty cake!
There’s a rock!
Paddi!
I’m sorry!
I swear on cake
that starting from the next second, I’ll focus on driving!
Tasty kumquats!
Look… Look up ahead!
I’m actually kind of good at this, no?
Paddi!
We can just bring the egg back.
If the mother bird can’t find one of her children,
she’ll be very upset.
We have to think of something.
You guys can’t be too long.
We won’t!
Is it closed?
Yes.
How come I can still see you guys?
This is Mr. Slowy’s ultra-thin eggshell invention.
The outside can’t see the inside,
but the inside can see the outside!
Mr. Slowy’s invention is incredible!
Already gone?
Come back quickly!
Full speed!
Speed up; let’s find food!
Why did I just hear Wolffy’s voice?
You didn’t.
Find the egg!
That was close.
I’m hungry.
Oh, right!
I’ll find some food and come back!
I’ve found dinner!
Weslie, help me!
Why does this egg seem to be moving?
Maybe it’s just me.
There’s a door!
I’ll hide here for now!
Why is this egg in the microwave?
Don’t you know that putting eggs in the microwave
is very dangerous?
Can this egg actually move?
Stop!
Wolnie, I’ll cook the egg in a moment.
We’ll be able to eat very soon!
Let’s hurry and head back.
What smells so good?
So many kumquats!
No, we have to put the egg back!
But…
picking some kumquats shouldn’t take too much time.
It won’t!
Paddi loves kumquats!
He’ll be very happy
if we bring kumquats back with us!
Weslie, come save me!
I’m going to get cooked!
Don’t cook it yet.
Let it hatch first,
so we can eat meat later!
That’s a good idea! I’ll go right now.
At least I’m safe for now.
By the way, I’ve heard that a good prenatal education
makes the meat even tastier.
How about I tell you a story?
Sounds good to me!
Once upon a time, there was an egg,
happily growing up on the grassland.
Then,
it was eaten by a wolf!
What kind of story is that?
Once upon a time, there was an egg.
After a lot of nurturing,
a cute little bird finally hatched from it!
This story is more reasonable.
Then,
it was also eaten by a wolf!
This egg… it…
Darn it, I’ve been caught!
It peed its pants!
It must be a very lively baby!
Little egg, you’ve grown another millimeter tall!
Hatch soon!
No wonder Wilie likes Wolffy so much.
He truly is a good dad!
Oh, right; let’s use an X-ray to see what you look like!
Goodness, what should I do?
You’re quite plump!
Keep growing!
Weslie, save me now!
Paddi, here’s a tasty kumquat!
We found the hummingbird egg!
You can come out!
Where’s Paddi?
Paddi!
Oh no!
Is this wolf’s fur?
Paddi’s in danger!
Wolnie, don’t let the egg baby get cold!
I just want it to hatch quicker
so that you can have food to eat, is all!
I don’t want to eat this egg.
Wolnie, you…
I know.
Throughout this time,
I know that you grew to like it a lot.
It reminds you of our son’s younger days, doesn’t it?
Since you like it so much, let’s raise it for fun.
Yeah!
Wolnie, it’s hatching!
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
Isn’t this Paddi?
You said that you wouldn’t eat me!
He is Paddi!
Wolffy, capture him!
I’m not Paddi!
I’m not!
Fine, I’m Paddi.
Paddi, how dare you deceive us!
Wolffy,
let Paddi go!
No way!
Then we won’t have any mercy!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
What’s the matter?
Paddi isn’t here, so we can’t assemble!
Hand over the Energy Seed right now,
or else I’ll eat Paddi!
But we didn’t bring the Energy Seed with us!
Trying to fool me?
What is Jonie carrying?
Hand it over now!
Oh no, I forgot to drop it off!
This isn’t the Energy Seed, Wolffy!
I’ll just grab it and check, then!
Auntie Hummingbird—
I mean,
Sister Hummingbird!
This is a misunderstanding; here’s your baby!
Help me!
I’ll be back!
Paddi, you’re driving well!
After what happened last time,
I’ve learned that I have to focus while doing things.
I can’t get distracted.
Tasty rubyfruits!
END