Marching to the New Wonderland
Messes Lead to Trouble
Paddi!
How many times have we told you?
You must clean up your garbage!
Paddi, a lot of accidents can happen this way.
What accidents come from uncleaned garbage?
What are you guys arguing about?
Mr. Slowy?
Mr. Slowy, look out!
Paddi!
Clean up your garbage!
Paddi’s such a deep sleeper.
How do we scare him?
Time to eat!
Time to eat?
Who are you guys?
We’re the garbage monsters!
Garbage monsters?
Monsters!
Paddi, if you don’t clean up your garbage,
we’re going to eat you!
Wait, no—
we’re going to eat all of your snacks!
Okay, okay!
I’ll clean up my garbage from now on!
Are they gone?
Also,
remember to return the pencil you borrowed from Sparky!
Paddi, it’s time for class!
Looks like I went to the wrong train.
Paddi,
are… are you okay?
Let me tell you…
Yesterday,
I saw garbage monsters!
Garbage monsters?
They warned me to clean up my garbage from now on,
or else they’ll eat all of my snacks!
What else did the garbage monsters say?
They did mention something else.
They said that I’m thinner recently,
and that I have to eat more!
Paddi, what are you doing?
Cleaning garbage is way too tiring.
This is way easier.
The garbage monsters…
they appeared!
What do you mean?
I’m sorry! I’ll clean it, I’ll clean it!
The garbage monsters are terrifying! I have to hide!
You can’t see me. You can’t see me.
Where’d Paddi go?
Doesn’t matter; it worked.
It taught Paddi a lesson, too.
Weslie?
Sparky?
So it was just them scaring me!
Paddi, do you want to—
What the heck?
Paddi, you’re not cleaning your garbage anymore.
Aren’t you scared of garbage monsters?
The garbage monsters are pretty cute; I want to be friends with them.
You have to clean your garbage!
Clean up your garbage right now!
Fine!
How annoying.
Littering? That’s not a very good kid.
King Wolffy is great at this!
I think I just heard Wolffy’s voice.
Not even one went in?
I have to clean it up again!
Paddi isn’t scared of garbage monsters anymore.
We have to find something that he’s really, really scared of.
But what is his greatest fear?
Wolffy!
Pretend to be Wolffy to scare me?
We’ll see about that!
Following garbage led me to the goats!
No, find the Energy Seed first.
They’re here.
Whoops!
I have to be very quiet.
Why are there so many things on the floor?
If you’re going to scare me, can’t you do better?
So you’re messing with me!
Since that’s the case, don’t blame me for having no mercy!
This really does feel like Wolffy.
I am Wolffy!
If you’re Wolffy,
come bite me!
Good thing I’m hungry.
Then eat some cookies!
What’s happening?
Finally, you showed yourself? Weslie’s right here.
Then you must be Sparky!
Just take off your costume.
I saw right through it way earlier.
What’s the matter?
You’re not Sparky?
Then who are you?
King Wolffy was never wearing a costume!
You’re… the real Wolffy?
That’s right!
Hurry! Run!
Catching goats this time was too easy!
I remember that there’s a trick here.
I have an emergency button to notify everybody!
It’s glued shut by gum!
Paddi!
Oh, that stinks!
Weslie, let me clean up this place!
All cleaned up!
Now you don’t have garbage to throw, do you?
King Wolffy can still catch you guys without throwing garbage!
Stay away from me!
Oh no!
I’ll be back!
Paddi finally cares about housekeeping.
Mr. Slowy, let’s go in!
Stop!
Why?
Have you showered?
Sanitized your hands?
Brushed your teeth?
No dandruff!
Only the cleanest goats can enter my train!
Starting today,
I want to be a clean goat!
END