Marching to the New Wonderland
Return What You Borrow
There’s nothing here at all.
What if we get lost?
If that happens, we’ll be out of supplies,
and we’ll die of thirst!
Andy!
I’ve been lost here for half a month.
Thank goodness you guys found me.
Half a month?
But can’t an ant’s antennae find directions?
My antennae can do lots of things,
but they can’t find directions.
Then how do you deliver parcels?
Expert couriers like me
have already memorized the directions by heart!
Except for this Bark Maze.
Wait, how do you guys find directions?
I have a navigator.
There are some places that you can’t imagine,
but no place that it can’t go!
You better put your money where your mouth is.
I’ll show you how it works.
Please take us to a nearby hotel!
The navigation is ready.
Let’s drive!
Turn right in fifty meters and jump.
Then, destroy the boulders.
You have arrived at your destination. Navigation ended.
I told you so.
If an expert courier like me can’t even get out of here,
how could—
Look!
It’s a hotel!
We’ll go to the hotel to rest and gather our things.
Paddi, I’ll give this to you.
Can you lend me your navigator?
No.
We need to use the navigator to deliver the Energy Seed.
If I can’t finish delivering parcels,
the company’s reputation will be tarnished,
and I won’t be able to fulfill my promise to deliver every parcel.
Please help me out!
Alright.
Keep it safe and don’t lose it; return what you borrow!
I will!
This road is accident-prone.
Please duck immediately.
So cool!
You are safe.
Your destination is behind the third tree leaf up ahead.
This is the first time I’ve made a delivery so smoothly in this area.
Image matters.
Terrible image. You get a bad review!
Another bad review.
However, this thing is incredible!
Is it able to find food?
Navigation begins. Three steps straight are grainfruits.
Four steps left are pine nuts.
Five steps behind are scarlet bananas.
Paddi will be very happy when he sees these fruits!
Navigator, let’s head back to the hotel now!
Where’s the navigator?
This is bad.
The trains are done recharging!
Paddi, turn on the navigator so we can depart!
Alright.
Depart… Depart for where?
The Big Tree’s Summit!
But Andy…
You’re finally back!
That’s right! I’m back!
Paddi, which way do we go?
Uh…
Use the navigator!
The leftmost one!
Stop!
Are you okay?
I’m okay. Which way do we go now?
The second one on the right.
Why can’t we escape him?
It seems like we’re going in circles!
What’s going on?
I’m sorry, I lended the navigator to Andy,
I don’t know where to go now!
What?
Tracking missile, fire!
I’ll be back!
Paddi!
Don’t be angry; I’ll ask for the navigator back!
That’s if you can find Andy.
We don’t even know where he’s gone!
That’s easy!
Who would like to make a delivery?
Me!
Deliver me to Andy. Thanks!
Within these few places,
I’ll definitely be able to find the navigator.
If I can’t find it, then I, Andy, vow to never return to headquarters!
How did I get back here?
Thank goodness Paddi isn’t here.
Andy isn’t here?
Then I’ll keep looking.
This bush looks super weird, but finding Andy is more important.
Darn it, it’s just going in circles!
Where the heck am I?
This is the Bark Maze.
Who are you? Where are you?
Turn left and look down.
It’s Paddi’s navigator.
I’ve got an idea for catching goats!
How did I get here?
Antennae, if you functioned,
I wouldn’t have gotten lost.
Don’t you have the navigator? How could you get lost?
What a coincidence.
Give it.
So good!
I wasn’t asking for that! Give me the navigator!
Of course goodies must be hidden.
Give it back right now; we need it to navigate!
Alright, wait a minute!
Andy, where are you going?
I’m sorry, I lost the navigator!
What?
I’m sorry, I’m sorry!
I promise that I’ll find it!
You also promised that you’d return it to me,
yet you lost it, didn’t you?
I didn’t mean to.
You might as well have just lost yourself, then!
How can you be a courier if you don’t even know directions?
You can be angry at me.
You can yell at me.
But you can’t crush my dreams!
I want to be a courier!
I didn’t—
I swear on the reputation of the ant colony
that I will return the navigator to you!
Was I too harsh?
Andy!
Get a grip, antennae.
I must regain the dignity of the ant colony!
My potential has finally exploded!
This trap is for goats! Don’t mess with it!
Goats are nearby. Currently approaching.
Awesome!
The navigator!
Andy!
Stay away!
I know that you’re still mad at me.
I just want to apologize to you.
I said, stay away!
I didn’t mean anything that I said!
I’ve always thought of you as my best friend!
Danger!
Paddi!
I’ve got you, Paddi!
Wolffy,
I won’t let you hurt my good friend!
Andy!
Run!
Sirius!
How do we escape Wolffy and get out of the Maze?
Straight—
The navigator’s broken; how do we get out of here?
Come here!
Forget it; go this way!
Are you not mad at me anymore?
You were right. It’s my fault.
I lost your important navigator,
and it’s broken now, too.
It’s alright.
Mr. Slowy can help us fix it when we get back!
We’ve gotten out!
Your navigation abilities came back!
Somebody help me get out of this maze!
I’ll be back!
END