Marching to the New Wonderland
Paddi’s Search for Water
I can’t walk anymore!
What do we do?
It’s too hot here.
How are we going to get out of this Bark Desert without water?
Looks like the search for water must be left to me!
Not again!
Just follow me and we’ll escape this Lone Branch!
Follow me; don’t be scared!
Those were just accidents.
Trust me,
this time, we’ll definitely get out of this desert!
You’re the reason we’re stuck in the Bark Desert in the first place.
I’m sorry.
The temperature’s too high; we can’t summon the trains.
Oh no, Mr. Slowy fainted!
Mr. Slowy!
We can’t solve this without water!
Looks like you’ll have to count on me.
Paddi, we’re counting on you.
The radar detected a water source nearby!
That fast?
We found some!
Wolffy?
What a waste!
Do you think you’re filming an ad or what?
Exactly! I’m filming an ad.
Just one Energy Seed
can be traded for an unlimited water supply!
Wolffy is waiting for you!
Will the goats just come to our door because of an ad?
Stop dreaming.
Wolnie, what’s most valuable in a desert?
Water!
Yet you’re wasting so much of it?
I’m making sure that the goats see it.
They’re in a desert now, so when they see the ad,
they’ll definitely use the Seed to trade!
What a good idea!
The Energy Seed?
What is this?
This is a glass seed.
I want to trade for water!
There’s no water! Get out!
That ad is definitely one of Wolffy’s tricks.
We have to find water on our own.
I’ve detected that there’s a plentiful water source here!
Where is it?
Right here! Everyone, dig!
Okay!
Still nothing?
The latest search information
shows that there’s more water this way!
Follow me, everyone!
There’s more water that way!
The latest search information
shows that there’s more water this way!
Follow me, everyone!
We won’t trust you ever again!
Why not?
Paddi,
you keep switching locations without any perseverance.
You won’t find water with this kind of mindset.
If there’s better options, why don’t we choose them?
I’ll dig by myself!
Is it water?
This isn’t water; it’s tree sap!
We won’t trust you ever again, Paddi!
Is Paddi still out searching for water?
He won’t keep it up for long before coming back.
But… where in the world is the water, though?
Wolffy?
Clean and cool water to quench your thirst!
Now, only one Energy Seed is required!
Don’t miss it!
Mr. Slowy, what should we do?
Right now, we can only go to Wolffy for water.
Are we really using the Seed to trade for it?
Of course not; we need to outsmart him!
Then I’ll go get Paddi.
No need to. Let’s not find him.
We won’t be long.
We’re running out of water! Why haven’t the goats shown up yet?
Don’t worry, Wolnie.
The goats must be on their way!
Wolffy!
You’ve finally arrived!
Come get me!
We already made a battle plan!
You’ve been captured, yet you’re still laughing?
Where are the other goats?
Tell me now!
I don’t know!
I know!
Wolnie!
Who knew we’d be caught the moment we went in?
My Wolnie is incredible!
We’ll get the Energy Seed very soon!
But all of our water is gone!
It’s your fault for wasting our water!
It’s alright, Wolnie!
As long as we get Paddi and obtain the Energy Seed,
we can grant all of our wishes!
This is bad.
Where in the world is the water?
I’m so thirsty.
Mr. Slowy?
Without any perseverance,
you won’t find water with this kind of mindset.
Perseverance… Mindset…
Perseverance…
I understand, Mr. Slowy!
I must persevere until I find water!
Perseverance, perseverance, perseverance!
Persevere… I must persevere…!
Water… I won’t give up…
I finally dug to water!
Mr. Slowy! Weslie!
Did you see it?
I saw it!
Who knew that you’d actually find water, Paddi?
Good job, Paddi!
That’s for sure!
We’re sorry for not trusting in you before.
Well, I was wrong, too.
Is right now the time for you to admit your mistakes?
I hope you can forgive us, Paddi.
I never blamed you guys.
Haven’t you guys had enough?
Don’t come near me!
Reunite with your little friends!
You can’t run from me, Paddi!
Is this gun actually that powerful?
What’s going on?
I’ll be back!
It turns out that every hole I dug had water!
I’d have dug into it if I’d just kept going a little more!
Awesome!
I found water again!
We have enough water already!
END