Marching to the New Wonderland
Our Anniversary
Wolffy,
do you smell anything?
I know!
It’s the smell of instant noodles!
I made an extra bowl for you.
Smells so good!
Thanks, my friend!
Today is an important date; do you remember?
Of course I remember!
Today is the date where I planned important things with Justice Spider.
How could I forget?
Wolffy!
Make sure that Wolnie doesn’t find out about this plan!
Okay!
The slumber fruit is ready.
Infiltrate the goats carefully,
then trigger the slumber fruit.
Happy anniversary, Wolnie!
Wolffy, you’re amazing!
However, the goats are very sly.
If you want to be able to mix in with them,
you must pass a lot of training!
I’m ready!
Then let’s begin.
Wolffy,
you didn’t actually forget about our anniversary, did you?
the plan is going accordingly.
Good.
Because of Wolnie and I’s anniversary,
I’ll just leave you to it.
No need to thank me, my friend!
You just said that you’re willing to join us
in fighting against Wolffy?
That’s right.
Why should we trust you?
I was just too egocentric.
Now, I come here with the utmost sincerity!
How sincere can you be?
Is this enough sincerity?
Justice Spider is really very sincere, Mr. Slowy!
Let’s just forget the past and forgive him!
Truth is, everyone makes mistakes.
We should give Justice Spider another chance.
Mr. Slowy is right!
It’s wonderful that you understand, Weslie.
I just broke your game console.
You’ll forgive me, won’t you?
Hold on!
Do we all remember?
Today is a big day!
What day is today?
Could it be Mr. Slowy’s birthday?
Wolffy,
I need to have a chat with you.
What is it, Wolnie?
Today is—
Justice Spider? How’s the plan?
The infiltration was a success!
Awesome! I’ll get ready right now.
Wait for me!
Wolnie, Justice Spider has something he needs my help with.
I’ll be right back!
Justice Spider again?
What kind of cake should we give to Mr. Slowy?
How about a chocolate cake?
With tender strawberries and mangoes on top!
Well…
I can bake this cake for you.
It can be proof of my change of heart.
Alright, then we’ll leave it to you.
Remember to make it a chocolate cake, Justice Spider!
I want tender strawberries and mangoes!
Were you listening to me?
They just need to open the cake box
and the slumber fruit will automatically be triggered!
I guess I misunderstood Wolffy.
All this time, he was secretly making our anniversary cake!
I have to pretend I didn’t see it.
No.
I have to be nicer to him!
Do you need anything, Wolnie?
You’ve been working all day.
You must be exhausted.
Here, drink some tea.
Wolnie…
Let me give you a massage.
I’m not exhausted, Wolnie.
I think it’s harder for you than it is for me to take care of Wilie.
Well, true.
Let me give you a massage instead, Wolnie.
Hello? Justice Spider?
The cake is ready.
I’ll get it to you immediately.
Wolffy?
Is this cake for Justice Spider?
Wait for me, Wolnie.
I’ll be back soon!
I’ve got a surprise!
Stop right there!
Wolffy!
Justice Spider has spent so long making the cake.
He isn’t lying to us, is he?
It’s not nice to randomly doubt others.
Since we decided to trust him,
let’s just trust him all the way!
Wolffy!
Why’d you sneak up right behind? You scared me!
Where’s the cake?
Your cake is here!
I created a new flavor just for you.
Wolnie, what are you doing here?
You did give the cake to Justice Spider!
Take the cake and leave; I’ll handle it over here!
Don’t leave!
Wolnie, listen to me!
No!
Justice Spider hasn’t arrived yet.
Let’s start the birthday party first.
Where are you guys taking me?
We have a surprise for you!
Stop!
Stop, Justice Spider!
That’s mine!
—This is mine!　—Let go!
Let go!
This is my anniversary cake!
If you don’t believe me, just open it!
Don’t open it!
Today is our anniversary, Wolffy!
I can’t believe you decided to celebrate Justice Spider’s birthday instead!
Today isn’t my birthday, though.
What?
Wolnie, you got it wrong.
Our anniversary is tomorrow!
If today is neither a birthday nor an anniversary,
why did you make a cake?
Yeah, why?
Cake?
There’s no time left. The slumber fruit is activating!
Wolnie, I…
love… you…
What in the world happened?
Wasn’t there a surprise?
Hold on!
Tell me,
why was there a slumber fruit in the cake?
This was actually Wolffy and I’s plan
for catching goats.
Because he wanted to make it an anniversary surprise,
Wolffy asked me not to tell you.
Who knew you’d come to ruin it?
Wolffy?
Wait for me!
Hold on.
We trusted you so much before!
Aren’t we friends?
Please be nice!
That tickles!
We’re sorry, Mr. Slowy.
Wolffy and the others ruined your birthday party.
Who said it was my birthday?
Didn’t you say that today was a big day?
Today is…
test day!
Of course it’s a big day!
END