Marching to the New Wonderland
Home Construction
I’ll definitely get you guys this time!
Oh no!
Why is the bird only chasing us and not Wolffy?
Your train looks so much like a worm.
Of course it’ll only chase you!
Great, we’re safe!
Snatching my goats? No way!
What’s going on? Put me down!
That was so close!
Look, guys!
The pear crushed all of these fruit houses.
What is he saying?
Elder Caterpillar is saying that you guys
are the ones who destroyed the fruit houses!
What are you doing here, Professor Beetle?
Wherever there’s a need for justice, there is me.
We didn’t destroy the fruit houses!
The bird that was chasing us earlier did it!
Bird?
The bird migration is early this year.
Could the Big Tree be withering faster,
affecting the climate?
He apologizes for the misunderstanding.
You may leave.
Then we’ll head out; goodbye!
Hundreds of birds will be stopping here tomorrow.
We’ll be dealing with a crisis,
and the fruit houses are the only way we can be safe.
We’ll help you rebuild the fruit houses!
The houses are all fixed!
Look, Elder is all emotional!
He must be very happy with the houses we built.
Elder says,
Thank you all; goodbye.
Alright.
Kids, we should be on our way now.
Got it, Mr. Slowy!
Goodbye!
I should have guessed that they don’t know how to construct houses.
Home construction is pretty fun.
We also get to help out other people.
What’s the matter?
Darn it!
Sparky, fix the train with me, would you?
No problem!
Mommy, where are we going?
The houses that the goats built have all collapsed.
The bird flock is coming very soon.
We have to hurry and find somewhere to build new houses.
Right, Grandpa?
I thought the houses we built were rather durable,
but apparently, they all collapsed.
Weslie, why don’t we quickly fix the train
and go back to help them build more houses?
But we don’t know how to build houses.
Then what?
I know!
Please wait!
Could you please teach us how to build houses?
We’ve come back to help you guys build houses!
We appreciate your good intentions,
but we better hurry and evacuate now.
Please wait!
Grandpa Caterpillar already taught us
the best way to build fruit houses.
Please let us try one more time!
Let them try!
This way, even if the birds come and peck, it won’t break easily!
We’ve finally finished constructing the houses before the flock arrived!
Alert! Alert!
Hurricane has detected that the bird flock is approaching!
Wolffy?
Scared me to death. Turns out it was just Wolffy.
You think I, King Wolffy, am not scary, huh?
I’ll show you my true colors, then!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Jonie!
Let’s cloak!
Don’t think that I’m out of ideas just because you’re invisible!
Weslie, the fruit houses will break
if we keep doing this!
Jonie, lift the cloak!
Hide-and-seek time is over!
Have your fun with him; I’m leaving!
I’ve got it!
What are you thinking?
What’s going on?
What did you guys do to me?
Why are you only chasing me?
Help me!
I’ll be back!
Yay! The flock is leaving!
Thank you all!
Grandpa Beetle, what is Elder saying?
He says that he’d like for you guys to please build new houses.
Alright.
END