Marching to the New Wonderland
Our True Team Leader
It’s Sirius!
Mr. Slowy is sick!
We have to listen to Weslie, our team leader!
Weslie will definitely say,
as always: change our path.
Change our path!
Next, it’s: hide in a nearby hole.
Hide in a nearby hole!
We should be safe now.
You’ve been tricked!
Wait a minute.
Aren’t we partners in justice?
Why are we laughing so deviously?
This is clearly a smile of justice!
How is it devious?
I see.
Okay.
Have a taste of my just “White-Hair Spider Silk!”
What’s next is,
“Now’s our chance! Let’s get out!”
Now’s our chance! Let’s get out!
Sparky,
how did you guess Weslie’s every word?
Every time we run into Wolffy,
if he isn’t hiding, he’s escaping.
Anybody can guess it.
Thank goodness Weslie is our team leader
so that we could get to safety.
Why must we escape every time?
We’re actually capable of taking on Wolffy and the others
and fighting them!
That’s Wolffy, though!
If we lose, it’s game over!
Tomorrow, it’s my turn to be team leader; we won’t lose!
As the head train, I must protect everyone.
Let’s go!
I definitely won’t be like Weslie,
only running away.
Sparky, dodge it!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Lightning Angel, diamond drill!
Sparky, turn back and find another way to cross!
Watch this!
Wolffy’s in front of us! We have to get away!
Who cares if it’s Wolffy? Watch this!
The goats aren’t avoiding us?
So it’s the foolhardy Sparky who’s the team leader!
Invincible cannon!
Full speed ahead!
Overestimating your abilities!
Just surrender!
Aren’t we partners in justice?
Why is even our dialogue so devious?
It’s for the plot,
Justice Spider.
For the last hit, you can finish off the goats!
Not that one!
I defeated Wolffy!
Clearly, unmatchable energy with our magic assembly!
Sparky, you’re incredible!
—Brilliant, Sparky!　—Great job, Sparky!
Thank goodness we’re alright.
Watch this!
Stop messing around!
Wolffy, how did you get injured this badly?
Who the heck did this to you?
It was those goats, Justice Spider!
But it seems like they haven’t done anything.
Don’t think that they’re actually cute.
Truth is,
not only do they snatch old grandmas’ lollipops,
they also steal babies’ crutches! They do everything evil!
So they are evil!
I must teach them a lesson in the name of justice!
It’s fine; as long as Sparky is the team leader,
I have ideas.
In a moment, we’ll pretend to retreat.
Sparky will definitely fall for it!
It’s them again.
Sparky is the strongest!
We can’t fight him, Justice Spider!
Run!
Why aren’t you following the plan?
Whenever I think of all the bad things they’ve done,
I get absolutely infuriated!
I’ll teach them a lesson in the name of justice!
Chill out.
The hero is invincible!
Go!
Wait, hold on!
Under my lead,
the Magic Train is unimpeded!
We’re not supposed to go this way, Sparky!
I’m going after Justice Spider and Wolffy.
Going after them for what?
To teach them a lesson or two.
They won’t dare harass us from now on!
That kind of makes sense.
We’ll run out of power very soon
if we keep driving the Magic Train around.
When that happens, if we run into Wolffy again, it’s game over!
I’m scared of not running into Wolffy.
You’re right to listen to me.
Full speed ahead!
Looks like this is all I can do.
Weslie!
Where are you going?
I’ve spotted Wolffy and Justice Spider!
They’re right up ahead!
Let’s go!
We can definitely win!
Something doesn’t feel right.
Everything is fine with me around!
Draw back!
You guys have nowhere to run!
We’re not going to run away!
Let’s attack!
Up to you now, Justice Spider!
Diamond drill, activate!
What’s the matter?
Not enough power; the diamond drill can’t break through!
What now, Sparky?
What now?
I don’t know, either!
Weslie—
Goodness!
What now?
Your plan worked perfectly!
They really did walk right into it!
If it weren’t for the reckless Sparky being team leader,
this plan would never have worked!
Weslie was right.
I shouldn’t have been this reckless.
Hand over the Energy Seed now,
or else I’ll rip your trains to shreds!
Sparky!
Uh…
Don’t worry, I’ll protect you guys!
Wolffy,
I’ll fight you!
I’ll count down from three. If you don’t hand over the Energy Seed,
I won’t be sorry!
Three,
two…
The Energy Seed is with me!
The Energy Seed?
Watch closely.
If you can catch it,
then catch it!
These little goats are so sly. Is there a trick?
Danger!
Stop!
Let me do it; it’s dangerous!
It might just be a bomb!
No, you’ve got it wrong!
It’s all my fault for being reckless and arrogant.
The Energy Seed got taken.
I’m sorry, everyone.
Look, what’s this?
The Energy Seed?
What I used back there
was a fake Energy Seed made from popping seeds.
The real Energy Seed has always been here!
Weslie, you were right.
As team leaders, we can’t just charge forward.
You’re our true leader.
Wolffy, stay away from me!
This is dangerous!
I have to do something!
Chill out!
No!
Energy Seed, please grant me power!
Weslie, just you wait!
I’ll be back!
END