Marching to the New Wonderland
The Misdelivered Parcel
Right now, the tasks we need to complete include
gathering fruits, collecting dew,
and learn more about local insect knowledge.
Me! Me!
We’ll gather fruits.
Alright, you guys will gather fruits.
We’ll collect dew.
Yep!
Good.
Then I’ll go and get some more information
about the local insects’ knowledge.
Let’s get ready to go!
We’re ready!
Wait.
If we all head out,
who’s going to watch over the Energy Seed?
Paddi!
Yes!
I’m giving you an honorable and difficult task.
Watch over the Energy Seed!
I will do so!
To prevent this from failing, I’ve added double layers of protection.
The first layer of protection
is putting a box around it.
This way, we don’t have to worry about Wolffy seeing it!
The second layer of protection
is putting another box around it.
These are the books we’re sending to Wilie.
Help me get it delivered, could you?
Let’s get ready and leave.
I must complete Mr. Slowy’s clear tasks.
Nothing’s unusual outside.
Nothing’s unusual inside, either.
This task is way too easy for me!
Courier service!
Paddi, did you want to make a delivery?
It’s the box next to me.
Deliver it to Wilie, would you?
Is it this one?
Yes; now go on.
Don’t disturb my sleep.
I’ve never seen such a lazy goat.
Paddi, how are things?
The Seed is still here; everything is normal.
Don’t worry, Mr. Slowy!
Why do you still have the gift box?
Have you still not sent it out?
Oh no!
I’ll get it delivered right now!
Andy,
you took the wrong parcel!
I’m so tired.
For our company, keep it up, everyone!
Hello, Auntie Ant.
These are your ratings for this month.
Looks like everyone is very satisfied with my services.
You’re holding them upside down!
All of your deliveries this month have received negative reviews!
You’re ruining the company’s reputation!
I’ll go get a positive review right now
and bring back our company’s reputation!
How can we help you?
I’m looking for Andy.
Andy took a parcel to the Wolf Fortress just now.
Just now?
Darn it!
My online order must be here.
Wolffy, help me open the door.
Please sign for it.
Parcels?
Why isn’t my parcel here yet?
What?
How dare my son’s parcel be late!
Wolffy,
call them and complain!
Got it…
Paddi?
I’ve finally caught up to you!
Here,
let me switch the parcels.
No. How can a parcel out for delivery be switched?
But you took the wrong parcel.
This is the correct one!
How come Wilie’s parcel is still not here?
Any more delays, and I’m giving you a negative review!
Don’t! I’ll be there soon!
Paddi, I have to go!
Wait!
Give me the parcel first!
Paddi, what are you doing?
Give it to me!
No!
My parcel!
The Seed!
What now?
For my company’s reputation,
I won’t give up!
Andy!
Give me back my parcel!
Oh no!
I’m alright.
Help me!
Andy!
Hurricane!
Andy, are you okay?
Paddi!
I’ll help you.
Andy, put on your seatbelt!
Look!
Andy!
Andy, run!
I’ll distract it!
If I don’t deliver the parcel now,
I won’t get a positive review.
Your parcel!
It’s finally here!
A positive review!
Yay!
Andy!
Paddi, are you okay?
Quick, switch the parcels!
You took the wrong one!
I’ve already delivered the parcel to Wilie.
That “parcel” is actually the Energy Seed!
What?
What now?
No need to worry; I have a solution.
What is it?
Leave it to me.
Andy!
Is this really going to work?
With our intelligence,
it’ll definitely be fine!
We’ve already been caught before we started?
The couriers nowadays always misdeliver things.
You’ve already opened it?
Hurry and give us our actual parcel!
The Seed!
We’re sorry; this is your actual parcel.
Wolnie, as long as my bomb invention works out,
the Energy Seed will be easy to get!
Speaking of the Energy Seed,
the parcel that was misdelivered to Wilie just now was…
The Energy Seed!
Give the Seed back to us!
I can’t believe you lost the Energy Seed!
Although you got it back,
Andy gets the credit.
As punishment, you may not eat fruits.
I know I was wrong.
Here.
You can have mine.
Andy,
you really are my good friend!
END