Marching to the New Wonderland
The Troubles of Sharing Lodging
I can finally have a good sleep.
Paddi, what happened?
Help… Help me!
How many days has it been since you took out the trash?
Just a few days.
Take out the trash daily from now on!
Mr. Slowy, Paddi’s long-term garbage piling
has made Hurricane get sick.
Fixing Hurricane is going to take a lot of days.
It’s not liveable for the time being.
Then where am I staying for now?
That’s easy.
Raise your hand if you are willing to have Paddi stay with you.
Paddi has stayed with us for many days already,
so…
Does nobody welcome me anymore?
Don’t worry, I’m still here.
Why don’t you stay with me for the next few days?
Mr. Slowy, you’re the best!
I can finally sleep.
I’m scared!
Don’t be scared; it’s just a nightmare.
I’m here.
There’s a cake!
When will the Sun rise?
Mr. Slowy,
you didn’t sleep well last night, did you?
No, I slept soundly last night.
Look at how vigorously I’m eating!
Mr. Slowy must have not slept for the entire night.
Right.
When we stayed with Paddi before, it was also difficult!
Mr. Slowy might be pushing through it
because he doesn’t want Paddi to be upset.
Good morning, everyone!
Paddi?
Sparky, can Hurricane be fixed today?
No matter what, we have to wait until tomorrow.
I’ll help you; we must fix it by tonight!
Do you also not want to stay with me, Mr. Slowy?
How could that be?
Here, let’s stay together for a little longer.
Yay!
Let’s head back to the room.
Teach me how to play chess!
Alright.
Mr. Slowy is so selfless.
In order to get a little sleep,
I have to make Paddi sleep a little later!
Paddi, it’s still early.
Why not complete these puzzles before sleeping?
Okay!
Finally, I can sleep a little.
Why are you also sleeping?
Mr. Slowy,
I’ve already done these puzzles many times before.
Nothing interesting.
I have some new ones; do you want to play with them?
It’s fine; I still have a plan B.
Late-night snacking!
Paddi, I steamed a lot of baozi!
Come and eat some before sleeping!
I can play, and I can eat!
Mr. Slowy…
You’re so kind!
Take your time and eat; I’ll sleep a little.
Paddi, you can’t eat while lying down!
Mr. Slowy,
I’m finished.
Watch me use my greatest inventions!
The Refreshing Eyeglasses,
the Vitality Wristguard,
and the Alertness Spray!
The Sun is finally up!
Mr. Slowy…
What are you guys doing here?
Mr. Slowy,
we know that you must not have slept well last night,
so we prepared these for you
to let you get a good night’s sleep!
You’re all so sweet.
Does nobody want to stay with me anymore?
However, I slept very well. I’m going for a walk now.
I slept so well last night!
Paddi!
What do you guys want?
We’re sorry.
We were afraid of your bad habits,
which is why…
which is why we didn’t want to stay with you.
You can come stay with us whenever you want from now on!
Just like I said, what kind of bad habits would I have?
However, I only want to stay with Mr. Slowy right now.
Move over, I’m going to find Mr. Slowy to play.
I found you, Mr. Slowy!
Come play with me!
No matter how bad your habits are,
I’ll never avoid you, Paddi.
Mr. Slowy!
How come Mr. Slowy’s snoring
kind of sounds like a moving train?
Finding goats when I’m just passing through? How lucky!
Mr. Slowy!
Wolffy!
Don’t worry, I won’t forget about you!
Mr. Slowy, wake up!
You’re so loud!
Thank goodness I have earplugs.
That old goat is busy sleeping; no one can save you!
You won’t be so lucky this time!
I can’t believe that Mr. Slowy’s snoring is this powerful!
Watch me end you, Paddi!
I beg you to stop sleeping, old goat!
My house will be gone soon!
What?
Mr. Slowy and Paddi are gone?
Everyone, go find them now!
Okay!
You guys are cruel this time around!
I’ll be back!
What happened?
Hurricane is finally all fixed!
Yay! I can finally stay alone!
Didn’t you two like staying together?
END