Marching to the New Wonderland
The Baby Sitter
We’re staying at the Hotel tonight.
We can play!
The goats have left their trains!
I finally have a chance!
There you are!
Come with me.
Don’t take me; I didn’t do anything!
This is my big chance to get the Seed!
Kid, I’ve found your dad for you.
Daddy! We’ve found Daddy!
Wilie, what happened here?
Daddy, I want to play badminton.
Nobody’s playing with me.
You could ask your mom to play with you.
Mommy told me to find Daddy.
Daddy, I’m thirsty!
I want to drink milk!
Alright.
Daddy, I want to sleep.
Daddy, Daddy!
Daddy, I want to hear a story.
Once there was a wolf who always wanted to catch goats.
He tried and tried…
What a funny wolf!
Daddy, I’m not sleepy anymore.
Play with me some more!
Constantly being with Wilie won’t leave me time to catch goats.
Welcome to our daycare. This is a children’s paradise.
Wilie, there are a lot of kids who can play with you here.
Yay!
I’ll leave my son to you guys.
Rest assured!
We will take care of Wilie just fine.
Little goats, I’m coming to get you!
Where’s Wilie?
Didn’t you say you’d find me a sitter?
Where’s my sitter?
The sitters who applied aren’t qualified enough.
They’re not even close to me.
How could we let them take care of Your Highness?
But you don’t have time to take care of me, either.
I don’t care. You must find me a sitter today!
What kind of game are you guys playing?
He’s so cute!
I’m choosing him!
Choose me for what?
I choose you to be my sitter.
Sitter?
That sounds fun to play!
I want to play! I want to play!
Okay.
Starting today, you are my sitter!
Sitter, I’m hungry!
I’m hungry, too!
You’re the sitter. You’re the one who has to prepare lunch for me!
I’ve already prepared it.
Here you go!
I was weaned a long time ago.
I want to eat honey balls!
Honey and balls?
I’ve got it!
I’m going to make them right now!
Looks like I chose the right sitter.
This dish isn’t easy to make.
Honey balls must first be formed with the freshest pollen.
And then… the purest honey!
Only then can honey balls with pure flavor be made!
The honey balls are ready!
Your Highness,
try one of the balls I made.
Your Highness, are you okay?
You—
Is it because the balls I made aren’t good?
I’m sorry.
It’s all my fault!
Don’t cry!
Come drink something.
My Seed, my goats,
there you are!
Some bees have reported you for snatching their honey.
Your Highness,
I just finished cleaning them,
and you’ve made it all dirty again!
Let me help you clean instead.
I did pretty good cleaning for the first time.
Your Highness is incredible!
Let’s go wash off the dust on us.
Wilie,
someday, you’ll have to learn how to take care of yourself and others.
Take care of others…
Here is the massage room.
Welcome!
Thank you.
This way, please.
Alright.
Capture one goat, and the others will come easily.
Where would you like to start, my guest?
How about the hands first?
Alright!
Actually, do the neck first.
Okay!
Actually, do the back first.
Wait a minute!
Do you want a massage or not?
I’m used to using my own method of massaging.
Let me teach you first.
Ready?
First, the pressure must be soft.
It’s as if you’re kneading some dough.
Kneading, kneading…
It feels amazing!
Got it now? It’s your turn to massage me.
I’m so cold.
Your Highness?
What should I do? Her Highness has a fever.
Oh, right! Ask Daddy for help!
What was that sound just now?
Oh, I’ll sleep a little longer.
Hold on!
Where’s the goat?
Where’d Daddy go?
Daddy is the best at taking care of sick people.
Whenever I have a fever…
That’s right; that’s what I’ll do!
Once there was a wolf
who always wanted to catch goats.
He tried and tried…
Your Highness, are you better now?
Thank you, Wilie. You’re such a good sitter!
You should thank my dad.
He taught me all of this.
However, you won’t be my sitter anymore.
Why not?
Because…
you’re going to be my good friend!
Friend?
I want to tell Daddy!
Don’t you run!
Wolffy, what are you doing here?
I won’t let you guys escape this time!
Siri—
Daddy!
Daddy, I made a new friend!
Son, what happened?
It turns out that Daddy works very hard to take care of me.
Now, I’ll take care of you!
My lovely son. You get it now.
Aren’t those the goats?
Forget about them.
Didn’t you want to play badminton?
Daddy will play badminton with you!
Yay!
END