Marching to the New Wonderland
Arti-fleece-ial Intelligence
Master,
is there anything I can do for you?
My smart housekeeper is finally working!
From now on, I’ll call you Marky.
Marky waits for Master’s command.
Marky, pour tea for me.
Pour tea for me!
Pour tea.
I meant for you to pour some tea for me to drink,
not for you to pour the tea out!
Pour tea. Pour tea.
No. I’ve got to add self-learning to him.
Self-learning model update is complete.
Marky waits for Master’s command.
Marky, pour a cup of tea for me.
Yes, Master.
Would you like black tea or green tea?
How about a cup of green tea?
Yes, Master.
Why is Officer Snail going even faster than we are?
What’s the matter?
Why have we stopped?
Did we not agree that we must reach the west branch
within the next three hours?
Marky, pull up the surveillance.
Take a look at what the kids are doing.
Paddi’s still on it.
Outrageous! I can’t believe they’re goofing off!
Marky, I command
that you are in charge of supervising the kids.
We must reach the west branch within the next three hours!
Roger that.
We must reach the west branch within the next three hours.
What are you guys doing?
Who was that?
That sounded like Mr. Slowy’s voice.
But Mr. Slowy isn’t here.
Let’s just continue.
What’s this?
A robot? How fun!
So cool!
You guys are ridiculous.
You’re all goofing off!
Didn’t I tell you that we have to get to the west branch within three hours?
At this rate, we won’t even get there within three years!
We weren’t playing, Mr. Slowy.
Weslie was teaching me a new driving skill just now.
Right, right!
You still won’t admit it?
I very clearly saw it through Marky’s surveillance!
We were wrong, Mr. Slowy.
When you know you did wrong, fix it.
Hurry and get on the road!
I can finally relax and have a cup of tea.
What the heck?
Why did we stop again?
Marky, pull up the surveillance.
That’s odd. Why is the surveillance footage not moving?
They’re cheating me? This is too much!
Mr… Mr. Slowy?
Would… Would you like a piece of cake—
We have a massive responsibility,
yet you guys are eating and having fun!
I’ve had enough!
You don’t focus on driving,
and you even deceived me!
This is the absolute last straw!
Marky, upgrade!
Marky has finished upgrading.
We’ll see if you guys dare to disobey me ever again!
Full speed ahead.
We must reach our destination within the next three hours.
The enemy is too strong.
Upgrade. Upgrade.
Initiate infrared scanning.
I can finally enjoy a relaxing cup of tea.
This is bad, Mr. Slowy!
What now?
The train has detected a cliff fifty kilometers ahead!
If we don’t stop now, it’s game over!
Stop the train!
Marky,
I command you to stop the train immediately!
We must reach the west branch within the next three hours.
Full speed ahead.
Mr. Slowy,
the robot you invented won’t listen to you.
How dare he not listen to his master! Watch this!
Activate backup batteries.
Interesting.
Not bad for a robot that I invented.
Watch this!
Stop the train!
Pull the brake switch!
Everyone, get into the other trains and then disassemble!
Help us! Stop the train!
Somebody help us!
You didn’t think I’d ambush you here, did you?
Help us, Wolffy!
Is this a plead for mercy?
I won’t let you guys go!
We must reach our destination within the next three hours.
Trying to escape my encirclement?
How naïve!
How come they’re suddenly stronger?
Go, Wolffy! Go, Wolffy!
The goats are pretty perseverant this time.
About half as persevering as I, Wolffy!
Unfortunately, this game is about brains.
Once I capture the driver,
you guys can’t escape!
What is this thing?
Aren’t the goats operating?
We must reach the west branch within the next three hours.
Eliminate the obstacle.
How strong!
But I, King Wolffy, am even stronger!
We must reach the west branch within the next three hours.
Are you okay, Mr. Slowy?
I’m okay. Where’s Marky?
Wolffy captured him over to Sirius.
Stop it! Stop it right now!
What are you doing?
Stop right now!
We must reach the west branch within the next three hours.
I’ll be back!
END