Marching to the New Wonderland
Heavy Fog
I’ll have to make another pair.
That road just now was thrilling.
It was even better than a rollercoaster!
Yeah!
The parcel is here!
Princess Vivi sent us some tasty marble fruits!
Get Mr. Slowy to try some!
Mr. Slowy! Mr. Slowy!
Danger!
That was a tasty marble fruit, Mr. Slowy!
How is it dangerous?
I was wrong.
What the naked eye sees is often an illusion, Paddi.
You must see with your mind’s eye.
Mind’s eye?
Never mind.
Mr. Slowy is old and can’t see well.
Let’s forgive him.
Oh no!
Everyone, come take a look!
We can’t see the road with such heavy fog!
As I said, see with your mind’s eye,
and you will be able to see.
The road is right ahead!
Paddi, how about you use Hurricane to find a route?
No problem; leave it to me!
I beg you to stop doing the dishes, Wolnie!
Don’t worry.
I’ll definitely catch some goats and come back!
Wolnie,
at least let me take some hunting weapons with me.
Where’s Sirius?
With such heavy fog, I can’t see anything clearly!
He forgot his weapons; how is he going to catch goats?
Wolffy?
Wolffy!
Where are you?
Out of power?
I have to rely on myself now.
I think I heard Paddi yelling.
I have to go find him!
You can’t go, Mr. Slowy!
If anyone’s going, it should be us!
Why is that?
Do you think I, Slowy, am a cowardly goat who fears death?
Your vision is so bad, you can’t even see where you’re going.
How are you going to find Paddi?
Actually, I—
Let us go search for Paddi instead.
Weslie, where are you guys going?
Weslie!
Don’t split up! Let’s move together!
I’ll stay here and fix the trains; you guys go search for Paddi.
Okay.
I’m coming to rescue you all!
How’d I get back here again?
I better sleep instead.
When I wake up, this nightmare will be over.
One goat, two goats…
eighteen goats…
Paddi?
Weslie, Tibbie, Jonie?
I’m not dreaming, am I?
It really is the little goats!
Wolffy? Run!
Wolnie, I’ve caught goats!
Who’s there?
What are you doing here, Mr. Slowy?
To rescue you guys!
You better run, Mr. Slowy.
Don’t worry about us!
Cool!
Wolffy!
I’m over here!
Right here!
As I said, see with your mind’s eye,
and you will be able to see.
The road is right ahead!
So what Mr. Slowy said was right?
Amazing!
Run! Run!
The goats went over there?
Are you seeing with your mind’s eye, Mr. Slowy?
Now is not the time for questions.
Follow me!
Run!
Come here, you little goats!
Wait for me!
Stop! Danger!
Help! Wolffy’s come to catch goats again!
It’s me.
Look closely; do you see what’s up ahead?
There’s a chasm!
Help me!
Frozen attack!
Mr. Slowy!
Now is not the time for praise.
Hurry and follow me!
Great; everyone is safe and sound.
Thank you for rescuing us, Mr. Slowy!
Protecting you guys is my responsibility.
Your mind’s vision is incredible, Mr. Slowy!
From now on, we’ll use our mind to look at the world!
My mind’s eye isn’t it.
This is it.
High tech see-through glasses.
My newest invention!
Frozen attack!
That’s still incredible!
Wolnie, I’m sorry.
I still didn’t catch any goats!
Wolffy!
Whether or not you caught goats isn’t important.
What’s most important is that you’ve safely returned.
Wolnie…!
END