Marching to the New Wonderland
The Light of the Fireflies
Long, long ago, one night,
the Moon disappeared from the sky.
The Big Tree plunged into darkness.
Mom, Dad, where are you guys?
Help me!
Don’t be afraid!
Are you guys listening to me or not?
What happened after that?
After that, the Moon reappeared,
but the hero was gone.
Listen to me.
Tomorrow, there will be another total lunar eclipse.
The Big Tree will be in total darkness.
Also,
total lunar eclipses cause Energy Seeds to lose their light
and their energy.
What?
Therefore, you must find fireflies
and borrow their light,
so that during the total lunar eclipse,
we can keep the Energy Seed glowing.
Then let’s hurry and find them!
Borrowing the fireflies’ light?
I’ve got it!
What’s wrong?
I think I heard Wolffy’s voice.
Don’t worry; I set up some traps earlier.
If he arrives, he’ll surely be launched away.
What?
Traps?
I’ll be back!
Where are the fireflies?
Help me!
Thank you for rescuing me!
Why were you being so careless,
Mr. Cockroach?
I… I’m not a cockroach!
You’re not?
I know!
You’re a lychee bug.
By the way,
may I ask if you know where I can find
fireflies that can glow?
I do!
It’s pitch-black in here.
There’s nothing here at all.
So beautiful!
Twinkle, they look the same as you.
Does that mean…
that the lychee bugs nowadays can also glow?
I’m a firefly!
So you’re a firefly, too?
That’s great!
I’d like to borrow your light to help with something.
He can’t help you!
Why not?
Because I’m a firefly that can’t glow.
I’m not even allowed to attend firefly parties!
Why can’t you glow?
I haven’t glowed since I was born.
I don’t know why, either.
However,
my grandpa once glowed during a total lunar eclipse
and rescued a lot of insects!
But nobody believes me.
Twinkle,
I believe that you can glow just like your grandpa did!
But how do I glow?
I’ll help you!
Do I really have to jump that far?
Going beyond your limits is what fuels your instincts.
Weslie!
Help me!
Thank you, Twinkle!
You’re welcome.
Never mind; I actually don’t really want to go to the parties.
It’s too loud there; it’s not for me.
Twinkle,
the party outfit you’ve urged for a month has arrived.
I have an idea!
Your ticket, please.
Only fireflies that can glow are allowed to enter the party.
I can glow!
The total lunar eclipse is almost here.
Have we found fireflies?
I know where the fireflies have their evening parties.
Let’s go!
Once I capture the fireflies,
the goats will come to me and fall right into my trap!
Let go of my friends!
I missed a firefly?
So it’s a bug that can’t glow.
Twinkle! Twinkle!
What happened?
Where are the other fireflies?
A big, evil wolf captured them all!
Was it Wolffy?
Could it be
that he overheard us talking about borrowing firefly light?
I have to go save my friends!
Twinkle!
Everything’s ready; just waiting for the goats!
Twinkle?
Quiet.
I’m here to rescue you guys!
Thank you, Twinkle!
We were mean to you before!
You should go; don’t let Wolffy find you!
No, I must rescue you guys!
Twinkle!
It’s you again, you glowless bug!
Help me!
Keep yelling!
No one is coming to save you!
Twinkle!
Weslie!
Finally here!
Wolffy, let Twinkle go right now!
Sure, I will.
Everyone, get out of the way!
Awesome; the total lunar eclipse is finally starting!
Let’s see how you’ll escape when it’s this dark out.
Darn it,
I can’t tell where the boulder is coming from!
Danger, Weslie!
I can… I can glow…
I can glow!
That’s strange; why does the boulder keep following me?
Weslie,
look at your headlights!
When did those get on my train?
That must have been when Wolffy did it!
Wolffy,
the Energy Seed is right here!
Are you surrendering?
My Energy Seed!
I’ll be back!
Twinkle, thank you for rescuing us.
You’re a true firefly!
Keep it up, Twinkle!
Thank you, Weslie!
Goodbye!
END