Marching to the New Wonderland
Who Stole the Royal Jelly?
I really want to sleep.
That was dangerous. We almost crashed.
A branch is blocking the highway!
What should we do?
I’ll have to see if there’s anyone nearby who can help.
Andy!
With how close Andy and I are,
he’ll definitely help me out.
Everyone, be careful while delivering them!
Andy!
Andy,
can you help me move a branch?
I can’t right now; I have a job to do.
What kind of job?
As a professional courier,
I absolutely will not tell you
that we’re currently delivering the royal jelly.
Is this the royal jelly?
It smells so good!
Danger!
Oh, is it poisonous?
It’s worse than poison.
It’s a diplomatic gift that
the Yellowjacket Queen is sending to the Hornet Queen.
If there’s any error,
it might just start a war!
I have a way
to make sure that nobody will take it!
What is it?
Hiding it in my stomach!
That way, nobody can take it!
Take the royal jelly and hide it, now.
Okay.
Wait.
You must also make sure that Paddi doesn’t see it.
Ever since I saw the royal jelly,
no other food seems appetizing.
Here’s some royal jelly, Paddi.
Really?
This is acacia honey.
I only want to eat royal jelly!
Then there’s nothing I can do.
If only this were royal jelly instead.
Why don’t I pretend it’s royal jelly, then?
So delicious! It’s like being in a sea of flowers!
Royal jelly tastes so good!
So you were the one who stole the royal jelly!
Can’t I even think about it?
Take him away!
Wait. I only ate acacia honey,
not royal jelly.
If you didn’t steal it,
then why are we missing a jar of royal jelly?
Evidence!
This photo depicts the person who stole the royal jelly.
It is Paddi.
I didn’t!
We have the evidence and the witnesses! You’re guilty!
Wait. There must be a misunderstanding.
Paddi might be lazy, sneaking food and naps,
but he would never steal your guys’ royal jelly!
Are you defending me or not?
Right! We believe Paddi!
Get him!
I didn’t steal the royal jelly!
Search carefully, everyone!
We must find Paddi!
They say that the most dangerous place is the safest place!
Who drew me this badly?
No; no matter how I draw, I’m still drawing myself.
There’s sound over there; let’s go take a look.
Paddi?
What’s going on?
Did you find anything?
No, I didn’t.
This poster is…
If the royal jelly doesn’t arrive on time,
we’ll lose our reputation.
How about you search over there?
Paddi,
I believe that you’re innocent.
Put on this ant costume and get out of here.
Andy…
I won’t leave, though.
I must capture the royal jelly thief with my own hands!
Then we’ll split up and search.
These honey cakes are Paddi’s favorite.
We don’t know how Paddi is doing.
No need to worry.
Paddi will definitely be fine,
but it’s all those ants’ fault.
I hope he returns soon.
That way, we can assemble
and use our strongest searching power to find the royal jelly.
This smell…
It’s my favorite, honey cake!
There’s cake!
An ant?
Get rid of the ants and protect Paddi!
Sparky, it’s me!
I was going to use you to teach them a lesson.
Paddi!
There you are!
Take them all back to the anthill for interrogation!
Yes, ma’am!
Wait!
I can help you guys find the royal jelly!
You stole the royal jelly!
If I stole the royal jelly,
I’ll never eat my favorite honey cake ever again!
How could you say that out loud?
That’s so…
Honey cake is way too trivial.
How the heck is Auntie Ant going to believe you?
That’s so, so hard for you!
Honey cake is both delicious and beautifying.
I can’t imagine what I’d do if I couldn’t eat it ever again!
Since you can swear on never eating honey cake again,
alright!
I’ll give you a chance!
Okay!
This medicine is too bitter; no wonder Wolnie hates it.
Thank goodness I stole the royal jelly.
Wolffy!
You’ve been surrounded!
No more futile resistance!
Hand over the royal jelly right now!
I didn’t steal the royal jelly.
Come search if you don’t believe me.
Come on.
Let me check the fridge.
Just stinky tofu.
Ma’am, the royal jelly was not found.
Wait a minute!
I’ll search!
Paddi has a strong sense of smell.
I have to stop him somehow!
It’s there!
I found the royal jelly!
Uh… Well, uh…
So you stole it!
No, it wasn’t me!
I was the one who stole the royal jelly.
Hear that, Paddi?
Take both of them!
As punishment, you must personally apologize
to the Yellowjacket Queen and the Hornet Queen
until Their Majesties forgive you!
I’ll be back!
Thank goodness you helped us find the royal jelly
so that our courier company’s century-old reputation could be preserved!
To thank you,
leave this branch to us!
These cakes are for you to eat on the road.
Thank you!
Oh no!
I have to tell Andy that the royal jelly was already found!
He’s still helping me look for it.
Andy!
END