Marching to the New Wonderland
The Breakthrough Dancer
You’ve been surrounded, Wolffy!
Wait, hold on!
I… I surrender!
Look!
It’s an airplane!
Oh no!
Get him!
I’ve got it!
Give it to me!
Stay… Stay away!
Throw it to me!
It’s mine!
What are you guys doing?
In order to obtain this supreme honor,
you must have a certain amount of strength.
What strength?
Only the best dancers
can obtain this supreme honor!
Let the Arboreal Dance Competition begin!
[APPLAUSE]
Mr. Bee,
we just want to take back what’s ours.
I admire your courage.
Go on, kids!
Let’s see what you’ve got!
[APPLAUSE]
The Energy Seed is mine now!
I’ll be back!
Aside from the Dance Champion, nobody can touch the award!
[APPLAUSE]
If that’s the case, I’ll go win it.
I have a faster way for getting back the Energy Seed.
Watch this!
The perfect plan:
a smoke bomb, lure the tiger down from the mountain!
A smoke bomb, lure the tiger down from the mountain!
Fire!
Help!
Go take a look!
Luring the tiger worked!
I’ll be back!
Looks like luring the tiger isn’t a good plan.
I still have an even better second plan:
remove the firewood from under the pot!
Removing the firewood failed again!
I’ll be back!
The third plan!
The fourth!
The fifth!
Your ninety-ninth plan also failed, Weslie.
That’s alright!
I still have an ultimate plan!
It’ll definitely work!
What is it?
The ultimate plan
is to have Tibbie win the title
so that we can get back the trophy and the Energy Seed!
You should’ve said that earlier!
I won’t let you guys down!
The Smart Dancing Shoes are finished!
Where are they?
Daddy,
are you giving these new shoes to me?
Yay!
Please, Son,
these are Daddy’s dancing shoes.
Could you give them back to Daddy?
Daddy,
I want to do the crackle dance!
The title and the Energy Seed are all mine!
Wolffy,
if you’re not using the stuff in this bottle,
I’m dumping it.
I want to use it for perfume.
My itching powder!
Itching powder?
Oh, it itches!
Mommy, let’s dance together!
Itchy! Itchy!
[APPLAUSE]
Vajra dancing!
What’s going on?
Stealing my thunder?
Twister!
Golden snake!
Crackle!
Butterfly!
I’m so tired.
She’s incredible!
I shall announce
the advancement list of this division!
First place: Tibbie!
Second place: Wolffy!
I can’t believe Tibbie is ranked higher than I!
Not good. I have to think of something.
Soundproof bubble!
Alright. Start!
This is bad!
We’ve been surrounded!
As long as I seal off your camp,
there’s no way for Tibbie to get to the competition!
You’ve missed the boat, Mr. Wolffy.
Princess Vivi invited Tibbie over last night.
She’s not with us right now.
What?
Don’t lie to me!
Mr. Wolffy, if you don’t go now,
the competition will be over!
I forgot that I made traps!
What’s wrong with me?
The 957th dance competition finals
will now begin!
First, representing Division A, we have Tibbie!
Tibbie! Tibbie!
Next up, representing Division B, we have…
I’ve finally gotten out of the trap area!
[APPLAUSE]
I… I’m here to participate in the competition.
The competition has already ended.
It’s ended?
The results are in.
This year’s Dance Champion is…
It’s Tibbie?
I knew it.
No.
She’s just the runner-up.
The champion is
Wolnie!
She’s the well-deserved Dance Champion!
Look, she keeps dancing no matter what!
Dance Champion!
I love you!
The Dance Champion award ceremony
now begins!
That’s my wife! That’s my wife!
I love you, Wolnie!
Starting today,
you are the Arboreal Dance Champion!
Where’s the trophy?
Where’s the title trophy?
The trophy?
That’s the second-place reward.
Tibbie, placed second, already took it.
That can’t be!
We got the Energy Seed back!
Thanks to Tibbie,
we finally got the Energy Seed back!
Tibbie, you might have been the runner-up,
but in our hearts,
you’re the greatest Dance Champion!
Dance Champion! Dance Champion!
END