Marching to the New Wonderland
Lift Your Cloak, Rainbow!
Jonie!
Cloak!
That’s odd.
Wolffy clearly told me that the goats were up to no good here.
Where are they?
Uncloak!
Jonie!
Cloak!
That’s odd. Where did the goats go?
Jonie!
I know! Cloak!
We don’t seem to be in danger.
I forgot to wash my train yesterday; I don’t want others to see it.
Lift the cloak.
There you are!
I’ve finally caught up!
Quick, turn into head trains!
Weslie!
Do you think this invisibility thing is enough to stop me?
Good thing I’m prepared!
Cloak, Rainbow!
Rainbow is incredible!
Why can’t it lift the cloak?
What’s the matter, Jonie?
My cloaking device is broken!
Sparky,
can you help fix my train?
Isn’t it fine this way?
A cloaked Rainbow is so cool!
It’s not cool at all!
Being invisible on the road is very dangerous!
Did… Did I hit something?
I told you that this is very dangerous!
Alright. You can leave it to me.
I can’t see it at all; how can I fix it?
Why don’t we think of solutions while we’re on the road?
I won’t let you go this time!
Cloaking! Cloaking again!
Do you guys just not have anything new?
Who the heck was that?
What happened out there just now?
Where’s Rainbow?
How wonderful would it be if I had invisibility, too?
I must get the cloaking device into my own hands!
Rainbow!
Rainbow?
It’s just a branch.
Is it you, Rainbow?
Look out!
Help me, Rainbow!
Will I never get to see Rainbow again?
Don’t lose hope, Jonie.
Let’s take the trains and search farther ahead.
Rainbow!
Jonie,
hand over Rainbow’s cloaking device!
No!
You’re what I’ve waited for!
Get me the cloaking device!
Rainbow!
Watch how I’ll deal with you guys!
What the heck?
Invisibility is awesome!
Jonie, what happened?
Don’t come over here!
Sirius is cloaked!
We can’t leave you behind!
Let’s assemble, Jonie!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Let’s run, Jonie!
Did you assemble just to run?
Can you escape, though?
What now? What now?
Aha!
You’re speeding!
Who was that this time?
Do you not have eyes?
Do you guys not look while driving?
None of you are obeying traffic regulations!
You are not obeying traffic regulations, either!
We’ve finally escaped Wolffy.
Oh no, Rainbow is broken!
Help me fix Rainbow, Sparky!
What?
Is the shield malfunctioning, too?
Does this mean that we’ll never be able to get out?
The shield is functioning.
It’s the cloaking device.
Wolffy took it.
The cloak wasn’t good at all; forget it.
No, we have to fix it!
We can’t have one without the other.
Sparky, hurry and help Jonie fix it.
Roger that.
From now on, you must obey traffic regulations!
Little goats, I’m coming for you!
Sirius?
Where’s Sirius?
Darn it, Sirius is still cloaked!
Where are you, Sirius?
Sirius?
Is that you, Sirius?
Let’s go, Sirius!
When did I change the carpet?
I’ll be back!
END