Marching to the New Wonderland
Partners in Justice
Sir, are you having trouble with your height?
Right now, if you buy our elevator shoes,
your dreams of growing taller will immediately be fulfilled!
I’m going to find you guys!
Last time, I bought three pairs, but they did nothing at all!
I want a refund!
The number that you have dialed cannot be reached at this time.
Please call again later.
Then I’ll call later.
Wait, I didn’t dial this call!
Haven’t you had enough?
Justice Spider, the little goats are up to no good again!
Okay, I’ll be right there!
Justice Spider is way too gullible.
With his help, catching goats is a piece of cake!
Help me kick the ball over here!
Okay!
I’ll help you!
Justice Spider has arrived!
Who did this?
So it was you, Wolffy!
Let me explain, Justice Spider!
Then explain!
I…
I’ll go get the Seed first.
I’ll explain to you later.
Sirius!
Wolffy!
Don’t you run, little goats!
Come here!
Outrageous!
All we can do now is hurry through!
What?
We’re finally safe.
Sit tight, everyone!
We have to fly over a gorge!
What now, Mr. Slowy?
Let me think of something.
What other ways can I get the Seed?
I’ve got it!
Justice Spider!
There you are!
What’s wrong, Justice Spider?
I’m a defender of justice. I’m not your friend.
Actually, Justice Spider, I—
No need to explain. There’s nothing to explain.
Who did this?
Destroying flowers!
Unforgivable!
I’ll definitely find the wrongdoer
to prove that I’m a good wolf!
The wrongdoer has put themself in.
Today, I shall act on behalf of the heavens!
I just picked these flowers; aren’t they pretty?
Yes… Yes, they are.
So you were the one who destroyed the flowers!
Watch how I’ll punish you!
Wolnie!
Wolffy, what are you doing?
Justice Spider, I…
We’re splitting paths from now on.
We’re not the duo of justice anymore.
Justice Spider!
What are you doing, Jonie?
I thought that my train could get up there if it were cloaked.
The train’s weight isn’t going to disappear with a cloak.
Nope, I can’t reach it!
Let me try.
If only we had a pair of wings.
Wings?
That’s it! We can ask Twinkle to help us!
But who’s going to find him?
I’ll go.
Mr. Slowy?
No!
The road to the Fireflies’ Village is very difficult.
We can’t let you go alone!
Enough.
Protecting the Seed here
is more important than going to the Fireflies’ Village.
If Wolffy comes to take the Seed
while you’re out searching for Twinkle,
then what?
Alright, then.
Be back soon, Mr. Slowy!
Justice Spider!
Just…
Go away!
Look at my eyes, Justice Spider.
What do you see?
There’s something in it.
Look again, closer.
There’s…
evil.
Are you not able to see
the fire of justice that burns in my heart?
Where’s the fire?
I don’t want to hear you speak.
In short, we’re splitting paths.
Don’t ever let me see you do bad deeds again!
Just wait a minute!
Oh no!
What should I do?
Help… Help me!
It’s so far down; there’s nothing I can do.
Wolffy, you’re sacrificing yourself to save me?
What’s going on?
Hurry! They’re sinking!
Wolffy?
How’d I get back up?
Did…
Thank you for rescuing me!
Actually, I—
I was wrong about you.
You truly are a good wolf for a good cause!
You’re my good friend!
In that case,
let’s stand up for justice together!
Awesome!
Give the Seed back to us, Wolffy!
You can’t escape!
Once again, justice triumphs over evil!
You guys are the evil ones!
You’re so ungrateful!
Is this how you treat the ones who rescued you?
Weren’t you the one who rescued me?
That’s… That’s right!
I was!
You guys say that you rescued us.
Any proof?
I don’t think so.
That proves you’re lying!
I can prove it!
This is a photo I took at the time.
So that’s what happened.
I was wrong.
Have this back.
You can’t give that back to them!
You lied to me again, Wolffy!
I’m going to punish you!
Come here!
Little goats, I’ll be back!
END