Marching to the New Wonderland
Overkill
What a beautiful sea of flowers!
I haven’t seen this type of flower before.
Stay clear.
The book doesn’t document this type of plant.
Don’t touch it!
Most brightly-colored mushrooms are toxic.
Don’t eat them!
No touching this,
no touching that.
I’m so hungry.
Food!
Mr. Slowy won’t let us eat it.
This color…
This shape…
It must be a white mushroom!
Let’s eat, everyone!
Yay!
I need to use the bathroom!
Us, too!
Didn’t you say that the mushroom is edible?
Why did we all get diarrhea?
The book said something different, though.
It’s because this is a different world!
Why?
Why doesn’t the toxic mushrooms chapter have this thing?
Is this…
Village Chief Mandy’s writing?
“A successful scientist,
“in addition to being very knowledgeable,
“must have a heart courageous enough to experiment.”
Courageous enough to experiment?
I get it!
How’s Mr. Slowy?
No movement.
You don’t think Mr. Slowy is in trouble, do you?
What’s wrong with Mr. Slowy?
Did we irritate Mr. Slowy
by not listening to him before?
After a few days of reflection,
I finally understand!
Let’s go and try new things!
Mr. Slowy has changed.
We should just listen to him,
so he might go back to normal.
This flower looks so unique!
It seems so dangerous, Mr. Slowy!
Says who?
See?
It’s safe!
Safe!
We’ll stop here today.
Who knew that the feeling of trying new things would be so exciting?
Mr. Slowy,
we’re very tired.
Can we go back?
Trying new things is always tiring.
We have to push through the difficulties and keep going!
In such a dangerous place
with such a safe hotel,
the goats will definitely camp here!
When that happens, the goats and the Seed will be mine!
A Bee Hotel!
We can finally get a good night’s sleep!
We’ll camp in that cave.
Is it really okay to camp in the cave, Mr. Slowy?
That place is… so scary!
It doesn’t look safe at all.
How would you know if you haven’t tried it?
Let’s go.
Could they have seen through my plan?
Don’t be scared! I’ll protect you!
What’s wrong, Paddi?
My foot…
Mr. Slowy!
This place is so scary!
It’s just a dead branch; there’s nothing to be scared of here.
Mr. Slowy!
Let’s just go back to that Bee Hotel from earlier.
We are explorers of knowledge!
Why would we retreat?
Think of our great predecessors.
Only when Captain Goat dared to go out to sea
did they discover new land!
Only when Apothecary Goat dared to taste a hundred herbs
did they discover a life-saving remedy!
But the books say
that Captain Goat has been missing since their last voyage,
and Apothecary Goat got two-year-long diarrhea after eating the wrong herb.
Who
dares
to
—en-　　—Help!
ter
my
grot-
to?
Andy?
Welcome to the Ant Express branch that I designed!
This doesn’t look like a courier branch at all.
Come on, I’ll show you guys around.
This is an explorer’s paradise!
My business premise isn’t so bad, is it?
What’s that?
Don’t touch it!
This grass is the centerpiece of the building.
It’s what holds up all of these columns.
If it’s pulled,
this place will collapse.
Grass is growing inside the room?
And it’s such strange-looking grass!
I’ll help Andy get rid of it!
I pulled the weeds for you; no need to thank me!
What’s going on?
You’re in trouble, Mr. Slowy!
That grass can’t be pulled!
What?
This place is collapsing!
Run, Mr. Slowy!
It’s all my fault.
I’ve hurt everybody.
Mr. Slowy!
This way!
You didn’t think I’d ambush, did you?
What’s going on?
Thunderbolt!
Jonie, activate Rainbow’s Shield!
We’re finally safe now!
Yay!
I can do that, too!
Sirius!
I’m sorry, Andy.
It’s all my fault
that the grotto you designed was…
Thank you!
If it weren’t for you,
I wouldn’t have known that I’m actually terrible at designing.
I should just be a courier instead.
Mr. Slowy,
I found this.
Another one of Mandy’s writings?
Village Chief Mandy is right!
We shouldn’t let failure affect our determination to move forward!
Let’s keep going!
Is this really one of Village Chief Mandy’s writings?
I feel like I’ve seen this handwriting before.
I wrote this.
You’re so smart, Weslie!
It’s time to get going!
I’ll be back!
END