Marching to the New Wonderland
Moss Skating
Now let’s see if you can escape!
Make a U-turn!
Watch this!
Today is your day!
Your driving skills are incredible, Weslie!
For me, driving Thunderbolt
is as easy as running.
Now, there’s no place where I can’t get through!
What’s going on, Weslie?
Uh…
This moss seems a bit unique.
This moss is extremely slippery; we must not run off,
or else we’ll slide farther and farther!
Let’s check on our trains and do some maintenance.
Alright.
Even water droplets, I can drive past.
Of course I’m not scared of some moss!
Wolnie, are you okay?
I’m okay; my foot just hurts a little.
What now?
It’s alright. I’m not that happy with these shoes anyway.
I’ll buy another pair.
Didn’t you just buy this pair of shoes?
Why are you buying new ones again?
It’s very slippery with all this moss at home.
I have to buy a few extra pairs of slip-resistant shoes.
Son!
Be careful!
I want to moss skate, too!
Then Daddy will teach you!
Yay!
When it comes to moss skating,
I, your dad, am the world’s best at it!
This piece of moss…
looks a lot like Weslie.
Be careful! Dad will teach you how to skate instead.
What a coincidence.
—Wolffy!　—Weslie!
Everyone’s trains are all fixed!
It’s too slippery; there’s no way to cross.
Just wait. Let’s find Mr. Slowy.
He’ll definitely have a solution!
The moss is too slippery, Mr. Slowy.
It’s very hard for the trains to keep going.
In order for these these mosses to stop growing,
fierce sunlight is required.
Unfortunately, there’s no sunlight here.
You guys find Weslie.
Have him drive Thunderbolt
at full power so we can find a way out.
There’s too much moss!
That’s odd; where did Weslie go?
Why is Brother Weslie here?
Brother Weslie is here to visit us!
For the sake of my son,
I won’t lock you up just yet.
Are you not worried about me escaping?
I’d like to see you try!
As long as you’re gone, getting the Energy Seed is way easier!
Daddy, come teach me how to moss skate!
I’ll be right there! Just wait, my son.
I’ll deal with you later!
These mosses are everywhere.
How am I supposed to escape?
Want to learn how to moss skate?
First, pretend we’re ice skating.
The main ideas are pretty similar.
That’s it!
Why don’t I just learn along with them?
When you’re moss skating,
don’t move your feet as if you’re walking.
Rather, move your left, then your right.
It’s left, right, left, right. Skate step by step.
Turning also requires a lot of precision.
Watch closely.
Isn’t this cool?
Awesome!
Who knew that the intelligent Weslie can’t moss skate?
Alright, son.
Let’s continue.
Daddy, why won’t Brother Weslie
come over here to learn with us?
Because he likes our living room.
He wants to stay there for the visit.
He’s not in the living room, though.
Weslie!
Son, Daddy will teach you more later!
Wolffy really is a good coach!
Stop!
Thunderbolt!
Who knew that letting go of Weslie
would lead me to find even more goats?
What now?
Run!
—Daybreak! —Rainbow! —Lightning Angel! —Hurricane! —Morning Sun!
You can’t even moss skate! How can you drive trains?
They can’t, but I can!
Weslie!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Trying to run?
That won’t be easy!
I won’t let you guys get away this time!
What should we do, Wolffy?
The whole train is covered in moss!
I’ll capture you, Weslie!
Worry about yourself first!
I remember.
Moss wilts when there’s sunlight.
Finally something good!
What is “good” about this?
Our train is too heavy; we can’t get across!
I’ll be back!
END