Marching to the New Wonderland
The Jeweled Bird’s Nest
You’re in charge today.
You must keep an eye on the Energy Seed.
Don’t let any bad guys take it!
Yes, sir!
Aren’t I just watching over it?
What bad guys are there?
Legend has it that there is a type of bird
who loves to collect shiny, glowy things.
They’ve been dubbed the “Jeweled Birds.”
Glowing property like the Energy Seed
is exactly what the Jeweled Birds are looking to collect,
so we have to be extremely careful.
You don’t have to worry, Mr. Slowy.
Don’t let your guard down. Look outside.
Keep an eye on the Energy Seed at all times.
Secure the Energy Seed.
I vouch for my snacks
that nothing will go wrong.
I don’t believe that if I look away for one second, it’ll be gone.
It’s actually gone! How is this possible?
Oh no, I have to get the Seed back!
If I don’t, I’ll definitely get yelled at!
Hurri—
Everyone will find out if I summon Hurricane.
Stop, Jeweled Bird!
Ouch!
After giving so many gifts all these years,
I don’t know what I should give anymore.
I don’t mean to snoop on your diary, Wolnie.
I just want to give you a surprise!
So what Wolnie wants the most is the Energy Seed?
This one is… not very doable.
Wolnie’s second most wanted is to eat mutton?
This one isn’t very doable in the short-term, either.
Wolnie likes gems!
This will do!
I must take back the Energy Seed when the bird is distracted!
What weapon should I use?
Alright, I’ll just use this one!
Please give the Energy Seed back to me!
If it won’t return the Seed, I’ll have to act.
I’ll trade you this tasty lollipop for it!
Can I?
How could it dislike lollipops?
What should I do?
Legend has it that there is a bird who loves to collect shiny, glowy things.
That’s right; it likes shiny, glowy things!
This is the Big Tree. How can I possibly find gems?
I didn’t get a birthday gift this year; I’m so upset!
Do I really have to let Wolnie down?
Gems!
They really are gems!
But why would there be gems here?
So these gems belong to that bird?
Is this…
the Energy Seed?
The goats are watching the Energy Seed closely.
How could it possibly be here?
It must be a fake.
For the sake of Wolnie, I’ll fight you!
Why can’t you pick on someone your own size?
Good thing I stuffed some gems in my pockets!
There you are!
Paddi?
How about we make a deal, Jeweled Bird?
Paddi has somehow mistaken me for that bird.
Alright, then. What sort of deal do you want to make?
Look at this shiny, glowy thing! Do you like it?
This is a big gem!
What exactly do you want?
Can I trade this with you for the Energy Seed?
What?
The Energy Seed?
Is this… the Energy Seed?
So that really was the Energy Seed!
Oh, I’ve screwed up!
Why is it Wolffy?
Help me!
Once I get the Energy Seed,
I’ll be able to fulfill all of my wife’s wishes at once!
Help me!
Why can’t I find it? It must be over here!
Wolffy, the Seed is over there!
Look!
Thank you for helping me find the Seed!
I beg you to return it to me!
If not, I’ll get yelled at!
You won’t be yelled at if I eat you!
Oh no.
I’m not doing anything; I’m just passing by, is all!
That’s not true!
He wants to steal the shiny, glowy thing under your foot!
Look, these are your favorite gems!
The Energy Seed is mine!
Oh no!
I have to think of a way to get back the Energy Seed!
Can’t you be a little quieter?
Wait! Wait!
Help me!
I’ll be back!
I’ve finally gotten back the Energy Seed!
You’ve done a great job, Paddi.
You deserve commendation.
Wolnie, here’s a gift for you!
A flashlight?
This is the real gift!
Thank you, Wolffy!
END