Marching to the New Wonderland
Inseparable
Help!
Come here, little goats!
Keep laughing. We’ll see who’s laughing at the end.
Sirius!
You can’t laugh now, can you?
What now?
Watch this!
Come on out,
Thunderbolt!
Is this what you’re looking for?
My spider silk is the most durable silk in the world!
You can’t destroy it
unless your train has one thousand horsepower!
Coincidentally, my Thunderbolt has no more, no less,
but exactly one thousand horsepower!
Chase them!
Catch us if you can, Mr. Wolffy!
My Sirius is no pushover, Weslie!
Tibbie, it’s up to you now!
Got it!
Awesome!
Weslie, Thunderbolt,
I won’t forgive you guys!
Catching a cold and sneezing is so upsetting.
A cold?
I have an idea!
All finished!
I don’t see anything that’s wrong with it.
Thunderbolt, speed up!
You guys know what’s wrong with it now, right?
No worries; watch this!
How is it?
According to the scan,
Thunderbolt is perfectly normal!
Weslie,
try assembling the trains.
Okay.
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
It worked!
Darn it.
Something’s very wrong with Thunderbolt!
I’m not giving up on Thunderbolt!
I’ve got it!
This idea is working really well, Weslie!
The train is even faster than normal!
But how do we stop?
There’re ants!
Thank goodness I turned in time.
In front!
Brakes! Hit the brakes!
We’re going to crash!
Thank goodness it’s run out.
We’d better just fix Thunderbolt instead.
Have you found what’s wrong?
Not yet.
How about now?
Now—
I’ve been scanning for all day, all night,
but I haven’t found a single problem at all!
Stop asking! Just let me go!
Look, I’ve even caught a cold.
What if the virus spreads?
That’s it!
Could there be a virus?
A virus? I’ll check!
Thunderbolt really has been infected with a virus!
Is it curable?
Of course it is! Watch this.
Little goats! Hands behind your back!
Justice Spider, fire!
Thunderbolt!
Weslie, don’t!
Hold on, Thunderbolt!
The virus removal program is complete!
Weslie, catch!
Here, quick!
Oh, no, you don’t!
Weslie!
With you, I’ll have unlimited power!
Don’t get cocky!
Weslie will definitely come with Thunderbolt to rescue us!
Thunderbolt caught my virus.
It’s totally defenseless!
You guys should just wait until I get the Energy Seed
and then go into my stomach instead!
Are you okay, Thunderbolt?
Start up!
Mr. Slowy and the others are in danger.
We have to hurry and rescue them!
Come on, Thunderbolt! Start up!
Aha!
Wolffy!
Weslie!
There you are, Weslie!
Let everyone go and give the Energy Seed back to us,
or else I won’t forgive you!
Your Thunderbolt already caught my virus.
What are you going to use to fight me?
So this was all your doing!
Just surrender!
In your dreams!
Thunderbolt!
It’s caught a virus; why call it?
What can ants pushing a broken train do?
Weslie, catch the virus removal program!
Sirius,
fire!
Thunderbolt is back!
Magic assembly,
unmatchable energy!
Let’s see who wins, little goats!
Ask and you shall receive!
Everyone, attack!
Alright!
You’ve recovered at last, Thunderbolt!
Thank you for your virus removal program, Sparky!
No need to thank me.
I’m just glad that everyone’s okay!
END