Marching to the New Wonderland
Reprise of the Meteor Shower
After delivering the Seed all day,
we can finally have a rest.
Dinner is ready!
Come and eat, everyone!
Getting to eat dinner that Tibbie makes every day
takes away all of my fatigue!
Wait! I almost forgot this.
What kind of special day is it, Tibbie?
There’s even an extra dish!
It’s because of Weslie!
He promised to take me to see the centennial meteor shower!
I’m so happy!
Meteor…
…shower?
Yeah!
You said that you’d take me to a place where I can see the meteor shower!
Darn it, I went the wrong way!
How much longer?
The meteor shower is starting soon!
Well, uh…
The centennial fantastical meteor shower is now over!
For those who missed it, you’ll have to wait until next time!
The next one will be in one thousand years, though!
It’s over!
I’m sorry, I went the wrong way.
My meteor shower…
You lied to me, Weslie!
It’s lunch time!
Come eat, everyone.
I’ll go ahead!
Those aren’t edible.
It’s not good to be picky, Paddi.
We must appreciate food, no matter what it is.
It’s so salty!
Actually, it’s no big deal.
We must not waste food.
Eat!
I’m full.
Tibbie is very upset that she didn’t get to see the meteor shower.
Let’s think of ways to help her.
We have to bring back her smile!
Just leave it to me!
What did you take me out here for, Weslie?
You’ll see in a moment!
Weslie!
It’ll definitely work this time!
Just give me one more chance.
Fine.
This time, a meteor shower made from twinklefruit
will definitely make Tibbie happy!
Tibbie, look out!
I’m sorry, Tibbie!
A shooting star!
Look, Tibbie!
You lied to me again! I won’t trust you anymore!
I wasn’t lying this time, I swear!
I must find the meteor!
Turns out that the shooting star just now was just Sirius.
Why did you venture out just to get this garbage?
Sirius got damaged!
These aren’t ordinary, though.
They’re fragments of the centennial meteors!
Meteor fragments?
Tibbie will definitely be very happy if she sees them.
How are these fragments useful?
I want the Energy Seed!
Look, Wolnie.
As far as I can tell,
these meteor fragments may contain massive amounts of energy!
If we use this energy well,
getting the Energy Seed will be a breeze!
Weslie!
Trying to run?
Tibbie…
I’m sorry, Mr. Slowy.
I don’t want to talk right now.
Wasn’t Weslie with you?
Forget him.
You…
Just go, Sparky.
I want to be alone.
Alright, but…
you’re stepping on my foot.
Oh, sorry!
I know it wasn’t your fault,
but I don’t want to see you right now.
What in the world did Weslie do?
How come Tibbie is even angrier now?
You have nowhere to run, Weslie!
Come on out,
Thunderbolt!
You’ve finally arrived!
Who cares that Thunderbolt is here? Same results!
Mr. Slowy!
Answer my call!
What should we do?
Don’t pick up yet.
Let’s wait until Tibbie calms down.
Tibbie, it looks like Weslie urgently needs us.
You guys answer his call.
I’m not trusting Weslie again, anyway.
Meteors!
They’re meteors!
Weslie didn’t lie to me!
I saw the meteors, Weslie!
They’re so pretty!
Tibbie! Run, you guys, now!
What?
Oh no!
It’s Wolffy!
I’m going to eat you tonight, Weslie!
I don’t think so!
Didn’t I tell you guys to run?
How could we leave you behind?
Look out!
Tibbie!
Wake up!
Hand over the Energy Seed right now!
How could this happen?
I’ll be back!
This is the most beautiful meteor shower
that I’ve ever seen!
Yay! Tibbie is smiling again!
END