Marching to the New Wonderland
The Traffic Safety Captain of Justice
Be careful around here, Mr. Slowy.
We can’t get caught by Officer Snail!
Why not?
Because…
Stop! Vehicle inspection!
Please cooperate.
How much longer, Officer Snail?
Not much; just a few more days.
A few more days?
Every time Officer Snail does inspections, he takes a few days.
We have to deliver the Energy Seed
and can’t waste time.
Just hide from him.
Red alert!
Vehicle inspection ahead!
U-turn!
Stop!
Vehicle inspection!
Justice Spider?
How come it’s you?
Officer Snail has already retired.
Starting now,
I’m the new traffic captain!
I’m his assistant.
Wolffy?
You guys must undergo inspection!
How can this be?
Red alert!
Dangerous driving!
Dangerous cooking!
Dangerous playing!
I can’t believe you, Officer Snail!
How am I supposed to drive with all of these red cards?
As long as you learn to drive safely, you’ll be fine.
Let me demonstrate.
How long is this demonstration going to take?
Usually, it takes around ten days.
What?
Let… Let me explain!
No need to explain.
I don’t deserve to be the traffic safety captain.
I speeded and nearly caused an accident.
I don’t deserve to keep the Big Tree’s traffic safe.
The traffic safety captain badge I’ve dreamed of
is finally mine!
Isn’t it just a badge, though?
Back in the day,
I lost to Officer Snail during my traffic safety captain testing,
so I missed out on getting this badge.
With it,
I’m now the Big Tree World’s traffic safety captain!
Captain Justice Spider, the little goats are super cunning.
They must be rigorously inspected!
On the trains!
As long as Justice Spider finds even the tiniest problem,
I can lock up all of you guys!
When that happens, both the Energy Seed and the goats will be mine!
There’s nothing bad here; let’s…
leave.
You can leave, Wolffy!
Captain Justice Spider, there are hazardous materials!
Where?
Here!
Isn’t that just soda?
Don’t underestimate them; soda can be very dangerous!
See?
It’s too dangerous!
You’re right, it is!
You’re all under arrest!
The Energy Seed is mine!
This isn’t yours. Don’t meddle with it.
I’ll keep it safe.
But…
I’ve come to visit you, little goats!
Stay… Stay away!
Their sentence has not ended yet.
You may not privately contact them.
I can just get the Energy Seed first!
I’ve gotten you at last!
Do not meddle with other peoples’ belongings.
If you do it again,
I’ll lock you up, too!
I… I’m sorry!
Look out!
Thank goodness I was quick
so that the juice wasn’t spilled.
They’re causing a traffic accident?
I shall arrest you!
He’s just a child playing with toy cars!
How is that wrong?
If it’s a big deal, we’ll stop playing!
Have this car!
You purposefully hit me with a car?
Attacking Captain Justice?
You’re coming with me, too!
Hold on, Captain Justice Spider.
Have some soda and calm down!
Soda?
You’re carrying hazardous materials on your person! Come with me!
Wait a minute!
Captain Justice Spider,
you can’t randomly arrest people like this.
I’m the traffic safety captain now.
I’m in charge!
How dare you question my rightful decision!
Also,
you didn’t brush your teeth this morning!
You’re arrested, too!
Everyone has been captured.
What should we do now, Mr. Slowy?
Don’t worry, everyone.
Officer Snail will definitely show up and do us justice!
Officer Snail really did show up!
Become the traffic safety captain again, Officer Snail.
I almost caused a traffic accident.
I don’t deserve to be the traffic safety captain.
Only after Justice Spider became the traffic safety captain
did we realize how good you were before.
It’s too late.
I’m no longer qualified to be the traffic safety captain.
Yes, you are!
Wolffy?
It’s all my fault, Officer Snail.
The truth is…
Officer Snail losing control of his vehicle wasn’t his doing.
I was thinking about other stuff at the time
and didn’t find you to explain what happened.
How dare you, Wolffy!
I have a key.
I can make up for it by taking everybody out.
Hurry and stop Justice Spider, Officer Snail!
But… I couldn’t even tell if I’d done something wrong.
How could I still be a good captain?
You are the best traffic safety captain!
Although you’re a bit talkative,
you’re just thinking of our safety!
Officer Snail,
I support you as traffic safety captain!
You’re the Big Tree’s best traffic safety captain!
Everybody…
Alright.
For you guys,
I will become the traffic safety captain once again!
Yay!
After my tireless efforts,
the Big Tree World’s traffic has become much smoother!
This isn’t smooth traffic at all!
There isn’t any traffic!
Justice Spider,
give the traffic safety captain badge back to Officer Snail right now!
How dare you guys disobey my commands!
I shall arrest you all!
If you’re arresting them, you have to ask me first.
I’m the real traffic safety captain!
Looks like we’ll have to do this the old-fashioned way
to determine who is the real traffic safety captain!
Deal!
Go, Officer Snail!
Officer Snail has to win!
I have supporters, too.
Go, Officer Snail!
The old rules state
that whoever reaches the finish line first is the traffic safety captain!
Ready, set, go!
Oh no, I’m out of fuel!
You can’t give up, Officer Snail!
You can definitely win!
Go, Officer Snail!
Officer Snail,
use these!
The title is mine!
Officer Snail crossed the finish line first!
Thank you guys.
I lost again.
I’ve gotten back the Energy Seed for you guys.
Please be careful when driving.
Roger that!
END