Marching to the New Wonderland
The Gift
How come you’re waiting over here for a ride, Andy?
I’m here to deliver a parcel to you guys.
Why would we have a parcel?
This says
that the general manager is having a birthday party today
at the Juice Ponds,
and we’re invited.
A birthday party? There must be lots of good food!
We can have some fun today!
How come there’re only five invite tickets?
I don’t know; all I do is deliver parcels.
I’ve got to go. There’re still lots of invites to send out.
Mr. Slowy, how do the six of us
split five tickets?
Drawing lots!
Why’d I have to be the one who can’t go?
I’m going to get all dressed up for today’s party!
I wonder what kind of good food is at the party.
I have to finish these up first and eat more there!
Paddi, have you seen my gift box?
No, I haven’t.
If only I could go to the party as well.
What’s this?
My crystal cup!
I went through a lot of trouble to find that!
It’s my birthday gift for the general manager!
Pay me back!
I didn’t break it!
Why would you break my crystal cup?
Really, I didn’t break it!
Am I such a rude goat?
Sparky…
You guys…
None of you guys believe me!
Where did you put your crystal cup, Andy?
I left it behind on your train earlier.
I come back, and it’s like this.
Oh no, this was all my fault!
All done!
As long as I give her this gift in front of the goats,
both the Energy Seed and the goats will all be mine!
I’ll be back!
Why don’t any of you believe me?
Sparky!
I just took my train out
and found a crystal cup that’s exactly the same!
You can just return it to Andy
and forget about this whole thing.
Doesn’t that mean I have to admit to breaking it?
No way!
What should I do?
I know!
I’ll give this gift back to Andy.
That way, he won’t be mad at Sparky anymore!
Help!
I, Wolffy, am not too bad.
Making another one only took three minutes!
That’s odd. How come I’m not sore
after falling from so high up?
Because I’ve cushioned you!
Help! It’s Wolffy!
Thank goodness the gift is alright.
Andy!
Paddi?
Andy,
this is the crystal cup that Sparky wanted me to pay back to you.
Sparky is paying it back to me?
Yep!
He spent a very long time
searching for an identical crystal cup!
It turns out that Sparky has a sharp tongue but a soft heart.
Tell him that I’ve forgiven him already.
Resolved at last!
General manager! General manager!
What a beautiful gift!
Why isn’t it the popping fruit?
This is for you, general manager!
A popping fruit?
Popping fruit?
My popping fruit is over there? Now’s my chance!
Why isn’t it exploding?
I’ve failed again!
How dare you send me a popping fruit, Andy!
You’re fired!
I can’t believe you set me up, Sparky!
How did this happen?
I must find the person who broke Andy’s gift!
Sparky!
Tell me, why did you set me up?
What?
Playing dumb? I thought it was the crystal cup you paid back,
but it was actually a popping fruit!
The general manager fired me just now!
Popping fruit?
I didn’t send you anything.
Andy!
Truth is…
I was the one…
who broke your gift!
It was you?
I know you two are good friends, Paddi,
but you can’t help Sparky with this kind of stuff.
I mean it.
I thought that if I returned the gift to you
under Sparky’s name, everything would be fine.
But I don’t know why the gift suddenly turned into that!
Paddi,
who’d have known that you broke the crystal cup?
Explain the whole deal to me first.
I’ll definitely succeed this time!
These popping fruits…
How come you have these popping fruits?
Well, uh…
Could it be
that you were the one who put the popping fruit inside the gift?
I have to tell everyone!
Don’t you dare?
So that’s what happened.
I’m sorry, Sparky.
Can you forgive me?
Fine.
Help me!
Andy?
Andy!
I’m over here, Paddi!
Don’t worry about me right now.
Hurry to the birthday party
and stop Wolffy from placing popping fruits!
Apparently, the popping fruits are Wolffy’s!
I remember now!
Paddi,
let’s hurry to the birthday party
and stop Wolffy!
Morning Sun!
Hurricane!
Go on! You have to succeed!
Wolffy?
Hand over the Energy Seed right now,
or else I’ll make these two popping fruits explode!
Chill out, Wolffy!
I’ll take you inside to get the Energy Seed!
How come these popping fruits
are identical to the popping fruits from earlier?
Perhaps…?
—Morning Sun!　—Hurricane!
Did you think I’d have only one controller?
—Thunderbolt!　—Rainbow!　—Lightning Angel!
A shield can’t protect against my popping fruit!
How is this possible?
You’ve only destroyed one popping fruit; there’s still one more!
Look behind you, Mr. Wolffy!
Look out!
I’ll be back!
General manager,
are you okay?
I’m okay, Andy.
I wrongly blamed you.
I now declare Andy reinstated!
Yay, Andy!
Thank you guys!
END