Marching to the New Wonderland
The Zombie Fungus
Is this a gift for me?
The kids get it.
Please sit, Grandpa Beetle.
Grandpa Beetle, this is a cake for you.
I’ll give you a massage.
Jonie is still the best.
What’s the matter with everyone today?
They’re all ignoring me.
Mr. Slowy must be very happy
seeing us respect our elders so much!
We’ve arranged for you to relax in luxury
with a 24/7 total body check.
Please come with us.
He’s already gone insane.
This is going to have serious consequences!
Capture him!
General manager,
the zombie fungus is now fully contained.
What’s that?
There’s still one more!
Quick, capture him!
What are you doing?
Looks like he’s not doing too badly.
Please come with us.
We’ve arranged for you to relax in luxury
with a 24/7 total body check.
Me too! Me too!
We only serve senior goats.
See? This is honoring the elderly.
You guys should learn!
But we have been.
While I’m not around, you guys have to make sure to eat on time,
take baths, do your chores, keep guard,
and clean up.
Yes, Mr. Slowy!
That’s it.
I’ll head off, then.
Thank you.
The old goat has fallen behind!
The Sticky Tree Sap Gun sticks to you for fun!
If I trap all of the ants with tree sap,
catching that old goat is a piece of cake!
It’s tree sap, after all; once it sticks, it sticks!
It’s gone!
Old goat, I’m coming for you!
What are you guys doing?
Let me go!
Infection?
Fungus?
I’m not sick!
Help me!
Didn’t they say luxury relaxation?
Why doesn’t the TV here have a screen?
Perhaps it’s not plugged in?
Doctor, where is the extra-strength medicine for the infected?
Extra-strength medicine?
The extra-strength medicine…
is right here.
What’s all this colorful stuff?
It’s so good!
Especially these colorful beans!
What are they made of?
There’s even massages? Not bad!
He’s so happy even though he’s been caught.
Looks like we can’t contain his illness anymore.
We must use our last resort.
Before using our last resort,
let the little goats meet him one last time.
When are you coming back, Mr. Slowy?
We still have road to cover.
We’ll see.
The ants here are treating me very well.
They’re reluctant to let me leave!
Excuse me,
is there anything we can do for you?
See?
They treat the elderly much better than you guys do.
Now,
the last of the most luxurious services remains.
When it’s done, you may go home.
Alright; I must try this one out!
I’ll be back later!
Hello!
What did you guys capture Wolffy for?
He’s grown zombie fungus on his head.
We’re taking him through decontamination.
Growing fungus?
Decontamination?
Oh no!
They don’t think
that Mr. Slowy growing grass on his head means that he’s sick, do they?
Wolffy?
It’s locked!
What now? What should I do?
Don’t even think about it.
As long as you have grass on your head,
they’re not going to let you leave.
Grass?
This is just smart grass; it’s not a disease!
It won’t grow if I don’t think!
No wonder they treated me so well.
I can’t give up, either!
It’s gotten longer?
It looks like they’re even more sick.
Take them to the decontamination site!
Yes, ma’am!
After taking this warm bath, you’ll be cured.
However, this medicine smells absolutely terrible.
Let me explain!
You think they’ll listen?
We’d better think of a way to escape.
You’re right.
I’ll think of a way to escape!
Actually, you better not!
Hurricane!
Help!
Mechanical arm, activate!
Stupid tree sap!
Are you okay, Mr. Slowy?
I’m so happy to see you guys.
I won’t ask for anything anymore.
Being able to be with you guys is enough!
We’ll treat you better from now on!
The fungus… died?
It’s a miracle.
Congratulations, you’ve recovered!
Mr. Slowy wasn’t sick to begin with.
A reunion?
Did you forget about me?
Wolffy!
That’s right; we forgot about you!
You must undergo herbal therapy.
I’ll be back!
END