Marching to the New Wonderland
Full Speed Ahead
We haven’t found food for many days now.
I’m hungry.
Come over here, guys!
These fruits look super weird.
Who cares?
Let’s just eat until we’re stuffed!
All I wanted was to get some dessert,
but who knew that my staple food was here, too?
It’s Wolffy!
Trying to run?
Watch this!
How come a fruit still explodes?
I’ll say, Weslie,
it’s a good thing that earlier,
those weird fruits didn’t stick to us.
These are exploding fruits.
It has adsorptive properties.
Once it sticks to you, you have to continue moving,
or else it’ll explode.
We really do have to thank Wolffy this time.
If it weren’t for him, we’d be the ones in trouble!
As the saying goes, illness enters by the mouth.
Make sure to not eat random things.
I found some food, Mr. Slowy!
Tell me,
how long will this last us?
How powerful do you think this one is?
It should be enough to send the Magic Trains flying.
Throw it out, now!
Here’s a super vacuum!
What should we do?
I know!
Use shovels, everyone!
As long as we keep moving,
it won’t explode!
I worked hard to find this.
Why must we throw it away?
I have an idea!
As long as it moves with the train,
it won’t explode!
I’m sorry.
I didn’t know that it was an exploding fruit.
Forget it.
As long as we keep moving ahead at this speed,
we’ll think of something eventually!
This is bad!
The road up ahead is blocked!
We’re going to hit them!
Hit the brakes!
I can’t!
If we stop, the exploding fruit will explode!
Then what?
Good thing we added jumping mode earlier.
Watch out!
Vehicle inspection?
We can’t stop!
It’ll explode if we stop!
Don’t panic!
Tibbie, you’re up!
I…
I know!
Weslie,
thank you for the heads-up!
We should be safe for now.
A cliff has just been detected up ahead, Mr. Slowy!
What should we do?
Don’t be scared; you’ve got me!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Go!
Great!
Thank goodness we’re okay.
Nothing can stop us from advancing!
Just a bit more!
I just want to grab a fruit.
How could it be this hard?
Here comes my happiness!
Let’s speed up, Weslie!
Hurry, speed up!
Get us up there!
Oh no!
It’s Wolffy!
This is bad, Weslie!
Wolffy is catching up to us!
Oh no, Sparky!
Something’s wrong with the train!
It’s no big deal; watch this!
Sparky was so quick.
Thunderbolt can move again!
No, he’s not finished.
I’ve got you guys!
Mr. Slowy!
Little goats,
we meet again!
Hand over the Energy Seed right now!
I’m giving you guys two choices.
One: I’ll eat you.
Two:
hand over the Energy Seed and then I’ll eat you!
Aha!
Why is it me?
This is your chance to make up for it!
Fine… Fine, then!
Wolffy!
I surely won’t tell you
that the Energy Seed is on me.
So the Seed is with you?
Give it to me, Paddi!
Stay away!
Give it to me!
This thing…
feels so familiar for some reason!
You’re right!
This is your favorite, the exploding fruit!
Oh, not this thing again!
Mr. Wolffy,
big thanks for saving us yet again!
I’ll be back!
END