Marching to the New Wonderland
The Power of Knowledge
We can relax at last!
Since we’re all free today,
let’s catch up on the last few days’ classes.
Seriously?
Mr. Slowy, in order to deliver the Energy Seed faster,
my Thunderbolt’s power system needs an upgrade.
Upgrade?
Upgrading Thunderbolt
requires understanding of its components.
Here we go again.
Thunderbolt’s recycling system converts electricity into magnetic force.
It was designed on the basis of
the Wattery-Ohmen-Telas-Newton theory.
The specifics of this system are—
Stop!
Mr. Slowy, we can’t delay delivering the Energy Seed.
Right, right.
We better hurry and get on the road!
We’ve driven for seven days straight; aren’t you guys tired?
We should rest for a bit.
We’re not tired at all!
Let’s get on the road!
These kids.
They would rather drive than stop and study.
How come none of the kids want to listen to me talk?
Wordiness.
It’s the biggest barrier to communicating with children.
Kids nowadays
have very rich intuition.
However, nagging hurts their intuition.
Moreover, it directly affects their physical and mental health.
Goodness!
What…
What in the world have I done?
Then what should I do?
Want to communicate with children without barriers?
Want to be a child’s best friend?
Yes, yes! Tell me!
Stay tuned for the next episode of Professor Beetle’s Lecture!
Isn’t it just getting rid of wordiness?
Piece of cake!
One second to freeze!
That’s how cool the Cryolaser is!
Why does it take one second and not two?
Why is it a laser and not ice cream?
Why did you make a freezing gun, Daddy?
Why?
Son,
how come you have so many “why”s?
Well, I just want to know!
Let me try it, Daddy!
Don’t!
Little kids can’t play with such dangerous things!
See?
It’s really very dangerous.
Don’t be scared, Daddy!
I’ll take you for a warm bath.
I’d like that, son.
All that you’re doing is finding Mr. Slowy
to ask whether to go left or right.
Do you need to bring this much stuff?
Yes, we do!
A few days ago, we just asked Mr. Slowy one thing,
Have you eaten, Mr. Slowy?
and he lectured us for three days and three nights.
This time, we must prepare for it!
Mr. Slowy?
What’s up?
We just wanted to ask…
whether we should go left or right.
Left.
You’re done?
I’m done.
Mr. Slowy has become more concise!
But…
Why should we go left?
The left path seems like one we’re very likely to get lost in.
It’s safe.
He’s so straight to the point!
Is that mask your newest invention, Mr. Slowy?
This is the Concision Mask I made based on the algorithm of the increase and
decrease in trade-offs combined with the artistic conception of word order
and the principle of probability theory in both liberal arts and natural science.
It can sum up a thousand words in just a few,
turning wordy sentences—
concise.
Concise! Concise!
What’s this?
It smells a lot like maltose!
Don’t lick that!
Oh no!
What is this, Mr. Slowy?
Is it dangerous?
This is not good.
I’m trapped in resin; I can’t get out.
Good thing the kids are still okay.
Still okay.
Glad you’re okay! We’ll pull you out.
Don’t come over here!
Come over here!
Alright!
Work together to pull Mr. Slowy out, everyone!
Help us!
What should we do, Mr. Slowy?
Such a dangerous spot, yet you dared to step into it?
This is tree resin!
It’s very hard to get out once you’re stuck!
Now that you’ve all jumped in,
who’s left to rescue us?
We were wrong, Mr. Slowy.
What should we do now, though?
Let me rescue you guys!
Stay away!
Am I supposed to listen to you?
No way!
Why didn’t you tell me that there’s resin?
I did; I told you to stay away.
Sirius,
rescue me!
shovel up this pool of resin!
Even Sirius can’t…
Game over, it’s game over…
Daddy,
what are you guys playing?
Stay away, son!
Hurry and call your mom over here!
Mommy said that if Daddy still can’t find any food,
he just shouldn’t come home.
If that’s the case,
then only Wilie can rescue us.
No way, old goat!
Are you trying to get my son killed?
This is tree resin; if we don’t get out now,
we’ll all turn into amber!
Amber?
Do you have any solutions, old goat?
When resin is rapidly cooled, it solidifies faster.
Solidified resin is extremely fragile.
So as long as we can quickly freeze the resin,
we’ll be okay.
Son,
hurry and get Daddy’s Cryolaser gun!
Okay!
Daddy!
Toss it to Daddy!
Oh no!
What now?
I’ve got it.
Wilie,
make a bridge out of bark and leaves.
Walk across it and activate the Cryolaser.
No, that’s too dangerous!
Don’t worry.
Grandpa Slowy says that I won’t sink.
I want to rescue Daddy!
I want to rescue everyone!
Wilie!
Keep it up, son!
There’s no rush; take your time!
Keep it up, Wilie!
Don’t be afraid, son!
Keep stable; you can do it!
Don’t be afraid; don’t stop.
Lay down and crawl slowly
to increase your thrust surface area.
Increasing the surface area takes away pressure, so you won’t sink.
You’re Daddy’s good son!
Why is frozen resin so fragile?
Why didn’t Wilie sink?
Why isn’t resin edible?
That’s the power of knowledge!
Actually, it’s the power of my Cryolaser gun!
Why did this happen again?
Don’t be scared, Daddy.
I’ll take you for a warm bath!
I’d like that, son.
END