Marching to the New Wonderland
Paddi’s Fake Sickness
He’s got a fever.
It must be because he’s too exhausted.
Then I’ll drive for the time being!
I’ll cook!
I’ll take care of Weslie!
The tasks have all been taken.
I don’t need to do anything, then!
Then Paddi
can have the rest of the tasks.
What task?
Why do I have to do the most difficult task?
You can sleep after eating.
If only I could be in his place!
I’ve fully recovered!
Thanks for taking care of me for the past few days, everyone!
My head is so warm; I’m so dizzy.
My whole body is so weak!
That’s too bad, then.
Too bad? What?
We’ve prepared a big dinner
to celebrate Weslie’s recovery.
Looks like Paddi won’t be able to join in.
Dinner? Where?
Wait!
This mushroom is toxic!
You can’t be this upset over not eating a mushroom, can you?
It’s not that!
Perhaps you’re emotional after I rescued you?
No!
Then what are you crying for?
I bit my fingers!
Hold on.
You also drank the mushroom soup earlier.
How come you’re not poisoned?
Don’t worry; my venom also happens to be the antidote,
so I’m fine!
Come have some toxic mushrooms, little goats!
We’re running low on food.
Gather some extra food, everyone!
Yay, time to find food!
Look, there are lots of mushrooms over there!
Eat them, little goats!
Hold on!
Does the old goat know that these are toxic?
Wash them before eating.
Wait!
These mushrooms are big, so we must eat them slowly.
Otherwise, it’ll cause indigestion.
You’ve been poisoned, Weslie!
Want the antidote? Use the Energy Seed to trade for it!
Poisoned?
What do you mean, “poisoned?”
Did you not eat the toxic mushroom?
I just yawned a bit, is all.
I’ll be back!
I can’t believe that such pretty mushrooms are toxic.
Good thing we didn’t eat them!
Paddi, why did you eat it?
Don’t worry; I’ve eaten it, and it’s fine!
It’s so good; you guys should try some!
Here it is!
What Paddi ate is the triangle mushroom.
It’s a type of toxic mushroom.
Toxic?
What kind of symptoms come from eating it, Mr. Slowy?
Firstly, you’ll laugh and cry.
Hilarious!
Sand got in my eyes!
Laughing…
Crying…
Next, you’ll do somersaults.
I’m so hungry.
Somersaults?
Can we still save Paddi, Mr. Slowy?
Paddi has triangle mushroom poisoning.
I’m afraid that he…
“Triangle mushroom: a type of toxic mushroom.
“Symptoms of poisoning include laughing, crying,
“somersaulting, muscle cramps, alopecia, and paralysis.”
Tasty!
“Sweetheart mushroom: non-toxic.
“Tasty and edible.”
They got it wrong. I’m not poisoned!
I’ll go tell them!
For the time being, we have to take care of Paddi.
If he needs anything, help him.
A happy life is all about
eating, sleeping, and repeating!
Time for medicine, Paddi.
Fine. Happily ever after comes with a price.
Awesome, Mr. Slowy!
Paddi won’t be sick anymore after drinking the medicine.
No, no. I can’t get better that quickly.
Oh, yeah!
The book said that biting random things is a symptom.
Paddi’s biting things!
Don’t! Don’t bite that!
Who put a rock inside my pillow?
Mr. Slowy says that sleeping on hard pillows helps sick people.
The next symptom is muscle cramping.
I’ve got muscle cramps!
The right arm is next.
Both legs are next.
In severe cases, even his head will cramp!
And when he cramps, he’ll cramp for an hour!
What should we do now?
Doesn’t Wolffy have the antidote?
Then let’s go to him.
Going to Wolffy is too dangerous!
I’ll just keep thinking of solutions.
It turns out that pretending to be sick is exhausting.
But my happily ever after has only just begun!
Hot, hot, hot!
Paddi, I’ve come to clean your room.
The book says
that after physical changes to the body,
paralysis is next!
What are you guys doing?
Don’t worry, Paddi.
Weslie’s already gone to Wolffy for the antidote.
What?
Hand over the antidote, Wolffy!
Not until you hand me the Energy Seed first.
Once Paddi gets better,
we can still get the Seed back.
Wolffy, catch!
No!
Paddi, what are you doing here?
I wasn’t poisoned to begin with!
What?
I didn’t eat the triangle mushroom.
I just pretended to be poisoned because I wanted to slack off.
Darn it, the Energy Seed!
Hurricane!
I must get the Seed back!
They’re definitely mad at me.
I was worried about dinner, but here you are now!
It’s my mistake, so I’ll make up for it!
Fire!
Outrageous!
Watch how I’ll deal with you, Paddi!
You’ve already been surrounded, Wolffy!
Does everyone… forgive me?
Paddi,
magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
I’ll be back!
Justice Spider!
Help me, Justice Spider!
Justice Spider,
I’ve fallen victim to the toxic mushroom!
Give me the antidote!
But I have a tooth cavity
that needs a month-long treatment.
I can’t produce venom right now.
All finished cleaning!
Anything else I need to do?
There’s one more!
What is it?
To reward your quick cleaning,
we’re treating you to crackers!
My happily ever after!
END