Marching to the New Wonderland
The True and Fake Summit
What’s wrong, Wolnie?
There’s yet another wrinkle on my face!
When are you getting the Energy Seed?
Uh…
I’ve already disguised Sirius as the Magic Train!
Perhaps the goats will fall for it,
and we won’t have to do much!
You’re not fooling anybody with this “disguise.”
I’ve already tried everything, Wolnie.
I just can’t think of any other way!
If you can’t get the Energy Seed, then forget it.
Let’s just go home.
Really, Wolnie?
I’m only going back to get face masks!
Hello. Please receive your parcel.
What is this?
I’m sorry, the parcel just now was misdelivered.
I thought this was the Magic Train.
If I lose the Energy Seed’s delivery map again,
I might be fired.
The Energy Seed?
It was misdelivered?
You can have it back, then!
Thank you!
Wolnie, the Energy Seed and the goats will be in our hands very soon!
So where exactly is the Big Tree’s Summit?
This place
isn’t the same as the place that Grandpa Beetle’s map had.
Grandpa Beetle called to tell us
that he’s asked Andy to send a new map to us.
Your parcel is here!
It’s finally delivered!
Are you sure this is the map?
How did this happen?
Without a map, how do we know the way?
It’s alright; I looked over the map.
I know the way.
Do you really?
Don’t worry; this is my mission now.
Even without a map,
I’ll still take you guys to your destination!
Since we don’t have any other way,
we’ll just have to trust him.
Alright!
This way!
There’s no road up ahead.
I guess it’s not this way.
It should be the one in the middle!
I guess that was also wrong.
This way.
No, no, that way!
Left!
No, no, right!
Do you know the way or not, Andy?
If I remember correctly, it’s in this direction.
I found something!
This sign shows the way to the Big Tree’s Summit!
Then let’s get going!
I’ll stay out here, Paddi.
How come?
We’re almost there!
It’s better for me to wait for you guys outside.
It’s fine!
This must be where the Energy Seed is placed!
Let’s open the box together, everyone!
I’ve got it at last!
Wait a minute!
Why don’t we take a group photo first?
Sure!
I hate photos!
Ready?
Three shots!
Something’s not right with the statue!
Congratulations!
You’ve figured it out!
What are you doing at the Big Tree’s Summit, Wolffy?
There isn’t any “Big Tree’s Summit” here!
I knew you guys would come,
so
I specially prepared this Wolffy’s Summit for you all!
So you’re one of Wolffy’s!
I’m not!
How could he possibly be one of mine?
All he did was misdeliver a parcel,
allowing me to see the map before you guys could.
Give the Energy Seed back to me!
Let’s go help Weslie!
Oh no!
The signal isn’t good here.
I can’t detect Thunderbolt!
Then what should we do?
I’ll take you guys to the real Big Tree’s Summit!
We might run into Weslie!
Do you really want us to trust you again?
I wouldn’t lie to you guys!
I’ve seen this terrain on the map!
How can we know you’re telling the truth?
Andy definitely didn’t mean to take us to the wrong spot.
Let’s give him another chance!
Right now, both Weslie and the Energy Seed are in danger.
We have to try again!
Andy, take us there!
There’s no road ahead again.
I remember the map correctly, though.
How can this be?
Don’t lose hope, Andy.
There must be some other way!
Paddi,
you still trust me?
Of course!
We’re friends!
Andy might have been right!
It looks like the Big Tree’s Summit is behind the leaves!
Then let’s get on our trains!
Come on, Andy!
No thanks; I have to go back now.
Do you not want to see what the Big Tree’s Summit is like?
I want to see.
But I can’t abandon
the ancestral traditions of the ant colony.
There’s not much time left.
You guys go!
Okay!
When we’re done delivering the Energy Seed,
I’ll tell you what the Big Tree’s Summit is like!
The Energy Seed is mine!
You guys are here!
For the sake of Wolnie…
Today, no matter what,
I must get the Energy Seed into my hands!
I can’t hold on anymore!
I’ll help you!
Come on, Weslie!
The Energy Seed!
Run, everyone!
If there’s no Energy Seed,
then I’ll just turn you into mutton hot pot!
Let’s see if you can run after I block your path!
Looks like we’ve escaped Wolffy.
What is this place?
We’re at the Big Tree’s Summit, aren’t we?
This must be where the Energy Seed is placed!
But we don’t have the Energy Seed right now.
Paddi!
Your parcel is here!
It’s the Energy Seed!
How did you find it?
It fell from the sky.
Paddi and the others
should be at the Big Tree’s Summit by now.
Who threw that?
Isn’t this the Energy Seed
that Paddi and the others have been trying to deliver?
I have to hurry and send it over!
But we can’t go to the Big Tree’s Summit.
Who cares?
Thank you, Andy!
In our hearts, you’re the best courier ever!
Look!
The Energy Seed is finally mine!
END