Marching to the New Wonderland
The Toppling Big Tree
Oh no!
I’ve finally gotten you!
Take back the Seed, now!
Can’t you be more accurate?
You guys are evil!
Where there are evil people, there is me!
I’m here to help, Wolffy!
Justice Spider
has arrived!
Are you okay, Wolffy?
I’m fine.
Who are you?
I’m your best friend, Wolffy!
Those goats were harassing me again!
Today, I must teach you evil goats
a real big lesson!
We’re not harassing him!
It’s he who is harassing us!
Help us get the Energy Seed back, Justice Spider!
If we don’t have it, the entire Big Tree World will die!
Cut the nonsense. You guys are coming with me.
There’s nothing for you here.
You can leave.
I’ll leave them to you, then, Justice Spider!
You can leave them to me!
It’s finally mine!
How exactly do we use this Energy Seed?
I didn’t ask the goats.
Maybe it’s like this?
For the honor of the Energy Seed!
See? It’s working!
What’s going on? This isn’t the kind of power I wanted.
What the heck is going on?
Wolnie, this place isn’t safe! Let’s get out of here!
The Big Tree is starting to wither!
Justice Spider, look!
What should we do now, Weslie?
The Big Tree World is dying right now!
We must deliver the Energy Seed to the Big Tree’s Summit
in order to stop this disaster!
I’m not trusting you guys!
I’m going to teach you guys a lesson!
Look!
You’re going to stay there!
That place is terrifying! What is he going to do to us?
I’ll make you
take a three-month course in justice with me!
Look, this is a sign that the Big Tree is dying!
It’s very dangerous here!
What “sign” of “dying?”
This is just my house’s elevator!
Wolnie, make sure you and our son put on your seatbelts!
Don’t run away!
Sit tight, Wilie!
There’s more?
Wolnie!
Wolffy!
Wolnie! Son!
Thank you, Officer Snail!
Right now, the Big Tree is dangerous all over.
I’ll take you down safely.
Thank you, Officer Snail! Thank you!
Keep your eyes on the road!
Drive in the right position!
Class begins once you’re all done eating!
We’ve been caught!
You still want to run away!
Help!
You guys stay here; I’ll go help them!
Help us!
Let us help you! Just let us go!
Lightning Angel!
Help!
Justice Spider!
Since you all rescued so many insects,
I’ll trust you for now!
It’s not safe here; get out of here, now!
Wolffy?
Give the Seed back to us, Wolffy!
What a garbage “seed.”
It has no energy in the first place!
What?
I think it’s safer higher up!
I think it’s safer farther down!
I don’t care; I’m taking everybody higher up!
You can’t!
We must take everybody farther down, where it’s safer!
Actually, now is not the time to be arguing about this.
Well, in that case, let’s fight it out!
Fine!
Let’s not argue.
You two are so in sync, aren’t you?
Who’s in sync with him?
We better go to the Big Tree’s Summit now.
I’m not going!
I can’t risk my family.
I’m going back to Green Green Grassland!
Until we meet again!
Right now, let’s take the survivors to a safe place.
The Big Tree’s Summit is too dangerous.
Alright. Then we’ll get going.
Be careful!
Goodbye! Thank you guys!
—Higher up!　—Farther down!
I feel like going with Weslie and the others would have been safer.
This road is way too dangerous!
The Magic Trains!
Thunderbolt!
I can’t believe that Hurricane sacrificed itself for me!
My Lightning Angel!
I want to go find Morning Sun!
Wait!
The Magic Trains have already sacrificed themselves for us.
We can’t let them down.
Right now, we have to hurry and rescue the Big Tree!
Out of the way!
Sirius?
Place the Energy Seed!
Grandpa Beetle?
Old beetle,
when you ran to me and said you’d take my family to a safe place,
was said place the Big Tree’s Summit?
How in the world is it safe here?
Don’t worry about that right now.
Quick, place the Energy Seed in the Big Tree’s Summit
so the Big Tree can regain life!
Why isn’t the Energy Seed working?
I told you!
That garbage seed already has no more energy!
Then where did the Seed’s energy go?
Even this place is starting to topple!
What now?
END