Marching to the New Wonderland
A Magical Journey
As seasons change, the Big Tree’s energy depletes,
and the Big Tree begins to wither.
The Big Tree World enters imminent danger.
Only a new Energy Seed
can stop the disaster
and restore the Big Tree’s vitality.
The Energy Seed is useless! Everyone, run now!
I told you so!
That garbage seed already has no more energy!
How is that possible?
Thank you guys!
We’re very happy to be able to help you guys out!
Let’s just get out of here! This tree is a lost cause!
The Energy Seed is still here!
We still have hope!
The Big Tree is still struggling.
We can’t leave it behind!
The Big Tree’s Summit’s already collapsed!
Where would you even place the Energy Seed?
I know a place.
The Energy Seed’s final point of energy transfer is the Big Tree’s Heart.
Directly putting the Energy Seed in the Big Tree’s Heart
just might work!
That’s amazing! Take us there, Grandpa Beetle!
If that’s the case, then hurry and get on!
Wolffy!
Let’s go!
Alright!
There it is! Charge forward!
What?
There’s literally no road there!
If we crash, it’s game over!
We’re already in danger! Stop hesitating!
I’ll do it!
Open the door, Wolffy! Here we are!
Get off of me!
What’s the matter? Is that the wrong spot?
The Energy Seed!
We can’t just give up like this!
I’ll go down to get the Energy Seed!
Us, too!
If we don’t leave now, it’ll be too late!
Just come with me instead, everyone!
Take Wilie and leave first!
Fine, we’ll leave first.
You guys can’t be in trouble
before I’ve gotten to eat you!
We can go down right here!
Be careful, everyone!
How is the path already this badly broken?
Thank you.
Justice Spider? What are you doing here?
I figured that you guys might be in danger,
so I followed you here.
You have to think of your own safety while rescuing others.
We’re here, too!
If the Big Tree dies,
our courier company would go out of business!
We’ll also help you deliver the Seed!
Let’s go!
We found the Energy Seed!
I got it!
The Energy Seed!
Weslie!
Wolffy!
I’ve rescued you again, Weslie!
You owe me two bites of mutton now!
Daddy’s a big hero! Daddy’s the best!
Uh-oh, the wither has already spread to this area!
Let’s get out!
The Magic Trains have risen again!
Somehow, they were able to start themselves up
even without any drivers!
Plus, they even assembled with my Sirius!
This glow… Could it be…
I know!
These seven trains absorbed the Energy Seed’s power.
In other words,
these seven trains contain the full power of the Energy Seed!
We just have to take the trains into the Big Tree’s Heart!
We can try!
Then let’s go!
Okay!
Goat-wolf synergy,
invincibility!
This is… Green Green Grassland!
Mr. Slowy!
We’re back in Green Green Grassland!
Was I… dreaming?
Mr. Slowy,
weren’t we saving the Big Tree World just now?
Did we do it?
I think we did it!
Look!
We did it! We did it!
I’ve also succeeded in catching goats!
Brillant, Wolffy!
Let’s play together at home, Brother Paddi!
Help me, Hurricane!
What “Hurricane?”
Hurricane has already turned into seven-color energy!
There’s no way this “Hurricane” thing is going to show up!
It’s just a Hurricane; what’s scary about it?
Trains! The Magic Trains!
I’ll be back!
Thunderbolt…
Wonderful; you’re back!
Our journey isn’t over yet, kids.
Are we all ready for a new journey?
We’re ready!
Magic assembly,
unmatchable energy!
END