Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Icebound Ruins
Since ancient times,
wolves and goats were always at war.
After generations and generations of battle,
the relationship between the wolves and goats finally changed.
Wolffy and Weslie’s handshake is the symbol
of a new era of peace between wolves and goats.
However, the path to peace is not as simple as it seems.
There’s no “scientific expedition team” here at all.
Plus, a blizzard just started.
Let’s hurry back onto the Magic Trains.
Wait for me!
At this rate, you might as well just roll over here.
Help me!
Who the heck was the one who decided to come to this place?
You.
It’s so hot!
Water!
Mr. Slowy?
Where are you going with all of this stuff?
A scientific expedition team has discovered some ruins at the Ice Pole.
They’re inviting me to investigate with them.
Ice Pole?
That must be a very cold place!
Actually, the Ice Pole used to be an ocean.
It turned into an icy, snowy place
after it froze during the Ice Age.
Can we please come with you, Mr. Slowy?
Alright.
Yay!
On the way, you can practice writing travelogs.
No!
Alright, we better get going.
Okay!
Otherwise, none of us will have time for writing travelogs.
Here I come, little goats!
It’s Wolffy!
Wolffy?
Wolffy!
It’s Wolffy!
Don’t push!
One at a time!
Thank you, Wolffy.
I’d actually like for you guys to call me Uncle Wolffy.
Okay, Wolffy.
Where are Weslie and the others?
They went to the Ice Pole for a scientific expedition.
Going to the Ice Pole during such hot weather must be so much fun.
Sparky and Weslie have been shoveling snow for a while now.
Whats taking them so long?
We’re done shoveling at last.
We’re about to freeze to death.
Come inside and get warm.
Is there someone out there?
How… How could there possibly be anyone out in such a blizzard?
Bring the Magic Trains to maximum power.
We might just be able to move.
Okay!
Magic Trains, full speed ahead!
We did it!
But where are we supposed to find the expedition team?
It’s just snow, snow, and more snow.
There aren’t even any signs around.
How are we supposed to find them?
Look, guys!
There they are at last!
It looks like the expedition team is right up ahead.
Hold on.
Don’t you guys think
that this sign is very suspicious?
We’ve come all the way here, so we should at least check it out.
I think I already see the expedition team’s campsite.
Let’s go check it out, Weslie.
Alright.
What the…?
Why is this place completely deserted?
Be careful, guys!
Look, Weslie!
This puppet looks just like me!
I’m coming to rescue you!
Sirius, go!
At the time, this is how I drove Sirius
to defeat the evil Black Cloud,
saving Weslie, his friends, and the Flying Islands.
Wow!
Daddy’s amazing!
That’s for sure.
When are we going on another adventure?
Adventure?
Silly,
don’t you like having Daddy to play with you every day?
Bad news!
Mr. Slowy and the others sent an SOS!
They must be in danger!
Daddy!
I’m going to rescue Weslie and the others right now!
You’re awake.
Where are we?
We fell from the top.
Don’t worry.
I’ve already sent an SOS to Goats’ Village.
Let’s press on for a bit
and see if there’s another way out.
Mr. Slowy, why does it feel like we keep descending?
Uh…
I see the exit!
Could this be the legendary pre-Ice Age undersea capital?
It looks like the legend is true.
Legend?
Legend has it that long before land animals emerged,
there was a civilized city under the sea.
Within it was unexplained, mysterious technology
that was well before its time.
But then, the sea froze over.
Archaeologists speculate
that it was a phenomenon caused by the Ice Age.
Ever since then, the city has been sealed in ice.
It looks like there’s something at the top!
Could it be treasure?
The treasure is mine!
Translation missing
Aside from this pillar,
it’s completely empty.
It looks like it really is completely empty.
This must be a clock.
A clock?
Is it useful in any way?
This…
This was made for the purpose of allowing elderly people to better read it.
Isn’t it just a thing for telling time, then?
Let’s go. I’m hungry.
Wait a minute!
Such a big clock dial can’t be just for show.
Maybe it can even let us time travel.
Welcome, travelers!
Its him!
Don’t!
It might be a trap!
If he’s not captured,
he’ll bring harm to Goats’ Village again!
You think you can defeat me?
Only in your dreams.
Stop messing around, Weslie!
Thunderbolt!
Oh?
You have nowhere to run!
Can’t catch me!
Thunderbolt,
speed up!
Well, it’s nothing more than a fast-running train.
There’s more!
Oh no!
You have nowhere to run!
What else can I do?
Here we go!
Go, Thunderbolt!
Goodbye, Weslie!
Thunderbolt,
full speed
ahead!
Stop—
Stop dreaming!
Oh no!
This Ice Pole is massive.
Without a flare, where in the world am I supposed to search?
What’s with the sudden earthquake?
What the…?
Quick!
Quick, guys, get out of here!
What the heck?
What the heck is that?
Thank you, Weslie!
I’ll be on my way now!
Hey!
This flare is a little too strong, isn’t it?
This is the worst part of adventuring!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Is… Is that…
a…
a dinosaur?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter