Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats ran into Werewolf while on their scientific expedition.
After he lured Weslie into breaking the ice spiral
and causing a huge problem, he fled.
It was then that a big dinosaur appeared.
What will they do next?
What is this place?
It looks like I’ve gone the wrong way.
Sorry.
Not again!
Weslie?
Are you okay?
Of course I am.
It’s coming again!
Let’s hurry and go help Weslie!
Come on out,
Magic Trains!
Get on, guys!
Mr. Slowy!
We’re okay,
but
the Magic Trains have been crushed by the ice.
We’ll stay here and think of something.
Tibbie, Jonie, go help Weslie.
Okay!
Wolffy, while I distract it,
you get behind it and wait for a chance!
Now’s my chance!
That failed.
Wolffy!
Are you guys okay?
Jonie!
Tibbie!
Mr. Slowy told us to come help you guys.
Where are Mr. Slowy and the others?
Their trains have been crushed by some ice.
They’ll come later.
Never mind that right now.
It’s coming again!
Let’s go, Wolffy!
Now!
Take this!
It’s stuck at last.
Then let’s hurry and go help Mr. Slowy.
We have to finish shoveling this ice and snow
and go help the others as soon as possible.
Okay.
But how… how come we’re not getting any closer?
I know, right? I’m so tired.
I’m the one who’s tired!
Why did you shovel back all of the snow that I shoveled?
Sorry about that.
Apparently, the legend hidden in these ruins
is also hiding some mysterious energy.
I must analyze it thoroughly.
Mr. Slowy!
I’m fine.
Be careful,
Paddi!
I’m sorry!
I need to get the magnifying glass back.
Where’d it go?
I told you to be careful!
It’s faster to shovel this way, though.
The trains can move again, Mr. Slowy!
Where did Mr. Slowy go?
Mr. Slowy! Mr. Slowy!
Where did you go?
This is Mr Slowy’s scroll.
Sparky, come look at this!
Sparky?
Where’d he go?
Mr. Slowy?
Stop scaring me!
Weslie, help!
It’s about to fall into the sea!
Let’s rescue it!
I agree!
I disagree! If we rescue it,
won’t we be in even more danger?
Uh…
I don’t care.
Wait a minute!
If you’re going to rescue it, you have to think of something first.
Stop it, Weslie!
The ice block is failing!
Oh no!
Weslie!
I’m fine. Go rescue the dinosaur!
Tibbie!
Jonie!
Now’s my chance!
Go!
It’s us now, Jonie!
It’s stopped!
Leave the rest to me!
We did it!
I think it likes us now.
Bad news! Bad news!
Mr. Slowy and Sparky have vanished!
Huh?
I’ve scanned with Hurricane already,
but I just can’t find them!
I think we should split up and search.
I’ll search over there with Jonie, then.
I’ll go with Wo—
I’ll search over there.
Paddi,
stay here and wait for us!
I guess I’ll just go with Wes—
Don’t leave me all alone!
Don’t worry,
the dinosaur will keep you company.
Don’t just eat other people’s snacks!
—Mr. Slowy!　—Sparky!
Help me!
I hear a cry for help.
Stop licking me!
How did they just vanish into thin air?
Stop chasing me!
Paddi!
Paddi?
You didn’t eat Paddi, did you?
How can it be?
Even I have never eaten mutton!
Paddi,
are you in there?
Paddi?
Paddi!?
Thank goodness you weren’t eaten by the dinosaur.
You’re saying that like I should’ve been eaten by you instead!
Oh no!
Run, guys!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let's create this world with laughter
Let's march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let's create this world with laughter
Let's march to the new wonderland with laughter