Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
after the dinosaur crisis was resolved,
Slowy and Sparky suddenly vanished.
While searching for them, a mysterious area was discovered.
What in the world is this place?
Spacetime Chaos
Help!
That was close.
Why are we floating?
Look outside, guys!
This is such a weird place.
Where the heck are we?
Are you guys okay?
Yes. Were you the one who rescued us?
My name is Doudou.
My name is Tibbie.
I want to ask if you’ve seen Mr. Slowy and Sparky?
Mr. Slowy? Sparky?
While I don’t recognize them,
they’re likely to be up there.
Come with me.
Wait for me!
This place is huge, and there are so many people!
Yep!
This is the Spacetime Transit Hub.
I’m the Hub’s administrator.
Weslie!
It’s Mr. Slowy and Sparky!
It’s only been a few minutes. You don’t need to hug, do you?
What just happened?
This is the third quake already!
Why is this place quaking?
Long, long ago,
I was working at the Hub within the Dimension Gem,
monitoring the stability of each timespace.
But suddenly,
the Dimension Gem was shattered!
A quake occurred at the Hub,
spacetime got messed up,
and people from different timespaces appeared in the Spacetime Tunnel.
So I closed the cracks right away,
gathered them here,
and I’m now sending them back to their original timespace.
How come there’s still a crack over there?
That crack was made after the Gem shattered.
If not everyone is sent back to their original timespace
before the Ruins’ clock hand makes a full circle,
the Gem fragments won’t be able to reform.
When that happens, there won’t be just a quake.
The entire world will reset
and turn back into a single ocean.
Therefore, in order to restore spacetime to what it was,
the anachronists
must be sent back to their original timespace,
allowing the Dimension Gem to reform once again.
It was my fault, Doudou.
I was the one who broke the Dimension Gem!
You?
I mean, Weslie didn’t do it on purpose.
We’ve caused you a lot of trouble.
Is there any way we can help you out?
Could you guys help send people home?
Of course!
Speaking of which, is that dinosaur also an anachronist?
It must be.
Let’s hurry and send it home!
Just stay right here.
This is the waiting room.
They’re all waiting for a ride.
How are we supposed to know which timespace they’re from?
Scan them with the Timespace Ring.
Come on in.
This is the Control Center.
The system is checking the dinosaur’s information.
Apparently, it’s from the late Jurassic period.
Let’s send the dinosaur back home right now!
Okay!
You guys will have to wait.
This is the first time this has happened,
and I only have one Spacetime Shuttle.
It just left to take an anachronist home and hasn’t returned yet.
No need to wait. We have vehicles!
They’re all broken.
Ours still work. Let’s use ours.
Great! We can send a few more people at a time.
Passenger with ticket number thirteen, please come here!
Coming!
Wolnie!
Out of my way!
Yay! I’m finally eating mutton!
Don’t eat Weslie, Wolnie!
No, Wolnie!
Who are you? Don’t stop me from eating mutton!
Since I’m the one who broke the Dimension Gem,
I’ll send Wolnie home.
No, I should be the one to send her.
It was my mistake. Let me do it.
It’s more fitting that I send her home.
Let me do it.
No, I’ll do it.
—I’ll do it.　—I’ll do it.
How about you two do it together?
We’ll send the dinosaur home, then.
We’re coming, too!
Your trains have been connected to the Control Center
If you need anything, you can contact me.
The spacetime paths have been set up. You’re good to go.
Okay,
I’ll go check to see if there’s anyone else in the Tunnel.
I’m going to the next train to eat mutton.
Little Wolnie,
what’s so good about mutton?
Let’s eat strawberries.
I don’t eat strawberries with seeds.
Don’t worry,
there’s not a single seed left.
Here.
There really aren’t any seeds!
I’m thirsty. I want to drink milk.
But I only drink—
I know you.
Thirty-seven degrees exactly.
Is it good?
You know me so well!
However,
you’re stopping me from eating mutton,
so I hate you!
Hate?
Wolnie says she hates me!
Here we are.
I’m home!
What’s going on?
Why are there dinosaurs here?
Finally, we’re done with the dinosaur.
Bad news, guys!
What happened?
Come with me to the Control Center.
I’ll explain.
Doudou,
dinosaurs have appeared in Wolnie’s timespace!
We can’t hold them off for much longer!
Weslie!
How is this possible?
There aren’t supposed to be dinosaurs in that timespace!
Something went wrong in the Spacetime Tunnel.
The designated path got shifted,
causing the dinosaur to be sent to a timespace post-extinction.
Then, the dinosaur, who was already about to lay eggs,
continued to live down the timeline
with several baby dinosaurs.
The babies kept growing and reproducing,
which is why dinosaurs have now appeared in Wolnie’s timespace.
Since that’s the case,
let’s hurry and send the dinosaur to its correct timespace.
So many dinosaurs! What should we do?
Watch this!
Wolffy, are you okay?
Wolffy!
This is bad!
Help!
Thunderbolt can’t take much more!
Stupid dinosaurs,
I’m right here!
You didn’t even realize that I escaped, huh?
Wolffy?
Wolffy!
Come and get me!
Wolffy is distracting all of the dinosaurs!
Oh no, it looks like Thunderbolt is stuck!
Come on! Move!
Run, guys!
Don’t worry about me!
Wolffy!
No!
How beautiful.
Is this Heaven?
What’s going on?
Weslie,
we just sent the dinosaur back to its correct timespace.
The messed-up timeline should be repairing itself,
and the dinosaurs over on your side should be gone by now.
Are you guys okay?
Take care. My name is Wolffy.
Make sure to remember me.
I’ll always remember you!
Goodbye, Wolffy!
“Wolffy?”
Who’s that?
Yay!
I’ve left Wolnie a beautiful memory!
No, you haven’t.
Once people return to their correct timespace,
they’ll lose any memory they had of being in other timespaces.
But why?
Remember,
you can’t just change history as you wish.
All done.
Let’s send more anachronists home.
You’re just in time.
I have something important to tell you guys.
We didn’t go to the wrong place again, did we?
It’s not that.
It’s that I was doing a headcount just now
and realized that a portion of the anachronists left the Spacetime Tunnel
and went to your timespace.
I guess we’ll have to find them as soon as possible
in order to prevent the world from resetting.
This is all my fault.
Don’t say that.
As long as we find all of the anachronists,
the problem will be solved, won’t it?
Then let’s get started right away!
Darn it, the trains are all broken.
I’ll take you guys on Sirius!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let's create this world with laughter
Let's march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let's create this world with laughter
Let's march to the new wonderland with laughter