Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats and Wolffy arrived in the Spacetime Tunnel.
While helping Doudou send the anachronists home,
they realized that a portion of the anachronists
had gone to Green Green Grassland.
The goats and Wolffy must find them right away.
An Unfamiliar Little Goat
Sirius is falling apart!
My driving skills aren’t too bad.
You say you’re good at driving,
but you destroyed these plants.
That’s not because of Wolffy.
That’s the shattering of the Dimension Gem
causing spacetime to distort.
That means we have to find the anachronists quickly.
Hurry and go search for anachronists, guys.
I’ll take care of repairing the trains.
My Sirius needs some repairs, too.
Hello, Wolnie?
Where are you?
Come back and cook!
Wolnie?
Wolnie!
Wolnie’s not in trouble, is she?
Did she run into a robber?
Did a dinosaur appear over there?
Has a new enemy appeared already?
Sirius, just hold on for a bit longer
until I get to Wolnie!
I’m coming to rescue you, Wolnie!
Wolnie, what happened?
You’ve done a lot.
So now you’re back, huh?
You’re okay?
Me?
Why would I not be okay?
Then why did you
“Ah!”
on the phone?
I was just about to tell you about that. Come here.
Where did you catch this goat, Wolnie?
What do you mean, “catch?”
When I was coming back from grocery shopping,
he suddenly fell from the sky and passed out,
so I took him in.
I see.
I haven’t met this goat before, though.
Ask Weslie about him later.
Hurry up and start cooking!
I will!
Wolffy, I’m tired!
I’m thirsty!
Continue cooking.
Wolves!
They’re going to cook me!
What should I do now?
I need a weapon first!
Aha!
Still not awake?
To be honest, this goat looks quite chubby.
The grassland in their village must be very fertile.
I knew it! They do want to eat me!
I’ll ask him when he wakes up,
and then I’ll take you to their grassland for fun.
Yay!
Not only do they want to eat me,
they want to eat our entire village, too!
I have to finish making this weapon.
My exquisite design
goes perfectly with mung beans.
I’ll use my Bullets of Justice
to punish evil and promote good,
gaining the ultimate victory.
All done!
Sitting for too long makes my legs tired.
I’ll help you with your legs!
How about a foot wash as well?
Now!
Don’t be discouraged, Marky.
How’s the pressure, Wolnie?
Translation missing
Now!
My soup!
Rags! Rags!
There’s not a mouse, is there?
Wolffy, come clean this spot up!
I did it!
Where’s my notebook?
Is it still back there?
That was a breeze
Where are you from,
and where are you going, my friend?
I… I’m sorry!
I’ll go turn myself in!
I just wanted to ask him what timespace he’s from.
Was I that scary?
We’d better hurry up and keep searching.
How long will it take for us to find all of the anachronists?
Is that a primitive person?
Wait!
I’m not a bad guy!
Where’d they go?
Weslie, I rescued an unfamiliar goat.
Come over here and tell me who he is.
I think I saw a primitive person.
Once I find them, I’ll—
I just saw them!
I’ll call you back later!
Wait a minute!
Wolffy,
I’m going to get groceries for soup again.
I hope that when I return, there won’t be any more mice.
Yes… Yes, ma’am.
I’m headed out, then.
Take care.
It’s not here.
Where’d that mouse come from?
I can’t believe it spilled my wife’s lovely soup.
How hungry was that mouse?
It even ate my rubber bands.
Hands in the air!
Oh no,
I’m about to be braised,
maybe steamed,
or even salt-baked!
Why does Wilie always put his toys in random places?
I’ll just put it away.
Where’s the goat?
Did the mouse eat it?
Was… Was it just me?
Maybe it was really just me?
I have to find it fast.
Why is this house so big?
Found it!
This isn’t my notebook.
Of course it isn’t. This is my son’s notebook.
Don’t…
Don’t eat me!
I don’t eat goats anymore.
Now, the goats and I—
Don’t eat me!
Don’t
eat
me!
Don’t eat me!
Go on.
Why were you chasing me?
Because—
I know.
You must be a fan of mine.
Fan?
Oh, well.
Now that you’ve found out about my celebrity status,
I’ll give you an autograph.
You’re a celebrity?
Why are you dressed so primitively?
Do you mean my clothes?
This is this year’s trendiest clothing.
I just knew that it’d stop being original
after I wore this.
Sorry, you’re not who I’m looking for.
Stop!
I’m a celebrity!
Look!
There are a lot of your fans over there!
There aren’t any fans.
Where’d he go?
I didn’t think they’d be the wrong person.
I’ll just find Wolffy for now
and think of something later.
A notebook?
Goats’ Village’s logo?
Did someone from the village lose it?
I’ll take it back to Goats’ Village and see whose it is.
Is it you, my fan?
Oh no!
I knew it!
Stop!
I haven’t given you an autograph yet!
I’m sorry, I really wasn’t looking for you!
Okay, are you injured at all?
Did I scare him because my face looks too stern?
It’s alright, kiddo.
Like I said, I don’t eat goats anymore.
Don’t fall for it, Marky!
If wolves don’t eat goats, what do they eat? Fried rice?
You look very pale.
Do you have a fever?
Someone help me!
Your forehead is so cold.
Is it too cold in here for you?
Wait a moment,
I’ll get you a blanket.
Alright.
Are you feeling a bit warmer now?
I’ll go make you a cup of hot tea.
Stay here and rest.
My tea tastes very good!
Tea that a wolf likes?
Could it be…?
Mmm!
With how sweet my smile was just now,
he’ll definitely trust that I won’t eat him.
Where’d he go?
Why did that little goat leave without even saying goodbye?
If I don’t run now, I’ll get turned into tea!
I’ll have to find my notebook at a later time!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter