Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the unfamiliar goat who thought Wolffy was going to eat him
escaped Wolf Fortress
and ran into Weslie.
Does Weslie recognize this skittish little goat or not?
New Friends
I found it!
I’ve finally found my notebook!
Is this notebook yours?
Yeah,
it even has my name,
“Marky.”
Well, don’t lose it again.
Where are my two rocket blueprints?
They’re gone!
They were tucked in right here!
Did I…?
Sorry, I might have accidentally lost them earlier.
Don’t worry,
I’ll make sure to find them!
Take me with you!
That wolf must have forgotten about me by now, right?
Where in the world are my blueprints?
What do the blueprints look like, by the way?
My yellow blueprints are about this big,
and they have purple-colored drawings of rocket designs on them.
The blueprints can’t just have flown out by themselves.
Where in the world are they?
Right there!
So it was the naughty bear cubs who took the blueprints.
I’ll go get it.
Wait for me!
This goat is working so hard to help me get back my blueprint.
His selfless figure appears to grow larger and larger.
Sorry.
It’s okay.
How are we supposed to get to it if it’s all the way up there?
It’s time for another miracle,
the Creaky Squeaky Flying Machine!
Just run while pulling the two strings on the sides, and you’ll fly!
Are you okay?
I knocked down the blueprint!
Wrong one!
—Let’s go home.　—It’s those bear cubs throwing paper airplanes again.
Your blueprint is still in the tree.
This time,
it’ll work.
You’re flying!
Got it!
Marky!
I
couldn’t possibly fall.
Brother Goat,
look!
I got it!
Great!
To be honest, your invention is actually pretty cool.
Thank you!
You’re the second person to encourage my innovations.
By the way, what’s your name?
My name is Weslie.
My name is—
Your name is Marky.
I remember it.
Alright, let’s go find the rest of your blueprints.
Actually,
I’ll ask my friend to help us.
We’ll find them faster that way.
Come with me.
Weslie’s friend must be a very talented goat.
Why am I back here again?
Wolffy,
I need your help with something.
Open the door!
Why are we here?
I’ve been looking for you, kiddo!
You left without saying a word last time.
Do you know him, Wolffy?
He’s the little goat I was telling you about earlier.
It’s kind of a long story, so I’ll tell you more inside.
Did he faint again?
His health is quite poor, huh?
…And that’s what happened.
By the way,
I accidentally lost his rocket blueprints.
Could you help me find them?
No problem!
I’ll just use my satellite to search.
It’ll take a photo of every corner of the grassland.
Afterwards, we’ll take our time and hunt through.
This many?
A familiar ceiling
and familiar sounds?
Weslie? What’s he doing with a wolf?
By the way,
do you have any tools that could be of help?
Asking a wolf for help?
What is he doing?
Good eye!
Have a look at my Extendable Goat Catcher!
“Goat Catcher?”
Great! With this, I’ll be able to catch them,
and I won’t lose them again.
He’s going to use that thing to catch goats?
Weslie is one with the wolves?
I’d better get out of here.
I must tell all of Goats’ Village
that Weslie is a traitor!
There’s one more thing.
I forgot to take my notebook again!
What did I run so fast for?
I’ll just go back and get it.
Marky!
He left again?
His notebook is still here, so he can’t be far.
Where are you, Marky?
I’m back again.
Why did you go outside, Marky?
I’ve been caught!
My notebook!
How do I get it back?
Look!
I don’t see anything.
Where’s the notebook?
Marky!
Great, I got my notebook back!
Marky, where are you going with your notebook?
The last blueprint is in a canyon near here.
Let’s go get it together!
I can’t believe
you guys are using the blueprints to trick me!
Huh?
Have fun conspiring with the wolves, Weslie!
Marky!
That little goat disappeared again.
If you hear me, come out!
We can talk about this!
I’m not listening to you guys.
I don’t want to lose our friendship.
Marky, please come out. Let’s talk,
okay?
Friendship?
How did you know that we’re all called Marky?
That doesn’t matter, though.
What matters is that we’re friends now!
So you weren’t talking to me!
Is that
my blueprint? It really is down the canyon!
Was I wrong about them?
Marky,
all of the stuff I just said was for you.
Get away from the canyon edge, Marky!
It’s very dangerous!
Just listen to us, you little goat.
Just listen to us.
—Marky!　—You little goat!
We warned you that it’s dangerous!
I might as well get the blueprint, too.
Wow!
I’ll slowly fly to the ground now.
So thirsty…
How come it’s paper?
—Marky!　—You little goat!
I’m coming to rescue you!
I’ll leave Marky to you!
No problem!
Watch this!
Come here!
Don’t worry.
It’s okay,
little goat.
I’d rather fall!
What are you doing?
We’re not going to fall!
Is that…?
They sacrificed themselves to save me!
Maybe they weren’t so evil after all.
Weslie!
Wolf-something!
You…
You guys are over here? But over there—
My name is Wolffy.
Plus, I’m not dead.
Here.
Thanks, guys!
That hug just now was to thank you two,
but I’m keeping my distance now
because you, Weslie, are helping wolves catch goats!
Catch goats?
Exactly which village are you from, huh?
How do you not know that I don’t eat goats anymore?
If I wanted to eat you, you’d have been gone a long time ago.
Yeah,
Wolffy is friends with us goats.
Then…
Then what did you want the “Goat Catcher” for?
I meant using it to catch the blueprint
so it wouldn’t get lost again.
Really?
Fine.
If you wanted to eat me,
you would have eaten me while I was asleep yesterday.
There we go.
Now that you mention it,
the name of this thing made me think that
you’re
still catching goats.
Alright.
Then I’ll change the name of it
to Green Green Grassland’s cutest,
so much that even the goats think so,
“Little Cutesy!”
I’m sorry, I was wrong about you guys.
It’s okay.
Thank you, too.
Are we still friends?
Friends!
Then let’s play together again sometime!
I’m going home now. Goodbye!
So which village is that kid from, anyway?
I have no idea.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter