Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Weslie asked for Wolffy’s help in finding the blueprints.
Marky saw this and thought Weslie to be a bad guy,
which led him to danger in a panic.
In the end, Weslie and Wolffy worked together to rescue Marky,
resolving the misunderstanding.
Marky Enters the Village
I forgot to ask Marky where he lives.
Marky?
Weslie?
Didn’t you go home?
I live right here.
Goats’ Village?
Yeah.
Marky,
where in Goats’ Village is your house?
Why haven’t I met you before?
Look, Weslie!
It’s flying by itself!
Wow,
I’m inside of this box!
This is so cool!
Marky,
have you not seen these things before?
No, I haven’t.
I left Goats’ Village for only a short while,
and now, there are so many novelties!
Novelties?
Could it be that Marky isn’t from this timespace?
It looks like I’ll have to report this to Mr. Slowy.
Can you wait for me a bit, Marky?
I’ll be right back.
Okay.
He’s so fast.
Even bushes can move?
I’m almost done with repairs.
This next step is very dangerous.
I must get it right.
Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy, are you okay?
I’m okay.
How about you rest for a bit?
No need to.
I’m learning from failure,
and I’m almost there.
One more time!
By the way, did you need me for something?
I found a goat that’s from a different timespace.
Well… Well, that’s great!
Go look after him.
I’ll find you once I’m done repairing the Magic Vehicles.
Okay.
I’ll head back, then.
By the way,
bring me a can of engine oil later!
Got it!
Next up…
I can’t concentrate at all.
Never mind, I’ll just rest for a bit.
Marky!
You’re back, Weslie!
I have something to tell you.
What?
Are you saying that I might not be from this timespace?
Once our Village Chief finishes repairing the Magic Vehicles,
I’ll take you to see him.
Magic Vehicles?
What are those?
The Magic Vehicles are vehicles that our Chief made for us.
We’ve flown them into the sky,
swum them under the ocean,
and taken them onto the Big Tree to adventure.
They’re awesome!
Your Chief is incredible!
Can I go see him right now?
He’s busy with repairs right now, though.
That’s great!
That way, I can learn on the spot.
I’ve always wanted to become a scientist.
If there’s an opportunity to learn, I’m taking it.
Marky…
Alright, then.
I’ll take you to him right now.
I must destroy the Magic Vehicles.
I can’t let the goats take those people home.
Our Chief is right inside.
So this is a Magic Vehicle?
It’s so cool!
Oops, I forgot that Mr. Slowy asked me to bring engine oil.
Marky,
I’m heading back to grab something for our Chief.
Okay, sure.
I won’t disturb your Chief.
Okay.
This is so cool!
No touching.
It’s a wolf!
Darn it,
I’ve been caught!
I have no choice but to finish him off.
So the peace between goats and wolves is real?
Even wolves can be Village Chiefs?
Village Chief?
Chief, I’ve heard that you’re a great, great inventor!
Apparently, he thinks I’m Slowy.
An assistant is just what I needed.
I love to invent, too!
Can I ask if there’s anything you need help with?
Sure.
What the…?
I know!
This must be
a tool for inventing!
Correct!
You seem to be very talented.
Come and help me, then.
Is this inventing as well?
Of course it is.
Chief!
I’m okay!
Electrical leakages like this one
mean that this area is broken,
so it must be destroyed.
I see!
I must do a good job.
Ah, young people and their speedy work.
I’ll take care of what’s outside.
The control room is all yours, kid!
Okay!
I can’t believe the Village Chief trusts me so much.
I won’t disappoint him!
It’s working!
I guess I am talented!
One more time!
All done!
Village Chief, are you okay?
Why don’t you rest for a bit?
No need to.
Chief!
I must destroy this thing by today!
What’s going on?
We’re flying!
Mr. Slowy! Marky!
What’s wrong, Weslie?
Are you not on the Magic Vehicle?
Then who is?
Marky!
It’s the Magic Vehicle!
Faster!
I’ll just crash this thing into pieces!
Crash into pieces?
Won’t that—
You’ve been fooled!
Don’t!
So he’s behind this!
How is he okay after jumping from so high up?
Marky!
Weslie!
We’re about to crash!
No, I have to stop it!
What now?
Is that…?
Marky? Marky!
Wake up!
Are you okay?
I’m okay,
but the Magic Vehicle—
Magic Vehicle!
My Magic Vehicle!
Mr. Slowy!
It’s you!
Mr. Slowy! My teacher!
It’s really you, Marky!
You’ve aged a lot!
What are these two wings?
That’s my mustache!
Mr. Slowy is
your teacher?
It turns out that my teacher became Village Chief.
Mr. Slowy, since Marky is a goat from Goats’ Village’s past,
why haven’t I heard you talk about him before?
Well, Marky
is Smarc.
Yeah, my full name is Smarc.
It’s nice to meet you.
Dad!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter