Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Marky encountered some twists and turns after entering Goats’ Village.
Weslie found out that Marky
is, in fact, his own father.
What will Weslie do
in the face of his father as a child?
Smarc’s Ambition
Have some more. Help yourself.
Thanks.
The goats of the future are so welcoming,
but
this is way too much.
I can’t eat it all.
Oops, I forgot that Dad is still a kid.
To avoid confusion,
don’t tell Smarc that you’re his son.
Once the Magic Vehicles are all fixed,
we’ll send Smarc home to his timespace.
Hey, Marky, Weslie will take care of you for the time being.
I must treasure these moments
that I’ll have together with Dad.
I heard Mr. Slowy say
that Weslie is living with his dad right now.
I wonder how theyre getting along.
Well, Weslie must be very happy.
I can tell that just by listening.
I accidentally knocked over some books.
It’s alright.
I’ll pick them back up.
This person…
Oh no,
he won’t recognize himself, will he?
This person
is so handsome!
Those are my parents.
They’re working in outer space right now.
Outer space?
I want to go there, too!
By the way,
how did your dad get to outer space?
He went there by inventing his own rocket.
Your dad is incredible!
I want to invent my own rocket, too!
No wonder you were so worried about those blueprints.
My dream is to explore outer space,
and creating a rocket is the first step to achieving it.
Even though everyone thinks that it’s not possible,
I believe that I’ll succeed someday.
You certainly will.
Thanks.
I’m headed out for a bit.
Apparently, Weslie’s dad has thought
about going to space ever since he was little.
Let’s try something.
You’re Marky, right?
I’m Tibbie.
Jonie.
Sparky.
Paddi.
Hello!
Uh…
Hello.
This is for you.
No thanks, I have rockets to make.
We have things that are even more fun.
Come play with us!
But—
Come on!
You actually weren’t too bad for a first-time gardener.
Yeah, and as for being a chef,
you’re very talented.
Your singing voice is also…
also very surprising.
Thanks, guys. But I still want to be a scientist.
Well, I still have rockets to make.
Let’s play together next time.
What now?
All done.
Let’s test its accuracy and sensitivity.
Implementing Lightning Angel’s robotic arm
onto Morning Sun seems to have worked.
What the heck?
Stop it!
I’ll just have to rework it.
Mr. Slowy?
Weslie?
Do you need something?
I have a question for you.
A question?
Sure, ask away!
How do you make a rocket?
That’s easy.
Why would a normal kid ask that kind of question?
It’s Dad.
He wants to make a rocket, and I want to help him.
Smarc?
Weslie,
creating a rocket is the most important thing Smarc will do in his lifetime.
He should achieve it himself
rather than passing the buck.
I understand, Mr. Slowy.
Instead, why don’t you take advantage of the situation
and have him do some fun things with you?
I want to go to the amusement park with Dad,
eat ice cream with him,
watch fireworks with him,
go swimming with him,
and fly kites with him.
Hold on,
just choose one for now.
How about this one?
Thank you, Mr. Slowy.
It’s literally so sunny out.
What’s with the darkness here?
Nothing that we tried worked.
If only Marky’s interests could be changed,
he could become a chef or a singer later on,
and he wouldn’t go to outer space.
That way, he would always be by Weslie’s side.
Guys…
Let’s try to think of something else.
Thanks for doing so much for me, guys!
Weslie!
However, after Dad goes home to his timespace,
he’ll forget everything that happened here
and remember his original ambition instead.
So we did all of that for nothing?
No,
I really appreciate your intentions,
so I’ll treasure these moments.
I’m going to ask Dad to play a game of soccer together.
We’ll play, too!
Okay, let’s go!
Finished at last.
Up next,
launch!
It’s working!
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
I thought it was going to work.
I guess I’ll just have to keep trying.
Why are you guys dressed like that?
That’s because we’re going to have a soccer match,
and we wanted to invite you to play with us.
Sure.
We’ll be waiting for you!
Make sure to come!
This shirt…
Have I forgotten something?
Look, guys!
Is it Marky?
It’s almost dark out.
Marky probably won’t be coming.
Could you not be so blunt?
What if Weslie heard that?
Sparky, with how loud you’re talking, how could he not hear it?
It’s alright.
Let’s keep playing.
Weslie, are you actually alright?
Yes, I’m alright.
—I’m late!
Sorry!
Are you guys still playing?
Of course!
Wow,
even the goal nets are broken.
How come I can’t do it?
Is there something wrong with the ball?
It’s not the ball.
It’s just because you’re not strong enough.
Not strong enough?
What do you think Marky is making us wait here for?
He said he has something to show us.
Look, guys!
It’s Marky’s rocket!
Thanks for the inspiration, guys!
It turns out that the rocket couldn’t fly
because it didn’t have enough fuel.
Congrats! You did it!
Great!
Marky did it at last!
Congrats!
Thank you, Mr. Slowy.
I do, however, also have some good news,
which is that the Magic Trains are all fixed!
Yay!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter