Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Weslie was aware that Marky was his own father.
While keeping him company,
he accidentally inspired Marky
to successfully create the invention of his dreams
and reach his goals.
A Day at the Amusement Park
We can take the Magic Trains out to play again!
Here we are.
This time, not only have I repaired the Magic Vehicles,
I’ve upgraded their abilities, too.
They’re brand new inside and out.
For example, Weslie’s Thunderbolt
has become even faster than before.
—Also, its—　—Open the door, Mr. Slowy!
Sorry.
I can’t wait! I’m going to be the first one on!
Hold on!
Make sure to finish reading the instruction manual before getting on.
Just these.
Just…
Just these?
Yep.
Read them thoroughly.
How luxurious!
How beautiful!
Weslie,
I’ll help you read the instruction manual.
No need for that, Mr. Slowy.
We already know how to drive.
I’ll take a look inside.
I’ve added a viewing function to Thunderbolt.
This way, you can access information at any time.
Lightning Angel now has a costume function.
It can make any costume you want right away.
Sparky’s Morning Sun now has a lot of exercise equipment.
Paddi’s Hurricane now has a cooking function.
Last but not least, Jonie’s Rainbow now has a medical function.
Your inventions are amazing, Mr. Slowy!
Now we can safely send Marky home!
Home?
What’s wrong, Marky?
I’m going to miss you guys.
You shouldn’t have said that, Paddi.
I’m sorry!
Actually,
Thunderbolt still needs some repairs.
You guys can have fun today.
Thank you, Mr. Slowy.
Yay!
I want to go to the amusement park!
Then let’s go together!
Okay!
Yay!
I wasn’t talking about you guys.
You guys still have to search for anachronists.
Yes, sir.
The amusement park, huh?
That one! Let’s do that one first!
Didn’t Mr. Slowy tell us to search for anachronists?
What are we doing at the amusement park?
Well, Mr. Slowy didn’t say that we couldn’t search at the amusement park.
Let’s start searching, then.
Here comes my ultimate!
Bring it on!
Have a taste of this bomb!
I’m having so much fun today.
What should we do next?
Marky,
with how happy you are,
would you be upset if you made a mistake?
Of course I would be.
What’s more important, though,
is fixing your mistakes.
Fixing?
Happy birthday!
Blow out the candle.
Thanks, Dad!
I want to spend a birthday with my dad, too.
Your dad will come back, Weslie.
I’ll go get some food.
There are so many people at the amusement park.
How are we supposed to find any anachronists?
Little goats,
you guys all look so upset when I’m not around.
You’ve missed me, haven’t you?
Leave! You’re in the way of my photo!
Wolffy?
I came to help find people!
Let’s split up and search, then.
Okay.
Where’s Marky?
There, there, Piggy,
don’t cry anymore.
I’m sorry,
I wasn’t being careful.
I didn’t mean to ruin your cake.
My cake!
There, there.
Hey, here’s a rocket.
It can fly!
It’s so pretty!
Thank you!
Let’s go.
Goodbye!
Wasn’t that the first successful rocket that you made?
I can make more rockets,
but if I make mistakes,
I must fix them.
I bought some ice cream for you.
Sorry, they’ve all melted.
Let’s go get some more.
Why am I so unlucky?
Who is it?
Do you know
who you’re talking to?
Who cares about a walk-on like you, huh?
I’ll show you just how powerful I am!
You have nowhere to run!
I’m not running!
I looked over there,
but I didn’t find any anachronists.
There’s none over here, either.
I didn’t find any, either.
That just leaves the roller coaster area, then.
Let’s go together and take a look.
Here we come, roller coaster!
Stop right there!
You missed!
Can’t get me!
This is perfect!
Scared now, huh?
Whats happening?
What’s going on?
Look!
They’re in danger! Let’s go help them!
Morning Sun!
Lightning Angel!
Hurricane!
Rainbow!
Sirius!
Help!
Darn it, I can’t make it in time!
Thunderbolt!
Weslie!
Oh no!
I’ve got you!
Wolffy!
We’ll go rescue other people now.
Paddi!
Watch this!
Tibbie, someone needs help in front of you on the left.
Sparky, someone’s trapped behind you on the right.
Got it!
Don’t worry, I’ve got you.
Help me!
It’s okay.
I’ll fix the track.
Mr. Slowy’s inventions are incredible!
Kids,
it’s getting late.
It’s time to send Marky back home.
Be safe on the road.
Nothing to worry about. I’ll be with them!
Goodbye, Mr. Slowy.
I’m going to miss you, Mr. Slowy.
Don’t be sad. We’ll meet again.
Do you not want to take a ride on my new airplanes?
I do!
I understand, Mr. Slowy.
We’ll be on our way, then.
Goodbye, Mr. Slowy!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter