Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
before they parted, Weslie learned from Marky
how to bravely fix mistakes
and make amends.
Later, the two of them rescued a runaway roller coaster,
foiling Werewolf’s plans.
Meeting Dad Again
Recognition success.
I’ll send Marky home.
Then we’ll help by sending other anachronists home.
On it!
I think someone should remain here with Doudou
just in case something bad happens, though.
You can leave a hard task like that to me.
No!
You’re just trying to slack off!
I don’t care!
Taking back that dinosaur was so dangerous.
I’m not going this time!
Safe travels, guys. Keep in touch.
Okay!
Let’s get going, then.
Wait a minute,
I changed my mind!
It’d be better if I go with you guys for such a dangerous task.
But—
It’s fine,
no need to thank me.
Let’s get on the airplane.
Wait a minute!
I don’t care! I don’t care!
What’s wrong with him?
Do you mind remaining here, Tibbie?
No problem.
Let’s get going, Marky.
Yeah!
I want to help out, too.
Is that…?
I’m going home!
I’m going to make sure to study well when I get home
to achieve my dream of going to outer space.
Marky,
why do you want to go to the cosmos so much?
Do you not like the grassland?
Of course I like the grassland!
However,
the cosmos has many secrets waiting to be discovered.
With your persistence,
you’ll certainly reach your ambitions.
Thanks!
I’ll take a look back there.
I guess he really does just like outer space.
Have some snacks and cheer up.
Pad—
Leave the driving to me.
You go hang out with Smarc.
Thank you, Paddi.
I thought I recognized them.
A hand?
Paddi!
Paddi, wake up!
Wake up!
What are you doing here?
Weren’t you on Thunderbolt?
I didn’t get onto Thunderbolt.
Just now, I…
Dim sum?
There’s nothing good about stuff that just falls into your lap.
I will not eat it.
I’ll just sniff it.
After that, I don’t remember what happened.
Then…
Then who is the “Paddi” on Thunderbolt?
What’s going on, Paddi?
Weslie, I found Paddi at the Hub!
Yeah, I’m at the Hub!
Then…
Then who’s driving?
It’s too late!
Werewolf?
Stop!
Oh no, you don’t!
What’s going on, Weslie?
What happened, Weslie?
Weslie!
Mom?
Dad—
Yay!
Yay, you’re finally awake!
This lady saved us.
Lady?
Mom!
Did we
enter a timespace of the past?
Why were you two little kids
flying such a big airplane?
We were traveling.
That’s way too dangerous.
Sorry.
I’m back.
Are the kids awake?
It looks like they’re fine.
You pulled another all-nighter again, didn’t you?
It’s alright. I can handle it.
Working is important,
but you need to make sure you’re resting well, too.
Weslie,
What happens if you get sick?
don’t you think these two people look a bit familiar?
Remember to eat well and wear more layers.
Why are you crying, buddy?
I’ll take him.
You’re so tired. How about you rest?
I’m fine.
Hey, buddy,
Daddy is taking you to fly on an airplane!
We’re flying on an airplane!
Dad…
Flying! We’re flying!
Let’s fly!
Aren’t…
Aren’t they your—
How’s the situation in outer space?
It’s under control for now,
but it’s still not great.
I guess we’ll have to go there ourselves.
Then,
our son…
It’s too dangerous this time.
I hope Weslie can grow up healthily on the grassland.
Couldn’t you guys not go?
If we don’t stop this catastrophe,
the entirety of Green Green Grassland will be gone, too.
For the sake of everyone,
for the sake of our son,
we have to go no matter what.
I hope that he’ll understand us when he’s older.
Dad…
He will.
I’m sure he’ll understand you when he’s older.
Thank you.
When are we leaving, then?
It could be at any time.
How about we take a photo for the baby?
Could you guys take a photo for us?
Dad—
Mister, miss, get ready!
Okay.
Three, two, one,
say “cheese!”
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
That sound…
Oh no!
Smarc!
What is it?
Go take a look.
I will.
His name is Smarc, too?
So that means I’m…
Have fun being stuck here forever!
Weslie! Apparently, I’m your father!
Never mind that right now!
We can’t stay stuck here!
What’s wrong?
Grab my hand!
Kids!
What happened?
What am I doing here?
These goats are such a pain!
This is so much fun!
What should we do, Weslie?
We have to get in through the door on the bottom!
But how are we supposed to get down?
In a moment, when I tell you to let go, let go!
Let go!
How…
How did you guys get in?
Well, do you have what it takes to catch me?
I won’t accompany you guys back this time.
Have a nice trip!
Stop right there, you bad guy!
I’ll catch you once I get out of here!
—I’d better just send you home first.
—Weslie, come help me!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter