Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Werewolf, disguised as Paddi,
tried to trap Marky and Weslie in a wrong timespace,
but Weslie foiled the plan.
What other things will happen next?
Dad’s Gift
Here we are.
I have to go now.
Thank you for sending me home.
Goodbye.
I almost forgot!
Weslie, don’t leave yet!
I just remembered something.
Wait for me!
Wolffy!
What’s wrong?
Werewolf just attacked Weslie while disguised as me!
Good thing we realized it in time.
Then where is he right now?
We don’t know. Weslie chased him off.
It’s him again! I better not see him!
I see him!
You’ve been surrounded, Werewolf!
Hands behind your back!
I can’t believe that I, Jollie, was found!
Jollie?
So I wasn’t mistaken earlier!
No need to say it. I know!
Come on, want to hug me?
Don’t eat my snacks!
I just remembered something.
Wait for me.
Dad must be making an important invention.
I can’t let anyone disturb him.
Go.
Don’t make noise here.
I can’t believe that the weirdo Smarc has friends.
He looks so weird, just like Smarc is.
You’re wrong
My dad, Smarc, is a genius inventor, you know!
Huh?
He just called Smarc his dad!
I knew it. He’s so weird!
Alright,
don’t disturb Smarc’s in
vent
ing!
Smarc is inventing again!
Get ready, guys!
Don’t let a fire spread
like last time!
What are you guys so nervous for?
So you don’t know?
This is my new invention!
Are you sure you’re able to find Werewolf, Jollie?
Of course I am! I’m Jollie, you know!
But what are you wearing this blanket for?
Since the enemy is in the dark,
we must be in the dark as well.
Found it!
Here it is!
Really?
Isn’t this the same place you started from?
You speak so mysteriously, but you’re just lying to us.
I’ll put a curse on you guys!
Who dropped this ketchup?
Ketchup?
Why do these look so much like a wolf’s footprints?
They’re not mine.
Might they be…?
Let’s follow the footprints and see.
Told you that I possess great magical powers!
The footprints are leading to the operating area!
Hands in the air, Werewolf!
Is that…
Doudou?
Doudou!
Doudou, what happened?
There was a wolf just now
who tried to close the gate of Smarc’s timespace,
but I stopped him.
Where’s Werewolf?
He ran off.
Let’s go after him!
Wait a minute!
Have you guys forgotten that Werewolf can shapeshift?
Oh, yeah.
Then let’s take a look first.
So soft! It must be fake!
Show your true self!
Just give up already!
Oh no!
The actual Werewolf is right here!
Sorry, Doudou!
It’s okay.
Let’s hurry onto the airplanes and go after him, then!
He’s coming out!
Weslie,
this is for you!
What’s this?
What’s that?
This is a…
I was trying to make this birthday cake look like you,
but I guess I’m just too clumsy.
Blow out the candle!
Thanks, Dad!
I want to spend a birthday with my dad, too.
This cake is so good!
Thank you, Marky!
By the way,
I also have—
Hold on.
Weslie,
we’ve found Werewolf!
Come and help us!
I’ll be right there!
I have to go now.
What were you saying to me just now?
They’re waiting for you. Go on.
Goodbye, Marky!
Goodbye!
Goodbye, Weslie!
Thank you, Dad.
Goodbye!
That was awesome!
Did you make these fireworks?
What were you celebrating with these fireworks?
That’s right.
What did I do this for?
Aha!
I can use this to create force for launching!
He’s still such a weirdo.
Maybe he really will get to outer space someday.
Watch this!
Wait, what?
How are the missiles the same?
Stop right there!
I can do that, too!
How does he know that one, too?
Paddi, above you!
Go after Werewolf!
Goodbye!
Weslie!
You have nowhere to run!
Look out, guys!
Darn it,
he’s getting away!
You’ve got me!
Watch this!
You’re no match!
Tibbie, are you okay?
I’m sorry!
I got scared.
It’s all my fault
that he got away again!
It’s alright.
What matters is that we’re all okay.
Oh no!
It’s another quake!
I need to go home and check on Wolnie and Wilie!
Be careful!
I think I just saw Werewolf inside of Hurricane!
You’ve been surrounded, Werewolf!
Hands behind your back!
Are you guys looking for the help of Jollie?
Jollie?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter