Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
after Marky returned to his own timespace,
not only did the pursuit of Werewolf fail,
but they also unknowingly brought the past Jollie to Goats’ Village.
Now,
what should they do?
The Two Eggs
What are we waiting for?
That’s Jollie!
Get him!
You guys couldn’t catch me even if you flew airplanes!
Wait, you actually have airplanes?
Stop, Jollie!
I’m running with my legs,
but you guys are flying airplanes!
That’s cheating!
Those who cheat shall slip on banana peels!
How come I’m the one who slips on a banana peel?
Jollie!
Someone come rescue this handsome, twisted-destined egg!
I’ll get you.
Lower!
Even lower!
Jollie!
I’m only three hundred years old! I’m too young to die!
You saved me!
I guess I’ll give you a few kisses!
Lightning?
What the heck is going on?
What the…?
After all these years of observation,
I have finally become familiar with this new world!
It’s Darton!
I need to let the goats know!
It’s time for me to take over the world!
Mister,
you zapped my brother’s water gun just now.
Pay us back!
There’s no way
I’m paying back a water gun!
Pay us back!
Pay us back now!
Uh…
Don’t shoot me with a water gun!
Stop!
Oh, Darton doesn’t like water?
I don’t need to involve the goats, then.
I’ll capture him on my own.
I just wanted to come and play in this world for a bit,
which is why I ran away from you.
Don’t send me home!
We’re sending you home right now.
Sending only myself home is no use.
Darton came with me this time!
Darton’s here, too?
So Darton was the one who made all of those scorch marks.
We need to find Darton right away!
Let’s go!
Tibbie, you stay here and keep Jollie company.
What do you mean, huh?
You guys are just afraid of me escaping, aren’t you?
Am I that kind of egg?
Yes, you are!
I’ll put a curse on you.
I want to do something to help, too.
Apologies,
I accidentally heard your true intentions just now.
I like girls with ambition, just like you.
You know, I can detect Darton’s approximate location.
With my powers, we can capture him together
and surprise Weslie and the others!
You’re… You’re not lying to me, are you?
My bottom line is that I never lie to girls.
Trust me.
I’ll trust you, then.
Let’s
get going!
Darton is right up ahead!
—Let’s go!　—Okay!
Jollie, have we really come to find Darton?
If not that, then what?
We didn’t come to play, did we?
Well,
is this not playing?
Stop!
Stop chasing me!
See?
The roller coaster takes us all around the amusement park,
so we can see the entire area
and find Darton.
What did you say?
I said this is so fun!
Pay us back!
Tibbie, let’s go look over there!
Jollie, where’s Darton?
Pay us back!
He should be over there!
Jollie,
how come we haven’t even seen Darton’s shadow
after going to so many places?
It’s because you’re walking too slowly!
But
how am I supposed to walk fast while carrying all of the stuff you bought?
That doesn’t matter!
What matters is that Darton got ahead and escaped
because you’re walking too slowly!
So it’s my fault?
No one’s innocent, silly.
No matter what you’ve done wrong,
I’ll always forgive you.
So come with me, Tibbie.
Okay!
Go search the second floor right now!
Pay us back the water gun!
Pay us back!
I’ve finally escaped them.
Messing around with Darton is so much fun!
Darton!
So you were also shooting me with water guns,
Wolffy!
Uh…
It…
It wasn’t just me!
How dare you mess with me!
Unforgivable!
Sirius!
Do you really think you can escape my grip with some stupid car?
How dare you look down on my Sirius!
Bring it on,
Darton!
Wolffy!
Sorry!
You’re not going anywhere!
Oh no!
You’re no match!
He’s gone?
Are you okay, Wolffy?
A little roughed up, but okay.
I’ll help you with repairs.
Oh no, you don’t!
Darton,
return to your world right now,
or otherwise, all of spacetime will reset,
and you’ll disappear!
Don’t think I’m going to believe you guys.
Even if spacetime resets,
the fittest shall survive,
and I am one of them!
Is there any way to stop Darton?
Darton hates water.
Paddi, see if there’s a water source nearby.
We’ll hold Darton back.
How dare you stand in the way of my new world ambitions!
You guys are so clingy!
Weslie, Weslie,
there are no water sources nearby.
I’ll check to see if there are any a little farther out!
Okay.
The rest of us will keep following Darton.
Don’t let him escape!
Roger that!
Not again!
Nope, I still haven’t found a water source.
Next, let’s go to the ice cream shop up ahead.
Darton loves ice cream.
Darton really is up ahead!
Huh?
You didn’t lie to me, Jollie!
I can’t believe we actually ran into him.
Darton seems to be at a disadvantage right now.
Tibbie,
go and give Darton a mortal strike
and show everyone what we’re made of!
I’ll be the shield.
Just go straight to Darton!
Tibbie, what happened?
We can’t move!
It wasn’t my fault.
It was yours.
What kind of tactic was that?
Whatever.
I’ll just finish you guys off!
I’ll help you guys with repairs right now.
Darn it, there’s no time!
How come there’s no water anywhere?
Think of some other solution!
Solution, solution,
solution…
There’s liquid here!
Darton!
Paddi?
Liquids?
Stay away!
Let my friends go!
Come here!
Where’s Darton?
Am I out of soda?
I’m going to avenge myself!
Stop chasing me!
You really think that this stuff can hurt me?
There’s a liquid in there?
We did it!
We’ll just have to forcibly send you home, Darton.
I won’t let you guys catch me!
Come back, Darton!
Goodbye, little goats!
I’ll take my time with you guys once I’ve restored my electricity!
What’s Jollie doing here?
Jollie?
Tibbie is still in there!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter