Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the past Darton and Jollie
managed to escape to Green Green Grassland.
The goats and Wolffy worked together to fight Darton
and finally made him lose his electric power.
The Escape Plan
Lightning Angel?
I can’t believe this!
Once I’m all charged up,
I’ll show you guys what I’m made of!
What…
What is Darton doing here?
This thing is quite flashy.
Good thing my location is on. That way, the others—
No!
Who was that?
Nothing to see here.
Was it just me?
What’s this?
This… This…
Can I use it for charging?
This feeling…
Yes,
I feel as though every inch of my body has been charged!
It’s just a wardrobe?
I thought I could use it for charging.
That was close.
How do I contact the others
without location tracking?
What was that?
Aha!
I hope they’ll follow if they see these.
Wake up, Jollie.
Jollie, what are you doing here?
Where’s Tibbie?
Is she on her airplane?
What the heck happened to you two?
I’ll have to start from this morning.
After I was woken up by my own handsomeness,
I started contemplating what clothes I should wear today.
Get straight to the point!
Tibbie and I went out together,
and Darton has probably taken her by now.
What?
Search for where Lightning Angel is, Paddi!
No problem. I’ll turn on location tracking.
Lightning Angel has no signal!
How are we supposed to find Tibbie without a signal?
As the omniscient Jollie,
I can tell you
that before you find Lightning Angel, you’re going to hit—
Hit?
We’re about to hit it!
We hit…
a bird.
Sorry!
Could that be…?
It’s Tibbie’s.
Let’s search that way.
I’m out!
What should I do now?
What now?
Alright,
this is good enough.
He’s gone?
I’d better get out of here.
No, if I leave,
we’ll lose Darton.
I can’t go.
I’ll just hide for now.
With so many people,
I’ll surely find a power bank for charging.
Hand over your power banks!
Why?
Are you not scared of me?
We’re not.
Well, you guys will be sorry, then!
Who did you say was the sorry one?
Sorry.
I guess I can’t act so mean.
Aha!
I can make myself look cuter first.
That should work!
I’ll do this one.
Excuse me, does anyone have a power bank?
We do.
Great!
Based on your outfit, you look like you must be a dancer.
Come dance with us!
No, I’m just here to borrow—
Useless.
Why is it so hard to get a power bank?
What else can I do?
What’s this?
Why haven’t I seen it before now?
Is there another person here?
So it was just a bow from a toy. I worried for nothing.
Thank goodness.
The clues are gone.
Which way do we go now?
How about I go look in the other direction?
Sounds good.
You guys go that way!
Wait!
As the omniscient Jollie,
I know that Tibbie
must be to the right.
That’s quite random, isn’t it?
I agree with him.
You’ve got my potential.
You’ll catch up to me in another one hundred years!
I discovered some clothes that Tibbie made
while analyzing the road just now.
Therefore, I think that this is a new clue that Tibbie left.
We were right!
You’re so smart, Weslie!
Let’s get going, then.
Okay!
Ugh,
how exactly am I supposed to get a power bank?
Why haven’t Weslie and the others caught up yet?
If I wait until Darton gets fully charged, it’s game over for me.
Nope,
I have to stop him.
Aha!
I can make a trap.
When Darton comes in, I’ll pull,
and I’ll capture him!
This is what I’ll do.
You’re right.
What a great idea!
I’ve been caught!
Stop right there!
Help!
Help?
You guys had the nerve to fight me head-on.
There’s no way I’m forgiving you!
Tibbie!
What’s going on?
We’ve come to rescue you!
I guess they really have come to rescue you.
That’s perfect!
Listen up!
If you want me to let Tibbie go,
trade me power banks,
or else…
Help me!
Don’t hurt Tibbie!
It’s a deal!
Weslie?
Really?
Alright,
let’s trade!
I’ll give you the power bank,
but you have to let Tibbie go first.
I can let Tibbie go first,
but
you guys have to be tied up first.
What?
That’s not what we agreed on just now!
No deal, then.
Wait!
We’ll do it.
Farewell, little goats!
I’m sorry for getting everyone in trouble again.
It’s not your fault, Tibbie.
By the way, where’s Jollie?
I’m right here.
The main character appears at the end!
Surrender, Darton!
You stupid eggshell,
don’t even think about stopping me!
How… How do I fly this thing?
My power bank!
Stop!
Give back my power bank!
I’ll finish you off!
Don’t come up!
Get off!
Jollie rescued us!
For me, this kind of thing is a piece of
cake.
If I capture Darton,
I’ll make sure to take good care of him!
Watch where you’re going!
Isn’t that my house?
Wolnie!
Wilie!
Darton!
Don’t call me “Darton.”
Call me “Chairman,” Wolffy!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter