Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Darton escaped while flying Lightning Angel.
Tibbie tried to make a plan for capturing Darton,
but she herself was captured instead.
Good thing the other goats made it in time
and rescued Tibbie.
Wolf Fortress, Under Hostage
Wolffy,
how dare you spray me with water!
So what?
You were so mean to me before!
Liquids?
Why are there liquids in your house?
I’m mad now!
Apparently, without that group of goats,
you’re nothing much at all.
Let me go!
All of the faucets are blocked at last.
How could you possibly keep liquid-holding things like this?
So many drinks!
I can’t miss a single place with liquids.
I need to let the goats know.
Well?
Did you find anything?
We didn’t find anything. What about you guys?
We didn’t find anything, either.
I didn’t find anything, either.
You’ve just been standing here the whole time and not searching!
Nope. The goats know that I hate liquids.
I need to think of something.
Wolffy,
make me a waterproofing tool, okay?
I’m not helping you.
Mommy,
what should we play now that camp is canceled?
Let’s go find Daddy and play together.
Perfect timing!
Darton?
Why is he here?
I’ll explain later.
What a big egg!
Hello, kiddo.
I’m a good friend of your dad’s.
Darton,
you—
Since you can’t go to camp anymore, why don’t I play with you at home?
Wolffy,
you better hurry up and do the thing that you promised me!
Wolffy…
Fine, I’ll help you make a waterproofing tool,
but don’t you dare hurt Wolnie and Wilie.
Good.
For the sake of protecting Wolnie and Wilie,
I must find a chance to knock him out.
Let’s play the get-rid-of-liquids game.
Like this. Find any liquids for me.
What’s with all of the hydrating mists in here?
I probably bought too many.
Wolffy, hurry up and start making the tool!
Yes, Darton!
Call me “General!”
Yes, General!
Now’s my chance.
Have a taste of this, Darton!
Darton… I mean,
General,
I was just joking with you!
We’re driving! We’re driving!
Wolffy,
what are you doing?
Uh…
General,
I was just trying to see if this shower head’s wrap was secure.
Call me “Chief!”
Let’s go elsewhere to keep playing and destroying.
Okay.
Hello.
The number that you have dialed is currently busy.
Please try again later.
Why can’t I get through to Weslie’s phone?
Why is there a toilet here?
What are you doing in here?
I was… I was ordering delivery.
What would you like to eat, Chief?
Anything is fine.
Let’s keep playing, Wilie.
Hello, an order of pizza
to Wolf Fortress, please.
Aha!
I can have the delivery person send a message to Weslie later.
Look, Chief! The food will be here soon.
We’re flying! We’re flying!
Why couldn’t I get through to Weslie’s phone?
Is this the Grassland Stories Hotline?
I, Jollie,
have a big story to tell you guys!
Yep, it was that dangerous Darton.
Excuse me, I wanted to ask…
I’m so tired!
I can’t walk anymore.
Stop slacking off, Paddi.
Haven’t seen them.
What’s wrong?
Paddi’s trying to slack off again.
Look at Jollie!
Are you guys really not going to come to interview me?
My kind of grace is not one that you’ll see everywhere.
Give me my phone back, Jollie.
I can’t believe they’re not interested in my handsomeness.
Focus on searching, okay?
I’ll put a curse on you guys!
Here’s your food, sir.
Dude, this isn’t our order!
Hey, dude,
would you mind taking the delivery and this napkin to Weslie?
This is very important.
Very important?
I know what to do.
Please leave a five-star review.
Wolnie, what are you doing?
We can’t just sit here and do nothing.
We have to think of something
and rescue Wilie first.
No need to worry, Wolnie.
I’ve already let the goats know.
In a moment, we’ll coordinate our offenses,
and we’ll defeat Darton by surprise.
Great!
Uncle, what are we playing next?
Go away.
I’ll go find Daddy to play, then.
Your dad is busy right now.
Don’t disturb him.
Aren’t I playing with you right now?
How dare you! I’ll—
I’m sorry, mister.
I didn’t mean to.
I’ll…
I’ll make some funny faces for you.
Who’s Weslie?
His order is here.
He’s busy right now. You can just give it to me.
Since Weslie is so busy, I’ll help him eat it.
What great service. They even included a napkin.
It looks delicious!
You’ve been slacking off the whole time, Jollie.
How come I smell food on you?
There isn’t any.
Look at your mouth.
I didn’t eat Weslie’s food order.
Delivery?
I didn’t order delivery.
Wolffy wrote this.
“Darton is at Wolf Fortress. Come quickly.”
He’s found Darton!
Come on, let’s go to Wolf Fortress!
I should just head back to Goats’ Village
and wait for you guys to return in triumph.
You’re not going back alone.
You’re just going to escape again.
I’ll take you back to Goats’ Village.
Playing with little kids is exhausting.
He’s worked so hard to play with me.
What are you doing?
I was wiping the windows, Darton.
The goats?
How dare you betray me, Wolffy!
Mister,
I made some watermelon juice for you!
What happened here?
Why are there still liquids?
What’s wrong with Mister Egg?
Nothing, nothing.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter