Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy, under Darton’s threat,
used various methods to contact the goats for help.
Unfortunately, they all failed.
In the end, it was Wilie
who trapped Darton in Wolf Fortress.
The True and Fake Darton
This is the life I should be living.
Don’t snoop on me!
Who’s “snooping,” huh?
I’m just worried that you’ll escape.
How dare you treat me like this!
So what?
I’ll do this, too.
And this!
I…
I won’t argue with you.
Those who bully me will get their karma!
Another quake!
We have to hurry and send Darton and Jollie home.
Are we leaving right now?
Yes.
No,
I have to organize my clothes first.
You weren’t wearing clothes when you came here to begin with.
I don’t care! I don’t care!
That’s simple.
You can have whatever clothes you want.
Are you ready now?
Not yet.
Uh…
My tooth hurts!
My tooth!
Ouch! Ouch!
Your teeth are very healthy. They’re fine.
I don’t care. It still hurts!
It hurts a lot!
Ouch! Ouch!
You can’t send me home
if you can’t figure out what’s wrong.
That’s too bad, then.
I guess Jollie won’t be able to eat
the premium caramel cheesecake.
Mmm!
Only this quality of cake is suitable for my palate.
Wasn’t your tooth hurting, Jollie?
I don’t want to go home!
You must!
How dare you guys bully me!
Leaving already?
What happened?
A bunch of trees fell over just now.
Could you guys help us move them?
No problem.
Why would the trees suddenly fall over?
Let me out!
You’ve been yelling for the whole day.
Can’t you just let me relax?
I’ll yell all that I want. Why do you care?
How dare you talk back to me!
How dare you question me!
I’ll show you what I’m made of!
How dare you splash me!
Still want to bully me?
You two are brothers. Stop fighting.
We’re not brothers!
But you guys are actual brothers.
I have no such brother like you.
Don’t leave!
Let me out!
I’m hungry!
I need to use the bathroom!
My toes hurt!
We’re not dumb. You’re just lying again.
Are you okay, Jollie?
Ouch!
Just ignore him. He’s just trying to escape.
Let’s go.
Don’t leave!
What’s going on?
Am I hallucinating?
Who are you?
That doesn’t matter.
Here’s a power bank.
I’ll help you distract them while you charge.
Where’s my carriage?
I set you free, yet you have all these requests?
We’re brothers, Darton.
Rescue your big brother, please!
Outrageous!
I can’t believe you’re ignoring the omniscient me!
Guys,
Darton escaped!
Jollie is trying to trick us again.
Oh no,
Darton has actually escaped!
Wrong one!
If only you guys had one thousandth of my intelligence.
Am I going to be stuck here forever?
I’m free!
Run!
Darton,
you have nowhere to run!
Where’d he go?
Let’s use Paddi’s Hurricane to search.
I’m right here!
Come get me!
Stop!
I’m so tired!
Once I finishes charging,
you little goats won’t be foiling my plans again!
Nowhere to run, huh?
Get him!
I can’t let them know that I’m the fake one.
Why doesn’t Darton hate water?
Never mind that.
Let’s get him.
Freedom is amazing!
Before they find out, I’ll find a place to hide.
How dare you run into the omniscient me!
You again?
Wait a minute.
He’s out of electric power right now,
so I don’t have to be scared of him.
What are you doing?
Help!
Come here!
I’m all charged up, Jollie.
How dare you disrespect me!
You splashed me with water,
and you chased me.
Call me “Chief!”
I may not be a fighter, but I’m a hider!
Getting rid of Darton feels wonderful.
Today, I’ll make some good food for Wolnie.
What is Darton doing here?
Help!
Do you need something, Wolffy?
Weslie,
I saw two Dartons running in different directions.
Two Dartons?
We’ve been tricked!
The Darton that we’ve been chasing is fake!
These are the consequences of disrespecting me.
They’re right up ahead.
There they are.
Surround Darton!
Darton,
you’re not escaping this time!
Catching me?
I don’t think so!
You overestimate yourselves.
I only splashed you twice,
but you zapped me for so long?
Am I heavier?
I’m sorry, Darton!
This is what happens when you mess with me.
You shameless egg,
pulling such a dirty trick!
Good game, good game.
What are you doing here, Jollie?
No!
Can’t you see that I’ve done my part?
We can finally send them home.
You black-hearted egg!
If it weren’t for you, I’d have escaped by now!
Me?
If it weren’t for you,
I would never have been captured again!
Can’t you two brothers just calm down?
We’re not brothers.
I can’t trust that Darton ever again.
I’ll just act alone.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter