Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
everyone was getting ready to send the egg brothers
back to their own timespace,
but they fell for Werewolf’s trap.
What will happen next?
A Great Maternal Love
Figured out which timespace they’re from.
Great.
Let’s get going!
Wait a minute, please.
Currently, there are a lot of people waiting.
Would you guys mind taking a few extra people back?
No problem.
So who’s going to take these two?
I can do it.
Jollie and Darton are so cunning.
What if it’s too dangerous?
The cunning ones are the ones who lock me in a cage!
Goodbye, little goats!
Don’t worry, I can do it.
We believe in you.
Look at how nervous she is.
Exactly.
Can she actually do it?
You can do it, Tibbie!
Exactly,
you’re the best!
You can hold him off!
Free at last!
Jollie, let’s go our separate ways from now on.
I agree.
I feel so much better without Jollie.
Mom,
what are you doing here?
You sure love to joke around, kid.
My children haven’t been born yet.
How am I possibly your mom?
Let’s see.
You’re pregnant with twins.
One is named Jollie,
and the other is named Darton.
How did you know?
Because I’m your son from the future.
Are you really my…
my son?
If Jollie is my brother,
then his mom is also my mom.
What’s wrong, Mom?
I’m pregnant with twins,
but now, you’re the only one!
Something must have happened to my other son!
Don’t worry.
He’s grown up, too.
It must be that I never slept well enough and always ate too much,
which is why I gave birth to an unhealthy dark egg!
He’s very healthy. He just likes to bully people,
zap things, and—
Shut up!
I’m glad that you’re both healthy.
Oh no!
What now?
I forgot to pay for the honey that I just bought.
I need to go back and pay!
Mom…
Where are Jollie and Darton?
I have to let Doudou know right away!
Bad news, Doudou!
Werewolf knocked me into some other timespace.
Also, Jollie and Darton are missing!
I’ll ask the other goats to go help you.
Whatever you do, don’t let Jollie and Darton
mess up anything in this timespace.
If anything happens, you have to fix it right away,
or else the timeline will shift.
Jollie! Darton!
—Me first!　—Me first!
Me first!
Me—
Let’s get out of here before Mom comes back.
I agree.
Neither of you are going anywhere!
Why?
You guys, from another timespace, smashed the honey from this timespace.
Now, the events following this,
including the whole timeline, might change.
What does that have to do with me?
Wait a minute,
I think I once heard Mom say
that she gave birth to us
after eating the honey.
Which means—
We might not get born!
—What should we do?　—What now?
Calm down!
All we need to do is find more honey.
Yay! We’re saved!
Where are we supposed to get honey from?
I know a place where we can get it easily.
Really?
You don’t need to tell me. I know where to find honey, too.
I guess I’ll listen to you this time, though.
Bee Palace?
Yep, this is the place.
Here we are.
This place is deserted.
Isn’t the honey at Bee Palace?
I know this place like the back of my hand.
Who dug a hole here?
Is he going to be okay?
Forget about those little details.
What matters is that we’ve found the secret entrance.
Why isn’t it opening?
I just knew it.
Stop doubting me!
It’s open!
I knew my reverse psychology would work.
I’ll go inside and get the honey.
I’m coming, too!
We got the honey!
Run!
They’ve escaped!
How dare they steal our honey!
Outrageous!
She must be an accomplice. Arrest her!
Yes, sir!
Mom, here’s your honey!
I’m such a mess.
How did I forget this?
This doesn’t look like it’s my honey.
We accidentally smashed your honey.
We had to meticulously plan out
how to get this jar from Bee Palace—
We stole it.
We borrowed it.
Have you two done a bad deed?
We just took some honey.
I don’t know why the bees were so mad.
This is called theft!
Sorry.
You’re still good kids if you can fix your mistakes.
Come on,
let’s apologize.
Okay.
Wait! Wait!
You guys came back?
What are you guys doing here?
Are you here to steal my honey again?
They want to talk to you.
Sorry for taking your honey.
That only happened because the defense here is terrible.
Exactly.
So many soldiers, yet they couldn’t catch us.
Stop it!
You don’t even realize that you’re wrong for stealing?
Torture them!
Wait,
since it was my kids who did wrong,
let me take their punishment for them.
Alright, then. Lock her in the dungeon.
Mom!
I’m sorry, Mom!
It was my fault, Mom!
It was my fault!
Next up, it’s time to punish you two.
Please, let them go!
They had a reason for doing this.
They just wanted to give honey to Mama Hen
so that she could lay her eggs.
But committing a crime still requires punishment.
Your punishment shall be helping me carry some stuff.
Okay.
Don’t do this again.
I’m so tired.
Hold on, guys.
What?
Have you changed your mind?
This jar of honey is your reward for today.
Yay!
Mmm!
Alright, it’s time to head back.
Wait a minute.
I’m about to give birth.
Yay! We’ll head outside, then.
Are they out?
Not yet.
They’re out!
Really?
Yes, really!
Yay! We’ve been born!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter