Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Lightning Angel crash-landed in the wrong timespace.
Tibbie was captured while searching for Jollie and Darton.
The two eggs took honey back to Mama Hen, but she scolded them.
In the end, they rescued Tibbie.
Getting Back on Track
This should be the correct timespace.
I wonder what the Wolffy from this timespace is doing.
I just knew that Mom loves me more.
She gave all of the leftover honey to me.
Mom obviously gave it to me!
I’m older! Listen to me!
Let go!
I’m younger! Be nice to me!
Oh no!
Are you guys okay, Weslie?
I’ll help you with repairs.
We’re okay.
Hey, uh,
we’ve reached our destination,
so we’ll be on our way.
Goodbye.
Your Thunderbolt is all fixed, Weslie.
We can leave now.
What’s going on?
Are you sure that you guys safely returned Jollie and Darton
back to the Bizarre World’s timespace?
Yes.
Over on my end, it’s showing that a shift occurred
in the Bizarre World’s timeline.
What?
Did something go wrong?
The trajectory of events is unfolding as it should.
Wait,
where’s the past Wolffy?
Paddi, activate Hurricane’s search ability.
There he is.
I know what went wrong now.
Following the trajectory of events,
Wolffy is supposed to accidentally offend Darton
while digging a tunnel.
Then, he is to be thrown into the dungeon.
Only with his help
do the locked-up Sparky and I successfully escape.
But now…
But now that Wolffy’s passed out here,
who’s going to rescue the past us?
How long until he wakes up?
It might be a day,
it might be a year,
or it might be forever.
However, in his case, he’ll wake up in a day.
What should we do now, then?
Why don’t…
Why don’t I take the place of my past self and offend Darton,
later going into the dungeon to rescue your past selves?
Are you not afraid of Darton, though?
Of course
I am.
But for the sake of my family,
I must be brave and face it!
With this plan,
we’re very likely to cross paths with our past selves.
Let’s all wear these
so we know who is who.
No matter if the plan works or not,
this will be our meeting spot.
Okay!
Deploy additional guards.
Keep searching for Jollie and the goats.
Yes, sir!
Why does my tooth hurt all of a sudden?
Sir,
you might have a cavity.
Regular brushing is required for healthy teeth, you know.
How dare you make fun of me!
Who tripped me?
I did!
Go ahead and lock me in the dungeon.
You…
You helped me pull out a cavity.
Well done.
You know, Darton, I wasn’t trying to help you.
Call me “Chairman!”
I did that on purpose!
Lock me in the dungeon if you dare.
Wolffy,
well done!
Apparently, there’s a worm in the apple.
Why zap me when you’re both happy and unhappy?
It broke?
There’s no way you won’t be angry about this.
This…
Finally angry?
Lock me in the dungeon now!
Found them at last!
I’ve been looking for these photos for a long time.
They were in here the whole time.
Well done, Wolffy!
All I want is to get locked in the dungeon.
Is that so hard?
Look at how handsome I was in these old photos.
It looks like we’ll have to drop this plan.
Plan isn’t working.
You
get ready to leave.
Weslie is saying…
“Don’t be thwarted by challenges.
“Stick with the plan and keep going.”
How are things now?
Wolffy’s plan isn’t working.
It looks like it’s time for Plan B.
There’s a Plan B?
That’s Weslie for you.
So what’s the plan?
I’m coming up with it right now.
How about we use Lightning Angel’s wardrobe function
and infiltrate the dungeon?
Good idea!
You’re so smart, Tibbie.
Why have you come in person, Darton?
I was worried about Weslie and the others escaping,
so I came to check on them.
Eating while standing guard?
I shall punish you!
Hand over the food.
Got any more?
How dare you impersonate Darton!
You dropped something.
Don’t let him get away!
Stop right there! Who are you?
Can’t you tell?
I’m Wolnie.
You liar!
You’re no good at costuming.
Look, you don’t look like Wolnie at all!
Sorry.
It looks like there are people trying to break in. We need more guards.
I guess dressing up and infiltrating the dungeon doesn’t work, either.
Since we can’t get in through the front,
let’s dig a tunnel from the back.
We can’t just sit here and do nothing.
Why don’t we dig a tunnel and escape?
Do you have tools, though?
Yes.
Really?
A toothpick.
As long as I persist, I’ll get there.
Alright, I give up.
The toothpick was that strong?
Rescue complete!
Since irritating him isn’t working,
I’ll get on his good side.
Once I get his trust, I can do the rescue all the same.
Darton, my massaging skills are very, very good!
Satisfaction guaranteed!
How about I show you?
Then hurry up and get started.
Outrageous!
How dare you use your thick wolf hands
to touch my smooth, moist, glowing skin1
Unforgivable! Into the dungeon you go!
Thank you, Darton!
Great!
I should have just done this earlier.
Weslie,
Sparky,
here I come!
Weren’t there two goats in here as well?
Did you not see what happened?
They escaped.
We’re busy trying to catch them.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter