Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats returned Jollie and Darton
back to their original timespace,
but they accidentally disrupted the timeline.
Good thing the goats were able to work together
to bring the trajectory of events back on track.
What will happen next?
Outsmarting “Myself”
It’s been so long.
Why aren’t Weslie and the others back yet?
We’ll just meet up with Wolffy,
and then we can leave!
Someone’s there!
I’m going to have a big meal once we leave.
Hide!
It’s Tibbie!
Look closely.
That Tibbie
is the Tibbie of this timespace, possessed by Darton.
You really don’t know your place.
Let’s go.
Huh?
Wolffy still hasn’t come back yet?
I ran a search.
Why is he still in the dungeon?
Plan isn’t working.
You, get ready to leave.
Did he not understand what I meant?
Why does my head hurt so badly?
You little goats,
I’m going to get you!
Well, now he’s certainly not going to wake up for a while.
Let’s go rescue Wolffy.
What about this Wolffy, then?
I have an idea.
All done.
Disguise the past Wolffy
and secretly switch him with the present Wolffy.
Foolproof!
It might just work.
I’m such a genius.
Tibbie, you stay here and keep watch.
Okay.
Let’s go.
Wait!
How did this happen?
I guess I’ll just have to dig a tunnel.
What’s with the noise?
What are you doing, huh?
I’m exercising!
One, two,
one, two…
Quiet down!
If I can’t dig through the ground?
then I’ll dig through the walls.
I’m so smart!
Be careful, guys.
Make sure to not run into the possessed Tibbie.
Pull!
Ma’am, they’ve all been arrested,
but there’s an extra stroller.
This one right here.
This baby is… quite ugly.
Take them away.
What should I do?
They’ve all been arrested!
It’s okay, Tibbie.
Weslie’s so smart,
so he’ll definitely think of a way to get them out.
But right now, Weslie has been arrested, too.
What if he doesn’t have a way to get them out?
Then…
Tibbie, how about you go rescue them?
What plan does she have, though?
A plan…
Two of myself?
I’m relying on myself to rescue them!
Where have Weslie and the others been locked in?
Didn’t we just change this portrait yesterday?
Why must we change it again?
Darton says that he’s more handsome today than he was yesterday,
so it must be changed.
You two, stop the chit-chat and get to work!
Yes, ma’am!
Darn it, I’ve been caught!
Oh, it’s a mirror.
What is she doing?
Mirror, mirror, on the wall,
who’s the fairest of them all?
Well, of course it’s you, Tibbie.
Ma’am, we’re patrolling elsewhere now.
I know.
I guess tricking myself isn’t as easy as it looks.
Ma’am, we’ve got the new portrait.
Well… Well done.
Hold on,
take me right now to see those locked-up goats.
Yes, ma’am!
I hope the goats can come and rescue me.
Why have you guys gotten thrown in here, too?
Everything I did just now was for nothing, huh?
Tibbie will come up with a way to rescue us, right?
But she’s such a scaredy-cat.
What can she do?
We should believe in her.
Here they are.
Let them out.
I want to interrogate them individually.
Yes, ma’am.
No!
Darton did not give such orders, did he?
Wolnie?
What is she doing here?
No, I have to be braver.
Only then can I rescue them.
I was the one who arrested them!
Why would I set them free?
Are you trying to show off to me?
Do you really think I’d be scared of some stupid Tibbie?
I wouldn’t even be scared of two!
What are you guys doing?
There’s actually two?
What’s going on?
Darton,
she’s impersonating me!
I’m the real Tibbie!
Isn’t having an extra Tibbie pretty good?
No, Darton.
The other Tibbie must be trying to rescue the goats.
That’s why we must figure out which one it is.
I see.
Then bring the goats and the wolf over here.
Yes, sir!
Right now, Tibbie is no longer a friend of the goats.
Whichever one of you treats them the worst
is the real Tibbie.
Weslie,
which one is our Tibbie?
Neither of them are wearing a bracelet.
I can’t tell.
Begin!
That’s just tickling! How unconvincing!
Oh, this Tibbie is so cruel!
Oh, how cruel!
My cake!
She has a bracelet, so she’s our Tibbie.
No!
Giving in that easily? You’ve exposed yourself!
That’s just eating cake! How unconvincing!
Oh, this Tibbie is also so cruel!
Oh, how cruel!
I still can’t tell the difference.
How about this?
Whoever beats them up the worst
is the corrupted Tibbie.
She doesn’t have a bracelet,
so she’s the corrupted Tibbie.
We have to act as though it’s nothing.
Are there mosquitoes or something?
Yeah, I’m so itchy!
So many mosquitoes, huh?
Even my face is swollen.
Stop!
It’s your turn.
What a powerful punch!
We’ve been hit hard even through the air!
I couldn’t stop the force!
It hurts so badly that I’m passing out!
Who’s going to believe such bad acting?
Lock up this fake Tibbie!
I’m the real one, Darton!
Darton,
you’re a genius!
Now, go lock up those goats.
I’ll leave you to watch them.
Yes, sir!
We’re back at last.
Tibbie,
thank you for rescuing us.
I was really scared, though.
You’re truly brave, Tibbie.
Since we’re all back,
let’s leave!
What the heck?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter