Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Tibbie put on a “True and Fake Tibbie” show
at Darton’s base camp,
rescuing her friends in the end.
After leaving the Bizarre World’s timespace,
what will they run into next?
Return of Mecha-Goat
We’re back at last.
I’m so tired. I need to rest.
Another quake?
What are you guys waiting for?
We have to finish our job as soon as possible!
There’s no time for me to rest!
Exactly!
Come on, at least wait for us.
Here we go.
Jonie!
Is it Werewolf?
Don’t worry,
we’re here to protect you!
No, no,
it’s just that the quake tipped over my bookshelf.
Sorry for making you guys worry.
It’s okay. I’ll help you tidy up.
We’ll help, too.
I can do it.
The rest of you should get going.
Don’t be too long, you two.
Jonie,
what’s this?
Mecha-Goat gave me this when he saved me.
The others haven’t gone far. Let’s catch up to them.
So heavy!
Is that…
Werewolf?
Mecha-Goat, too?
What happened, Jonie?
The goats?
Werewolf?
Stop!
How do I get rid of them?
I guess the plan has to change.
Werewolf,
you have nowhere to run!
I don’t need him anymore!
Oh no!
He threw out Mecha-Goat!
Mecha-Goat!
Mecha-Goat, are you okay?
Mecha-Goat,
wake up!
Are you okay, Mecha-Goat?
What are you doing here?
Do you remember me?
You are Jonie.
Yay, you remember me!
Origin: Argali Clan.
Yes!
Height: 1.3 meters.
Right, right!
Weight: Two hundred and—
You…
You can stop there.
Good thing you’re okay.
How about we take you to the Hub?
No.
Why not?
I must rescue my friends.
Your friends are here, too?
They are there.
Then we’ll take you to the Hub,
and then we’ll go find your friends,
okay?
No. I must find my friends.
How about we take him with us?
Since mechanical goats can sense each other,
we might just find other anachronists.
Okay.
Mission commenced.
That’s odd.
How come neither Weslie nor Jonie have a signal?
I can’t get in contact with them.
They’re not in trouble, are they?
Paddi, check and see where they are.
Paddi!
Weslie and Jonie should be here soon.
Good thing I’m okay.
What are you doing here,
Paddi?
Werewolf!
Stop!
Stop it!
Thank you, Sparky!
I can’t let them ruin my plan.
They’re done for!
You’ve got it wrong.
You are the one who’s done for!
Oh, really?
—Magic Airplanes!　—Sirius!
For the sake of the plan, I have to distract them.
Come on! Come get me!
Come here!
Mecha-Goat, do we keep going straight?
Yes. The destination is the gorge up ahead.
Got it.
Mecha-Goat, do you need any charging?
No.
Then how about I have Rainbow do a full-body check on you?
Your hand is dirty.
How about I help you wipe it?
No.
Fine.
Can’t get me!
Maximum power!
What’s going on?
Mecha-Goat,
give me a hand!
You guys are incredible.
To help.
Are you guys okay?
Yes.
Here comes a dragnet!
Paddi, Tibbie,
surround his front and back!
Sparky and I will surround his left and his right!
Weslie and Jonie, surround his top and bottom!
Weslie and Jonie haven’t come back yet!
Instead of catching me,
you guys better worry
about Weslie and Jonie!
What?
Did he distract us on purpose?
That means Weslie and Jonie might be in danger!
Paddi, check to see if they have a signal!
I’m getting them!
Weslie, Jonie, where are you?
Weslie, Jonie, are you there?
What should we do? They’re not inside.
Let’s go find them, then!
Is this the place?
I don’t see any other mechanical goats.
Found them. They are over here.
Mecha-Goat, are you sure they’re here?
I don’t see them.
Weslie!
Hang on tight, Weslie!
What’s wrong with you, Mecha-Goat?
Mission accomplished.
I can’t hold on anymore! Help us!
My code does not contain the word “help.”
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter