Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Weslie and Jonie
rescued Mecha-Goat from the hands of Werewolf.
However, Werewolf messed with Mecha-Goat,
causing Mecha-Goat to, oddly enough, drop Weslie and Jonie down an ice chasm.
Will they be rescued?
Trapped in the Chasm
Mecha-Goat,
what did you do that for?
Mission accomplished.
Accomplished what?
Were you lying to us when you said that some of your friends
were stuck in our time?
Say something!
Enter command: “The goats are enemies.”
Command accepted.
Have fun remaining trapped in the ice chasm with the goats!
Say something!
Mission accomplished.
What do you mean, “mission accomplished?”
Weslie,
Mecha-Goat isn’t like this.
That Werewolf must have done something to him.
Jonie,
you’re injured.
I’m okay.
You only fell in here because you tried to save me.
I’m going to find a way to get you out of here.
Are those things in the ice walls houses?
It looks like people used to live here before.
This might come in handy.
Spacetime distortion is getting worse.
We have to hurry up.
Weslie, what are you doing?
I’m going to climb out using this tool.
Once I climb out, I’ll use Thunderbolt to pick you two up.
Be careful.
You may not leave.
Jonie’s injured.
We need to get her medical attention right away!
You may not leave.
Wake up, Mecha-Goat!
We’re your friends!
The goats are enemies.
Enemies.
Ouch, my leg!
Stop!
Mecha-Goat!
I think Mecha-Goat is unconscious for now.
We’ll have to take him back up with us.
What…
What the…?
This is the place.
Weslie and Jonie are down there.
I’ll go rescue Weslie and Jonie.
Wolffy,
it’s too dangerous to go alone.
You can’t go alone. We’re going together!
Apparently, without that group of goats,
you’re nothing much at all.
I can do it alone.
It’s too narrow. I can’t get down!
Well, of course an airplane can’t get down there.
Could there be a geyser here?
If there is a geyser,
we can get out by riding it.
Really?
But
this is just a mural.
What if there isn’t one?
There will be.
I was analyzing the area just now.
After comparing it to the mural,
I realized that the mural is depicting this exact place.
If I’m not wrong,
there should be a geyser
in the opening that we fell down.
We’ll use that small hole
and break up the ice on top of the geyser.
Then, I’ll put that big block of ice on top of the geyser,
and the geyser will take us out through the opening.
Great! I’ll carry Mecha-Goat.
No, your leg is injured.
Mecha-Goat is our friend.
My leg wound is just a scratch.
Friend?
Enemies.
En…
It’s so heavy!
It’s moving!
I’ll help you, Weslie.
Jonie—
Let’s get going.
Leave the rest of it to me.
Just sit back and rest.
Okay.
We’ve gotten Sirius back out.
Now, I’ll use Morning Sun’s drill
to make the opening bigger.
The rope fell off!
Sparky, are you okay?
I’m okay,
but
it looks like Morning Sun’s drill is broken.
Now what?
We’ll have to go down there by ourselves.
This chasm is so deep, though.
How do we get down?
Leave it to me!
No!
It’s too dangerous to go alone.
It’ll be fine.
Just leave it to me.
Wolffy…
Hold on to the rope.
See?
I can do things even if I’m alone!
If we’re all clapping, then who’s holding the rope?
Wolffy!
Nope, this ice is too tough.
I need someone else to help me.
No, no.
I can’t have Jonie help me anymore.
What happened?
Wolffy?
Thank goodness I’ve found you guys!
Come on, climb up with me.
Why didn’t they hold the rope?
How are we supposed to get up, then?
If I’m not wrong,
there must be a geyser underneath this ice.
So what’s the point?
We were just thinking of a way to dig through the ice on top,
but it’s just too tough.
That’s why I’m asking what the point is.
Look, guys!
What’s going on?
I think
you cracked it when you fell down earlier.
That’s for sure.
My years of enduring frying pans weren’t for nothing!
There’s no water, though.
Listen.
You’re right!
Wolffy,
let’s hurry and move the ice block on top of the crack.
Weslie, what exactly are you doing?
We’re done. Now what?
It’s time for an elevator ride.
An… An elevator?
Here it comes.
Hang on tight, guys!
What now?
Wolffy fell down there, too.
Is that another spacetime distortion quake?
No,
it sounds like it’s coming from the hole.
Weslie! Jonie!
I’m so glad you guys are okay!
Mecha-Goat?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter