Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Weslie, Jonie, and Mecha-Goat got stuck in an ice chasm.
Wolffy fell down and exposed the chasm’s geyser,
and they all used the geyser to escape.
What will happen next?
A Kind “Enemy”
Screwdriver.
Wrench.
Wipe sweat.
Wipe sweat!
Wipe my sweat!
How is Mecha-Goat doing?
I’ve done everything I can.
It can’t be!
I can’t believe that even Wolffy can’t fix this monitor!
Jonie…
Without this monitor,
how are we supposed to examine Mecha-Goat?
Without examination,
how are we supposed to know what’s wrong with Mecha-Goat?
Without knowing what’s wrong,
we have no way of saving Mecha-Goat!
Calm down, Jonie.
—We can—　—How am I supposed to calm down?
Do you guys not care about Mecha-Goat?
How could you guys do that?
There, there.
Just because the monitor is broken doesn’t mean we’re out of solutions.
It’s not that we don’t care about Mecha-Goat.
We’re just trying to tell you
that we can make a new monitor together.
With the power of so many people,
we’ll certainly be able to do it.
Plus, I’m a great inventor.
I’m sorry,
it was my fault.
I was just too anxious.
I shouldn’t have spoken to you guys like that.
It’s okay, Jonie.
We all know that you’re just worried about Mecha-Goat.
Alright, guys. Let’s get to work!
All done!
Let’s run an examination.
Mr. Slowy, do you know what exactly is wrong with Mecha-Goat?
His memory program must have been messed with.
Enemies spotted.
Ancient martial arts program, activate.
Hold on for just a second, Mecha-Goat!
No!
Let’s put you on low battery mode for now.
Low battery.
Jonie passed out!
You’re awake, Jonie.
Is… Is Mecha-Goat okay?
What in the world happened to him?
How come he doesn’t remember us?
Don’t worry.
Let’s work on restoring Mecha-Goat’s memory.
But—
Just leave it to us.
We’ve already thought of a way
to help restore Mecha-Goat’s memory.
Stay here and rest.
Alright.
Oh, yeah.
Maybe that thing will come in handy.
What do you guys want?
Go ahead, Sparky.
Danger.
Requesting backup.
Danger. Danger.
Huh?
These are our old photos.
Photos?
These were taken when we participated in the Sports Games together.
You’ll surely remember what happened once you look at them.
Back then, Paddi couldn’t even swim yet.
Even now, you’re still afraid of cockroaches!
Are you remembering something?
You are all enemies.
Aren’t we—
Warning. Warning.
Oh no!
Mecha-Goat can’t get waterlogged!
Cover Mecha-Goat and take him back to the laboratory!
Why?
Thank goodness he’s dry.
How exactly are we supposed to restore his memory?
Yes.
Forget it, Mr. Slowy.
You should rest for a bit.
I have already created a memory-restoring invention.
Really?
The Memory-Restoring Bat!
His memory will be restored with just a small smack!
Stop!
No matter how you look at it, that’s just a regular stick!
You don’t get it!
Any unfixable machine is better after a smack.
He’s our friend, not a machine!
Don’t worry,
it’ll be quick.
No!
Ouch!
Where’s my Memory-Restoring Bat?
Right here.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Why won’t you just listen to us, Wolffy?
Warning. Enemy spotted.
Mecha-Goat,
do you remember this?
You gave these goggles to me when you saved me.
Goggles…
Fire!
Mecha-Goat?
Go.
You’re done for!
Again!
Keep firing!
Go.
Fire!
Thank you.
Goodbye.
If you put them on,
you might just remember everything that happened.
Well?
Do you remember anything?
Goats’ Sports Games.
Competition.
Friends.
Low battery.
Oh no, he’s out of battery.
Charging.
Charge up for now. I’ll go bring the others over here.
Hurry up. Stop lagging behind.
I’m still sleepy.
Does Mecha-Goat really remember us?
Yes,
but he ran out of battery just now.
I was charging him up.
Where’s Mecha-Goat?
What the…?
Mecha-Goat!
Mecha-Goat?
Don’t worry,
we’ll find Mecha-Goat.
I found Mecha-Goat!
Mecha-Goat,
we’re here to help you!
You’re all enemies.
Stop him!
He’s too fast! We can’t get to him!
Hold on! I can’t run anymore!
I think it’ll work!
Come back with us, Mecha-Goat.
How have you been, my friends?
It’s that guy again!
We can’t let him take away Mecha-Goat!
Thunderbolt!
Mission accomplished. Retreat!
Stop!
Thunderbolt,
speed up!
That was close.
You’re not going anywhere!
Oh, for goodness sake!
You’ve got me, too!
Oh no, don’t let Mecha-Goat fall into the water!
Thanks for the help, guys.
I’ll be on my way!
Stop!
Darn it, the planes are stuck!
Oh, well. I’m glad that Mecha-Goat is okay.
I almost got caught just now.
Ouch!
Good thing I added a shield to this cave,
so goats won’t be able to detect it.
Remember,
don’t ever get close to those goats or that wolf.
Yes, sir.
Captain, let me examine the injury on your arm.
Injury examination program, activate.
What are you doing?
Based on the volume of the shout, the injury is concluded to be severe.
Based on the volume of the shout, the injury is concluded to be light.
Enough!
Go get me some water!
Yes, Captain.
W…
Warning. Waterlogged.
Warning.
You can’t even get some water?
Useless.
Frie—
—nds.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter