Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats tried to restore Mecha-Goat’s memory, but failed.
What’s more, due to their softheartedness, Werewolf took Mecha-Goat away.
Will the subtly altered Mecha-Goat get his memories back?
Friend or Foe?
Excuse me, have you seen a goat with red goggles?
No.
Excuse me, have you seen a wolf with a droplet shape on the forehead?
It’s about to rain. Let’s hurry home.
I wonder how Mecha-Goat is doing.
The enemy is searching for me.
Stay away from the enemy. Bring the medicine to Captain first.
The enemy is not in the hazard range. It is safe to leave.
A goat is flying!
Mecha-Goat?
Warning. Warning.
—Mecha-Goat!　—Warning.
Are you okay, Mecha-Goat?
Enemy.
Warning. Warning.
I’m here to help you, Mecha-Goat!
To help.
That’s right!
Stop swinging around!
Let’s think of a way to get down!
We’re here to help!
To help.
Do you guys not understand what it means to help others?
Oh no, it’s raining!
To help.
Hang in there, Mecha-Goat!
Unknown liquid. Warning.
Is it dark out?
You’re awake, Mecha-Goat.
Enemies are close. Warning.
Rusted parts. Movement impeded.
Ancient martial arts program, activate.
Mecha-Goat,
stop moving!
He’s going to break down if he doesn’t stop.
Let’s restrain him.
Stop!
That’s a deoxidant, Mecha-Goat.
We just wanted to help you get rid of rust.
Rust.?
Functions are currently being repaired.
You’re all rusty, and you need treatment.
We just wanted to help you.
To help?
Ointment?
Stay away from enemies.
Take the medicine to Captain right now.
Mecha-Goat!
Mecha-Goat, you’re still rusty!
Don’t touch any liquid again, okay?
Why is he taking so long just to buy medicine?
Mecha-Goat is useless.
Captain!
Captain, your medicine.
You’re so inefficient.
Come on, apply it.
Yes, sir.
At least this isn’t so bad.
Ouch!
Can’t you be a little lighter?
Okay.
Stay… Stay away!
A little lighter.
Go… Go away!
Waterlogged. Warning.
Rusting requires treatment.
You want “treatment” even after you caused all this trouble?
Get out of here!
Yes, sir.
Don’t let me see you ever again!
Mecha-Goat, where are you?
Jonie, let’s just head back and eat first.
I’m not hungry. Why don’t you guys head back and get ready?
Okay!
We’ll make some great dishes and wait for you.
Come on! Come on!
We’ll head back, then.
Mecha-Goat?
Stay away from enemies.
Where’d he go?
Did I knock him into the air?
Sorry.
Are you okay?
Stay away from enemies.
Enemy, please stay away from me.
Don’t try to leave just yet.
I’ll get you repaired before you go.
You’ll need more repairs tomorrow, too.
Stay away from enemies.
I ran into Mecha-Goat right here yesterday.
Warning. Surrounded by enemies.
Have this deoxidant
and a layer of waterproof spray.
Flexibility one hundred percent restored.
Stay away from enemies.
Great, Mecha-Goat has recovered!
I’m really something, aren’t I?
I’m already better in such a short time.
I can’t believe they got me injured.
It’s game over for those little goats!
Mecha-Goat!
Captain?
Put in this new battery
and capture those goats for me!
Capture goats.
Hurry up! This is a command!
Yes,
sir.
He’s coming to get those goats for good!
Who put that waterproof spray on him?
Plus, wasn’t he all rusty for the past two days?
Something’s fishy.
Mr. Slowy!
What is it?
How are we supposed to restore Mecha-Goat’s memory?
Give me some time to think of an idea.
Mr. Slowy is inventing something.
Let’s go see if we can help him out.
I’ll help you wipe your sweat.
No need to. Thanks.
Mr. Slowy, are you hungry?
I have snacks!
Get out of here! Don’t disturb me!
How are we supposed to restore Mecha-Goat’s memory now?
Aha!
Let’s take him to the canyon where he was injured.
His memory might just come back.
Where are you taking me?
Mecha-Goat!
We’ve thought of a way to help restore your memory.
Mission commenced.
Capture the goats.
Ancient martial arts program, activate.
Huh?
Guys!
Run, Jonie!
Mecha-Goat, what’s wrong with you?
Mecha-Goat…
Jonie,
run!
Mecha-Goat,
aren’t we friends?
Jonie!
Friends…?
I’ll get you repaired before you go.
We’re here to help, too!
Mecha-Goat has recovered!
Capture the goats.
Friends.
Do you remember us now, Mecha-Goat?
Come to the canyon tomorrow! We’ll restore your memory!
What the heck?
How dare Mecha-Goat disobey my command!
I guess I’ll have to get the next step ready!
Jonie, are you okay?
I’m okay.
It’s just that Mecha-Goat’s memory—
Kids,
my chip experiment was a success!
Come give me a like!
Is that the chip?
Just put this chip into Mecha-Goat’s body,
and his memory will be restored.
Great!
Thank you, Mr. Slowy!
Do you guys think Mecha-Goat will actually go to the canyon?
He’ll be there for sure.
I believe in him.
I also believe
that Mecha-Goat will be waiting for us by the canyon.
With Mr. Slowy’s chip,
Mecha-Goat will recover soon.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter