Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Mecha-Goat progressively changed his bias towards the goats,
becoming on good terms with them.
But just as they thought
that they would be able to restore Mecha-Goat’s memory,
he disappeared.
A Missing Mecha-Goat
Mecha-Goat?
Mecha-Goat!
Has Mecha-Goat arrived yet?
No.
I couldn’t find any trace of him with Hurricane, either.
Look, guys!
What is it, Weslie?
I found Mecha-Goat’s wrist strap.
Plus, there’s oil on the ground.
Does all of this oil
mean that something happened to Mecha-Goat?
Let’s follow the oil and take a look.
Wait,
there’s a fork in the road.
Let’s see if there are any clues around here.
More oil?
This way!
Jonie!
Wolffy!
That was close.
Jonie, Wolffy, are you guys okay?
We’re okay. Let’s hurry and find Mecha-Goat.
Okay.
Mecha-Goat?
There he is!
Are you okay, Mecha-Goat?
Mecha-Goat…
Mecha-Goat,
how dare you betray me!
I did not betray Captain.
You were with the enemy. That’s betrayal!
Good thing I overheard your conversation
so that I could step in.
I just knew you were going to meet up with the goats, Mecha-Goat!
I won’t let you guys see each other!
Warning.
Low battery.
I’ve only gotten this far.
The goats are probably catching up by now.
I need to buy some time.
Aha!
If you want to find him, go on!
All done.
I’m going to make you fight everyone you see.
Don’t ever become friends with the goats!
Warning. Warning.
Danger ahead.
Danger is right!
Because I’m an intelligent, capable,
and resourceful
bad guy!
You’ll just have to have my newly-invented chip implemented.
Warning. Warning.
Danger ahead. Danger ahead.
Wait!
Did you guys just hear a weird sound?
This way.
So it was just the waves.
Let’s keep searching.
Mecha-Goat! Mecha-Goat!
What’s blinding me?
What’s that?
Let’s go take a look.
Aren’t these
Mecha-Goat’s goggles?
Mecha-Goat?
Mecha-Goat!
He couldn’t have
fallen into the sea, could he?
Split up and search, guys!
—Magic Airplanes!　—Sirius!
How’s the search going?
We didn’t find him.
Mecha-Goat isn’t here.
Mecha-Goat…
Don’t lose hope, Jonie.
Mecha-Goat might just be somewhere else.
Right,
let’s go back and keep searching.
We might just find him.
Mecha-Goat?
Mecha-Goat!
I didn’t find Mecha-Goat over there.
I didn’t find him over here, either.
If I hadn’t asked Mecha-Goat to come here,
he could have been fine.
Don’t worry,
I’m sure we’ll find him.
Exactly.
We can’t find Mecha-Goat anywhere.
The situation doesn’t look good.
Paddi!
With how strong Mecha-Goat is,
he’ll be fine.
Right, let’s keep searching.
Something doesn’t feel right.
What exactly is it?
Tibbie,
you dropped a head flower.
No, that’s not mine.
Are you sure?
You’re the only one here who wears head flowers.
Just because it’s a head flower doesn’t mean it’s mine.
It could be someone else’s.
This head flower…
What?
is dirty!
However,
I feel like I’ve seen it before.
I’m just helping you put in a new chip.
There’s nothing dangerous about it.
Danger ahead.
Trying to escape?
I don’t think so!
My chip!
Please don’t be broken!
Warning.
Danger ahead.
Still trying to run?
I guess I’ll just have to turn off your system.
Warning. Warning.
System shutting down.
I’ll get rid of this old chip of yours.
Soon, I’ll be getting my revenge!
Time to charge.
Battery restored.
Deleting all memories.
Activating new program.
Successfully integrated new program.
It worked!
Go defeat those goats for me right now!
Command accepted.
Mecha-Goat!
Are you sure?
Just because it’s a head flower doesn’t mean it’s mine.
It could be someone else’s.
Someone else’s?
A path with oil,
and a path without…
Aha!
An area having oil doesn’t necessarily mean that Mecha-Goat was there.
What do you mean?
Who says that Mecha-Goat must have left that oil?
It could also be that someone intentionally left it to throw us off.
Wolffy,
are you saying that Mecha-Goat is that way?
That way.
Even though we’re not certain, let’s still take a look.
Alright, let’s go.
Look, there are suspicious drag marks.
Mecha-Goat!
Watch out, guys!
Werewolf?
You hit me?
How dare you hit me!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter