Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
they found Mecha-Goat’s goggles by the seaside,
leading them to worry about his safety.
Later, Wolffy found clues that located Mecha-Goat,
but this time, Mecha-Goat’s personality has greatly changed.
Rescuing Mecha-Goat
It’s Mecha-Goat!
Are you okay, Mecha-Goat?
Target spotted.
Destroy them.
Ancient martial arts program, activate.
Are you okay?
Werewolf,
what in the world have you done with Mecha-Goat?
See how powerful I am?
These are the consequences of messing with me!
He’s so strong now that he even hits me, too.
Watch out, guys.
Mecha-Goat is out of control!
Targets spotted.
Destroy them.
You guys can keep fighting. Goodbye!
Guys, don’t hurt Mecha-Goat!
You should be telling him to not hurt us!
He’s too strong.
Magic Airplanes!
Sirius!
He’s attacking everyone, no matter who.
We have to hurry and put the new chip in.
But the chip needs some time to restore the program.
We can’t even get near him.
Mecha-Goat…
I have an idea!
Targets spotted.
Destroy them.
Targets
all cleared.
Why have I run into this guy again?
I can’t let him see me.
Oh, come on!
Oh no!
Target spotted.
Destroy it.
Why do you have to chase me?
Allen! Flat-Beak Allen!
Over here, Allen!
Flat-Beak Allen! Allen!
Allen!
I’ll protect you with my life, Allen!
I’ll protect you with my next life, Allen!
Hey, wait!
I didn’t think you’d use whatever means necessary
to get my autograph faster.
I really can’t win with you, can I?
Here you go.
Stop it, Mecha-Goat!
Enemies.
Destroy them.
Help!
Mecha-Goat—
Proceed with the plan, Jonie!
But… But…
We’re doing all of this for Mecha-Goat’s own good!
Mecha-Goat, I’m Jonie!
Do you still remember—
Are you okay?
Thanks.
Do you still remember this pair of goggles?
Now!
Now,
Jonie!
Weslie!
We did it?
Your plan worked, Wolffy!
I’m really something, aren’t I?
I had Slowy add a hypnosis program to the goggles.
Once Mecha-Goat wears it,
we’ll be able to briefly control him.
This hypnosis program only lasts one minute.
We have to hurry and put in the chip!
It’s gone!
What?
Could it have fallen out
somewhere near the canyon?
Then let’s hurry to the canyon!
Destroy them.
Quick!
Back to the Magic Airplanes!
Paddi, hurry and locate the chip!
Okay!
Trying to recover Mecha-Goat?
No way!
The canyon is right up ahead.
Found it!
Wolffy and I will distract Mecha-Goat.
The rest of you, get the chip!
Run!
You won’t get away with this!
Jonie! Paddi!
There’s someone in the bushes!
Watch out, guys!
Weslie! Wolffy!
Oh, yeah!
I can just destroy the chip,
and that’ll be how the story ends.
Mecha-Goat…
Have fun vanishing along with the chip, Mecha-Goat!
Done!
Why?
In the past, you were the one who helped me.
Now, it’s my turn to help you.
To
help?
Jonie!
We need to get Jonie medical attention right away!
To help…
Mecha-Goat?
Mecha-Goat,
thank you for your help.
They
are not enemies.
are my friends.
Take them to Rainbow for medical attention right away!
Paddi, go pick up the restoration chip!
Okay.
Jonie’s awake!
Paddi? Weslie?
Yay, you’re okay!
Where’s ​​Mecha-Goat?
He’s right here.
Thanks to you risking your life to protect him,
he’s now fully recovered with our chip.
Great.
You can have this back.
Thank you, Jonie.
You’re welcome.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter