Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Mecha-Goat suddenly went out of control, wreaking havoc across the grassland.
Good thing the goats and Wolffy
used the power of wisdom and friendship
to successfully restore Mecha-Goat
back to how he was.
Our Hope
I can’t believe Mecha-Goat doesn’t remember
a single thing that happened with Werewolf.
That’s because Mr. Slowy’s chip
completely removed Werewolf’s programming.
No matter what,
what’s important is that Mecha-Goat remembers us now.
Let’s go, Mecha-Goat.
Finally, Mecha-Goat is back where he belongs.
Let’s get back onto the Magic Airplanes and leave.
What are you doing, Paddi?
It’s the Seven Evil Wolves of the past.
What are they doing here?
I’m guessing that they found the Magic Airplanes by chance.
No need to worry, then.
After a while, they’ll get bored of looking and leave.
I can’t take it anymore!
I’ll just go chase them away!
Calm down, Sparky!
What’s the matter?
The Seven Evil Wolves are still loitering over there.
What should we do, then?
If this goes on any longer, the timeline might shift.
Leave it to me.
I’ll just trick them into leaving.
After all, I’m their relative.
Oh, yeah!
We almost forgot.
We’ll leave it to you, then, Wolffy.
Good luck!
It feels so good to receive praise.
Darton said that I’m useless without the goats,
so I’ll just prove that I can do things even without them.
Who exactly do these airplanes belong to?
Who knows?
Hey, guys.
Wolffy?
Wolffy, weren’t you requesting backup from the Wolf Clan?
I can’t believe you’re still here slacking off.
Aren’t I preparing transportation right now?
This way, it’ll be quicker.
Transportation?
Are you talking about these airplanes?
These airplanes are yours?
Yep! Let’s follow our original plan.
You guys catch goats, and I’ll go request backup.
What… What’s wrong?
How can you prove that these airplanes are yours?
How about you fly them for us?
Well, that’s a piece of cake for a genius like me.
Hold on,
I want you to fly this one.
No problem.
You’re still saying these airplanes are yours?
These airplanes aren’t too bad.
They can even produce clothing and snacks.
My snacks!
Didn’t you say you were going to chase them away?
It didn’t go as planned.
We should just do it together.
Yeah!
Without that group of goats,
you’re nothing much at all.
No!
Why not?
Look into my eyes!
Do you see my sincerity?
No.
Anyway,
I’ve now come up with a plan that is certain to work.
Guys,
I found signs of some goats!
Goats?
Where?
Right over there!
Goats spotted!
Here we go!
Yay!
Go!
We’ve been caught!
What are you doing, Wolffy?
Well, of course I’m showing you just how powerful I am!
Wolffy, you traitor!
You’re incredible, Wolffy!
He started talking, and then just started laughing.
Mr. Wolffy, wake up.
The plan begins now.
Guys, I found signs of goats!
Where? Where?
They’re right in the valley over there!
The moment they leave to catch goats,
I’ll take back Sirius and the Magic Airplanes.
You guys—
You guys better—
You guys better go and catch goats!
We’ve already caught them.
Huh?
Having these airplanes makes everything easier.
Why don’t I see Weslie?
Forget about him. Four is pretty good already.
This was your plan, huh?
This is bad!
No one move!
Wolffy!
What is it?
Uh… Nothing.
I was just worried that you guys would have too much on your hands.
You’re just in time.
What… What are you guys doing?
We know what you’re trying to do.
No!
I mean, we’re family! Just forgive me!
What the…?
You wanted to eat mutton, right?
Did you think we couldn’t tell?
As a family, how could we forget about you?
Guys…
Finally, I get to eat mutton.
Thanks so much, guys.
Didn’t you come to rescue us, Wolffy?
He’s a wolf, you know. How could he possibly come to rescue you guys?
Exactly.
A frying pan?
I was afraid you guys would have too much on your hands,
so I brought a frying pan to help.
What’s this?
A… A candle.
I wanted to set the mood a little.
Maybe you have come to rescue the goats.
I swear I came to eat them!
Suspicious!
Get him!
Long time no see, guys.
Weslie?
Get him, too!
Come and get me!
Weslie,
you can’t fool us with such an obvious trap.
Oops,
I forgot to cover the trap.
You have nowhere to run!
Huh?
Good thing I covered the other traps.
Get him!
He turned the lights off.
Go turn the lights on first.
Got him!
It’s a doll?
Then where did Weslie go?
Let me go!
Someone help!
Goodbye!
You forgot about me, didn’t you?
You
forgot about me, didn’t you?
Goodbye, Seven Evil Wolves!
Wolffy, you traitor!
You’re incredible, Weslie!
Wolffy was the reason why I got out safely.
Yeah,
and Wolffy was the one who got us into trouble to begin with.
Wolffy, as long as we work together,
there’s nothing we can’t fix,
right?
Right.
Apparently, without that group of goats,
you’re nothing much at all.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter