Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy wanted to prove himself
by retaking the airplanes captured by the Seven Evil Wolves,
but he failed.
Will his disheartened self be able to move forward?
An Old Friend
Not here.
Could she be here?
I was looking for someone! I’m sorry!
Tibbie, you dropped your head flower.
No, that’s not mine.
I think I’ve seen it before.
Have you actually come to this timespace?
What are you making?
I’m making a pretty head flower.
Does it look good?
You’re so talented, Stacy!
Thank you, Slowy.
This head flower must be Stacy’s,
because only Stacy would make this kind of head flower!
Ouch!
What a big cave!
Could Stacy be in there?
Huh?
What’s going on?
I guess I can’t make any noise.
What a dangerous cave!
I should search elsewhere.
Help!
Someone help me!
Could that voice be…?
Stacy!
I’m here to help you!
Grandpa!
It’s not her.
What’s the matter with you?
Could you help me?
I’m stuck down here.
I’ll get you back up right away.
Here, hold on to this.
Are you hurt?
I’m okay. Thank you, Grandpa.
I guess they just have similar voices.
How did you get stuck down there?
I don’t know.
Could you take me out of this forest?
She’s lost?
Yes, I can.
I’ll take you out.
Thanks.
Ugh,
that group of goats is always ruining my plans!
Good thing I’ve hidden another anachronist.
that you certainly won’t be finding.
Where’d she go?
How did she disappear?
Could she have escaped?
By the way,
did you happen to see a young girl
while you were in the forest?
A young girl?
Yes.
Really?
Where?
It’s me!
No, I mean a—
Grandpa,
there’s a monster behind me! Help me!
Where?
It’s just a vine, is all.
It’s dangerous here. You’ve got to—
Grandpa,
there’s a really big spider!
Help me!
It’s so scary!
Go away!
Coming, coming.
Be sure to follow me closely.
Grandpa,
wait for me.
Careful!
Grandpa?
Are you okay, Grandpa?
I’m fine. What matters is that you’re okay.
You help other people with such enthusiasm, Grandpa.
You’re just like a friend of mine.
A friend of yours?
That can’t be.
When we’re able, I can introduce you to each other.
Yeah, sure.
Alright, we’re finally out of the forest!
Don’t go in there ever again.
Well, I’ll be on my way now.
Aha!
Grandpa!
Wait a minute, I have something to give you.
Isn’t…
Isn’t that Stacy’s head flower?
Excuse me—
What is it?
Oh my goodness!
Nothing.
That’s suspicious.
Was it not an accident that we ran into all of those things back there?
Plus, she has Stacy’s head flower.
Might she be Werewolf in disguise?
Leave Stacy alone!
She’s coming for me!
What’s wrong?
Wait for me!
That’s odd. Where in the world has she gone?
Grandpa,
wait for me!
Grandpa!
There she is.
Wait for me, Grandpa!
I have something to give you!
She’s gone at last.
There you are.
Stay… Stay away! Stay away!
Is there some kind of misunderstanding?
Have you been chasing me this whole time?
I’m telling you,
I won’t be fooled!
No, I just want to give—
GIve what?
Why aren’t you saying anything?
Look out!
So close!
Werewolf?
Does that mean that this person isn’t Werewolf?
I was wondering where she ran off to.
Apparently, you took her over here.
There’s no way you’re ruining my plan!
Run, Grandpa!
She’s rescuing me?
Stop!
You may have an airplane, but don’t think that I don’t!
Come on out,
Daybreak!
Why is there no Daybreak at a time like this?
I…
I can’t run anymore.
You keep on running. Don’t worry about me.
I won’t leave you behind!
I guess I was wrong about you.
Ducking here and there, what a nuisance!
Darn it, we have to think of something!
Oh, yeah! That place might just be able to stop him!
Quick, go this way!
You think you can just hide?
How naïve!
Here we are.
Nowhere to run, huh?
Get ready to accept your fate!
Grandpa, what do we do now?
Now!
I’ll capture you guys right now.
Why are you laughing?
What a big mouth, still laughing at a time like this!
What the heck?
The cave is collapsing!
Now’s our chance! Run!
How dare you mess with me!
Stop right there!
The exit is right up ahead!
There’s no way you’re escaping!
Oh no, we’re about to get stuck in here!
Look out!
Grandpa!
Aha!
That was close. Thank goodness you’re okay.
Thank you.
Let’s get out of here, then.
Don’t you dare!
We’re safe at last.
Excuse me,
why do you have this head flower?
Well, it’s mine.
What?
Is this one yours, too?
Isn’t this the one that I lost?
It’s yours?
That can’t be.
Stacy’s head flowers are unique.
Grandpa,
do they look good?
Could you be…?
It’s all dirty. I’ll… I’ll wash it.
What happened to me?
I don’t look like this!
You’re
Stacy?
How do you know my name?
Is it…
Is it really you?
There’s Mr. Slowy.
Who is she?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter