Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Slowy encountered a strange person.
They escaped Werewolf’s attacks together.
Apparently, the strange person was Stacy.
What should Slowy do next?
She’s Grandma Stacy?
She doesn’t look like us, though.
Something must have happened to her when she time traveled.
Weslie!
Wolffy!
Wo—
Wolf!
Over here, guys! Defeat him together!
Calm down, calm down!
Listen, he’s a good wolf!
A…
A good wolf?
Uh…
Hello.
So this is the future, huh?
By the way, do you guys know Slowy?
He—
Why have I suddenly developed a cough? That’s odd!
The person you’re speaking of has already moved away, right?
Really?
He moved away?
He’s such a genius.
If he were here now, he might be able to help me recover.
It’s okay. We can help you, too.
Grandma Stacy—
“Grandma?”
How could you address such a beautiful young lady
like so?
Well, Sister Stacy,
do you remember what happened to you?
It might have been when I just got here…
Who knew that this thing would actually come in handy?
This last one is all yours.
After I ate the candy, I remember that my face felt a little sore.
It looks like this was Werewolf’s doing.
Apparently, he can change someone’s appearance.
He once impersonated me, too!
Either way, if we run into any weirdly-behaving people from now on,
we need to be careful.
Am I able to recover?
I’ll go back and find a way to help you recover,
and then I’ll send you home safely.
I’ll see if there are any inventions at home that could help you.
We’ll think of solutions, too.
Let’s go!
I can also help
ruin it!
The weather is so good today. I’ll do some cleaning.
There are a lot of dangerous things in Wolffy’s lab.
I must be careful not to touch them.
My face!
Where’s my makeup bag?
I’m known for my beauty.
I can’t let anyone see me like this!
I’m home, Wolnie!
Eww!
Yeah!
No!
What’s wrong, Wolnie?
You’re home?
Wolnie?
Wolnie’s covering her head, acting all secretive.
Could it be
that she wants to celebrate my birthday?
But my birthday passed a long time ago.
Could it be that she doesn’t feel well?
I’m so ugly. How am I supposed to go out like this?
Wolnie,
do you not feel well?
Here, let me see.
No…
No, I’m fine.
Come on, don’t resist.
Let me see.
Don’t touch me!
Wolnie?
Why is Wolnie acting so weirdly?
Be careful if you run into weirdly-behaving people.
Could it be…?
Sister Stacy,
let us give you a makeover!
Done!
How do I look now?
This plushie looks a lot like Paddi’s hair, huh?
Don’t change the subject!
The potion is a success!
While the potion is being extracted,
I’ll go get Stacy.
I have a way to fix Stacy’s problem immediately.
As long as we raise both of our hands and cover our eyes,
it won’t matter how Stacy looks.
It looks like I don’t need to do anything.
I think I might never recover.
Sister Sta—
The potion is ready!
Where’s Stacy?
She thought she couldn’t recover
and was so upset that she ran off.
I’ll go find her right now.
Potion?
Where’s my makeup bag?
I’ll turn up the heating all the way.
Let’s see just how long you can stay wrapped up.
Found it at last!
Hey, Wolnie,
it’s been a bit chilly lately.
I’ll help you turn up the heating.
Wolnie, just take the head scarf off if you’re warm.
Wolnie?
Wolnie!
My foot!
Let me out!
It’s getting hot.
Where’s the remote control?
No!
Let me out!
Help!
I’m burning!
This is Wolnie’s favorite.
Let’s see if you react or not.
This is for you, Wolnie!
She’s reacting!
She’s my Wolnie!
Never mind.
Now’s not the time for jewels.
She doesn’t even want precious jewels?
She must be a fake Wolnie!
Wolffy,
what are you doing?
Just give up, Werewolf.
Huh?
Stacy!
There you are.
Hey, Stacy!
The recovery potion is all finished.
Really?
Yes, it’s in my lab.
The antidote is in the lab?
Come with me to use it.
What’s wrong?
When I go home, I’m going to move away.
I might never get to see my good friend, Slowy, again.
What I didn’t realize
was that his future self also moved away.
Actually…
Actually, I—
I’ve caught Werewolf!
Look, guys!
Werewolf?
There it is.
I’ve already tested her back at home.
She kept hiding her face
and didn’t even want a jewel.
She’s not like Wolnie at all!
She must be Werewolf in disguise!
Let’s expose who she really is!
You really are—
I told you, I’m Wol—
You really are fake!
My Wolnie is nowhere near this ugly!
Ugly!
Wolffy,
what did you say?
What a familiar temper.
Why don’t we try out the antidote first?
It’s over there.
Werewolf!
Werewolf!?
I’ve been caught,
but so what?
Don’t you dare!
Huh?
Give me
the potion!
What in the world do you want, Werewolf?
I’m not telling you!
Come on out!
The potion!
The potion is mine, of course.
I won’t let you have it!
Wolffy!
Since you guys want this thing so badly,
I’ll just give it back to you.
Catch!
No, no,
no! My potion!
My potion!
It’s no use.
The potion has already been contaminated by the floor’s germs.
It got crushed.
I’m sorry, I did it
on purpose!
I’ll destroy you all!
Sirius?
How dare you toss me around!
I’ll show you what I’m made of!
Disconnect!
I’ll be back!
Don’t come back!
I’ll never recover.
Don’t be upset. We can make more potions.
We’re all out of the antidote’s ingredients.
Wolffy!
I’m… I’m sorry!
How dare you call me ugly!
I’m sorry, Wolnie!
I can’t believe you called me ugly!
Could a single drop of the potion still work?
It worked!
Excuse me,
is there…
is there any more of the potion left?
Even if there is, I’m using it first!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter