Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Mr. Slowy successfully produced an antidote to help Stacy recover,
but Werewolf smashed it.
Luckily, there was one more drop of the potion left,
so Stacy recovered.
What will happen next?
A Long Farewell
Here we go!
Stacy, you—
I’m okay.
Let’s get going.
It’s not that.
It’s that you’re sitting in my seat,
and I can’t fly the airplane like this.
I’m…
I’m sorry,
I’ll leave right now!
What happened?
I’m okay.
You seem a little off, Stacy.
Well,
once I head back, I’ll be moving.
I might never get to see Slowy again.
This is for you.
I’m sure you’ll like it.
How did you know that I like fireworks?
If only I could watch them with Slowy.
You will.
Thank you, Chief!
What’s wrong, Mr. Slowy?
Well, you see…
Back then, I spent many nights creating fireworks to surprise Stacy,
but I was just too late.
In the end, I didn’t even get to say goodbye.
You guys better not tell her.
Thanks for taking me home, guys.
Take care!
Goodbye!
Wait,
I made some goji tea for you to drink on the road.
Thanks.
Also, the weather’s getting colder.
Make sure to wear more layers.
Or, why don’t you eat this cake before leaving?
Let me go!
I still have many things that I haven’t—
Enough, enough!
Stacy,
aren’t you going to say goodbye to Slowy?
I know that if I see him again,
I’d be too reluctant to leave.
As long as you exchange contact information,
you guys can still communicate no matter how far apart you are.
But—
I think Slowy wants to say goodbye to you, too.
Slowy…
I’ll go say goodbye to Slowy right now.
I’ll take you back to Goats’ Village.
Hold on, Mr. Slowy!
If your cover gets blown, things will get complicated!
I’m just taking her back to Goats’ Village.
It’ll be fine.
With Mr. Slowy acting like that, how can we not worry?
I guess
we were right to follow him.
It looks like everyone is worried about Mr. Slowy.
No need to worry. We’re here, too!
We’re almost at Goats’ Village, Chief.
Back in the day, we ran after each other just like this, too.
Running after
our
own
youth!
My back!
Are you okay, Chief?
I’m even slower than a little kid,
and what’s more, I’ve sprained my back again.
Oh, this is embarrassing!
I can’t even speak!
I’m fine.
I’m just a bit tired. You go on ahead.
I’ll help you walk, then.
No… No thanks!
I’ll just lay here for a little bit.
Did you just hear something snap?
I think that might have been my back.
Stacy, don’t you think that this cart
is kind of ruining my image?
No, it’s not.
Mom,
I want to ride that!
Let’s hurry up.
I almost forgot to go to the bus station to say goodbye to Stacy!
These fireworks will definitely make a great surprise for Stacy.
Look out!
What’s the matter?
Nothing.
The laboratory is right up ahead.
Let’s hurry over there.
Slowy!
Slowy isn’t here.
Hmm…
You both grow plants on your head?
You must be…
Oh no!
a relative of Slowy’s, right?
That… That’s right.
Apparently, he went to see me off?
It’s even on the calendar.
Then let’s hurry up and get going!
Wait for me, Stacy!
But the time…
Don’t worry,
I’ll get it for you.
Down here at last.
Thank you, big brother!
I’m almost there, Stacy.
Could someone help me?
I should have enough time.
Darn it, I’m late!
What the…?
Help!
It’s mutton pot for dinner tonight!
We’re not going to be your mutton pot!
Morning Sun!
Enough yelling!
No one can rescue you!
Let them go!
Mr. Slowy is here to rescue us!
Don’t move!
With just a spark, you guys will
be done for—
Shall we braise them in soy sauce or steam them in clear soup?
I want all!
I haven’t even said goodbye to Stacy yet.
We won’t ever get to watch the stars together,
paint together,
or plant flowers together again.
How touching!
But no matter how touching it can get,
stomachs still need to be filled!
Let them go!
Haven’t you had enough?
This little guy is pretty cute, huh?
Dad, I’m getting bullied!
Are you the ones bullying my son?
Thank you, Buffie.
By the way, you dropped a firework.
Your hand is shaking really hard.
Oh no, I can’t get to the bus station in time!
Don’t worry!
Let’s go sit down over there.
It’s Slowy!
Wait—
Have you been waiting for a while now,
Slowy?
Is there something you need from Mr. Handsome?
My time is very precious.
Need something? Say it.
Sorry. Wrong person.
Don’t worry just yet.
He’ll be here shortly.
Let’s wait for a little longer.
We’re out of time. I have to get on the bus.
Will Slowy and I ever meet again?
Of course you will.
No matter the distance, he will keep writing you letters,
and you will write back.
You two will plan to meet up again
to watch fireworks together.
You two will make a lot of beautiful memories.
I like
this future.
I’m glad you do.
Wait!
Stacy!
Am I… Am I too late?
No. You’ve still got time.
You can make it.
In the end, I still didn’t get to see Slowy.
Look, Mom!
They’re beautiful!
It’s Slowy!
Goodbye, Stacy!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter