Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Slowy, regretful that he hadn’t said goodbye to Stacy,
went with Stacy to look for his young, past self.
Unfortunately, they just missed each other.
Then, Stacy realized Slowy’s true identity,
and the two happily bid farewell.
Bladey’s Dream
Where are Weslie and the others?
You fell asleep.
They’ve already left to send anachronists home.
If they’re so hardworking,
then I’ll—
I’ll eat something first.
By the way,
would you mind giving the past Jay a ride?
I hope you don’t mind.
Want a banana?
Take this, Paddi!
Take what?
Banana!
Paddi,
are you okay?
You evil wolf,
I won’t let you harm a single strand of goats’ wool!
You’ve got it wrong. I was just—
Still trying to ambush?
Is there some sort of misunderstanding?
Nope!
What’s happening?
It’s a quake.
Run!
Paddi, wait!
Isn’t this, without a doubt, goat-hunting?
To protect the Goat Clan,
I must stop him!
Why is everyone gathered over here?
Have I missed something?
Here we are.
I’m so hungry.
I need to make something to eat with Hurricane.
Uncle Wolffy and Auntie Wolnie have gone out to catch goats.
Today, Uncle received many fresh baskets of wild grapes.
Want to try some?
Really?
Take me!
Look out!
Don’t let a wolf bribe you.
He wants to eat you, you know.
Who… Who are you?
Scallions in hand,
large beads on the chest,
and a flower on the head…
Are you Grandpa Bladey—
I mean,
Brother Bladey?
I came to protect you
from getting eaten by this wolf.
I don’t eat goats.
I only eat bananas.
Liar!
Every wolf eats goats.
Alright, let’s not fight.
Uh…
I think you’re right to worry.
That’s why I’m taking us
into Wolf Fortress to prove your worries wrong!
Take me to the food.
There must be something fishy with those.
Watch out!
Something’s fishy. Watch out!
I secretly put the grapes in the kitchen.
You’re so smart. I’ll go right away.
I’ll help you distract him.
Wait.
Can’t resist eating us anymore, huh?
If you want to eat us, get past me first!
Uh…
Why don’t we try, then?
You asked for it!
No, not like that.
Wow, incredible. I concede.
Next, let’s test strength.
I concede with strength. How about something else?
Isn’t it the best out of three?
Do we still need more?
What?
We’re doing the best out of five!
Next up, let’s test flexibility.
I can lift my leg up to my ear.
Since that other guy is very strong,
his flexibility must be very poor.
Like this?
Why did Jay hide it so well?
I’ll help myself, then.
That wolf is very powerful.
I can’t beat him at anything.
No worries, though.
I’ll protect you, no matter what.
No need to get so emotional.
It’s the least I can do.
My grapes!
I’ll find you something to eat.
I didn’t catch any goats today. Wolnie’s going to be mad for sure.
Wolffy,
when did you travel to this timespace, too?
I was just coming home, is all.
This is perfect!
Let’s have mutton hot pot for dinner tonight!
Oh no,
this is the Wolffy from this timespace!
Another wolf!
I can’t believe you caught two goats, Jay!
No, they’re just here to visit.
Since you’re guests,
why don’t you stay here and eat?
You dare to show off such silly moves?
I can do it myself.
It’s all my fault.
If I weren’t so focused on food, we wouldn’t have been caught.
No,
it was my skills not being good enough
and not being able to protect you.
No, it was me.
It was me.
It’s me.
It’s me who has to thank you guys.
Which one should I eat first?
You get some credit tonight,
since you finally know how to hunt goats.
I’ll give you a mutton leg to eat later.
Stop eating all those bananas,
or you’re going to lose your wolfness.
I must get the key.
What are you doing?
Oh no!
I was feeding them bananas.
They’ll be even plumper when they’re full.
You’re finally getting it!
Where are you going?
It’s almost time to eat.
Huh? The goats?
Where’d they go?
Are you sure you don’t know?
What’s that behind you?
It’s… It’s nothing!
Let me see, then!
There’s one right there!
I must protect him!
Thanks for protecting me.
Did I really just defeat a wolf?
I’m sorry, I was wrong about you.
It’s okay.
You guys better leave.
Uncle Wolffy is going to wake up soon, and that won’t be good.
Hurricane!
If you can summon an airplane,
why didn’t you summon it just now to rescue us?
I was too scared.
Where were you guys?
We were really worried.
What’s there to worry about?
With the world’s best, Bladey, protecting me,
I’m not afraid of anything!
Thanks for the compliment.
Paddi, what in the world were you doing,
being out there for so long?
Uh…
While sending Jay home, we ran into a lot of problems
that Paddi solved right away.
Paddi being diligent?
That deserves congratulations.
Want a banana?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter