Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
young Bladey snuck onto Paddi’s airplane
to take Jay home together,
but they were captured by Wolffy.
In the end, with Jay’s help,
Bladey casted his “ultimate”
and defeated Wolffy, successfully escaping.
A Baby Sent From Heaven
Let’s split up and search for anachronists.
Okay.
I should have enough time to make something to eat first.
The Grassland Trio!
How come the baby is just crying and crying?
He must be hungry,
so… he can eat that.
He stopped crying.
You—
You can take it all!
We just wanted to say thank you.
Never mind. Let’s eat something, buddy.
Here,
call me “Dad,” buddy.
you’ll get pears if you call me “Dad.”
Don’t eat their stuff.
I, Dad, will give you a big one.
The baby is mine!
Mine! He’s mine!
It looks like
we’ll just have to use the most direct way
to determine who’s the baby’s father.
Bring it on!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Mmm, baozi!
It’ll be perfect with some soymilk.
Be aware, guys.
When searching for anachronists,
be on the lookout for Werewolf.
He might ambush us.
Got it.
Why did the baozi fall?
And there’s a bite taken out of it?
My food!
Is Werewolf here?
No one’s there.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Are we doing this wrong?
It’s a tie every single time.
How about
the baby calls you “Papa,”
calls you “Father,”
and calls me “Dad?”
I’m so smart, aren’t I?
I guess that’s fine.
Buddy,
—here comes Dad!　—here comes Papa!　—here comes Father!
Where’s the baby?
Help me, Weslie!
A lamb?
Adorable!
Don’t throw things!
Hey, don’t cry!
What have you done to our son?
I…
I didn’t do anything!
Give my son back to me!
Why would you guys have a goat as a son?
We found him.
That day, we were walking,
when all of a sudden…
It’s a bug!
Run!
We’re scared of bugs!
It’s flying this way!
Thank goodness! We’re safe!
…And that’s what happened.
Why didn’t you guys return the baby to its actual parents?
What do you mean?
I’m the baby’s father.
I’m the baby’s father!
I am! I am!
Enough!
Give the baby back to me!
Daddy!
I’m… I’m sorry.
I’m okay.
Daddy…
See? The baby will still miss his parents.
We should just help him find them.
But the grassland is huge. How do we even search?
This baby…
You’ve seen him?
Yeah, his parents have been looking for him for a long time.
They’re in that big forest over there.
Alright. Let’s get going.
The baby lives right up ahead.
Here they are!
Why don’t we call Weslie and the others first?
What are you scared of?
You’ve got us.
It doesn’t look like anyone lives here.
I’ve already set up all kinds of traps on this path.
Step on it!
Look out, buddy!
Buddy,
come back here!
What’s wrong with this place?
Ouch!
What’s with all the traps here?
Buddy!
Werewolf?
I’ve been caught!
So this was all your doing!
We’ll just have to do this the hard way.
Run!
Hurricane!
Hang on tight, guys!
Wait,
where’s the baby?
Weren’t you holding him just now?
How did this baby get in here?
Perfect!
Hey, don’t touch that!
Don’t—
The baby is on Werewolf’s airplane!
Let’s catch up to them!
I found Werewolf! Hurry up!
Roger that!
He’s gone?
Go take a look.
Buddy,
we’re here to rescue you!
Buddy, don’t… don’t move, okay?
We’ll come to you.
It’s a bug!
The branch is breaking!
Hurry up!
We did it!
Are you guys okay?
We’re fine.
Come back here, buddy!
Didn’t expect this, huh?
Look out!
I can’t move!
You’re so done for!
Watch this!
Look out!
Daddy…
Don’t hurt him!
I’ll get rid of you first, then.
What the heck?
Surround him!
Okay!
Hey, this isn’t fair!
Are you not afraid of us?
Of course I’m not scared!
I’ll get my revenge on you guys once I fix my airplane!
What a cute baby.
Where are your parents?
Daddy!
I see.
I’m not your dad.
The baby never once called us “Dad.”
We’ll leave the baby to you guys.
Mommy…
What
did you just call us?
Mommy!
We’re mothers!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter