Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Paddi ran into the lamb that the Grassland Trio were raising.
However, Werewolf, trying to reset the world, stole the baby.
After much difficulty, Paddi rescued the baby,
who started to take a liking to him.
The Naughty Baby
Let’s go search for the baby’s parents.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
Daddy…
Daddy!
I’m not your dad.
Sorry!
He disappeared the moment we turned our backs.
Stay in Goats’ Village with the girls, okay?
Stop it.
Paddi, why don’t you stay here and take care of the baby?
What? No!
We’ll be back soon.
They’ve all left?
Alright, alright. I’ll take you for a walk around the area.
Paddi’s alone?
Now’s my chance!
Who…
Who is it?
I’m Big Humphrey.
What…
What’s the matter?
I saw it all.
He saw me shapeshift?
Since I’ve been caught…
How dare you
step on a flower
and try to run away!
You don’t even understand what it means to protect nature.
You should feel bad about what you’ve done.
This weather
is perfect for sleeping and eating—
Chips,
cake,
and lo mai chi!
Exactly.
Chips,
cake,
and lo mai chi!
There he is.
New releases! Free samples!
Free?
I want some!
Mmm!
Keep on eating.
The best is yet to come.
Mmm!
If you like it, have some more.
All done!
Wait, what?
That fast?
Thank you.
I’ll give your brand a positive review.
Let’s go, buddy.
I guess I underestimated him.
I can’t let him leave.
What… What now?
You dropped something.
This broom isn’t mine, though.
This broom is mine,
but all of the garbage on the ground is yours.
Today, I will speak on behalf of the environment,
and I will fine you to clean up the Grassland!
I need to get out of here.
Look, a saucer!
Where?
I don’t see it.
You haven’t cleaned up your garbage yet!
We’ve looked around the whole grassland, yet found nothing.
Daddy!
Don’t mess up my hair.
Did you not find anything?
Your hair!
I told you not to mess up my hair!
Your hair looks just like the Patriarch’s.
Oh, yeah. The Patriarch.
We haven’t asked the Patriarch yet.
You’re right.
Let’s hurry and find the Patriarch, then.
I’m coming, too.
Don’t mess up my outfit.
Whose baby is this?
Daddy! Daddy!
He’s calling you “Daddy,” so just admit it.
Daddy!
He calls you “Daddy,” too.
Uh…
But Patriarch,
the baby looks just like you.
He must be your child, right?
What are you talking about?
I’m so young and handsome.
Do I look like I have a child that’s this old?
You do.
Come back!
Stop it!
How could such a naughty baby be my child?
You’re so naughty.
Could he be the Patriarch as a child?
I was much more handsome than this baby when I was a child.
See?
No one can see how you really looked with all of that editing.
Besides, I have a scar on my shoulder.
The baby doesn’t have one.
Now that Sparky mentions it, though,
the baby might actually be an anachronist.
No wonder we couldn’t find his parents on the grassland.
You’re so smart, Sparky!
Let’s go to the Hub to confirm it.
Quiet.
Don’t wake the baby.
Daddy…
You truly do care for the baby, Paddi.
Perfect. I can take a nap, too.
Good thing I made it in time.
No one can stop me now.
What’s the matter with you?
Are you done yet?
You’re the one who’s not done. You haven’t finished cleaning.
Can’t I just go back and do it later?
No need for that.
I’ve brought it over for you.
This is the garbage that you left behind. Continue.
If you don’t finish, you’re not leaving.
You leave me with no choice!
It’s Werewolf!
I guess the baby is, in fact, an anachronist.
He must have been trying to take away the baby these past few days.
Paddi,
take the baby with you and find Doudou!
We’ll hold him back!
Okay,
got it!
I’ll leave him to you guys!
Yay, we’ve taken him down!
Something’s off.
Wasn’t this a little too easy?
Look, he’s coming out.
Big Humphrey?
Are you okay?
Autopilot?
Then where’d he go?
Could he have…?
Daddy! Daddy!
Don’t disturb me, buddy.
I need to hurry you to a safe place.
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!
Werewolf,
what are you doing here?
Lure the tiger down from the mountain.
When I bumped into you,
I got onto your airplane.
The one that Weslie and the others took down was just Big Humphrey.
Let go!
I won’t let you take the baby away!
I won’t let go!
Daddy!
Buddy!
Are you okay, buddy?
Daddy!
Hand over the baby right now!
No,
I won’t let you hurt the baby!
Paddi,
we’re here!
Have I been caught?
I can’t let them catch me.
Are you okay, Paddi?
Paddi?
Paddi, are you okay?
I won’t let you take away the baby.
Thank goodness. He’s just asleep.
Great!
It looks like Werewolf’s recent attacks
have all been targeted towards the baby.
I guess he already knew that the baby is an anachronist.
If he’s really an anachronist,
the Ring can scan him and show his home timespace.
Let me do it.
Daddy?
It’s okay, buddy.
You’ll be able to reunite with your real dad soon.
Buddy,
don’t touch that!
The Ring is broken.
What now, Doudou?
We’ll have to wait until I fix it to scan.
Daddy! Daddy!
Oh, well.
I’ll just have to look after this little rascal for a bit longer.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter