Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the bond between Paddi and the baby grew stronger.
What’s more, they realized
that the baby is an anachronist.
However, with the Timespace Ring broken,
will they be able to send the baby home?
Paddi the Dad
Get up, Paddi!
Paddi!
Can’t you clean your dirty room for once?
No throwing stuff, buddy.
What’s wrong with you?
Hey, don’t scold him.
He’s just a kid, you know.
Someone help!
Is anyone there?
Paddi, have you seen Jonie?
She just came back. She’s over there.
What’s wrong with Wilie?
Wilie
has been hiccupping for two minutes straight!
This is the baby you’ve been talking about, right?
Don’t bite that!
The baby’s still young.
Eating unsanitary things is very bad for him.
I think he’ll be fine.
Here, I’ll play with you.
You’re so cute!
You’re not cute anymore!
Stop biting!
Let go!
Ouch!
Are you okay, buddy?
It looks like his stomach hurts.
it must be because he bit something unsanitary just now.
I think he’ll be fine.
Jonie!
They’re okay now.
Great!
Buddy,
I’m sorry.
Is the baby okay?
I can’t believe it.
How many times have I—
Just be careful from now on, okay?
Simply being careful isn’t enough.
If you want him to quit a bad habit,
you’ll have to set examples for him.
Set examples?
Yep! With how mature and steady I am,
Wilie will be just as mature and steady.
Alright.
I’ll make sure to be a good role model!
Paddi.
I’m full.
Paddi!
Don’t eat that!
Don’t litter!
I won’t do it again.
You’re not supposed to toss those out!
I’m so tired.
If only there were an invention to make the baby listen to me.
Oh, yeah!
I think Mr. Slowy has an invention called the “Obedience Pacifier.”
I must capture that anachronist this time.
Paddi,
what did you call me over for?
Buddy,
give the toy to Sparky.
Oh no,
he’s going to throw it.
How did you do that, Paddi?
That’s not all.
Buddy,
clap.
Sit.
Spin.
Hand.
Wow,
he can do that, too?
What about having the baby sleep, then?
How in the world did you do this?
Tell me!
Sleep, buddy.
Paddi,
just tell me.
Uh…
I’ll tell you after lunch.
You better.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
The baby’s gone!
Not here…
Where in the world are you, buddy?
If the remote control weren’t missing, then—
Remote control?
Uh…
What?
You secretly used the Obedience Pacifier?
No wonder the baby was so obedient.
I’m sorry.
Well, let’s put this aside for now.
What matters is that we find the baby.
Sparky…
I’ll use Hurricane to run a search.
Search!
Werewolf?
He was the one who took the baby!
Let’s go after him!
They surely won’t guess that I’m in here again!
Stop crying!
Stop crying.
We lost the signal. Now what?
Their last location was around here.
Let’s go down and look.
Stop crying.
Stop crying!
Did you hear that,
Sparky?
Hear what?
The baby’s crying.
The baby must be around here somewhere.
Stop crying! Just stop crying!
This way!
Why do I feel like we’ve been here before?
Let’s go in.
Isn’t this the cave where we found Werewolf last time?
Then we should be careful and not make too much noise,
or else—
They’re here already?
You’re the one being loud.
Over there!
Buddy!
Two babies?
One of them must be Werewolf in disguise!
Daddy…
What now?
Oh, I have an idea.
Don’t cry, guys.
Here are some toys to play with.
It looks like this is the real baby.
Yep, I’m your “baby!”
We’ve got you at last,
Werewolf!
You caught me, huh?
But
so what if I’ve been caught?
Holding on to me is what matters!
I’ve got you!
You have nowhere to run!
There’s no way you can catch me.
Let’s… Let’s get him!
Goodbye, little goats!
He escaped!
Daddy…
Daddy.
I’m sorry, buddy.
Good thing you’re okay.
Home at last.
Today was exhausting.
Where’s the AC remote control?
Don’t throw that!
You’re… You’re giving it to me?
You’re awesome, buddy!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter