Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Paddi used an invention to turn the baby obedient,
but Werewolf utilized it to capture the baby.
In the end, Paddi use his understanding of the baby
to rescue him.
Stand Up, Buddy!
Are you hungry, buddy?
Wait a minute, I’ll help you—
The baby…
The baby is standing up!
Am I dreaming?
The baby’s really standing up!
Come look, guys!
The baby is standing up!
Did he really stand up?
Paddi, you were dreaming just now, weren’t you?
It wasn’t a dream!
If you don’t believe me, I’ll make him stand up to prove it!
Here, buddy.
Stand up and get it.
Look,
he’s about to stand up!
Stand up!
Here,
stand up and get it!
I’m so tired.
Forget it.
We’d better split up
and go search for more anachronists.
Wait,
who’s going to take care of the baby?
Daddy!
You are.
Buddy, did you really stand up,
or was I just dreaming?
Daddy…
With only Paddi being around,
snatching up that little guy will be a piece of cake!
Buddy,
where are you going?
Yes, that’s it.
A little closer to the cake!
Paddi!
Where’d this old goat come from, foiling my plan?
What are you doing here, Patriarch?
I can’t believe you’re asking!
After that day, none of you guys have come to visit me!
I was so bored being all alone.
We didn’t have time to play with you.
I’m upset!
Then why don’t you come back to Goats’ Village with me and find Mr. Slowy?
But I’m hungry and tired.
I’ll go find some food, then.
Go on.
Daddy…
Your dad will be back soon.
What is a cake doing here?
Success!
I can’t believe you’re more of a glutton than Paddi is.
I found some app—
Where’d they go?
Who are you?
Why have you captured me?
I didn’t want to capture you.
You came here by yourself!
Don’t get too ahead of yourself.
Weslie and the others will be here to rescue us very soon.
The most dangerous place
is also the safest place.
The goats will never realize
that I’ve hidden you guys in this cave yet again!
This wolf looks like he’s got such a big ego.
I’ll take the chance to defeat him.
You evil wolf,
do you dare to challenge me?
Challenge?
Exactly.
If I win, you must let us go!
How does that sound?
Nope.
Don’t you want to prove your own strength?
I don’t.
Since that’s the case, don’t blame me!
I was just kidding. Don’t take it so seriously.
Too loud!
It’s okay.
I’ll think of a way to get you out of here.
Don’t even think about it!
I’ll be keeping an eye on you guys!
What’s the matter?
I… I think he’s hungry.
Why should I care?
Your order of food and milk has arrived.
What now?
The baby wet himself.
Your order of diapers has arrived.
What’s wrong, buddy?
How about I tell you a story?
Once upon a time, there was a cute baby.
One day, he was captured by a wolf!
What now?
He…
He probably wants to watch TV.
There’s no way!
You know I’m holding you hostage here, right?
Why can’t I detect the baby or Patriarch’s locations?
Could Werewolf have taken the baby to that cave again?
Buddy?
We’ve already found him in the cave twice.
Werewolf couldn’t have possibly hidden someone in there again.
Sorry, are you okay?
Don’t fly so fast, kid!
I apologize. I was looking for a little baby,
and I wasn’t being careful.
A little baby?
Could it be—
You’ve seen him?
No,
but I did make two deliveries just now,
and both of them were things for babies.
Where did you deliver them to?
To the cave nearby.
He really is in that cave again!
Thank you.
Don’t fly so fast, kid!
Where’s the baby?
Where’d the baby go?
Where are you going, buddy?
Is that
the key to the cage?
Is he—
Buddy, give me the key on the table.
I knew it. He doesn’t understand what I’m saying.
The key! The key!
The key.
It’s the shiny one!
There you are, guys! Wonderful!
What’s with all the noise?
Where do you think you’re going?
I’ve already told you guys
that flying too fast is very dangerous!
He’s catching up to us!
Werewolf is attacking us!
Oh no,
we have to run!
I can’t move.
I can’t move, either.
Daddy!
Are you okay, buddy?
Buddy, can you press the button above your head?
Go, buddy!
Buddy…
Buddy,
try standing up!
Trying to run?
No way!
The baby is standing up!
You’re coming with me!
Huh?
Buddy,
press that button, too!
Paddi!
You’re here?
Werewolf,
I’ll be the one to catch you!
What a big mouth.
Thank you, Tibbie.
You’re welcome.
You guys win this time around.
The baby really did stand up.
Yes, really.
I can vouch for it.
—Stand up, buddy.　—Stand up, buddy.
Stand up, buddy.
Forget it.
The baby is still young.
It might take a while before he can stand up.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter