Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
while under Werewolf’s threats,
Paddi and the Patriarch
escaped danger thanks to the baby standing up.
Next,
what kinds of surprises will the baby bring to the goats?
Being a Father Is Hard
What a cute baby!
Once you’re all grown up,
how about you become the Patriarch of the Outer Grassland?
Let’s fly!
We’ve been looking for so long.
Whose family does the baby belong to, anyway?
Well…
He might just be your baby.
How is that possible? I’m still so young!
Let go!
Hey, let go!
—Ouch!　—No, no!
Let go, buddy!
Ouch!
I’m sorry, Patriarch!
I’m sorry!
I’m…
I’m okay!
I’m a big octopus!
Now that you mention it, Paddi and the baby are quite similar.
They might actually be related.
We’ll know with just a scan.
Mr. Slowy?
The Gene Analyzer!
Just take a piece of wool and scan it,
and we’ll know if they’re blood-related.
Do I have to pull out my wool?
That sounds painful!
It’s not.
Just hang in there. It’ll be quick.
Forceps of that size?
That’s definitely going to hurt!
No! No!
Alright, alright. Stop scaring him.
Let’s use loose wool. This piece will do.
What does it say?
Paddi is the baby’s father?
But I’m still just a kid!
That means that this is Paddi’s future child.
That must be it.
Really?
Now that you’re a dad,
you need to start acting like one.
But what are dads supposed to do?
Oh, yeah.
Wolffy, what do you do with Wilie?
What do I do with Wilie?
Wilie,
today, I shall pass down self-defense tactics to you.
Okay!
Self-defense tactic number one:
diversion of attention.
Help!
Someone help this father-son duo!
Isn’t that Big Humphrey?
Where?
Now!
Anything else?
Yes.
Self-defense tactic number two:
stealth in foliage!
Come here!
Now’s our chance!
Where’d they go?
How about that?
Seems pretty boring.
With all that detail,
Wilie probably won’t understand it, anyway.
I’ll just do it myself instead.
No way!
Wilie doesn’t yet realize just how smart
he is!
Speaking of which, I haven’t spent much time with Wilie lately.
What are we going to play today, Daddy?
Wilie, why don’t we practice the abilities
that I’ve taught you?
Okay!
Self-defense tactic number one: diversion of attention.
Look,
there’s a pig in the sky!
A pig in the sky?
There’s no way anyone will be fooled
by such an unrealistic sentence.
Now, let’s practice tactic number two:
stealth.
Start.
All done!
Let me see.
Not like that.
Why can’t you even do this one right?
I’m sorry, Daddy.
Whatever. Let’s end here for today.
Daddy…
I’m sorry, Daddy.
Why can’t you do anything right?
Practice harder!
I’m sorry, Dad.
Was I too hard on him?
I have to find Wilie and apologize to him.
Buddy,
how we play hide-and-seek today?
Wilie?
Wilie!
Brother Paddi?
What are you doing here?
I was resting.
Do you want to play hide-and-seek with us?
Hide-and-seek?
Yeah!
One, two, three, four, five,
Go hide, buddy.
six, seven, eight, nine…
Here I come!
I found the baby!
The baby’s too little, so he’s no good at hide-and-seek.
Where’s Brother Paddi?
How could you leave me out of hide-and-seek?
Let’s go search over there.
Don’t you dare run! I’m going to get you guys!
Get us?
A bad guy!
Help!
They’re getting away!
Help, Brother Paddi!
Wilie’s acting is great,
but I won’t be fooled by the oldest page in the book.
A single goat is no match for me!
What should we do?
Aha!
What did you stop for?
Tactic number one: diversion of attention.
Look,
there’s a pig in the sky!
A pig?
You’re trying to trick me, aren’t you?
Why’d the hammock break again?
I’ll be on my way, then.
I’ve been found?
Wolffy?
Paddi, have you seen Wilie?
Wilie?
He’s playing hide-and-seek with us.
Where are they?
We were just here playing hide-and-seek!
The baby’s gone, too?
Was Wilie’s cry for help actually real?
Cry for help?
Why didn’t you watch over them more carefully?
Hurry up and split up to search!
Okay!
We need to hurry back and find Brother Paddi!
Stop!
He’s catching up to us!
Show yourself!
I can’t believe you’ve turned me into such a mess!
Don’t even think about leaving!
Tactic number two: stealth.
Is he gone?
The abilities that Daddy taught me are quite useful.
Buddy,
are you okay?
Don’t cry!
Don’t do it!
Hey, buddy!
Found you!
Daddy!
Daddy?
Are you guys okay?
It’s you again!
I won’t let you hurt them!
You think you can stop me?
You’re no match!
Not too bad, huh?
Have a taste of this, then!
Run, son!
Trying to run?
Daddy!
You dodged it?
Alright,
let’s see whether or not you can do it again!
Stop it!
Who?
Don’t you dare
hurt
my
baby!
Don’t forget that I’m a dad, too!
Wolffy, now’s our chance!
Leave it to me!
I’ll be back!
That’s my line!
Hey, buddy,
you have nothing to worry with me around.
Wilie,
from now on, I won’t ever require you
to learn things you don’t like.
No,
the things you taught me were super useful.
I want to learn more!
Son…
Paddi, where are you?
Doudou says that the Ring is all fixed,
and we can send the baby home now.
The baby is going home soon.
Paddi, are you there?
The Ring is fixed already?
What?
You don’t want to see the baby go?
All ready.
Come on over, guys.
Great,
let’s go.
The results say that the baby is from a past timespace.
This means that Paddi isn’t the father, then.
Am I not his father?
Daddy!
It’s alright. I’ve technically been a dad already, anyway.
Mr. Slowy’s Gene Analyzer should be accurate.
What went wrong?
Forget it.
We’ll know once we send him home.
Alright.
Let’s get going, Paddi!
Okay.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter