Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
due to Paddi and Wolffy’s unvigilance,
Werewolf captured both Wilie and the baby.
It’s a good thing that the children were rescued,
but will Werewolf give up just like that?
Braving the Wolves’ Camp
Alright,
time to find the baby’s father!
We’re going to Goats’ Village.
To prevent scaring the goats,
from now on, Wolffy is—
Call me “Goatie!”
Okay.
Let’s get going, then.
Okay!
Goats’ Village is right up ahead.
Which era of Goats’ Village is this?
I’m so excited.
I’m excited, too.
I’m not excited anymore!
Goatie!
We’ve been surrounded!
What should we do now?
Leave those goats alone!
Village Chief Mandy!
Don’t underestimate Warrior Wolf.
Warrior Wolf?
He’s one of Wolffy’s ancestors!
You’ll be sorry.
Fire!
Did you think I’d be scared of you, Mandy?
Soldiers, attack!
Good luck, General!
Get back here!
I’ll be back!
Are you okay, Goatie?
Are you guys okay?
Yes.
I’m glad.
Also, you guys are…?
We’re…
I’ll pretend to be the baby’s father
and snatch him over!
Where are you going, huh?
Listen to me, guys!
Quiet!
You’re looking for the baby’s father, I see.
Well, his father left the area
to search for him.
Then let’s search around the area.
Aren’t you afraid of them being bad guys, Chief?
With how happy the baby is with them,
I can tell that they’re not bad guys.
The grassland is way too big.
Plus, there’s no sign of the baby’s father.
Hurricane can’t locate him.
What’s that?
A goat’s been caught!
Rescue him!
Roger that!
Alright, buddy,
I’ll come play with you.
Where’s the baby?
Buddy, when did you get out?
You can’t go, buddy. We’ll play with you.
Don’t cry, buddy!
Buddy,
peekaboo!
Peekaboo!
Where’s the baby?
Don’t run off, buddy.
What is it, miss?
Sorry, wrong person.
I’m a “buddy,” too.
Yeah, I’m not so sure about that.
Enough said. Come with me!
No!
It’s a goat!
How do we rescue him?
Hold on, guys!
I’m… I’m a wolf!
It’s Werewolf?
How dare you mess with us!
You guys are the ones who captured me.
Shut up!
Take him to the dungeon!
We can take this chance and capture him.
Hold on,
I have to disguise myself first.
You’re coming with us.
What the heck?
Watch where you’re going!
What the…?
Wool?
Paddi?
Are they…
I’m real!
I knew it!
General, I knew all along that they were goats!
I was waiting for a chance to expose them, is all!
We’ve been caught!
It’s all my fault.
Wolffy,
it’s up to you.
What now?
What should I do?
You’re not going to say that you were also waiting for a chance, right?
General,
I, too, was waiting for a chance to expose them!
Huh?
General,
he—
Lock them up!
No,
what I’m trying to say is that they’re—
don’t!
You two
have done well!
Lock them in the dungeon!
It’s my fault for getting them caught.
I’ll make sure to rescue you guys.
Don’t worry,
Wolffy will surely find a way to rescue us.
Thank goodness that Tibbie and the baby are safe.
You’re here, too?
What are you guys doing here?
Where’s the baby?
I don’t know where he’s gone.
General, here is the dungeon key.
Wonderful job, you two.
I need to find a way to get the key and rescue the goats.
Where’s the baby?
I’m not telling you!
What is the baby doing here?
The baby is mine!
General, there’s a baby here.
No, why am I—
I’m going to cook him!
He’s so cute!
General?
What am I doing?
Soldiers!
Yes, sir!
Cook him!
Oh no!
Don’t you dare!
Goodbye!
He’s so cute!
We can’t do it!
Neither can I.
He’s so cute!
Listen up,
I have decided to adopt this lamb!
Yeah!
What?
I’ll play with you, buddy!
I guess I’ll have to find a way to rescue the baby.
The baby can’t return to his home timespace anymore,
so my job is finished. Goodbye!
I need to rescue the baby right away!
How am I supposed to rescue the baby
and get the key?
Do you like that?
You can have it.
Good job, buddy!
Up next is to wait for an opportunity to rescue him.
I’ve been waiting forever!
The baby wet himself!
Someone change his diaper!
Now’s my chance!
I can, sir!
Hurry up!
What’s going on right now?
Eww!
Really?
Don’t look at it!
If you keep doing that, I’m going to—
I never want to eat again!
Stop gagging!
I want my General to still have an appetite for mutton,
so I’ll go clean the baby up outside and then bring him back in.
Go on.
Don’t be long!
Where’d that wolf go?
Buddy?
Buddy!
Who released the goats?
Who was the last one to hold the key?
You.
Buddy?
Buddy!
I can’t believe they escaped!
We should be safe here.
When did the baby’s arm get hurt?
I have a bandage.
All done.
I’m sorry,
it was my fault for getting you guys caught.
Darton was right.
I’m useless.
What are you talking about?
Apparently, without that group of goats,
you’re nothing much at all.
How dare Darton say that!
I mean, you just made a mistake.
In the end, you’re the one who got us out, weren’t you?
You’ve been working hard to help us from the start.
You’re even more diligent than I, Paddi, am.
Besides, we’re a group.
We have to rely on everyone!
Let’s keep working together, okay?
Guys…
Then let’s go search for the baby’s father!
Buddy!
“Buddy?”
Where are you, buddy?
Excuse me, are you looking for—
My baby!
This is your child?
Yes,
I’ve been looking for my baby for so long.
Apparently, he was rescued by good-hearted goats!
Thank you so much!
Great, we’ve finally found the father!
Goodbye, buddy.
Let’s go, buddy.
I’m in a rush, so I have to go. Thanks, guys!
That’s odd.
He wasn’t afraid of me, even though I’m a wolf.
Also, he took the baby away super hastily.
Where are you, buddy?
“Buddy?”
Buddy, I’m looking for you!
Patriarch, what are you doing here?
Who are you guys?
Do I know you?
Is he not the Patriarch?
By the way, have you guys seen my son?
This is him.
Isn’t this
the baby?
Is he the actual father?
Then who was that other guy just now?
We’re going home, buddy!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter