Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats were captured while looking for the baby’s father.
Luckily, Wolffy rescued them in time
so they could return the baby to his family.
However, that guys wasn’t the baby’s real father.
Can the goats rescue the baby in time?
Father–Son Reunion
I guess this guy is the baby’s actual father.
Looking more closely,
the baby and the Patriarch do share some resemblance.
Now that you mention it, they do look a bit similar.
Oh, yeah!
The baby’s shoulder injury is the same shape as the Patriarch’s.
Are you telling me
that his mark isn’t a birthmark,
but a scar from an injury?
What are you guys talking about?
No wonder this old goat looks so similar to the Patriarch.
Are you okay, sir?
Wolf!
He must have eaten my baby!
He’s a good wolf. He doesn’t eat goats.
Not all wolves are bad wolves, you know.
Wolves like me have died out.
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
Where did my baby go?
The guy that took the baby must have been Werewolf in disguise.
Don’t worry—
Don’t worry,
We’ll help you find the baby.
You know what? I’m a dad, too.
I understand how you feel.
I’ll be sure to help you!
The goats aren’t around,
so I’ll take the chance and get out of here.
Where’s the baby?
The baby’s missing!
How dare you still be worried about food, Paddi!
I was just thinking that if the baby saw these dim sum,
he would really want to eat them.
Let’s keep searching.
There you are!
You had me searching for so long.
I won’t let you go!
Stop!
You can’t outrun me!
How is he that fast?
Got you!
There’s a slope here.
Be careful, guys.
What was that?
Hurry up, guys.
Daddy!
What’s the matter, Paddi?
Nothing. I think it was just me.
Let’s go.
I’ve come prepared this time.
You won’t be messing with my airplane again.
Where’d he go?
Not again!
Enemy approaching!
Turn around!
The gate to Goats’ Village is open!
Get ready to attack!
They’re fighting?
It’s not safe here.
Let’s go out and hide for a bit.
If you guys want to fight, then fight! Why are you following me?
Retaining distance with the enemy.
How dare this pack of wolves break down our gate!
It’s time for revenge!
Mandy is right!
So many delicious goats!
If we don’t eat them now, we’ll never get to!
Warrior Wolf is right! Get those goats!
I never said that.
Go!
Have fun fighting.
I’ve finally escaped them.
Where’s the baby?
Over there!
Buddy?
Stop!
You’re stopping just because some old goat says so?
Don’t you have the dignity that comes with being a wolf?
Oh, you’re right.
Can’t you see that there’s a baby?
What if he gets stepped on?
Come here, buddy!
Daddy!
Buddy!
Goodbye!
My baby!
There, there, don’t cry!
There won’t be any goats stopping me this time around.
How did you guys know where I was?
With all that commotion, how could we not know?
Hand over the baby right now!
You have nowhere to run!
I’ve got cannons, too,
and I have more than you do!
Goodbye!
Don’t! The baby is still on the airplane!
Oh no!
Tibbie?
Are you okay?
Sparky!
Werewolf is running away!
Catch up to him!
I’m so close!
What a nuisance!
You have nowhere to run!
Hand over the baby!
Darn it!
Move!
Paddi!
Thunderbolt!
Help!
I’ve failed again!
Let’s get ready, guys. We’ll be heading back soon.
The baby’s awake.
Daddy!
Buddy!
Aww, buddy.
I can’t believe he can say “Daddy” now.
Paddi,
it’s time to go.
Thanks for helping me find my baby.
Goodbye.
Daddy!
Buddy!
Be safe,
and be a great patriarch when you grow up, okay?
I’m going home now. Goodbye!
Okay.
Patriarch?
Oh, it’s you guys?
Where’s the baby?
We’ve already returned the baby to his father.
Oh, really?
Well, what a pity.
Sure, he was naughty, gluttonous, unhygienic, messy,
and disobedient—
He’s you, you know.
But
as long as he could fix those one hundred-plus flaws,
I was actually thinking he could be the next Patriarch.
Daddy!
I’m thirsty from all that talking. I’ll eat an apple.
Thanks.
Here’s your apple, buddy.
These are all of your favorite snacks.
Make sure to keep warm while sleeping.
When you’re traveling outside, make sure to stay safe.
Also, just one last time, I’d like you to call me
“Daddy.”
Well, Paddi! How rude of you!
Sorry.
What… What’s going on?
Look, guys!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter