Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Werewolf, disguised as the baby’s father, took him away.
Luckily, the goats stopped Werewolf in time
and retrieved the baby,
returning him to his father.
A Vanished Wolnie
Doudou! Doudou!
Even the buildings are getting distorted now.
It’s because we’re running out of time.
We have to hurry and find all of the anachronists,
or otherwise, the world will reset!
Sparky and the others are already searching.
Let’s hurry up and help them.
I’m stuck!
It’s dangerous, son.
Get down!
Weslie, I’m going to go home and check on Wolnie and Wilie.
Wolnie!
Wolnie?
Wilie!
Wolnie!
Stop yelling.
I’m tidying up over here.
Daddy! Daddy!
I’m glad you’re okay. I’ll take care of all this.
Done at last. I’m so tired.
Daddy, Daddy,
let’s draw together!
Sure.
Daddy? Daddy!
Daddy’s tired.
Wait until he wakes up to play with him.
Okay.
It’s cold.
Where’d they go?
Wolnie?
Wilie?
Did they go out?
I’ll make some food and wait for them to come back.
Where in the world have they gone?
I’ve heard that this is happening to buildings on other grasslands, too.
Wolnie! Wilie!
Brother Tai, have you seen my Wolnie?
Wolnie? She’s over there.
That’s odd. He said “my” Wolnie just now.
Wolnie,
there you are!
My dear?
Wolnie!
My dear,
he’s attacking me!
Wolnie,
don’t worry.
I’ll protect you.
Huh?
“My dear?”
I’m your husband!
Just wake up already,
Wolffy!
Wolnie has always been my partner!
Whiter has always been Wolnie’s husband.
Yeah.
There’s no way!
Wolnie is my partner!
I have a wedding photo!
What kind of wedding photo is this, huh?
Wait, what?
How is this possible?
Where’s my Wolnie?
Come on,
let’s go home and check on Whiffie.
What’s wrong, Wolffy?
Weslie…
…And that’s what happened.
Could Werewolf be behind this again?
What could he have done?
Did he alter the past or something?
Weslie,
bad news!
The monitor is showing that a deviation occurred in a past timespaces!
Was it Werewolf again?
Whether or not it was, hurry over and see what happened!
Okay!
Let’s get going!
Here we are.
I’m going to see what happened!
Calm down, Wolffy!
Rushing into it like this
will complicate things if you run into your past self.
Well, then what?
I have an idea.
Wolnie…
I heard Wolnie say
that you two met each other over fried rice.
At the time, I was trying to gather inspiration,
so I went to the canteen for dinner.
Just as I was about to eat,
I got kicked out.
But I was just way too hungry,
so I unknowingly ate the fried rice Wolnie made for spouse-choosing.
That’s how I met her.
Here.
It’s a bioweapon!
Run!
Wolnie…
It’s been so long.
Why haven’t I come to eat yet?
Could it be
that this is what went wrong?
I know where my past self is,
so I’ll go get him.
Keep watch here, okay?
Wolffy,
aren’t you starving?
Come eat!
Who are you, huh?
How dare you disturb my work!
I’m your dad’s cousin’s son.
Everyone is eating now,
so let’s go.
I’m not going.
Someone delivered food to me just now, so I’ve already eaten.
I’m very full.
You’re full?
Even if you’re full, you’re coming with me!
Come with me!
Here comes my new invention, the “Crabber!”
I’m not coming with you!
No,
you have to come with me!
I already said I’m not going!
I guess we’ll have to do this the hard way!
There’s no way I’m coming with you!
The Crabber has a weak point, you know.
No way!
Your weak point is that you can’t flip yourself over.
Come eat fried rice with me!
No!
I’m so tired.
Fine, I concede. Release me.
Just kidding!
You’re so cunning, Wolffy!
You’re too smart, Wolffy!
Mister, just stop chasing me!
No! Come with me to eat fried rice!
You want to eat? Eat it yourself!
No!
No, you must come eat!
I won’t!
Yes, you will!
Where’d he go?
He’s gone.
I can’t believe he escaped.
Will I never get to see Wolnie and Wilie again?
No.
For the sake of Wolnie and Wilie,
I can’t give up.
I guess no one is going to eat it.
I should just toss it.
I’ve lost him at last!
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah!
I’m okay.
Sorry, I ran a little too much earlier,
and I’m hungry now.
Uh,
the fried rice…
could I eat it?
Yes!
There he is!
Look.
Doudou says he placed alarms in each timespace.
From now on, if Werewolf does something again,
we’ll be alerted.
Wolnie, Wilie, I’m home!
Wolnie?
Wilie?
Where are you guys?
Have things not recovered yet?
Daddy!
Wolffy, what are you doing?
Wolnie!
What’s wrong, Wolffy?
Wilie!
I can’t breathe! Let go!
No, I’m never letting go of you guys again!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter