Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
under Werewolf’s doing,
Wolffy lost his family,
and the grassland feel deeper into crisis.
Wolffy, after a massive amount of effort,
finally restored history,
protecting the grassland.
A Strange Weslie
Nowhere to run, huh?
Weslie,
you must accept the fried rice!
This is a thank-you gift from Wolnie.
If it weren’t for you alerting me so quickly,
I might have lost my family forever.
But it looks kind of gross.
Can I not eat it?
I promised Wolnie
that I’d give the fried rice to you,
or else I’d face consequences.
Fine.
Disgusting!
It’s good, right?
You’ll have to eat more to outrun me, you know!
Thinking back on it,
we used to chase each other like this all the time.
At the time, you were still trying to eat me.
Every time I was just about to eat you,
you were able to escape from my grasp.
That was because I ran fast.
That was because I wasn’t focused enough.
Weslie,
the food was good, right?
What food?
Did you not eat enough at my house?
You’ve got a big appetite for how small you are.
I haven’t eaten at Big Humphrey’s house.
He must be mistaken.
The rice is getting cold.
Go share it with the other goats.
At last, the goats will get to know
the taste of this special fried rice!
Oh no!
Should I have them eat such disgusting fried rice?
But I promised Wolffy that I would.
Weslie, what are you holding?
This is Wolffy’s fried rice.
Never mind.
Actually, have it.
What are you doing, Weslie?
Fine. This is from Wolffy’s family,
made to thank us.
I’ve already eaten some,
so I’m going to search for anachronists now.
You first.
Me first!
If there’s food, why not wait for me?
Stop!
Don’t eat it, guys!
What’s the matter with you, Weslie?
This is Wolffy’s trap.
He’s trying to capture us!
How could that be? That’s a thing of the past.
Weslie!
I’ve got you!
Wolffy!
Give it to me!
What in the world do you want, Werewolf?
I’m not telling you!
You forgot about me, didn’t you?
Yeah,
Wolffy’s a good wolf now.
Oh no,
everyone must have been possessed after eating that rice.
I must go to the Wolf Fortress and find the antidote!
What in the world is wrong with Weslie?
Disgusting!
Wolnie, where do I put these boxes?
All of those? How about in the warehouse?
Warehouse?
Sirius’ prototype is in there.
There’s not much space.
What prototype?
Is it that big?
Come take a look at it, then!
Have a look at my favorite piece of work!
So secretive.
Isn’t it just some normal airplane?
What do you mean, “normal?”
Although Sirius’ prototype is its first edition,
it’s made of super-strong deep-sea stainless steel,
a cloud particle collision avoidance design,
and an expansive area of illusory spacetime!
It’s certainly the most powerful airplane of its time!
Isn’t that cool?
Mouse!
Where is
the prototype?
Where in the world are the anachronists?
Let’s keep searching.
By the way,
don’t you guys think that Weslie was acting strangely earlier?
Yeah,
he had us eat some disgusting fried rice.
How strange.
Tibbie was talking about Weslie’s attitude towards Wolffy.
Yeah, he even said that Wolffy’s a bad guy!
Giving us such disgusting fried rice
does make him a bad guy.
Guys, meet at Wolf Fortress!
Wolffy’s prototype has been stolen.
Let’s investigate.
What happened to this bridge?
Help!
Oh no,
he’s in danger!
You’re safe now! Calm down!
It’s you, Weslie!
Huh? Do you know me?
Oh, thank you!
You’ve saved me twice today!
Twice?
Yeah.
This morning, I was delivering a letter,
but the wind blew the letter onto a tree.
Some things went wrong as I was retrieving it,
and I fell from the tree.
It was you who rescued me.
Thank you so much,
Weslie!
Did you not eat enough at my house?
This is where it last was.
How could the prototype have gotten stolen?
Well, what does the prototype look like?
That prototype may not look the same as Sirius on the outside,
but their functions are the same!
Oh, yeah!
Werewolf’s airplane
had the same functions as Sirius.
What?
How are his functions the same?
He must have been the one who stole my airplane!
Hold on.
If Werewolf used your prototype,
then you must know what the airplane’s weak point is.
Nope.
How could my inventions possibly have weak points?
I have an idea!
It looks like Paddi has really thought of something.
We just need to sit back and wait for Weslie to arrive.
He’ll surely think of a solution.
Paddi!
Darn it, I’m late!
Stop!
Weslie,
you’re just on time!
Come help us!
Wolffy!
The Opposite Hammer?
I won’t let you hurt my friends!
Weslie, what’s wrong with you today?
Wolffy’s a friend of ours, too!
Exactly!
Friend?
Wake up, guys!
He’s trying to capture us!
Is there some kind of misunderstanding?
Hand over the antidote, Wolffy!
What antidote?
You’ve got it wrong!
Listen to me!
Hand over the antidote!
Weslie,
calm down!
Weslie, why are you acting so strangely today?
Is something wrong?
Exactly,
Weslie.
Wolffy’s our friend.
He wouldn’t hurt us!
You’ve all been possessed!
Have you lost your memory, Weslie?
Weslie, I don’t catch goats anymore.
Oh, really?
Come with me, guys!
What in the world is going on?
Weslie, let me explain!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter