Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy thanked the goats with Wolnie’s fried rice,
and Weslie began acting strangely.
Just when things couldn’t get more chaotic,
it was discovered that there are two Weslies.
What in the world is going on?
Chasing After Weslie
Why are there two Weslies?
Watch out, guys!
The one in front of you is Werewolf in disguise!
No wonder you were acting so strangely today.
You’re fake!
I’m the real Weslie!
He must be one of Wolffy’s clone goats.
I guess I can’t get them out of here for now.
I’ll just have to retreat and find another way to get the antidote.
Just give up already!
You can’t run from us!
Trying to run?
Get him, guys!
You’re not going anywhere!
I’ll be back to rescue you guys!
Darn it,
we can’t let him get away!
Come on out, Thunderbolt!
What’s a “Thunderbolt?”
What’s that?
Beautiful!
Last time, you impersonated me,
and this time, you’re impersonating Weslie.
But the moment he entered, he kept asking Wolffy for the “antidote.”
That doesn’t seem much like Werewolf.
I saw that, too.
No, he must be Werewolf!
Either way, let’s take him back to Goats’ Village.
What’s wrong, Weslie?
My Magic Airplane crashed too hard.
All fixed!
That was fast!
Its sensory system broke, is all.
What is a sensory system?
Well, every Magic Train has its own sensory system.
Thunderbolt!
They only respond to their drivers’ calls.
By the way, if you’re all here,
who’s keeping an eye on Werewolf?
Paddi is.
Paddi?
Why would you guys let Paddi watch over Werewolf on his own?
Paddi,
are you not tired of watching me like that?
I’m not letting you get away, you know.
Why can’t I see anything?
What’s the matter?
Oh, my eyes!
My eyes!
What in the world did you do to me?
You’re just so sleepy that you closed your eyes, is all.
Don’t sleep!
Keep your guard up!
Sleeping for just five minutes should be fine, though.
To be honest,
this is very normal for Paddi.
I smell cake!
What an expert!
Mr. Slowy had me bring you dinner.
Tricking Paddi couldn’t get any easier.
It looks delicious!
Hold on,
why haven’t I met you before?
I’m… I’m Planie.
No.
Planie always wears his hat, even when he’s shampooing.
I went to wash it because it got dirty!
See? It’s back now.
Oh, what the heck? It’s Planie.
I thought you were hiding something in your hat.
Well, hurry up and eat the cake.
I almost forgot about that!
Hold on,
we literally just had a meal.
Mr. Slowy wouldn’t let us eat this much stuff.
Therefore,
there must be something fishy with that cake!
Since when has Paddi been this smart?
Plus, this cake
smells a little different.
It must be laced with something.
I just knew that a food trap
wouldn’t be enough to get past Paddi.
I have no choice now.
I’ll just go in for the attack!
It tastes pretty good, though.
You ate it?
It was an accident…
I… I knew it.
What have you done to Paddi?
He’s just asleep, is all.
Everyone’s been possessed by Wolffy.
Let’s get out of here for now.
Paddi!
Just five more minutes.
Wake up!
Werewolf is gone!
What?
Werewolf escaped?
Who set him free?
He might have a partner in crime.
Let’s hurry up and search.
Where are we going?
We’ll escape into the forest and then think of a way to get the antidote.
I’ve already set traps waiting for you up ahead!
Who’s playing with airplanes in the middle of the night?
Sorry, sorry!
Can I have the airplane back?
Uh…
There are two Planies, too?
As expected, Weslie.
You even managed to break through this!
I… I didn’t say anything!
But
no matter how smart you are, you’re not going anywhere!
Huh?
Who are you?
Come on out!
Have a taste of this!
Let’s see if you can dodge this!
What?
You guys ruin everything for me!
You’re not going anywhere this time!
Since Werewolf is over there,
it looks like this Weslie isn’t Werewolf in disguise.
Either way, take him back to Goats’ Village for now.
I know how to uncover his true identity.
I’ll get him!
Don’t forget that I’m still here!
Are you okay, Paddi?
I won’t take more of your time. Goodbye!
Stop!
Hey, wait for me!
Have a taste of this!
What the…?
It’s just a silly smoke bomb. I’ll speed out of it.
Sparky, wait!
—Weslie!　—Sparky!
I’ll catch up to you, even if on foot!
Look out!
Paddi!
Are you okay?
It’s you?
Why did you save me?
Well, I’m your friend!
I’ll go find antidote right now
and have all of you guys recover.
Could he also be a real Weslie?
Wait, Werewolf!
I’ll be on my way!
They didn’t even bother helping me fix up the house.
Outrageous!
What’s with all these banana peels?
These kinds of tiny traps could never get in my way.
Good thing I have a plan B!
What?
How naïve.
What’s going on?
Hand over the antidote, Wolffy!
What antidote?
Let me go!
Playing dumb, huh?
What… What are you doing?
Hurry up and say it!
Stop it!
Let Wolffy go, Werewolf!
I’m Weslie. I’m no “Werewolf.”
Weslie,
you impostor of a Weslie!
But he saved me just now.
I don’t think—
He did that to fool you.
Let me finish talking, would you?
By the way,
read aloud the words on this paper.
What does this mean?
This is—
Didn’t expect me to return, did you?
It’s you again!
Morning—
Hurri—
Summoning the Magic Airplanes for help?
Luckily, I came prepared.
You’re coming with me!
Read it aloud!
Come on out, Thunderbolt!
How do you also know Thunder—
—bolt?
Aren’t you the only one who can summon Thunderbolt?
But he can summon Thunderbolt, too.
Therefore, he’s also the real Weslie.
Could it be
that he’s from a different timespace?
Don’t worry, we’re not bad guys.
As for him, he’s already changed.
He’s one of us, too.
Oh, I see.
I was thinking that you guys had been possessed.
So, how did you get here?
I don’t know what happened, either.
At the time, I got blown away by a strong gust of wind.
When I woke up,
I heard Wolffy saying that he prepared fried rice for you guys.
Later, I thought that you guys became possessed after eating it.
Let’s send you back to your home timespace.
You guys won’t have to worry about that!
Oh no!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter