Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats and Wolffy chased after the past Weslie to no end,
thinking that he was Werewolf in disguise.
Later, they figured out his true identity,
but as that happened,
Werewolf captured him.
Double Weslie
Werewolf hid the last three anachronists in the cave.
This time, he must also be
here!
Here?
Sparky,
have you found anything?
We didn’t find them anywhere else.
How are we supposed to search such a huge grassland?
You’re so smart, Weslie. Can you think of something?
Aha!
What is it?
Since we can’t find them,
we’ll just wait for Werewolf to tell us himself.
Werewolf likely can’t differentiate between the present and past me.
If he thinks that I’m the one he should be after,
he’ll show himself.
How do we make him think he got the wrong one, though?
Well, the captured one is my past self,
and I believe in myself.
Let’s go.
Didn’t think there’d be another cave in here, did you?
I’ve jammed all communications, too!
They won’t be able to find you.
Plus,
you won’t be summoning Thunderbolt, either!
Hey, why aren’t you scared of me?
Why would I be scared?
What’s important is that the past Weslie gets sent home.
Should I be worried about you eating me or what?
What?
Are you saying that I got the wrong one?
You’re the present Weslie?
I couldn’t have gotten the wrong one, right?
Nope,
I’ll just capture both of them to be sure!
Future me, it’s up to you now.
All done.
Tracking success.
What if you get captured, too?
Well, getting captured by him is exactly what I want.
But—
Don’t worry.
I believe in myself.
Werewolf’s coming!
Let’s begin.
Goodbye, Weslie!
Goodbye, my friends!
I did get the wrong one!
You’re not going anywhere!
Weslie!
Oh, what a pity.
You were so close.
Let Weslie go!
Out of my way!
Look out!
I’ll be sure to take care of Weslie!
Weslie!
Weslie! Oh, Weslie!
My poor Weslie!
—It’s all my fault for not protecting you!　—Alright, alright.
Werewolf’s gone. Long gone.
Then let’s go check on Weslie’s location!
Just give up already.
You’re not going anywhere.
It’s not over just yet!
My friends will come and rescue me!
Oh, really?
Do you truly think that they’ll find me just like that?
Hidden pretty deeply, huh?
Here you go!
Neither of you are getting out!
How are things going?
When will they be able to catch up to us?
He found the location tracker.
Let’s just summon Thunderbolt instead.
Werewolf set up a communications jammer.
Then let’s climb out.
This pit is too steep.
I tried many times, and I couldn’t get up.
If one can’t do it, then let’s try it with two!
Got it!
One, two…
Quick,
the door is over there!
Weslie is right up ahead!
Hand Weslie over right now!
No one’s here.
This is the location, though.
It’s the location tracker.
What?
What the…?
He saw through our plan.
Now what?
There’s one more thing we can do.
Let’s head back onto the airplanes.
If Werewolf’s airplane is Sirius’ prototype,
then Sirius should be able to detect its location
while it’s running.
Well?
Did you find it?
No, I couldn’t find the prototype’s location.
Don’t lose hope.
Let’s search around the area.
This place is huge.
The exit is over there.
What’s going on?
They got out of the pit?
They’re going to escape, aren’t they?
No, they’re not!
The sap is stuck on my eyes!
I’ll help you!
The sap is stuck on my legs, too!
My traps would never be so easily passable.
You guys have nowhere to run.
You think you can trap us just like that?
I’ve got another pair of legs right here!
Left!
Duck!
Jump left!
Up!
Jump!
Turn left!
How come you’re even faster than before?
We’re almost at the exit!
Duck!
You’re not going anywhere!
The sound came from that way!
Let’s go take a look!
Since you want to do this the hard way, don’t blame me!
Thunderbolt!
Tibbie?
Are you guys okay, Weslie?
It looks like we’re still within the communications jammer’s range.
This area was jammed, huh?
No wonder I couldn’t locate the prototype’s signal.
Why are you guys so clingy, huh?
Alright, Weslie.
Come here!
Stop!
Let’s split up!
As we run, try to summon Thunderbolt!
Okay!
Thunderbolt!
Just… Just run!
I
believe in myself!
Thunderbolt!
Thunder
bolt!
What?
There you are, Thunderbolt!
How… How the—
It’s our turn to fight back!
I just knew that Weslie would come back to rescue us!
Hold on, guys!
I have someone on my hands, you know—
My mechanical arms!
Have a taste of evolved mechanical arms!
Just you wait!
Two Weslies collaborating is incredible.
Thanks.
Why do they look so similar?
That’s for sure,
because
we’re both
Weslie!
Uh…
I’m a little busy.
I have to go.
What’s up with Wolffy?
Was that wolf
really him?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter