Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Weslie inadvertently got captured
while trying to rescue his past self from Werewolf.
Despite the challenges, the two worked together
to outsmart Werewolf
and successfully escaped.
A Wolvified Weslie
Our escape was all thanks to the brave and intelligent you,
Weslie.
No,
I have much to learn from the brave and intelligent you.
But aren’t I you, though?
Let’s send the past Weslie home now.
Where’s my Reversal Hammer?
Reversal Hammer?
Weslie, calm down!
Could it have
fallen in the forest around Wolf Fortress?
We have to find it, then!
Things that don’t belong to this timespace need to be returned.
Without the Reversal Hammer,
sending Weslie home
will be useless!
Werewolf!
Hand over the Reversal Hammer right now!
If not, you’ll be sorry!
You think you’d win?
Goodbye!
That’s right,
we’d win!
Hand it over!
No way!
Watch this!
I’ll teach you all a lesson!
Oh no,
he’s going to crush us with that big rock!
He just looks different, is all.
Take back the Reversal Hammer!
Not again!
You can’t catch me!
The Reversal Hammer?
I’ve got it!
Weslie!
Oh no,
the past Weslie got struck by the Reversal Hammer!
I’m fine.
Where’s the Reversal Hammer?
Weslie, are you sure you’re okay?
Darn it, he took the Reversal Hammer!
Stop!
Let’s get him!
Where did Weslie go?
Could it be that his natural instincts got messed up
after being struck by the Reversal Hammer?
Jonie and I will go find Weslie, then.
You guys hurry after Werewolf
and take back the Reversal Hammer!
Who’s there?
Weslie?
Do you need me for something?
Yes.
I want to eat wolf. Can I eat you?
Huh?
Alright, stop joking around,
Weslie.
Aren’t you just kidding, Weslie?
You’re actually biting me?
What’s wrong with you, Weslie?
Calm down!
I guess I’ll just have to tie you up for now.
Missed me.
What?
Do you want to be steamed in clear soup or braised in soy sauce?
Neither.
Stew it is, then!
By the way,
where are Wolnie and Wilie?
Are they in there?
Wait, you should just cook me first.
My meat is very tender.
It can be braised in soy sauce,
steamed in clear soup,
or eaten cold.
Sweet and sour isn’t bad, either.
Salt-baked is pretty good, too!
Wolffy,
are we having a feast tonight?
Oh, you’re here as well, Weslie?
There they are!
Where should I hide this Hammer?
It’s way too unsafe to hide it in my airplane.
I need to hide it in a place where the goats can’t find it.
Here is fine.
Oh, it’s a frog.
Ouch!
What
is wrong with you guys?
Hurricane detects that Werewolf is around here somewhere.
Let’s capture him as soon as possible!
Werewolf is so cunning.
It won’t be that easy to capture him
unless he delivers himself to us.
Help!
Help me!
They’re all so aggressive!
Could it be
that they’ve all been struck by the Reversal Hammer?
We have to rescue them, then!
Morning Sun!
Don’t worry, Wolnie.
I’m going to call the goats to come rescue us.
How did I get here?
Odd.
Now all that’s left is to find Weslie.
And to lock up this guy, too!
Sparky, help us!
Weslie’s acting very strangely and wants to eat wolves!
We’ll be right there!
Wolffy—
Don’t worry, Sparky’s coming to rescue us.
It’s not that.
We’ve been caught!
Help!
Calling for help?
I’ll cook you first, then!
No!
Wolffy!
Ouch!
Wolffy,
are you okay?
I’m okay.
Don’t worry, I won’t let you guys go anywhere!
Stop it, Weslie!
There you are!
My wolves!
You’re recovering right this instant!
You thought you could lock me up just like this?
I’ll teach you guys a lesson!
Do it, Wolffy!
On it!
Here comes my super-kill!
Come eat me!
I’ve got him, Weslie!
Go on, Reversal Hammer!
Darn it! Surround him!
The Reversal Hammer?
A wolf?
Weslie’s been captured!
Thunderbolt!
Oh no,
all of our airplanes are stuck!
Come help!
I want to eat wolf.
Darn it, the airplane is going down!
Enough already. Just let me eat you!
Let go of me!
Nope.
What a big wolf!
Look, guys!
It’s Werewolf’s airplane!
What happened?
What is this place?
Werewolf?
Run!
Where’s the goat?
The Reversal Hammer?
You’re not going anywhere!
Great,
they’ve come to rescue me!
Why—
Sorry, Weslie.
We can’t let you mess around.
I’ll help you recover in a minute.
We need to fight Werewolf first!
Where’s Werewolf?
I’ll be back!
That’s my line!
Why am I tied up?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter