Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the wolvified Weslie
nearly ate Wolffy and his family.
However, at the same time, he foiled Werewolf’s plan.
In the end, he recovered.
What will happen next?
Crisis
Thanks for sending me home.
It’s the least we can do.
Goodbye.
I don’t know
when I’ll get to see you guys again!
Actually,
you’ll see us once you return to the village.
Oh, yeah.
Well,
I’ll be on my way.
Take care.
We’ll miss you.
Goodbye!
Safe travels!
Yay,
I can finally go home and rest!
Wolffy?
Why’s he sneaking around?
Wolffy!
Have you guys sent Weslie home?
What are you holding, Wolffy?
What’s with the secretiveness?
It’s… It’s nothing.
It’s just stuff that Wolnie wanted me to buy for her.
Wolnie uses a shaver, too?
It looks like a shaver on the surface,
but in reality, it’s a…
a women’s cell phone.
No matter how I look at it, it looks like a shaver.
Oh no, oh no!
Wolnie’s calling me.
Wolnie, I…
I won’t be home for dinner.
It…
It is a cell phone.
These slippers are a bit big, aren’t they?
Are Wolnie’s feet this big?
These…
These are for killing cockroaches.
Killing cockroaches?
This is what you’d need!
What’s up, Doudou?
Something’s gone wrong in the timespaces!
Hurry over here!
What?
Let’s head to the Hub right away!
Okay!
I’ll bring my stuff home first and catch up to you later.
Here you are.
What happened?
The past Weslie is gone.
Could it be
that Werewolf took the past Weslie?
I… I guess so.
It’s him again!
We have to find him as soon as possible!
Weslie, what…
what’s wrong?
What… What’s going on?
I think I’m
turning transparent.
That…
That must be because the past Weslie
is in a critical condition!
Huh?
Then, Weslie, come to Rainbow for medical attention!
That’s no use.
We’ll have to rescue the past Weslie.
It’s okay.
I’m sure we’ll find my past self.
Jonie, take Weslie back to Goats’ Village for now
and see if Slowy has any other solutions.
Don’t worry. You’ll be okay.
Let time move a little faster.
My undersea world will be back soon!
Mr. Slowy,
Weslie’s turning even more transparent!
It’s no use.
The present Weslie can only be saved
if the past Weslie is rescued.
Don’t worry.
I believe in you guys.
I’ll see if there’s anything else we can do!
Why can’t we find him anywhere?
We’ve already looked in all the places that we can.
It’s Werewolf!
What is he doing here?
Is he coming to laugh at us or what?
Forget about him.
Get on the airplanes!
We’ve searched every place
except for Werewolf’s airplane!
Stop, Werewolf!
Caught up to me, huh?
I can’t let them—
Let Weslie go!
Let…
Let Weslie go?
You’ll have to catch me first!
Werewolf jammed his airplane’s signal.
Weslie must be in there!
Get him!
Stop!
Shut up!
Stop it!
Give Weslie
back to us!
Are you okay, Tibbie?
I’m okay. Let’s get Weslie.
Weslie!
Weslie isn’t here.
Where have you hidden Weslie?
What “Weslie?”
I don’t know what you’re talking about.
Playing dumb, huh?
If you didn’t take Weslie, what were you running for?
Hello? Mr. Slowy?
I should be worried about you guys capturing me.
If you don’t tell me right now, I’ll—
Let’s head back to Goats’ Village!
Weslie
doesn’t have much longer.
If you don’t go now,
you might not even get to say goodbye.
Stupid goats.
Weslie, wake up!
Don’t fall asleep!
Wake up!
Weslie!
Paddi?
Tibbie?
Guys?
What’s with all the sad faces?
I know you’ve already done your best.
You’ll be okay!
You have to be!
There, there. I know it’ll be okay,
so don’t cry anymore.
Girls look prettier when they smile, you know.
Paddi,
no more slacking off from now on.
Sparky, keep an eye on him for me.
No! No!
You’ve grown up now.
No more of that capriciousness.
This is outrageous!
I’m going to find Werewolf
and force him to tell me where the past Weslie is!
Sparky.
Sparky!
I’m sorry.
It was my fault for being impulsive, smashing the Gem,
and causing all of this trouble in the first place.
But now, I’m out of chances to fix it.
It’s up to you to lead everyone
and do the next right thing.
Jonie, keep an eye on them
and don’t let them mess around.
Work hard to find the anachronists
and save the world on my behalf.
If we’re going, we’re going together!
We can’t leave behind any person!
How long have we known each other, Wolffy?
For around five thousand episodes.
Oh, that many?
We met when goats and wolves were sworn enemies,
and we’ve still been through so much together.
At last, we managed to become friends,
yet now, I have to go.
Our time as friends may not have been long,
but
I’m very glad to have known you, Wolffy.
Me too!
We’re flying!
Dad…
Mom…
Mr. Slowy?
I’ve… I’ve failed your parents.
I didn’t look after you well enough.
No, Mr. Slowy,
thank you for taking my parents’ place
for all of these years
and raising me.
If, someday,
my parents return,
please give this bell to them for me.
Tell them that I’m very proud
to be their son.
Goodbye.
You’re so smart, Weslie.
Can you think of something?
I’ll take care of you from now on, Weslie.
Let’s play soccer after homework, Weslie!
What should we do now, Weslie?
From now on, we’re friends!
To our friendship!
Weslie!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter