Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Werewolf put the past Weslie
in a critical condition.
This resulted in the present Weslie’s condition deteriorating, too.
Weslie must be saved!
Can it be done?
Resurrection
Weslie,
I’ll be sure to give the bell to Smarc.
What the…?
It looks like there’s something written on the bell!
“Ice…” “Ice Pole!”
How did text suddenly appear on the bell?
Could this be
a clue that the past Weslie left us?
Ice Pole?
Oh, yeah.
At the time, Werewolf was at the Ice Pole, too.
That means Weslie might be hidden somewhere at the Ice Pole!
Let’s get going, then!
You’ll be okay, Weslie!
There’s something over here!
Follow me, guys!
Sparky and I will take a look down there.
Weslie?
Weslie!
Weslie has to be here, right?
Just hold on.
Let’s keep searching.
It looks like there’s a hole over there!
It’s Weslie’s bell!
Weslie!
We’re here to rescue you!
You’ll be okay!
Weslie!
Weslie,
wake up!
I knew that you guys would come.
Weslie!
What’s taking them so long?
We’re back.
Weslie!
Thank goodness Weslie’s okay now.
Let’s head back to Goats’ Village, then.
How come there’s not a single piece of food around here?
The goats?
Where’d Weslie go?
Great,
Weslie’s recovering!
Look out, guys!
What happened?
Oh no!
Tibbie!
Is everyone okay?
What in the world happened?
The smoke is super thick.
Where are you guys?
Don’t panic, guys. I’ll activate location tracking.
Paddi,
what’s wrong?
Where are you guys?
Right here!
Werewolf?
Stop!
Wolffy?
Are you okay, Jonie?
Hand over Weslie right now!
No way!
Look out!
Got you!
Out of my way!
Oh no!
Jonie!
Wolffy!
No worries. I’ve got you.
You can’t stop me!
It’s game over.
I’m
still here!
Sparky!
How dare you ruin this for me!
Now’s your chance, Tibbie!
Darn it, the plane is stuck!
Werewolf,
these are the consequences of your poor actions!
Let’s go.
Oh no, the ice mountain is collapsing!
Don’t go!
Save me! I’m sorry!
Should we save him?
Why should we?
He almost killed Weslie!
I’m begging you guys!
I’ll never do anything bad again!
Help me!
Please help me!
Poor thing.
Let’s get him out of there.
What do you think, Wolffy?
I mean,
I’ve done a lot of bad things, too,
but you guys forgave me.
As long as he can realize and fix his mistakes,
let’s give him another chance.
Wolffy!
Werewolf,
let’s go.
You guys
are too kind!
Mr. Slowy?
Weslie, you’re awake.
I’m so glad! This means that they found you!
Where did everyone go, Mr. Slowy?
Oh, they…
All of that happened, huh?
With Werewolf being so full of tricks,
he must have been behind all of this.
I need to find them.
Wait,
wear this.
It stopped.
Are you okay?
Yes.
That’s good.
From now on, you’re a changed wolf, so no more bad things.
By the way,
I’d like to give you guys a gift.
A gift?
Yep.
I hope you guys like it!
Why?
Why did you guys trust me?
Could it be
that I acted too well?
Despicable!
I can’t believe you tricked us!
Despicable?
I’m a bad guy, you know!
Is that not normal?
What should we do?
I know!
I’m going to blow you guys up.
Goodbye!
It’s Weslie!
Are you guys okay?
Ouch!
Werewolf,
you’ve been surrounded!
How dare you deceive us!
I can’t believe it!
If I die, you’re dying with me!
Oh no!
How could I do such a thing?
Huh?
Don’t get cocky too soon!
The best is yet to come!
He fled again!
Weslie,
I’m so glad that you’re still alive!
There, there.
I’m back now, aren’t I?
We’re never letting you go again!
Okay, okay!
Hey, guys!
Yay, you’re okay, too!
Thanks for rescuing me again, guys.
We should be thanking you.
It was all thanks to the clue you left us.
Alright, let’s send you home!
Okay.
You can drop me off here.
We’ll be on our way, then.
Sounds good.
Where’s my Reversal Hammer?
The Reversal Hammer is missing again?
My Reversal Hammer
is right here!
Weslie loves to play pranks on other people.
Goodbye!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter