Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats and Wolffy crushed Werewolf’s plan
and rescued both of the Weslies.
Later, they sent Weslie to his home timespace.
Which anachronist
will be the next to appear?
Dad and I
There are fewer and fewer anachronists.
Keep up the good work, guys!
Yeah!
Did everyone hear that?
We’ll continue chasing victory!
We won’t fight unprepared!
Let’s have a big feast before departure!
Can’t we at least have some instant noodles?
What are you talking about, Paddi?
Of course we’re going to eat and play!
Yay!
I’ll be in charge of making a cake!
I’ll be in charge of decorations!
I’ll be in charge of dancing!
I’ll be in charge of—
I’m a little busy, so I’ll head back to Wolf Fortress.
You guys go ahead.
Don’t be long, Wolffy!
Wolnie, I’m home!
What’s going on?
I should be asking you that.
You tied me up earlier,
and once you released me, you told someone to watch over me.
What exactly do you want?
Dad, I—
Not again!
I have no son as old as you!
Dad, calm down.
I have no daughter as old as you, either!
Alright, alright.
Have some fruits and calm down.
I’ll interrogate him about everything.
Fine.
Since you’ve been so kind to me these past few days,
I’ll trust you.
Interrogate him thoroughly.
Where did you find Dad?
I noticed him when I was looking for Weslie.
Why don’t you send him home, then?
He keeps yelling that he wants to go home!
But I haven’t seen Dad in so long.
I just want to spend some more time with him.
Why does he keep staring at me?
Wolffy…
Daddy, Mommy, I’m home!
Son!
Son, what are you doing here?
Daddy! Daddy!
Help! Help!
Daddy!
Silly,
it’s alright.
This is your grandpa.
There’s no way I’m a grandpa!
I’m Dad!
Daddy, help!
You really are his grandpa, Dad.
Shut up!
Dad—
Daddy—
Shut up!
—Shut up!　—Dad—　—Daddy—
Stop it!
Let me explain!
Grandpa is so young!
My grandson is adorable, too!
Let’s play together!
Sure!
It turns out that I’ve traveled to the future.
Plus, I have such a cute grandson.
Son!
Yes, sir!
How many goats have you caught?
Uh—
Of course he’s caught some.
He’s caught them many times!
They’re very afraid of me.
They call me the Flying King!
Really?
Daddy isn’t lying.
The goats often help him fly, too.
They help him fly?
Yeah,
Daddy always goes “zoom” and flies back home!
Wow!
Since my son has all of these skills,
how about demonstrating them to your father?
Beautiful! Beautiful!
Paddi, won’t you come play with us?
Paddi,
you ate up everything!
Nonsense!
There’s clearly one more big slice of cake over there!
I’ll just make some more.
Since it’s such a big slice—
Stop eating!
Wolffy hasn’t even had any yet!
Oh, yeah. He hasn’t come yet.
I’ll give him a call.
Wolffy, if you don’t come soon, there won’t be any food left.
I’m busy, so I can’t come.
Have fun, though.
Goodbye.
He says he’s not coming.
He’s not coming?
So, this cake—
Why don’t we bring this piece of cake over
and surprise him?
Good plan!
Let’s go
deliver this cake to Wolffy!
Didn’t Paddi eat all of the cake?
What are you guys even delivering?
You must have missed bonding time with your father, haven’t you?
Wolffy,
I’ll play with you today.
Yay, Dad!
Are we going to the amusement park?
No, of course not some place like that.
Today, we’re playing on the training ground that I made myself!
Here we go!
Now,
let’s experience that once again!
Go on.
Show me how much you’ve grown!
Right.
I have to prove to Dad
that his son has already grown up.
I’m no longer the weak Wolffy that I used to be!
Watch this!
You really have changed, Wolffy.
You’ve become even weaker.
Can’t you fly?
It looks like I’ll have to train you from the beginning.
Faster!
Use every bit of your strength!
I’m exhausted. Let’s rest for a bit.
Great.
Why are you laying down, Wolffy?
By the time I’m done resting,
you must move all the rocks to the other side of this line.
Understood?
Don’t I get to rest?
Yes, sir! I understand! I understand!
How long is this going to take?
I’m done!
Wolffy!
I… I wasn’t slacking off!
What are they doing here?
Hey, guys.
Wolffy, what are you doing?
What… What am I doing?
I’m…
I’m exercising.
What are you guys doing here?
I know you’re busy,
so we brought you food.
Surprise!
Oh, what a surprise.
How did you guys find this place?
We just so happened to see you while on our way to Wolf Fortress.
What a coincidence.
You’re acting very strangely today, Wolffy.
Are you okay?
Am…
Am I okay?
I’m…
I’m just hungry.
Where’s the cake you guys brought me?
Eat as much as you’d like, Wolffy!
Guys…
How am I supposed to “eat as much as I like?”
I’m so full.
Thanks.
We’re glad you like it.
I finished the cake, so you guys can head back now.
Safe travels!
I’m finally done with them.
Something’s off with Wolffy.
Dad!
Where’s Dad?
Dad?
Dad!
Which way did the kids go?
You almost tripped me there.
Where should I go from here?
Where in the world did Dad go?
Are the goats of the future always this strong?
Wolffy!
Slowy?
Dad!
I can’t let them notice Dad!
Dad, are you okay?
Dad, wake up!
Dad!
Wolffy,
who were you calling “Dad” just now?
I’ve been caught.
I—
Also, how come there’s two of you now?
Two?
It’s not even that clear.
Really?
That’s just double vision.
I broke your glasses.
I’m sorry,
I’ll get you an even better pair next time.
You can head back.
But who were you calling “Dad?”
You were mistaken. Goodbye!
Wait a minute.
Wolffy,
don’t think I don’t know.
What?
You
haven’t eaten the celebration cake yet.
How many cakes are there going to be?
Thanks, Slowy.
You’re welcome! Safe travels!
Don’t fall over!
Dad,
just hang in there!
Why did you have to set these things up at the entrance?
Huh? What?
We’re almost there, Dad!
Dad,
you’re okay?
I saw it all.
Did he see Slowy?
You
really
completed the entire obstacle course!
As I said,
I’m no longer the child from long ago.
These obstacles can’t stop me.
Great job, son!
You’re incredible!!
I’ve always been this incredible.
Good.
Let’s have you train five more times, then.
What?
No!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter