Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy discovered that an anachronist
was, in fact, his own father,
Darky.
As such, he secretly hid him in Wolf Fortress.
Will the goats find out about this?
Strict Dad
Once you’re done training,
we’ll go hunt goats together.
Hunt goats?
I can’t let Dad go out again!
Dad!
Dad, you’re already quite old.
Leave the goat hunting to me.
Stay here and rest.
I’m perfectly healthy right now! I don’t need to rest!
Dad, what I meant
is that you don’t need to do anything.
Come with me.
Look, Dad.
This is my gadget warehouse.
With these powerful gadgets
along with your special training,
catching goats by myself is a piece of cake!
What’s this?
Dad, this is
the Smart TV!
“Smart?”
Exactly! Not only can you watch television on it,
you can use it to see anything
that this pair of glasses sees.
Try them out, Dad.
See?
Cool!
Now, I can see everything that you’re seeing.
Since you have so many amazing things,
then your special training is now to catch goats on your own.
Then you can stay home and rest, Dad.
However,
there’s one condition.
Condition?
Listen to what I tell you, son!
You don’t need to do this, Dad.
Are you questioning my abilities?
I’ll go catch goats right now for you to see!
No,
I’ll listen to you, Dad!
Dad,
it’s about to rain. No goats will be out here.
Let me come home.
You only just went out!
If you can’t catch a goat, then don’t come home!
Where are the anachronists?
Wolffy!
Goats are coming!
He’s waving to us.
Let’s go to him!
Why are you guys getting closer? I’m telling you to leave!
Capture them, Wolffy!
He’s so impatient.
Let’s move faster!
What’s up? Have you noticed something?
No… No, I haven’t.
Your glasses are so cute, Wolffy!
Let me try them!
Now’s your chance! Get him!
Get… Get him?
What’s wrong, Wolffy?
If…
If I take off my glasses, bad things will happen.
What do you mean? You don’t normally wear glasses.
Either way,
just don’t touch my glasses, okay?
Why do they seem to not be afraid of you?
I’m… I’m pretending to be kind to them
so that they let their guard down.
Good.
Take them all out with one hit, then!
What’s wrong, Wolffy?
I thought I heard someone calling me over there.
How do I get them to leave?
It’s raining!
I’m headed back now.
Goodbye!
You may not return!
Dad, I can’t catch goats if I get sick!
Why are you guys following me?
Your place is the closest, so of course we’re passing the storm there.
I can’t let them go to my house and see Dad!
With how hard it’s raining,
we can’t get to my house in time.
Hide in here for now.
It’s dangerous to walk in severe rain,
so let’s use leaf umbrellas and wait for the rain to stop.
The rain has stopped.
Let’s continue searching for anachronists.
Okay!
I’ll catch up to you guys later!
Dad, I’ll come home and get warm first.
What were you whispering about, Wolffy?
Why are you following me?
I’m in charge of searching around Wolf Fortress.
Let’s go!
Your plan has caused a goat to voluntarily get close to you!
Keep it up, son!
Now’s your chance.
Attack him!
Such a small twig is useless!
Get a bigger one!
Oh, my back!
What do you mean you can’t pick up the rock?
As a man, you need to have a strong body!
Even a goat is making fun of you.
How are you supposed to catch one?
No,
this Sparky is very bold and powerful.
Cockroach!
“Bold and powerful?” Who are you kidding?
Is the cockroach gone?
He’s super agile.
Didn’t you see
how he grabbed both of my arms just now?
Let’s keep going.
What
just happened?
He tripped me.
This goat is way too cunning.
Useless!
Who is it?
Was it just me?
Wolffy,
are you okay?
I’m… I’m fine!
Wolffy,
I can’t believe a goat is caring for you!
You’re so useless!
I’m… I’m sorry!
You’re better off just digging a trap and leading the goat into it.
However,
don’t disappoint me again!
Yes! Yes, sir!
Wolffy, who are you talking to?
I…
I think I just saw anachronists over there!
Alright,
I’ll go take a look right now!
This trap is so obvious.
There’s no way Sparky will fall into it.
Why is there a trap here?
Well done, son!
Capture him!
Wolffy, help me up.
There’s a cockroach next to you.
Cockroach!
What’s the matter, son?
What happened?
Go away, cockroach!
Wolffy?
Wolffy!
Get up! Get—
Get up, Wolffy!
Dad…?
You passed out from just a small hit.
I can’t believe it.
Get up and keep hunting!
Yes, sir.
Louder!
Yes, sir!
Firmer!
When you’re tracking your prey,
you must watch it closely,
with a sharp gaze.
Yes, sir!
You must keep silent, too!
Yes, sir.
When catching your prey, you must act quickly!
Straighten your arms!
Dad is so strict.
What was that?
Nothing!
I caught it, Dad!
What are you saying, Dad?
Go away, cockroach…
Dad…
Cockroach…
Wolffy, why are you holding on to me?
I—
Well done, Wolffy!
Faking an injury to gain his trust? Great move!
Well done, son!
Dad!
You need to be responsible and become an outstanding wolf.
I won’t always be by your side, you know.
No,
I want to be with you!
Stand up straight!
Yes, sir!
Great, son!
He’s very scared right now.
Capture him!
Wolffy, can you let go now?
Uh…
How do I not capture him?
Ouch!
What’s wrong, Wolffy?
Oh, it hurts!
Son, what’s going on?
That goat escaped from my grasp!
He’s so strong!
Where are you going?
Ouch!
Did I hurt you just now?
Please don’t hit me!
Don’t give up, son!
My glasses got knocked off!
Stay away!
Stay away,
please!
Where are you hurt, Wolffy?
Son?
Son!
I’m sorry, I broke them.
That was great!
That was awesome!
I was just practicing my theatre lines just now, Sparky.
Thanks!
What…
What do you mean, “theatre lines?”
You’re back now?
Dad?
Sparky’s so strong.
He knocked me away with just one hit!
What are you doing?
Take care of your wounds.
What are you smiling at?
Hurry up!
Yes, sir!
You couldn’t even catch a goat with such advanced sciences?
It looks like it really is physical strength that’s the problem.
Run fifty laps around the forest!
What?
Now!
Chest up!
Tail up!
Who is it?
How come I feel like someone’s been following me?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter