Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
to keep Darky’s true identity undercover
while also not hurting his friends,
Wolffy repeatedly pretended that his goat hunt was a failure.
However, this made Darky very upset.
A Different Kind of Fatherly Love
There, there. Let’s stop training.
How about I take you to the amusement park?
Yeah!
You’re awesome, Dad!
Dad is awesome.
How many laps left?
If you don’t finish them all today, you’re not eating dinner!
I’m running right now!
Training like this every day even at this age.
When will it end?
Just tell him so.
These are Sparky’s favorite boxing gloves.
What if he’s mad at me when he finds out?
You guys are friends.
Do you think Sparky would get mad at you over a glove?
Yes.
Paddi!
Help me, Mr. Slowy!
Paddi,
you’re slacking off again!
It’s time to search for anachronists!
It’s okay, go ahead.
Sparky,
I’m sorry! I ruined your boxing glove!
Oh, come on.
It’s not like it’s that big of a deal.
Did you really hurt your leg over this?
Sparky…
You’re so kind, Sparky!
Sparky isn’t angry at Paddi?
See? It’s not that hard to just say it.
If I tell Dad that I don’t want to train anymore,
would he allow it?
You’re back.
Come over here.
Dad,
I don’t want to do any kind of running training anymore.
Oh, we’ve been thinking the same thing!
Come!
Being truthful is the way, huh?
I should have said so earlier.
This is the weightlifting chair that I just bought.
With it,
I’ll never have to worry about you slacking off again.
Start now!
If I don’t, what are you going to do about it?
Eww!
So heavy!
Training number two begins now!
Dad, what are you doing?
This machine trains your abs.
Pretty good, isn’t it?
No more, Dad.
What did you say?
Dad,
the truth is, I don’t want to do any sort of training.
I’ve already grown up.
I don’t want to do these parent-child activities anymore.
What did you say?
You’re right.
You’ve grown up,
so I won’t pressure you anymore.
This kind of weather should be enjoyed thoroughly.
It feels so good to not train.
One, two,
one, two,
one…
One, two,
one, two,
one…
Wilie?
Why has Dad taken Wilie to train now?
Wolffy!
Are you seriously making your son
pick up your slack when you won’t train yourself?
I’ll go take a look.
Dad,
what are you doing?
I’m doing some parent-child workouts with Wilie.
He’s still a child.
He needs to get a head start.
Grandpa says that once training is over,
he’ll take me to the amusement park!
Let’s continue.
Careful! Don’t get hurt!
You’re almost at the finish line! Keep it up!
This is even harder than my own training.
Wilie?
Your leg is hurt.
It’s a small injury.
You’re all feverish. I’ll take you home right now.
The only thing you ever care about is training,
but you’ve never once actually cared for us.
Daddy…
It’s okay, we’re almost home.
Time for dinner.
What’s taking Grandpa so long?
Has something happened to him?
There’s no way.
How could there be any danger in Green Green Grassland?
The strongest typhoon on record is landing on the grassland.
Typhoon?
It’s okay.
The weather forecast is usually inaccurate.
Let’s watch another channel.
We hope that—
A car crash has occurred in the north of the grassland—
A landslide—
If you don’t even want to watch such crucial news,
then don’t watch anything at all!
It’s alright. Nothing will happen.
Let’s eat.
Yes, Wilie.
It’s raining.
I’ll collect the clothes.
Mommy,
why is Daddy going outside?
He’s collecting the clothes.
Why is he out so late?
What a nuisance!
It really doesn’t hurt anymore.
This herb is so cool.
How did you discover this herb, Mr. Slowy?
It was because of Darky.
Dad?
At the time, I’d gone out to pick fruits,
but noticed that wolves were planning to attack Goats’ Village.
I need to hurry back and notify everyone!
This is bad!
Wolves!
We must take down the gate today!
Your Majesty,
Wolffy fell down back at home,
and he has a forty-degree fever.
Are you going back?
I’m attacking Goats’ Village!
Don’t disturb me!
Go!
Your Majesty, don’t leave us behind!
Darky!
Thanks.
What’s going on?
Why isn’t he capturing goats?
Once the medicine’s applied, your fever will go down.
That herb can be used in such a way, too?
It’s raining, Mr. Slowy.
Your story is quite long.
Let’s go.
Dad,
is that truly what happened?
Because of me, you—
Dad…
I want Dad!
You’re useless.
You can’t even handle such a small injury.
Dad is so kind.
Dad?
I remember it now.
Dad, I’m sorry—
Dad?
Have you been taking care of me all night?
Are… Are you okay?
Get off of me.
I collected these herbs for Wilie.
When you got hurt as a kid, it was this herb that helped you.
Let’s go home, Dad!
No.
Let’s do some parent-child activities.
The amusement park is fun, isn’t it, Grandpa?
I didn’t realize how much fun it’d be!
Let’s go on the next one!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter