Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy got into a fight with Darky over training.
However, he realized that he didn’t truly understand his father.
In the end, Wolffy understood his father’s love,
and the two made amends.
The Strange Apprentice
Have you guys found any anachronists?
No.
We must have forgotten to search somewhere.
Let’s search again!
How about we don’t? It’s not like we’ll find them.
What do you mean?
I…
I meant that I couldn’t find my cup!
Found it.
Look, guys!
I found a dark—
Dark what?
There’s a dark swan over there!
Who cares about a dark swan, huh?
Hurry up and search for anachronists!
Why don’t we search that way?
Why has Wolffy been acting so strangely lately?
I can’t let them discover Dad.
I wonder what he’s doing right now.
Red dates, ginger slices, ginseng…
I still need one more ingredient.
Is it turnips or is it corn?
I still need a goat! Then the mutton soup will be complete!
I’m going to take a nap.
Take your time.
Nope. If my son is working so hard to catch goats,
I need to go help him.
Hold on.
The goats are very cunning.
Who exactly are you?
Are you the one who’s been following me lately?
I can tell by the way you’re sneaking that you’re no good person!
Watch this!
What a strong aura!
You’re no—
You’re no match for me!
I hadn’t thought that this cloaked guy would be so powerful.
Your son has already made friends with the goats.
Would you like to work with me to capture them?
Why exactly are you following me?
Uh…
You’ve got a tall stature,
a nice face,
and a kind smile!
I…
I truly admire you,
and I want you to be my captain!
You’re not wrong.
You can be my apprentice, then.
It feels so good to be praised!
Wait,
I have to act colder.
By the way, I was just about to go hunt goats.
Come along.
No, I can’t let the goats see him.
You don’t need to catch goats yourself, sir.
You can leave it to me!
Young people today are quite respectable, huh?
I’m making sure you can’t leave, so the goats won’t find you!
What’s taking that guy so long?
I’m not that impatient, though.
I can’t take it anymore!
I’ll have to do it myself.
Captain,
the goats are way too powerful!
I’m no match for them!
Captain?
Where are you?
There you are, Captain.
How about we just stay home and relax for the day?
Ouch!
What’s with the mess in here?
Aren’t you injured?
It…
It just got better.
You’re a wolf that’s afraid of conflict, I see!
I knew that I’d have to take matters into my own hands.
No,
No, Captain!
Give me one more chance!
I promise to catch goats this time!
Although I said so,
I can’t actually go catch goats, right?
But faking an injury isn’t going to work!
What should I do?
If faking it doesn’t work,
jumping down from here might…
I should think of something else.
There you go.
You did get quite badly injured this time.
They’re terrifying.
I’m no match for them, no matter what!
How cruel!
I’m avenging you right now!
Don’t!
The goats are very cunning!
As captain, I shall bring you justice!
I won’t be long.
Captain…
No,
I can’t let you be endangered because of me!
Give me one more chance.
I’ll be sure to bring a goat back!
Nonsense!
With the state of your body now, there’s nothing you can do!
Even if it’s just a piece of goat wool,
I will still bring it back for you!
What would I want wool for?
How am I supposed to make soup without a goat?
A frog?
I’ll suck it up and take it.
We’ve been searching all day.
I’ll eat an apple and rest.
This is my apple! Go away!
Help!
My apple!
I can rest at last.
Stop!
Darky?
What is he doing out here?
Good thing the goats aren’t nearby.
Stop!
What is Paddi doing here?
It’ll be okay.
It’s game over!
Stop it!
Why is this frog so dodgy?
I told you to stop!
There we go.
What the heck is this?
I messed it up!
Who’s there?
Who knocked out my frog?
I should be asking who threw my apple!
I made it even worse by switching them back!
If you don’t show yourself, I’m coming over to you!
Bring it on, then! I’m not scared of you!
What…
What now?
I’d like to see who dares to mess with me!
What’s taking them so long?
Where’d they go?
You’re…
You’re so heavy!
Where are they?
They ran off!
They haven't even paid back my apple yet!
Paddi,
are you slacking off again?
No,
I… I was searching for anachronists.
Just now, there was a weird person acting aggressively in the bushes,
but they suddenly disappeared.
Could it have been an anachronist?
Let’s go take a look, then.
Frog!
I didn’t think all of the goats would be here.
Good thing I was quick enough.
Goats?
Goats,
here I come!
Calm down, Captain!
Those are goats, you know!
Why are you stopping me from catching them?
Calm down, Captain. The goats of today are very powerful!
We can’t just rush in.
Aren’t they just some goats?
I’m
not
afraid!
I want to see just how powerful those goats really are.
They do seem quite powerful.
That’s the voice.
He was that strange person on the other side of the bush.
Werewolf is with him, so he might be an anachronist.
Anachronist?
It’s… It’s Dad.
A… A wise man knows when to step down! Run!
Stop!
They’re catching up to us! What now?
You can’t possibly outrun airplanes with just two legs.
Come on out!
You’re not going anywhere!
Can’t catch me!
Watch this!
Could you fly the plane a little more stably?
You can’t catch me.
You have nowhere to run!
We’ve been caught! Now what?
How am I supposed to know?
—Take this—　—this!
Wolffy!
Sorry, operating mistake.
Thanks, Wolffy! Goodbye!
What should we do now?
Don’t worry. As long as we find Werewolf,
we’ll be able to find the anachronist.
Dad…
We’ve escaped them at last.
Who are you, really?
Who I am doesn’t matter. What matters is:
do you now believe
that your son has truly befriended goats?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter