Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Werewolf agreed to be Darky’s apprentice.
in order to prevent Darky and the goats
from seeing each other.
However, the situation went haywire,
and Darky and the goats still ran into each other.
In the end, Werewolf had no choice but to take Darky away.
A Strange Wolffy
A suspicious person?
We only failed to catch him because of Wolffy’s operating mistake!
Well, it’s not like he did it on purpose.
Speaking of which, Wolffy has been acting very strangely lately.
Could he be sick?
You guys are friends, so go check on him.
Grandpa,
what are you eating?
Pickles.
Your dad made them himself.
They’re not bad.
It’s salty!
You’re not supposed to eat that much at once.
It feels so good to eat together.
By the way,
what exactly happened yesterday
after Werewolf took Dad?
I must find out.
Dad, yesterday—
By the way, Wolffy,
you haven’t really befriended goats, have you?
Of course I haven’t.
I was planning on going goat-hunting after breakfast.
Wolffy, are you home?
Who’s that?
Oh no, it’s Weslie and the others!
Wolffy!
The kids in the area are always doorbell-ditching.
I’ll get rid of them.
What is it?
You’ve been acting strangely lately.
Are you sick?
No,
I’m perfectly healthy.
If there’s nothing else—
Wolffy!
Who’s calling you?
That’s Wolnie calling me!
Wolffy!
That voice—
Wolnie’s voice has been a little gravelly lately.
Wolffy,
where is my razor?
Oh, for goodness sake.
She’s always using my shaver to cut her fur.
Brother Weslie, you’re here!
Come in and play!
Where’s my shaver?
Dad,
the shaver should be somewhere in this room.
Keep searching.
I can’t let Dad and the goats run into each other.
I’ll have to find someone to help.
I’ll go get my toys!
Okay, Wilie.
Come with me, Wilie.
…That’s it.
No worries, I’m great at acting.
It’s just that Wilie…
Wilie, how about we play a game?
What game.
Hide-and-seek!
We play hide-and-seek all the time!
I always win.
It’s different this time around.
You only win if you don’t let Grandpa get caught by the goats.
That sounds like fun!
Yes!
Mmm!
This isn’t your breakfast. Don’t eat it.
Where are they?
Odd.
You think so, too?
Tell me, how many people are in Wolffy’s family?
Wolffy,
Wolnie,
and Wilie.
Just those three.
Why are there four plates on the table, though?
Why is there an extra plate?
That’s Wolffy’s cousin’s.
He said he was coming to visit,
but at the last minute, didn’t.
I see.
Wilie!
Come help me find my toy car, Grandpa!
Sure.
Wolffy, why’d you jumpscare me?
You’ve been acting very strangely lately, Wolffy.
Has something happened?
I can’t keep them here.
Just come with me, and you’ll know.
Where’s Wolffy?
Goats’ wool?
What is goats’ wool doing here?
It’s the wool on my goats’ wool coat falling out.
That must be some low-quality wool.
Once I catch some goats,
I’ll use their wool to make you a new one.
Grandpa,
let’s go outside and play!
Sure.
What does this plant have to do with your recent strange behavior?
It has everything to do with it!
I bought dandelion seeds,
but chamomile is what sprouted!
Tell me, how can I not be upset?
I understand your feelings.
It’s just like how I wanted to buy a mango cake,
but I was given a durian cake instead!
Exactly!
I understand you, Wolffy.
Paddi,
thank you!
Look, I just bought these new curtains.
How do they look?
They’re… They’re nice.
The curtains over here are new, too.
Didn’t Wilie go to get his toy car?
What’s taking him so long?
Wilie, I’m very tired.
Let’s go inside and rest for a bit.
We can play later, okay?
Wilie must have gone outside to play.
I’m so tired.
That voice…?
What happened?
The light must be broken. I’ll go fix it.
I’ll help you.
No…
No, thanks.
There we go. It just tripped, is all.
Wolffy, why has the light turned off again?
Turn it on!
Sure,
I’ll see if it’s fixed.
It looks like the light is broken for good.
Who was that person just now?
No one.
You must have been mistaken.
Who are you guys?
Who’s there?
Our cover is about to get blown!
I have no other choice.
Wolffy, what are you doing?
With the curtains open,
you guys can see more clearly.
See? There’s no one else.
Were we really just mistaken?
It must be that you guys are too tired.
Go home and rest.
You can visit another day, okay?
What in the world is wrong with Wolffy?
Never mind. Let’s go home.
Wolffy, what are you—
It’s you again.
Do you still remember what I said last time?
I do.
Last time, you said that I’ve got a tall stature,
a nice face, and a kind smile.
You admired me, and you wanted me to be your captain.
I meant what I said on the airplane.
Who I am doesn’t matter. What matters is:
do you now believe
that your son has truly befriended goats?
You can see it with your own eyes.
Those you saw just now were, in fact, that group of goats.
I guess so.
The goats have already come to your house to visit.
Do you still not believe that Wolffy is friends with them?
I’m still worried about Wolffy.
I’ll go back to check on him.
At last, we can eat breakfast in peace.
Wolffy,
I’m still a little worried about you—
I’m fine, really. I’m fine.
No need to worry.
You guys can go home.
Who’s he?
He…
He’s—
Hello.
Uh…
Who are you?
—Our cousin!　—Our uncle!
Which one is it?
One of our relatives.
Our uncle’s son. He’s our cousin.
Didn’t he say he wasn’t coming?
He said he wouldn’t, but he ended up coming, anyway.
Don’t let them find out your true identity.
That’s right,
I’m Wolffy’s cousin.
I hope we can be friends.
Dad wants to befriend goats?
What happened?
Goodbye!
Come back to visit!
Look, guys!
What’s wrong?
But I swear—
Alright,
let’s go.
You believe it now, don’t you?
Your son has befriended goats.
I’m very curious as to how you got in here.
That…
That doesn’t matter.
What matters is that, for the sake of your son’s journey,
we need to collaborate to catch the goats!
Alright.
Let’s do it.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter