Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats suddenly came to Wolf Fortress,
catching Wolffy off-guard.
He worked hard to hide it,
and Werewolf took this chance
to ask Darky to collaborate with him
in catching the goats.
Exposed
It was this sort of murderous glare.
There must be something more to him!
Actually,
I already knew who the thief was.
Who is it?
You have to believe me!
At the time,
Wolffy’s cousin was looking at us
with that sort of murderous glare!
My feelings wouldn’t betray me!
There must be something fishy with that cousin.
You’re overthinking it.
Am I?
The thief is
Piggy!
How…
How could I possibly be the thief?
He really is the thief!
How did you know?
Because the look in your eyes betrayed you.
Detective,
did you really solve the case with just the look in his eyes?
No, I had a gut feeling, too.
My gut told me so.
Gut feeling?
Why didn’t Dad capture the goats
when he saw them?
Never mind,
I’m just glad that Dad’s okay.
Come down.
What an athletic move!
I won’t be injured by such a small thing.
Ouch!
So, are we sneaking into Goats’ Village,
or launching a direct attack?
We’re not doing either of those.
I have this.
What the…?
A puzzle?
Can this catch the goats?
Might there be a profound secret to goat-hunting hidden in here?
Exactly!
Once you’ve found the secret,
catching goats will be a piece of cake.
It fits.
That’s one small step for a puzzle,
but one giant leap for goat-hunting!
You’re such a goat-hunting genius!
So,
I’ll go prepare some hunting weapons.
I’ll leave the puzzle to you.
Leave it to me.
I’ll be sure to find the secret!
There’s no “secret” in there.
I’m just making you stay here and not leave, is all.
Where should we search for anachronists today?
Hang on, Wolffy isn’t here yet.
I’m late again!
Speaking of Wolffy,
Talking behind my back again?
have you guys noticed
Have they also noticed something fishy about Wolffy’s cousin?
that Wolffy has
What?
full recordings of Flat-Beak Allen’s concerts in his house?
I noticed something else.
Tibbie!
His house
is very dusty!
I can tell that it hasn’t been cleaned in a long time.
Oh, what the heck.
It’s all a bunch of trivial things.
You’ve all missed the main point.
There’s more?
The main point is, their dark—
Dark?
He’s not talking about Darky, is he?
Their dark chocolate is delicious.
Scaring me to death.
Wolffy,
are you okay?
Yes,
I just ran a bit too fast trying to get here on time.
Let’s get going!
Nope. I need to get this clear.
Not this one.
Not… Not this one, either.
Not this one…
Not this one, either!
This is so hard.
Grandpa!
Wilie, remember what your dad said.
We’re playing a game.
You must call me “Uncle.”
Uncle,
when will you play with me?
I’ve already looked through this photo album many times.
♪ Don’t think of me as just a goat ♪
Watch some TV for now.
♪ Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant ♪
I’ll play with you once I’m done with the puzzle.
♪ Because of me, the sky is bluer ♪
I’ll continue.
Coming!
Brother Sparky!
Hello, Wilie.
I think I left something at your house yesterday.
Can I come inside and look for it?
Sure!
It’s game over if I’m caught!
I can look by myself, Wilie.
I’ll keep watching TV, then.
There he is.
It’s cartoon hour!
Cousin of Wolffy,
when did you arrive in Green Green Grassland?
Yesterday.
What did you come to Wolf Fortress for?
A vacation.
How many hairs does Wolffy have all over?
How many moles are on his body?
How many whiskers are on his beard?
What…
What kind of questions are these, huh?
Darn it,
I’ve gone overboard.
A puzzle?
You—
Sorry,
I just can’t help—
You’re good at jigsaw puzzles?
This puzzle seems very important to him.
I might as well get on his good side
and buy some more time to investigate.
I’m an expert at jigsaw puzzles!
I’ll help you out.
Great!
I can use him to help me solve the puzzle.
I’ll leave it to you, then.
I heard something!
There it is!
Dad, why did he rip away our shade?
Sorry.
Has anyone found anachronists?
No.
Me neither.
By the way, where’s Sparky?
Did Sparky not come with us?
I think I saw him go in the direction of Wolffy’s place.
There must be something fishy with that cousin!
Could he have gone to find Wolffy’s cousin?
Huh?
What’s wrong with Wolffy?
Let’s go and see.
This is the last piece.
All done!
A landscape?
It can’t be this simple.
There must be a secret that I haven’t noticed.
It’s that look!
Oh, he gets that look in his eyes when he’s shortsighted.
I was wrong about him.
Wilie,
I’m going home now.
Goodbye, Brother Sparky!
Are you okay, Brother Sparky?
It’s my fault for not putting the photo album away.
I’m alright.
These are…
Daddy and my grandpa!
Grandpa?
I lost. I was supposed to call him “Uncle.”
Which… Which means that
this is Wolffy’s father?
I just knew that something was fishy!
You’re an anachronist!
Yes,
and?
Go back to where you belong!
Otherwise, all of spacetime will be reset!
What do you mean, “spacetime reset?”
You think I’m going to believe that?
I’ve been wanting to capture you for quite some time now!
Run, Wilie!
Well done, Wolffy!
Sorry, Dad.
Sparky, there’s a cockroach on you!
Where?
Where is it?
There isn’t one.
Wolffy, what are you doing?
Out of my way!
Are you okay, son?
“Son?”
He’s Wolffy’s father: Darky!
Weslie?
Sorry, Darky.
We need to take you away.
Don’t take my dad away!
I don’t want Grandpa to leave!
Son…
A child has said it,
so just let it happen.
Werewolf?
Dad!
Goodbye!
That hurts! Let go of me!
Ouch!
I’ll be back for revenge!
He got away again!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter