Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Sparky was suspicious of Darky,
so he decided to get to the bottom of things.
As a result, he discovered Darky’s true identity.
When the goats and Wolffy were fighting over Darky,
he was captured by Werewolf.
The Suspect
Werewolf always comes to ruin things!
We were so close to getting Darky!
Wolffy,
why didn’t you tell us that you knew
that Darky was an anachronist?
I just wanted to spend more time with my father, is all.
But if you do that, spacetime will reset!
That’s why I decided to send him home a little later.
I understand how you feel.
Sparky, calm down.
There’s no time to waste.
We have to find Werewolf as soon as possible.
Weslie’s right.
Then let’s get going!
It looks like Dad is going to get found soon.
I’ll just follow them for now.
It was my fault for being impulsive.
Otherwise, we could have taken Darky away.
A fish scale?
Why is it a fish scale now?
I swear I grabbed Werewolf’s fur!
This is really strange.
Also, this shape and color
look a bit familiar.
Doudou!
That’s it!
It’s the same as Doudou’s!
Does this mean that Doudou is Werewolf?
Paddi!
Sparky?
I remember the time you said
you went to find Werewolf,
but found Doudou instead.
Uh…
Doudou?
Yeah, I guess so.
No wonder.
What do you mean, Sparky?
No wonder Werewolf can enter or exit the Hub at any time.
Just you wait, Doudou!
I’m going to clear up whether or not you’re Werewolf!
Paddi, run a scan with Hurricane.
Darn it,
the entire map is filled with Darky’s signals.
Huh?
What now?
We’ll just have to search them one by one.
Alright.
Split up and search!
Darky’s fur is everywhere.
Werewolf is so cunning.
No wonder Hurricane found so many points.
Let’s go in deeper and search.
It looks like Dad won’t be found for now.
It’s one of Dad’s arrows!
Is Dad around here somewhere?
Wolffy!
Weslie’s coming!
Have you found any clues?
No.
It looks like this place is covered in fur, too.
Yeah.
We found fur, too.
Let’s keep looking.
As long as we try our best and don’t give up,
we’ll find them.
Well said, Wolffy!
You always know when we need rapport!
If it works, it works.
It’s their footprints!
Look, guys!
There are footprints here!
Let’s go take a look.
They’re about to come!
What are you doing, Wolffy?
Nothing. My back was just itchy,
but it’s better now.
Well, I guess these were Wolffy’s footprints.
Let’s search somewhere else.
They’ve left at last.
It’s Dad’s hat!
They’ll certainly catch me if I just go up and grab it.
That was close.
This piece of clothing…
Darn it!
I’ve found a clue!
Look, guys! It’s over here!
Over here!
Where’d it go?
I swear I saw it just now!
You… You must have been mistaken.
Come on, let’s keep searching.
Fine.
Wasps!
Run!
Wrong way!
I can’t rush into it.
I need to clarify whether or not Doudou is Werewolf.
Where is he?
Sparky!
Trying to attack me?
I don’t think so!
Doudou,
here are your tools.
Thank you, Sparky.
No need to thank me.
I can’t scare him off.
What are you doing here, Sparky?
Am I not allowed here?
Of…
Of course you are.
He’s so nervous. He must be hiding something.
Let me test him.
Doudou, you’re so busy right now.
Let me help you with the controls.
No,
the system is authorized with my face.
You can’t use it.
Really?
What about other people?
There… There aren’t any other people.
Eyes flickering here and there,
nervous movements,
and constantly sweating when talking to me.
He must be hiding something!
You guys are always telling me that I’m impulsive,
but today, I’ve uncovered a big secret, haven’t I?
I just need to take him with me.
Hold on.
If I were Weslie,
I would collect more evidence first.
Doudou!
Doudou,
I haven’t seen you all morning. You’re back at last.
Yeah, I was busy this morning—
Busy this morning?
This morning was when Werewolf captured Darky!
Thank you for all you’ve done.
I’m going home now.
Alright.
Doudou,
is this one of your scales?
The goats will think that I’ve hidden in that cave again, right?
I’m hiding here this time, so they surely won’t find me!
Don’t you think so,
Captain?
Exactly.
With how wide that forest is
and the amount of fur and clothes I dropped,
they’ll have a lot of searching to do.
So tell me, why were you dumb enough
to always hide in that cave?
Well, uh…
Never mind that.
Put on some clothes and keep warm, Captain.
Sure.
What now, Weslie?
Let’s hide!
I think they’re gone.
Is everyone okay?
Yes.
Where’s Wolffy?
I’m right here.
Weslie?
Hang on! I’m pulling you up!
Dad?
Huh?
It’s Werewolf?
We’ve been caught!
Pull us up!
This is bad!
They’re about to escape!
Out of my way!
They’re coming up!
Watch this!
Help me!
Tell me!
This scale is yours, right?
It looks like it.
So you are Werewolf!
What “Werewolf?”
Enough pretending!
Where’s Darky?
I said I’m not him!
Your phone is ringing.
Wait a minute.
Come help!
Where are you?
We’ve found Werewolf!
I thought Doudou was Werewolf.
What are you talking about?
Werewolf is over here!
Either way, just hurry and come help—
I guess I got it wrong.
I said I wasn’t him.
Then why did you say that this scale was yours?
I said it looked like mine, is all.
Bad news, Doudou!
The Tunnel repaired this morning has broken again!
I’ll be right there!
Apparently, Doudou went to repair the Tunnel this morning.
Doudou,
I’m sorry, I was wrong about you.
It’s alright.
What’s going on?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter