Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Sparky believed Doudou to be Werewolf,
but it turned out to be a misunderstanding.
Elsewhere, Weslie and the others finally found Darky,
but got stuck.
Crisis at the Hub
Why is the quake so bad this time?
Get outside, guys!
Oh no, someone’s in there!
It’s too dangerous.
But I have to rescue them!
Oh, it was just a sign.
I’ll help you out of here.
What incredible strength!
I’ll protect you!
Let’s go.
You’re a hero!
I… I can’t hold on for much longer!
Dad, are you okay?
Get off of me!
I need to get out of here.
Perfect.
Why is Darky so heavy?
Be careful with my dad!
Watch this!
You’re not going anywhere!
Let go of him!
Let go of Weslie!
Don’t hurt my dad!
Stop it!
Let go of him!
Let go of me first!
I’ll let go
if you let go!
You—
This pit isn’t that deep.
We can stack up.
How about we work together—
I disagree.
We might as well just stay stuck in here.
Once the world resets,
you’ll all be done for!
If you stay stuck in here
when the world resets,
you won’t be escaping it, either.
What are you looking at? Get started already!
I’m sorry, I almost got you in trouble.
It’s okay.
Remember to stay calm and not be impulsive
when in these situations.
By the way, mister,
what’s your name?
You can just call me “mister.”
You’re incredible, mister.
I want to be just like you someday!
You will.
My friends always say that I’m too impulsive, though.
But would they blame you for it?
No, they’re very kind to me.
Yes, they’ve always been like that.
Mister, do you know them?
They’re my friends, too.
I have to go now.
Goodbye.
You’re such a hero, mister!
Cockroach!
Here’s the thing. If we’re going to stack up,
I’ll be on top,
and Darky will be right below me.
I’ll pretend to stack up, then quickly shapeshift into a bird,
take Darky, and go!
No way.
You’re not going anywhere!
We’re not falling for it!
Let go of him!
Dad—
Let go of Weslie!
Don’t hurt my dad!
Let go of me, or else she’ll be in trouble!
Not again.
Fine, then. I agree to be at the bottom,
but
we must respect our elders.
Darky, as the oldest, will be on top.
I’m not old!
I… I can’t hold on any longer!
I’m
not
old.
Goodbye, little goats!
Oh no, he’s about to escape!
Stop him!
Can’t catch me!
You two are despicable!
You betrayed us!
Go, Dad.
Let’s go.
No, my son is still in there.
I’m getting him out.
They’ll surely find a way.
If we don’t go now, it’ll be too late.
You can go home now!
Great!
Thank you, Doudou.
Will we meet again, mister?
We will meet again
some day in the future.
Really?
Until next time, then!
What’s happening?
What’s going on?
Doudou! Doudou!
What happened?
The quake caused a system error,
and the Spacetime Shuttle is out of control!
What?
Go slow the Shuttle down and buy me some time!
Okay!
Mister, I’m here to save you!
How fast!
Slow it down!
Oh no, the Hub is up ahead!
What is that?
It looks like it’s flying our way.
Run!
What should I do? What should I do?
Remember to stay calm and not be impulsive
in these situations.
Mister?
I can’t be impulsive. I need to calm down!
Maybe I can use the drill to smash the Spacetime Shuttle’s glass
and rescue him.
No,
that’s not going to slow the Shuttle down,
and besides, that’ll hurt him!
What else is there on Morning Sun that I can use?
Aha! Dumbbells and ropes!
It looks like he’s thought of something.
It can’t break through!
I know what you’re trying to do.
This is our last chance.
Darn it!
Let’s slow this thing down together!
Okay!
Hang on, mister!
Help us!
The rope is breaking!
Look out! Get out of the way!
Finally, it’s fixed.
Are you okay, mister?
Of course I am.
Thank you!
You guys are incredible!
Thanks!
It’s goodbye for good this time.
But I still don’t know who you are, mister.
How come your skin is dark like mine is?
Goodbye.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter