Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
a large quake occurred at the Hub.
Sparky and his future self
successfully prevented a crisis at the Hub together.
On the other hand,
the goats and the three wolves got stuck together.
They worked together for an escape, but there was a betrayal.
A Wavering Wolffy
Ouch!
Are you okay, Paddi?
I can’t believe Werewolf got away again!
Wolffy,
I know that you don’t want your dad to leave,
but if the world resets,
what about the rest of us?
Exactly.
You still have Wolnie and Wilie.
Wolnie?
Wilie?
Wolffy?
Let’s find my dad first, okay?
How are we supposed to get out, though?
Oh, yeah!
Do you guys still remember that thing that Mr. Slowy and Grandpa Bladey did?
Do you mean
the Mountain Crush Special?
Bring it on!
Here I come, Weslie!
Again!
Us, too!
Mountain Crush Special!
Crush Special!
Special!
Come on, Wolffy!
Again!
I… I can’t take it anymore.
Are you okay?
There you are.
Sparky?
I’ll get you guys out right now!
Didn’t you guys say that you found Darky?
Well, he escaped again.
We need to find them as soon as possible.
Wolffy,
can you use your Sirius to locate them?
I’ve already been looking for them.
That’s odd. Why can’t I find them?
Has Werewolf noticed?
Just remove this,
and Sirius won’t be able to locate us!
Since we can’t locate them,
we’ll have to search the signal points that Hurricane found
one by one.
Where are you taking me?
To the Safe Room.
I wasn’t planning on taking you this early.
Safe Room?
What’s that?
There you are!
It’s Wolffy! Stop!
You got out at last, huh?
Son?
Let’s go, Dad.
Where are you taking him?
Are…
Are you handing your father over to the goats?
I found my dad.
Great, we’ll be right there.
You’re worried about the world resetting
if your father doesn’t go home, right?
World reset?
Go back to where you belong!
Otherwise, all of spacetime will be reset!
Even if the world resets,
I know how to ensure your safety!
I’m serious!
If I know how to make the world reset,
I know how to ensure your safety, too!
Are you willing to just let your dad go home and die?
I’ll…
I’ll die once I go home?
No, Dad!
I—
Found them!
They’re over there!
I’ll cover for you. Find a chance to escape.
Let’s attack together, Wolffy!
Don’t even think about it!
Watch this!
Trying to catch me?
I don’t think so!
Have a taste of my power!
Careful, guys!
How come I’m always the one being followed?
Paddi!
Dad, it’s too dangerous here.
Get on the airplane with me!
Where’s Dad?
Dad?
The shield can’t take much more!
We’re done for!
Goodbye,
you annoying little goats!
Thunderbolt,
speed up!
Weslie!
Don’t forget about me!
Haven’t you had enough?
Dad, where are you?
Dad?
Dad!
What are you doing over here?
Am I going to die once I go home?
Dad…
What are you doing here?
You…
I was just looking at the scenery, is all.
Uh…
If I don’t go home, what will happen?
I don’t know.
Am I really going to die once I go home?
I…
I don’t know.
Then when did I die?
How did I die?
It wasn’t an embarrassing death, was it?
Dad!
I’m sorry, I got too ahead of myself.
I don’t know what will happen if you go home
or what will happen if you stay in this world,
much less what I’d do if I lost you again.
I don’t know!
However,
I know
that right now, I don’t want you to leave!
Son…
I don’t care how slim the chances are.
I need to trust that Werewolf
can find a way to save you.
Find somewhere to hide for now.
But where should I hide?
Aha!
We can’t keep this up.
Werewolf has so much firepower, though.
We have no way of attacking!
I know what to do!
Go into the forest!
You guys have nowhere to run!
You guys can’t escape from my grasp!
I’m right here!
Sparky!
Are you okay, Sparky?
Over here!
Wait,
I’m getting a bad feeling about this.
Nowhere to run now, huh?
What… What happened?
Look around.
How can it be?
I’ll teach you a lesson!
Take your time, guys. I’ll be on my way!
Stop!
Wait,
finding Darky is more important.
Paddi, locate Darky.
Roger that. Locating Darky.
It’s just like last time. There are a lot of signals.
Where did Wolffy go?
Should we try looking for Wolffy?
We might just find Darky, too.
Let me see.
Goats’ Village?
Put these unused things in the warehouse.
Smart, son.
Hiding in Goats’ Village means no need to worry about food.
We’re not here to catch goats, Dad.
Thanks for your hard work, guys.
By the way,
to thank all of you,
my newly invented Super Massaging Robot 2.0
shall give you guys a massage.
Come try it out! It’s wonderful!
Hide in the warehouse.
The most dangerous place is the safest place.
They’ll never figure out that you’re in Goats’ Village.
Someone opened the door at last!
I thought I was going to be locked in here forever!
Uh…
Why did you shut the door again?
It’s fine.
Let me out of here!
There are better hiding spots.
Let me out!
Let’s go.
Here!
Why is every place already occupied?
Why?
Wolffy, where are you?
Wolffy!
Where in the world are you, Wolffy?
Oh no, it’s the goats!
They caught up quite quickly, huh?
Aha!
Hide in that box, Dad.
I’ll go check on the goats.
Get inside!
Wolffy!
I can’t let them find out.
Dad, are you ready?
Dad?
Where’s the box?
What box?
W…
Weslie!
Wolffy, have you found Darky?
No… No.
What are you doing in Goats’ Village, then?
I…
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter