Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy decided to trust Werewolf
after some contemplation.
He secretly helped Darky hide.
Will the goats figure out
what Wolffy is planning?
Going Against the Grain
I feel much better after using the bathroom!
Did you wash your hands?
Where in the world has Darky gone?
I have no idea.
Go to Hurricane and check how many signal points are left.
Keep searching.
We’ve already looked over this area.
We still need to do this area, this area…
Darn it, even Goats’ Village has signal points.
I can’t let them search Goats’ Village.
Weslie, we need to hurry up!
We can’t let Werewolf be the first to find my dad!
You guys go here,
here,
and here.
I’ll go here.
Come on, let’s get going.
Get onto our own airplanes.
Why aren’t you leaving, Paddi?
This is Hurricane!
Let’s go!
Let’s move these tomorrow.
Why seal all of the boxes?
What if someone’s inside?
Where are you, Dad?
Dad, I’m coming!
Dad…
Wolffy, what are you doing?
Uh… I…
Don’t worry, it’s me.
What the heck?
Did you think that was funny?
Alright, quiet down.
They’ll surely be very upset with you
if they find out you’ve hidden Darky again.
That’s none of your business, okay?
Helping you is helping myself.
So?
Would you like some help?
Quit it with the hypocrisy, alright?
Haven’t you framed me enough times today already?
I don’t need your help!
Goats’ Village is huge. You can’t search it alone.
The goats will return soon.
I need to confirm one thing first.
Yes?
Do you really have a way
to ensure our safety if the world were to reset?
Of course. I swear on it.
So?
Want to work together?
Hide!
Hiding together
means you agree, don’t you?
If you dare lie to me—
Rest assured. Things shall go smoothly!
So tell me,
why did you have Darky hide in a box?
What if a child imitates that?
The situation was dire. It had to happen.
Here we are.
This is the warehouse.
Just now, I noticed some goats placing boxes inside.
So many boxes!
Not here?
Not here!
This is going to take forever!
Calm down.
Your random rummaging
is going to take forever.
Do you have an idea?
Of course. We’ve got a secret signal, you know.
Wait,
since when have you two had a secret signal?
That doesn’t matter!
Continue, continue.
Darky,
where are you?
How does that count as a “secret” signal?
Darky?
Darky!
It’s that one!
Dad!
See, I didn’t lie to you.
Dad, I’ll get you out of there!
Did you forget to turn off the warehouse lights?
Probably.
Let’s go. Goats are coming.
It’s so heavy!
Tell your dad to lose some weight, would you?
We’ve searched every point we could.
Where in the world is Darky?
Werewolf might have already found Darky.
If that’s the case,
we can reason with Werewolf’s tendencies
to work out where Darky could be hidden.
How do we do that?
The most dangerous place is the safest place.
They’re likely to be hiding in—
Goats’ Village!
Let’s do a search.
Wolffy must have glossed over this possibility.
Wolffy?
Don’t…
Don’t mind us.
Wolffy, what are you doing with him?
Uh… I…
Look at that box, guys!
Darky might be hidden inside!
We have no choice. Run!
Stop!
Split up!
Catch!
Dad!
Where’s Dad?
It’s not Darky?
Let go of Wolffy!
In the end, I still had to step in.
Dad!
What are you doing?
You weren’t in the box after all, Dad.
Oh, you worried me to death.
How was I supposed to fit inside such a small box?
Get on!
We can’t let them get away!
Come on out, Magic Airplanes!
Wolffy!
Now’s your chance. Run!
Stop, Werewolf!
Out of the way, Weslie!
I’m sorry, Sparky.
Are you okay, Sparky?
Yes.
Wolffy, why are you doing this?
Do you guys know how it feels
having to watch your own father leave?
I—
You and I are not the same!
You still have the chance to see your dad again,
but the moment my dad goes home,
I’ll never see him again!
Wolffy…
So…
Wolffy!
I’m sorry.
Is everyone okay?
I never thought that Wolffy would side with Werewolf.
I’m sorry.
I’m just doing this for my family, you know.
Well done, Wolffy.
Yeah,
Wolffy is friends with us goats.
Let’s keep working together, okay?
Guys…
But…
I’m very glad to have known you,
Wolffy.
Me too!
Well done, Wolffy!
Keep working with me,
and I’ll ensure everyone’s safety.
What’s next after this?
Next?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter