Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy agreed to work with Werewolf
to prevent the goats from finding Darky.
This caused a rift to occur within the goat-wolf alliance.
What will happen next?
Collaboration
Enough moping, Wolffy.
Why did you have to do this?
Why do you have to ruin everything?
I’m fixing my wrongdoings.
Fixing?
You’ll have nothing to fix once the world resets!
Are you willing to just watch your dad disappear, then?
Dad…
I, Darky,
would sacrifice my life for the Wolf Clan!
I must have died without regret!
You didn’t sacrifice yourself for the Wolf Clan.
What?
Then how did I—
At the time…
Dad?
Your fever’s gone down at last.
Who’s there?
Darky,
you abandoned the battlefield and caused harm to your people.
From this point forward, you must not step foot in the Wolf Clan again.
Dad…
After that, we left the Wolf Clan,
living a life with just us two.
Exiled from the Wolf Clan?
What happened after?
After…
You strictly trained me every day.
Day after day,
until one day…
Time to eat, son.
Apples again?
Dad, I want to eat fish tomorrow.
What?
Nothing.
Where’s Dad?
Has he gone out?
Yay,
I can finally rest!
There was a wolf fishing at the river
even in such bad rain.
That’s so dangerous.
Fishing?
Dad, I want to eat fish tomorrow.
Is it Dad?
It’s Dad’s hat!
Dad! Dad!
Dad, where are you?
Dad…
Dad!
After that, I searched for a long time,
but I just never found you.
I abandoned you just like that?
I won’t let you die, Dad!
Don’t worry, you’ll be okay.
We’re headed to the Safe Room right now.
Safe Room?
The so-called “Safe Room”
is a place where we can safely pass
the world’s reset.
Why should I trust you?
I want to live, too.
Really?
Yes.
Then Wilie and Wolnie are coming along, too.
No problem.
And also Wolnie’s parents,
Uncle Wonky, Uncle Wolfram, Cousin Darker,
my aunt, my other aunt, and the others.
Sure, sure.
And also Weslie and the other goats in their village—
Sure, sure!
Just bring the goats to Wolf Fortress first,
and I’ll meet up with you once I’ve brought your dad to the Safe Room.
That’s settled, then.
There’s no way I’m bringing all of you!
Hide right here.
The goats won’t find you.
But why hide in here?
Because the most dangerous place is the safest place.
They’ll surely never guess that you’re hiding in Goats’ Village again.
Stay hidden. I’ll catch up with Wolffy.
Okay.
Here’s a walkie-talkie. Call me if you need anything.
Wolffy, Wilie and I are going shopping.
Alright, I’ll pack our luggage.
The goats?
All packed up at last.
Time to let Weslie and the others know.
This is perfect!
I was just about to find you—
Wolffy,
I can’t believe you’re going against us with Werewolf!
I’m not. I’m just trying to protect my dad!
I never tried to hurt you guys.
Enough!
Calm down, Sparky.
Calm down. Let me explain.
Just now, I was going to let you guys know
about Werewolf’s Safe Room.
As long as we get in there, we’ll be fine.
Safe Room?
Werewolf?
No, we can’t trust that.
I’m serious!
There really is a Safe Room.
So tell us, where’s the Room?
It’s—
How big is it?
Can it fit all the people in the world?
Is there food there?
I…
I don’t know,
but Werewolf says—
You’d better just tell us where your dad is.
Yes, Wolffy.
Wolffy!
My dad?
Wolffy, let us have your dad.
What are you waiting for? Hand him over!
Enough!
Haven’t any of you guys thought about how I feel?
He’s my dad, you know!
How could you guys be so cruel?
We could trust Werewolf,
and we might just be okay!
But instead, you guys are pressuring me.
I have no such friends like you!
Wolffy!
I said some awful stuff just now.
I really shouldn’t have lashed out like that.
But I don’t want to lose my dad, either.
We made Wolffy mad.
Yeah,
we shouldn’t have pressured him like that.
He just doesn’t want to lose his dad, anyway.
But the world will reset.
I was wrong, too.
I need to apologize to the goats.
Let me see
whether the kids tidied up well or not.
Slowy?
Pretty clean.
With all those boxes,
I wonder if it’s clean under the shelves, too.
Oh no,
I’m about to get caught!
Not bad. Very clean.
Dangerous places are, in fact, dangerous.
I need to get out of here.
Darky?
You were in here this whole time?
I’m sorry,
I lost my temper just now.
No,
it was we who didn’t consider your feelings.
It’s alright.
I really should send my dad home.
Come with me, guys.
Are you sure?
Where’s Wolffy?
Where did he go?
I’m over here!
Wolffy,
why are you locking us up?
I’m collaborating with Werewolf.
What?
Wolffy, you’re joking, right?
Let us go!
Stop!
Stop right there, Darky!
Just give up. You can’t catch me.
Goodbye for good!
I’m going to get you!
Aha!
What’s going on?
Why did the power go out?
It’s so dark. Where’s the exit?
Stop, Darky!
Physically, I may not match you,
but I do have smarts.
Help!
Did I pass out?
What happened?
You locked us up for Werewolf!
Do you really need to ask?
Despicable!
What?
No, I didn’t!
Well done,
my friend!
Wolffy!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter