Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Werewolf impersonated Wolffy to trap the goats,
disturbing their friendship.
Elsewhere,
Slowy unintentionally captured Darky, who was hiding in the warehouse.
What will happen next?
Breaking Up
Let us go!
What…
What in the world is going on?
I need to apologize to the goats.
Wolffy,
it’s a pleasure to work with you.
Your dad will be very proud of you.
You’re so despicable, Wolffy!
I’m innocent!
Oh, this is your remote control.
Don’t lose it, okay?
I knew it!
I really didn’t!
I was…
I think I was—
Wolffy,
we’re meeting up with Darky now.
When we come back, we’ll stew these goats!
It’s unlocked.
I knew it!
He even had the remote control on him!
That traitor! I’m going to teach him a lesson!
Follow them, guys.
Why did you frame me?
Believe me, I’m doing this for your own good.
Hand over Darky right now!
See if you can catch up to me first!
Get him!
The more you chase me, the more you won’t be able to find Darky!
Kids, I’ve found Darky.
I’m taking him to the Hub with Daybreak.
That’s odd.
Wasn’t Darky in Werewolf’s hands?
Forget about it.
Let’s go to the Hub and wait for Mr. Slowy.
That’s odd.
Why aren’t the goats following us anymore?
My dad hasn’t been caught, has he?
Turn around!
I never thought that Daybreak could still fly
with a new set of wings after being stored for so long.
Yeah,
not only is it flying,
it’s upside down.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I’m just thinking about how, once I go home, I’ll—
—die?
I don’t want my son to be a loser like I am,
never being able to catch goats.
Not catching goats doesn’t mean being a loser.
You don’t get it!
I can’t just go home.
I need to stay and help my son catch goats,
then watch him become the hero of the Wolf Clan.
Where’s the key?
What are you doing?
I…
I just wanted to give you a goodbye hug.
Really?
Weren’t you looking for this?
Give me the key!
I may be old,
but there’s no way you’re getting the key from me just like that.
Just like that.
Time to meet up with my son.
Don’t mess around!
I can fly this stupid plane, too!
In front! Look in front!
Ascend! Ascend now!
See? I can fly it, too.
Stay put.
Werewolf?
You won't be getting there before I do.
Duck!
Paddi, are you okay?
Yes.
More snowballs! Duck!
Such nuisances!
Don’t hurt them!
Go away!
Sirius!
Wolffy?
Forget about him. Just go!
If Darky gets sent away by them,
it’s all going to be your fault!
Doudou!
You’re here!
I have some good news.
Have you seen Mr. Slowy and Darky?
No, what happened?
Maybe they’re still on the way.
Doudou, what good news were you talking about just now?
Come look.
There’s only one anachronist left.
In other words, Darky is the only one left?
Great!
Mr. Slowy and Darky should be here soon.
So it’s Slowy who has him!
Is it Mr. Slowy?
They must have overheard our conversation.
We need to go back up Mr. Slowy!
I’m coming, too.
What a beautiful sun.
Cheer up, now.
Just keep moving forward.
Things might just turn around.
Turn around?
Easy for you to say
when you’re not the one who’s leaving.
Things will never turn around!
You’re right.
You get what I mean?
Yes, things are turning around.
Wolffy has come to save me!
Hand over Darky right now!
Weslie, you’re here at last!
Full power!
That’s enough, Slowy.
Let my dad go!
Yes, let me go.
What did you say?
You’re cutting out.
Let my dad go!
He’s trying to buy time.
Just go in and get him!
Wolffy!
Weslie!
I’m sorry.
I can’t let you guys send my dad away.
We can’t just let the world reset, either!
Stop tugging!
Mr. Slowy and Darky are still inside!
I’ll take it from here, then.
Mr. Slowy!
Leave it to me!
Thank goodness I made it in time.
Mr. Slowy!
I don’t want to hurt you guys, Weslie.
But if your dad isn’t sent home,
everyone is going to get hurt!
My dad is staying with me!
Dad!
Wolffy!
I’m sorry.
I can’t believe we considered you a friend, Wolffy!
What… What the…?
Doudou!
Werewolf rescued Doudou?
I won’t forgive you guys!
Get behind me, guys!
Well done, son!
Let’s capture all the goats!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter