Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Wolffy had no way to prove his innocence
after the misunderstanding with the goats.
He also accidentally harmed the goats while fighting for Darky,
causing the misunderstanding to deepen.
The goats were very upset with Wolffy,
and Wolffy was left feeling bitter.
Werewolf’s Secret
Ladies and gentlemen! Boys and girls!
What?
Is there any good news?
Is there a performance?
Are there any freebies?
Nope,
none of that is the case.
My son, Wolffy,
has become a great goat hunter of the Wolf Clan!
He caught six goats!
There’s no way.
Weslie and Wolffy are friends.
Yeah,
they even helped me last time.
They’ve helped me, too.
Me, too.
Why would Wolffy be catching goats?
By the way,
I have some carrots. Take them with you.
We have some, too!
Oh, thank you.
I’m being serious!
Stop fooling around!
He’s so scary! Run!
Son!
Yes, sir!
Come on,
we’re taking some pictures.
I want the entire grassland to know
that my son has found success!
Let me out!
Why would Werewolf rescue Doudou?
Look, guys.
There’s a switch there, but I don’t know what it does.
It must be the switch to the cell!
We can’t reach it, though.
Leave it to me.
Oh, yeah! We can throw shoes at the switch.
In the name of freedom,
go on,
slipper!
It’s working!
I must land it!
If you miss all of them
and someone sees the ground full of shoes, we’re done for!
Calm down!
Let’s use the stick to press the button.
Oh no!
It’s all your fault!
You hurt Doudou!
How is Doudou right now?
Look,
this is what you’ve done!
What…
What is this?
This is his injured little finger!
Oh, Doudou,
your little finger is in so much pain!
By the way, why are you so worried about Doudou?
Why do you care, huh?
I’m going to avenge him
right now!
Don’t move.
I’m going to teach the goats a lesson today.
No one can stop me!
Wolffy, you—
Don’t make me.
Just you wait!
Thank goodness he didn’t notice that it’s a water gun.
Wolffy, let us out of here.
I can’t right now.
What exactly are you trying to do?
I’m taking you guys with me to the Safe Room.
This way, everyone will be safe.
Your dad will eat us before we even get to the Safe Room!
I’ll…
I’ll stop him!
Here, say cheese!
Awesome! Awesome!
Yeah,
another one! Another one!
I’m sending them to the papers!
Huh?
Either way, don’t worry, guys.
I’m going to clear things up with my dad.
We’d…
We’d better just get out of here.
I need to tell Dad clearly and firmly
that we don’t eat goats!
Dad,
did you hear what I said?
Yes.
You wanted your goat-catching story on television
and I’ve just sent it!
That’s not what I meant.
Well? What is it, then?
I…
Ouch!
Dad, I—
Well? What is it?
I…
Nothing.
Wonderful!
Help me type your goat-catching story onto the paper,
and I’ll continue posting it to my WeChat Moments!
Dad—
My son caught goats!
I’m so happy!
Oh, yeah. I need to ask for more likes.
I can’t let Wolffy threaten me again!
I must create an even better weapon!
Wrong one.
Wait a minute.
You want to bully me, Wolffy?
I’ll teach your airplane a lesson!
I think I remember
that this setup is identical to the one on my airplane.
Let’s change it up, then.
Almost there.
There we go!
What’s wrong with Wolffy?
When I was little, I never made any progress,
so I always made my dad upset.
Wolffy?
Today, he’s so happy about me catching goats
that he’s practically over the Moon.
I’ve never seen him so happy before.
Do you guys know how happy he is?
Yes, we do.
Dad, what are you doing here?
Your goat-catching story has reached every part of the world.
Up next is eating mutton!
So, which goat shall we eat first today?
No…
No!
Dad, no!
We can’t eat them!
What the heck are you talking about?
We’ve never eaten mutton once in our lives
and now is our chance,
yet you dare to say,
“no?”
We’re about to get eaten!
Little goats,
here I come!
You can’t eat them, Dad!
You—
They’re
my friends!
Out of the way!
Wolves eating goats is the natural order of life!
We must eat them today!
I’m doing this for your own good!
Well? What is it?
I…
I think
I twisted it.
Get up.
Hurry up! I’m doing this for your own good!
Stop playing. Go home and do schoolwork.
This is for your own good.
No inventions!
I’m doing this for your own good!
I’m not doing good at all.
Huh?
I’m not good at all!
You’ve always been like this,
making me do only what you wanted.
You’ve never once thought about how I feel!
It was like this back then,
and it’s still like this now!
I’m grown up now.
I know what’s actually best for myself,
so this time,
I’m choosing what I want!
I’m protecting my friends!
You…
Wolffy…
Wolffy, are you okay?
Yeah.
Sorry about that, guys.
I’ll figure something out.
We’d better get out of here.
All done.
There’s no way Wolffy will be able to mess with me
with that secret weapon.
Doudou, I’ve brought you some food!
Where’s Doudou?
Doudou?
Where’d you go?
Doudou? Doudou!
The goats…
I wake up, and Dad is missing.
I knew it!
Dad, what are you doing?
Eating mutton, of course.
I told you that we can’t eat them!
Is that why you hid the goats?
What do you mean?
Oh no,
they escaped!
Get them!
Did you not hide them?
Wait for me!
Thanks for that, Doudou.
We’re free!
Is that button not for opening the cell?
Oh no!
Is everyone okay?
I’m here to get you out.
Doudou!
No need to thank me. Let’s keep going.
Big brother?
“Big brother?”
Why did you run out with those goats?
Because—
Doudou, what did you call Werewolf just now?
I—
Doudou, your forehead!
What do you mean?
No, I—
Forget about them, Doudou.
Just go!
Doudou,
what exactly is the relationship between you two?
What are they talking about?
It’s the goats!
We…
We’re…
Doudou…
Enough!
Stop putting Doudou on the line!
We’re…
We’re
siblings!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter