Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the goats were captured,
and Wolffy repeatedly defended them.
Ultimately, with Doudou’s help, the goats escaped being eaten.
However, they later discovered that Doudou and Werewolf are siblings.
Truth and Peril
Siblings?
You’re twins?
Doudou,
what in the world is this about?
Have you been lying to us this whole time?
He’s my brother Taotao.
The truth is, both of us are Spacetime Guardians.
What?
The wolf fur turned into a fish scale.
A long, long time ago,
our people lived around the Dimension Gem’s area.
Back then, our village was very lively.
As for my brother and I, we were selected as the Dimension Gem’s guards.
Every day, we had to go inside the Dimension Gem to work.
I was in charge of patrolling the Spacetime Tunnel
and maintaining order.
My brother was in charge of timespace separation at the Hub,
because a new timespace is generated every day in this universe.
When a new timespace was finished generating,
you would have sixty seconds to separate them.
If they weren’t separated within that time,
they’d merge back together,
causing a major catastrophe.
But my brother would always complain to me
about how boring his job was.
Preparing for timespace separation.
How slow.
Ugh, I’m so bored.
Finally!
Sorry,
could you kick the ball over to us?
What a long and boring life for a fish.
I should be good to play for a while.
Hey,
can I play with you guys?
Sure!
Whenever my brother saw
that the timespace generation had a lot of time left,
he would sneak out to go play with his friends.
Once time was almost up, he’d come back to work.
Until one day,
he was so caught up in playing with his friends
and lost track of time.
It’s getting late.
I have to go now.
Let’s play again next time.
Goodbye!
I wonder how the timespace generation is doing.
Oh no!
Have I been playing for that long?
The catastrophe!
What happened?
Has something gone wrong on Taotao’s end?
I need to make it!
What in the world happened?
What’s happening, Taotao?
It was my fault.
I shouldn’t have snuck out to play.
I’ll help, too.
We should have enough time.
I can do it. I can do it.
I can do it!
It’s too late!
Run!
No!
We did everything we could,
but in the end,
we weren’t able to prevent the catastrophe.
No!
That’s how the ocean we once lived in
became frozen forever.
Ever since then, my brother dreams about his friends
every single night.
Taotao,
what are you waiting for?
Catch!
Taotao,
come on! Play with us!
Coming!
Help!
No!
Filled with regret,
my brother would lament in front of the ice statues every day.
—I’m going to revive you guys.　—For the sake of reviving his friends,
—I’m going to revive you guys.　—he slowly started losing rationality.
He wanted to go to a timespace of the past and try again,
but all of the timespace gates on that timeline
had been frozen shut.
With no other choice,
my brother started eyeing the Dimension Gem,
wanting to shatter it to reset spacetime.
However, we Guardians simply couldn’t break it on our own,
so he thought of getting your help to do it.
You can’t just sacrifice the entire world
to fix your wrongdoings, though!
Shut up!
Nothing else matters
except for my loved ones living again!
You—
What’s going on?
It’s another quake!
This one is different from those before.
Things are getting even worse now.
Let’s send that anachronist home!
Taotao!
Taotao?
What’s happening?
Rescue first!
Put the Magic Airplanes on autopilot,
and we’ll go on foot. We can rescue more people this way.
Dad, let’s go get Wolnie and Wilie.
Wolnie!
Are you guys okay?
Yes.
That’s good.
Take shelter here.
I’m helping with rescue.
Why rescue? With how dangerous it is,
we should just stay here together!
My friends are still over there.
I can’t just abandon them!
It’s okay,
Wolffy is very capable. You don’t need to worry.
Yeah!
Go, Daddy!
Thank you, son.
I’ll leave them with you, Wolnie.
Don’t worry.
Dad,
you don’t need to be angry with Wolffy all the time.
He really does admire you, you know.
Dad?
You’re here, Wolffy.
Help with rescue!
Thanks.
You’re welcome.
If the world ends, then let it end.
It’s not like we’ll be affected.
But sure, go ahead and “rescue” people.
You’ll regret it once you’ve lost your own life in the process!
But you still say that I don’t “understand” you.
Is this all my fault?
Thank you, Wolffy.
What do you mean?
We’re friends, you know.
“Friends?”
Dad,
I’m really scared!
It’s okay, I’ll protect you.
Go back to where you belong!
Otherwise, all of spacetime will be reset!
I shouldn’t even be here to begin with.
It’s all my fault.
Dad, what are you doing here?
Look out!
Dad, are you okay?
You…
Look out!
Why…
Why would you defy all odds just to save me?
I almost ate you guys just a while ago!
What are you talking about?
We goats and wolves are friends!
You can’t eat them!
They’re my friends!
Thank you, Wolffy.
What do you mean? We’re friends, you know.
Friends,
huh?
Dad?
Weslie?
—Dad!　—Darky!
It’s too dangerous here.
You can just leave Darky to me.
Sirius!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter