Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the grassland fell into chaos as spacetime was about to reset.
In the midst of the crisis, Weslie rescued Darky.
At such a critical juncture,
will Darky change his decision?
Darky’s Decision
Stop!
Taotao,
you agreed to take all of us to the Safe Room!
Shut up!
Stop dancing around it!
Can’t get me!
Just give in, Taotao!
This isn’t fair!
Wolffy!
Roger!
We did it!
Dad!
Dad, wake up!
Son?
You lied to me, didn’t you?
Yep.
I never actually agreed to bring everyone along.
Despicable!
So what if I am?
You think you can still mess with me?
Sirius,
merge!
Huh?
When did this guy change up my Sirius?
What… What the…?
Don’t panic, guys! Stay focused!
He’s so fast!
Now that I’ve merged with Sirius,
you guys are absolutely no match!
Paddi!
Still worrying about other people,
Weslie?
Guys…
It’s your turn!
What’s going on?
Give the controller back to me!
Give Sirius back to me first!
Guys, stop fight—
Let go!
No way!
Darky, attack Weslie!
Huh?
Such nuisances.
First, I’m going to teach you a lesson
for all the times you’ve ruined my plans.
Then, I’m going to destroy your friends down there!
Goodbye, Wolffy!
Wait.
Darky?
Are you trying to stop me, too?
No.
Since you like your friends so much,
go be with them
and die.
I don’t care what happens to the world,
but don’t drag me down!
You—
I’ve made a decision.
With how powerful you are, I’d rather work with you.
Great! Working with smart people is what I like.
Let’s hurry to the Safe Room now.
Sure!
Let’s just leave them to die!
Wolffy!
How are things?
Did you get him?
Daddy, where’s Grandpa?
I was lied to.
Taotao had never planned
to take us to the Safe Room to begin with.
Wolffy…
Dad,
why are you fighting against me with Werewolf?
Why?
He…
He doesn’t deserve any sympathy!
Look at what the world has turned into!
So many people have been affected by this catastrophe,
including even our own friends being harmed!
You’re so incredibly selfish
to sacrifice everyone’s lives like this!
Daddy?
Fine.
I’ll…
I’ll send my dad home!
Wolffy!
Doudou, do you know where Taotao is?
I might.
How are we supposed to fight him, though?
Aside from Thunderbolt,
all of our airplanes are broken.
I’ll go by myself, then.
No, that’s too dangerous.
You being the main character doesn’t mean you can take him on!
Wolffy, why don’t you go with him?
I’ve thought of an idea.
Wonderful! They’re not following us anymore!
Exactly.
Not again!
Hand over my dad, Taotao!
Wolffy? How do you still have an airplane?
I’ve reinforced Daybreak’s abilities,
but they will only last for a short while.
You have to be quick.
Out of my way!
How fragile.
He’s safe?
Weslie?
I’ll teach you a lesson!
My mechanical arm!
Well done, Wolffy!
There’s no way you’re ruining my plan!
I’m mad now!
Look out!
Weslie, rope!
We did it!
Wolffy,
give them the final blow!
Roger that!
Piece of cake.
No matter what you guys do,
you’ll never defeat me!
Yes, we will!
No matter how strong you are,
Weslie and I will defeat you!
I’d like to see you try.
Darky, what are you doing?
Run, Wolffy!
Darky, you traitor!
If it weren’t for saving my son,
I would never have worked with you.
You’ve lost, Taotao.
The future
belongs to them.
No!
Dad!
Don’t!
No!
Why?
Wolffy…
What are you crying for?
Dad, you’re okay!
Dad!
Taotao!
Repairs cost us some time.
Are you guys okay?
Yes.
Wolffy?
Wolnie…
Son…
The clock is ticking.
Let’s go.
Are we going to the Safe Room, Grandpa?
The Safe Room?
No—
I’ll do it.
Dad—
No need to say it. Let’s go.
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter