Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Darky pushed Wolffy off of Sirius in order to save him,
pretending to play along.
In the end, he successfully stopped Taotao.
What will happen next?
Sending Dad “Home”
Prepare the machine gun!
Roger that!
What’s wrong, Mr. Slowy?
Nothing. We just hit some floating trees, is all.
It’s all Taotao’s fault!
If it weren’t for him, none of this would have happened!
It’s my fault.
It’s my fault for not stopping him.
I will be sure
to fix all that he’s done.
Run!
No! No!
I’m back at the Hub.
Alright,
I’ve gotten the directions to Darky’s timespace.
You’re good to go now.
Grandpa, Grandpa!
Grandpa,
can you take me to the amusement park tomorrow?
Just be a good kid,
and your parents will take you.
Come over here, Wilie.
Dad…
Dad,
the truth is, we’re—
Where’s my brother?
Where’s Paddi?
Are you looking for him?
Paddi!
What are you doing here, Taotao?
Bad news, Weslie!
My brother’s gone!
He’s right in front of us!
Huh?
I’ll be right there!
Help me!
Paddi!
Are you guys okay?
Yes.
Not for long!
Fire!
Good thing the airplane he hijacked was Paddi’s.
It would be another story if he’d hijacked my airplane instead.
My airplane is pretty good, too, okay?
Enough!
I’ll stop him!
Give it up, Taotao!
It’s not yet time
to give up.
He spun them off!
I won’t let you do anything!
Stop it!
Stop wasting your time!
There’s no way you can get past Lightning Angel’s defenses!
Then I’ll break through them!
Hurricane can’t hold up for much longer!
If you don’t stop now, you’re going to kill yourself!
The past Taotao has already vanished along with his friends.
The current me
only lives for the sake of saving them!
Mr. Slowy! Tibbie!
Are you guys okay?
Yes, but Taotao…
My Hurricane!
It’s torn to shreds!
I’m not going to just give up like that.
I mean, he’s got a lot going for him, too.
Why don’t we go rescue him?
Taotao’s gone?
Let’s just get going.
I can’t bear to face a torn-to-shreds Hurricane.
Then
let’s send Darky home first.
Dad,
this isn’t the Safe Room.
This is…
This is—
Dad?
You brat,
did you really think I didn’t already know?
I do understand my son, actually.
Behind this gate
is the timespace that I’m returning to, right?
Dad,
I’m sorry!
Don’t feel guilty, son.
All of the things you did for me
will be kept right here.
All this time, I thought I understood you well.
I forced you into what I wanted,
wanting you to grow up and become an outstanding wolf,
a hero of the Wolf Clan.
However,
I didn’t realize
that, in fact, you already are an outstanding wolf.
You’re not just merely a hero of the Wolf Clan.
You’re a hero of the entire world.
I’m truly proud
to have such a wonderful son.
Therefore,
for the sake of my own son’s future,
I will do
anything.
Alright,
wipe your tears.
A man, a whole husband,
has nothing to cry over.
This isn’t heroic at all!
Crying like this
looks awful.
Don’t go, Grandpa!
Silly,
I’m just going away for a little bit.
We’ll meet again very soon.
Promise me that you’ll listen to your parents
and that you’ll grow up to be as strong as your dad.
I’ll leave them to you, Wolnie.
Dad!
I can’t let a brat like you be the only hero.
I’m going to be one, too!
Goats,
I’m letting you go this time.
As a farewell,
you better promise me
that you’ll live with my son
happily ever after.
Yes!
Well, I’ll be on my way, then.
Dad!
You’re the greatest dad ever!
I’m very proud to have a dad like you, too!
Goodbye,
you brat.
I won’t let you down, Dad.
Weslie,
are you guys okay?
Where’s my brother?
We’re okay.
He hijacked Paddi’s airplane,
and by accident, he crashed in the Tunnel.
When we went to rescue him, he was gone.
Taotao…
It’s my fault for letting him run out again.
Look,
the cracks are fixing themselves.
The Spacetime Tunnel is recovering.
It’s finally over.
I’ll send you guys home.
Then…
Will we forget our memories from this place when we go home?
I’ll always remember you guys, though.
Come on, I’ll lead you guys out.
You’re not going anywhere. Not one of you is going anywhere!
The exit is right up ahead.
You’ll be back in your own timespace once you pass through the gate.
Yay!
Congratulations! We did it!
Thank you for all of your help—
What’s going on?
What… What’s going on?
The timespace gate is closed!
What?
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter