Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
Darky decided to return to his timespace
for the sake of Wolffy.
Yet after a tearful goodbye,
the reset of spacetime hadn’t stopped.
What in the world is going on?
Doomsday
Why did the gate close?
Something must have gone wrong at the control panel!
I’ll go take a look.
Nothing bad happened, right?
All the anachronists have been sent home.
We’re fine.
Eat something and rest.
Thanks, Wolnie.
Why is this pudding shaking?
This cup of tea seems to be shaking, too!
No,
it’s a quake!
But why?
Didn’t we send them all home?
Why would there still be quakes?
This quake
is because you guys are still in this place.
What?
Are you saying that if we don’t go home,
spacetime will still be reset?
Yes, because you guys don’t belong here, either.
But the gate is closed. How are we supposed to leave?
The control panel has been broken. I’m fixing it right now.
Just hold on, guys!
We can’t just sit and wait, can we?
You’re right.
Let’s see if we can open the door.
Take shelter in the cave, guys! Be careful!
It’s so heavy!
I’ll help you.
No, it’s pretty light.
What’s happening?
Help!
I’ll try!
Let me try!
You can’t!
Don’t worry, it’ll be fine!
Too much force will break it!
Are you guys okay?
Yes.
What should we do? We still can’t open the gate.
Nothing’s working on our end, Doudou.
How about you?
Doudou?
Doudou!
Come on, get in the Safe Room with me.
Let go of me!
I need to open their timespace gate!
Forget it!
The world is about to reset!
You need to stop!
You’re just going to hurt even more people!
Doudou!
No!
Thanks, guys!
We’re glad you’re okay.
Enough chatting.
Let's fix the control panel!
You may have rescued Doudou,
but you won’t be succeeding.
Oh no,
the control panel has been buried!
Don’t worry, we’ve got you.
What’s going on?
Could you find me a shovel?
Sure.
It’s a letter from Slowy!
What’s with the strong wind?
Careful.
Are you okay?
Let’s go.
I’ll help you with repairs.
To help…
We’ve dug it out at last!
I’ll get to repairing it right away.
No!
I won’t let you repair the control panel!
Huh? They’re floating?
Hang on to me!
If we’re going to float, we’re floating together.
Help!
This last wire will determine whether or not it works.
It works!
I’m opening the timespace gate.
It’s open!
Hurry, guys!
Goodbye, my friends!
Where did the gate go?
It’s starting.
Resetting
at last!
What the—
The reset has begun!
Reset?
Dad…
Hurry to the Safe Room to bypass the reset!
Get to the Safe Room first.
We’ll see what we can do from there.
Buddy!
This is the Safe Room.
Where’s Daybreak?
Yeah,
where are Mr. Slowy and Wolffy’s family?
Look, guys!
Oh no!
—I thought it was over.　—Daybreak!
Run!
Slowy,
keep up!
I will!
I’ll be sure to protect you!
Wolffy,
get over here, quick!
They’re right up ahead!
Wolnie—
Go!
It’s my turn to protect you guys this time.
No!
Mommy!
Mr. Slowy!
Take care of yourselves.
Remember, keep Wilie safe.
Wolnie!
To be continued
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter