Time and space chaos makes time collide
Facing challenges, we’ll never surrender
Fearless of obstacles, with friends by my side
Together, we’ll rise against the current
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Laughing, joking, striding forward
Defeating evil one by one
Reaching the terminal of victory
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
Braving the winds and waves to chase our dreams
Growing wiser and braver every day
United by the power of camaraderie
Creating the most beautiful sunlight above
We’ll cross time and space to save the world
Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home
Our confidence will never fade away
Love will always be by your side to stay
In the previous episode,
the spacetime reset began.
The goats and wolves got trapped at the Hub
Slowy and Wolnie did not manage to escape
and vanished in the reset.
How will this end?
Reversing Spacetime
Wolffy!
Wolnie?
Wolnie!
Daddy!
Daddy, are you okay?
Daddy,
where’s Mommy gone?
Your mom… She…
The world still got reset!
We don’t even know where Doudou and Taotao went.
Everyone at Goats’ Village…
Mr. Slowy…
I don’t want it to end like this!
We’ll never get to see Mr. Slowy again.
Enough!
If Mr. Slowy were here,
would he want to see us like this?
As long as we find Taotao and Doudou,
there must be some other solution!
Right,
we just need to find them.
We’d better get going.
This is the only timespace gate left.
Taotao and Doudou must be through there.
There’s no time to waste. Let’s go after them.
Is this what the world is like post-reset?
What did you bring me here for, Taotao?
Don’t you remember?
We were born from the hands of this clock.
If we move the hands,
we’ll be able to speed up time,
return to that fateful day, and save our people.
Do you not want to save our people?
But—
What are you doing, Taotao?
I will save our people
even if I have to do it alone!
Taotao…
What’s that?
Taotao and Doudou must be over there.
Let’s go.
Watch out, guys!
Everyone is back at last.
What the…?
I think speeding up time used up too much energy.
Why is there suddenly a town here?
This must be the era
in which Taotao and Doudou once lived, right?
How long have we been out?
Never mind. Let’s hurry to the Hub.
All we need to do is separate the timespaces!
Who are you guys? You look suspicious!
It’s young Taotao.
I’m the future Doudou, and he is—
—the future you.
There’s no time to waste.
Separate the timespace.
Whatever. Timespace separation is more important.
Darn it, not again.
I didn’t think that speeding up time
would affect the body of a Spacetime Guardian so much.
Taotao…
Doudou…
I’m so close.
Run!
Why is the area starting to freeze?
All of the civilians will be frozen soon!
The frost is spreading inwards from the outside.
Everyone, split up and get the civilians under the ruins!
What’s… What’s happening?
Oh no!
Why can’t I avoid this ending?
It’s all my fault for playing too much.
That’s what caused this.
What the—
Doudou!
What is this about?
Why are you—
Could it be…?
Doudou, please be okay!
Taotao…
What should we do?
Oh, fire.
I need fire!
It’s too late, Taotao.
No. No!
I won’t let anything happen to you!
Why are you still so headstrong, Taotao?
From the start, you’ve always played too much
and have always been so self-centered.
Your clumsy self can never do anything right.
You’re always making me worry,
and I have to clean up after your mistakes.
But I can’t hate this side of you.
—This side of you always makes me laugh.　—Doudou, where are you?
—Whenever I need you, you’re right by my side.　—Doudou, where are you?
No matter how many problems you face,
you always find a way to solve them.
I believe… I believe that you will find
a way to change this ending.
No, Doudou!
Doudou!
Goodbye, Taotao.
We’ve gotten everyone onto the airplanes.
Where are we supposed to go, though?
Guys, look under the ruins!
It’s Taotao.
Are you happy now, huh?
Doudou, what happened?
Doudou!
Restore our world right now!
It’s too late!
Even Doudou has been frozen,
and my energy is almost gone.
There’s no way out.
No… No.
No,
you’re lying!
Surely…
Surely, there has to be a way!
Surely, we can bring them all back!
Surely, you’re lying to us!
You’re
lying to us.
I’m not giving up just like that!
We haven’t gotten to the point of giving up yet!
There’s no use!
I’ve tried everything,
but the ending is always the same!
If the first try doesn’t work,
then I’ll try again another hundred times!
I’m not just going watch our people be frozen
with my own eyes
and then sit here with regret forever, not doing anything!
I’m not going to let go of even the tiniest bit of hope.
It was my wrongdoing,
so I’ll fix it myself!
Fix it
myself?
Wait,
there’s one more thing we can do!
Let’s turn back into clock hands with you substituting for Doudou.
We’ll start moving the hands again
and reverse the flow of spacetime.
When the time comes, you guys take everyone into the Safe Room.
That way, none of you will ever be affected by spacetime again.
But with your current strength—
Enough!
This is our last chance!
Are you willing to do this with me?
This was our mistake,
so of course we’re going to fix it together.
Are you ready?
Let’s begin.
Go!
This is taking too long.
The ruins are going to freeze!
It can’t end like this!
Push as hard as you can, guys!
Guys…
I can’t let the goats take all of the credit!
It’d be easier with the Magic Airplanes!
My Hurricane…
We’ll help, too!
Guys…
Let’s count
and push together!
One!
Two!
Three!
♪ We’ll cross time and space to save the world ♪
♪ Laughing, joking, striding forward ♪
One, two, three!
♪ Defeating evil one by one ♪
♪ Reaching the terminal of victory ♪
One, two, three!
♪ We’ll cross time and space to save the world ♪
♪ Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home ♪
♪ Our confidence will never fade away ♪
♪ Love will always be by your side to stay ♪
♪ We’ll cross time and space to save the world ♪
One, two, three!
♪ Laughing, joking, striding forward ♪
♪ Defeating evil one by one ♪
One, two, three!
♪ Reaching the terminal of victory ♪
♪ We’ll cross time and space to save the world ♪
♪ Together we’ll create a warm and wonderful home ♪
♪ Our confidence will never fade away ♪
♪ Love will always be by your side to stay ♪
Mr. Slowy!
Wolnie!
Mommy!
What are you doing, guys?
I almost can’t breathe!
What’s the matter with you guys?
I still need to pack my things for the scientific expedition at the Ice Pole.
This is how we reversed the flow of time
and returned to the past.
End
Passing through endless, countless days
We see a fine, beautiful tomorrow
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter
Full of extraordinary strength
With sunlight beaming from our hearts
Flying through the earth and the sky happily
We tirelessly chase our dreams
With sincere and caring friends
We get over valleys and mountains of difficulty
In spite of the storms and challenges
Our determined hearts stay the same
We own constant courage and bravery
Let’s create this world with laughter
Let’s march to the new wonderland with laughter