The Ocean Star
Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy, why did you fall asleep right here?
Kids?
Didn’t you say you were going to find out the origin of the black star?
That star has been here for a week.
Plus, it’s still visible in broad daylight.
I’ve already found out its origin.
For the past few days, I’ve been digging through records
that the previous chiefs of Goats’ Village have left behind.
At last,
I found this.
Which flavor did you find, Mr. Slowy?
Is eating all you care about, Paddi?
What Mr. Slowy found
is obviously a box of shuttlecocks!
You’re both wrong!
This is a scroll.
Based on the scroll’s descriptions,
that black star above our heads
is actually a projection of the Ocean Star in the sky.
In the depths of the sea
is the “Ocean Star,” a gem that
absorbs pollution and toxins
and keeps the seas clean.
Every five hundred years,
the Ocean Star undergoes a transformation stage,
destroying all of the pollution it has absorbed.
When it does so,
it will form a projection in the sky
to tell the world that it requires protection for the time being.
Why?
Normally, the Ocean Star is extremely tough,
but it becomes extremely brittle during its transformation stage.
If the Ocean Star shatters,
all of the absorbed pollution from the last five hundred years will be released,
causing a major catastrophe for marine life.
When our goat ancestors faced this situation,
they would venture under the sea
to protect the Ocean Star
during every transformation stage.
Now, a new transformation stage has been ongoing for a week.
Let’s head under the sea together
and see if we can help.
But how are we supposed to get there?
Oh, kids,
have you forgotten about the Magic Trains?
Wolffy,
why are you hiding here instead of catching goats?
Wolnie,
we’re going to take over the world!
You’ve said that eight hundred times!
Has it ever been true?
It’s for real this time
because I’ve found the Invincible Overlord Gun
that my great-great-great-great-great grandfather left me!
That’s a gun?
Isn’t that a washing machine?
Hold on.
Just add an Invincible Overlord Gunstock
and then an Invincible Overlord Gun Barrel to it.
Look, Wolnie!
What makes you call this random mess of stuff
an Invincible Overlord” gun?
Wolnie, I didn’t realize you knew that the way to activate this gun
was to kick it!
Powerful, isn’t it?
Any creature that’s hit with this gun
will listen to your commands!
Is this gun really that powerful?
Let me try it!
Wait!
Dumb bird,
I now order you to—
Stop!
Don’t peck my Wolnie!
Go away!
Don’t peck Wolnie!
Go away! Go away!
That garbage gun of yours
is completely useless.
Don’t be upset, Wolnie.
Look,
the instruction manual says
that we need to load in Invincible Overlord Bullets
to truly unlock the gun’s abilities.
Invincible Overlord Bullets?
Under the sea is a gem called the Ocean Star.
It contains a high level of polluting energy.
It’s the best choice for the Invincible Overlord Gun!
You’re headed under the sea?
Don’t panic, Wolnie.
Great! I want to go, too!
There are a lot of pearl treasures under the sea!
Don’t be impulsive, Wolnie.
This trip under the sea is dangerous;
plus, if you go,
who’s going to look after Wilie?
I want to go too, Daddy!
Son,
you’re too little.
I’m not little anymore!
See?
I grew another centimeter taller!
I’m a man now;
I want to go, too!
Let’s go under the sea
and let Wilie see the world.
Uh…
Fine.
We’ll go treasure hunting under the sea as a family.
Cool, right?
Mr. Slowy!
This is my newly created Magic Generation Two,
the Magic Submarines!
The first to be presented is my very own Daybreak!
Magic Submarines!
Long time no see, Thunderbolt!
Lightning Angel!
Rainbow!
Hurricane!
Look, everyone!
My Morning Sun turned into a lobster!
It has claws, too!
My submarine is so awesome;
does it serve some kind of special mission?
Of course it does!
So, Mr. Slowy,
the “special mission” you spoke of is pulling carts?
They swing their flanks and tail
in order to move,
so they’re a little slower on land.
Then, Mr. Slowy, why didn’t you just build the submarines
at the coast to begin with?
You have a point.
Hello there, little goats!
Wolffy?
Faster, Sparky!
Wolffy’s catching up to us!
I’m already at my limit!
Where are you headed
if you’re going this slowly?
Wolffy!
You goats inside better come on out right now,
or else
you’ll all be sorry!
We’re going to be eaten!
Calm down, everyone!
I’ve already thought of something!
Sirius,
get them!
Mr. Wolffy!
You’re pretty smart, Weslie!
You know that turning yourself in is the easier choice!
Sirius, get Weslie first!
Mr. Wolffy,
catch me if you can!
Then I’d like to see you try to escape my grasp!
Sirius,
get him!
Come here!
You have nowhere to run!
I’ve got you, Weslie!
Uncloak!
What?
When did you guys attach behind me?
Thank you for taking us to the coast,
Mr. Wolffy!
Those darn goats!
Good!
We’ve escaped Wolffy!
Yay!
Look, guys!
What’s the matter, Weslie?
Look over there.
It’s an underwater city!
This place is so beautiful!
Look, Tibbie!
This house is made from an actual conch shell!
What a huge fish!
So much food!
It looks so good!
You guys!
We’re here to protect the Ocean Star,
not to fool around!
We’re sorry; we were wrong.
Little goats,
King Wolffy has arrived!
Wolffy!
I’ve finally caught up to you!
Hands behind your back!
What should we do, Weslie?
Wolffy’s caught up to us!
Let’s split up and run!
Okay!
Do you guys really think you can escape
from my upgraded Sirius?
Weslie,
don’t even think about escaping this time!
The submarine in front, stop right there!
I’m Mari, the undersea traffic captain.
You are in serious violation of the undersea code.
You must stop immediately to be educated!
How dare you try to stop King Wolffy from catching goats!
Out of my way!
What?
Not only are you in serious violation of the undersea code,
you also refuse to listen!
Sardines,
go!
I’ll be back!
The undersea captain is amazing!
Weslie,
are you okay?
I’m okay.
Thank goodness there was this undersea captain to save me!
Actually,
you guys are also in violation of the undersea code.
Submarines are not permitted in pedestrian zones.
What?
Therefore, you guys must be educated.
This is our undersea code.
You must read it thoroughly.
Captain, there has been a violation over there.
Alright, I’ll head right over to take care of it.
Wait a minute!
I wanted to ask about the Ocean Star’s whereabouts.
Mr. Slowy, let’s get out of the submarines and ask around.
How are we supposed to breathe outside of the submarines, though?
Don’t worry!
This is the Oxygen Badge.
Wear it, and you’ll be able to breathe under the sea!
It’s glowing!
It turns invisible, too!
How cool!
But these badges’ oxygen is limited.
When it flashes red,
remember to get it refilled!
Alright!
Weslie,
where do you think something as important as the Ocean Star
would be at?
Is this the Ocean Star
that you guys are looking for?
Yes! Where is it right now?
It’s at the Central Park Amusement Park.
What?
Amusement park?
To be continued