Pollution Crisis
I didn’t think that the Ocean Star would be in an amusement park.
Fellow travelers,
please board the vehicle!
Our next stop will be Central Park Amusement Park!
I’ve got to go. Goodbye!
Amusement park?
Hurry, follow them!
On it!
Follow mode, activated!
Right now, let’s study the rules
of civilized tourism.
Don’t run red lights.
Look, guys!
There’s a giant whale!
Is that an amusement park on the back of the whale?
Amusement park?
I can’t believe there’s such a big amusement park on the back of a whale;
the underseas are truly unpredictable!
Mr. Slowy,
the tour group is swimming down towards the whale!
Follow them!
Could this be where the Ocean Star is?
This place is so beautiful!
We haven’t been to this place before;
be careful, everyone!
Alright, Mr. Slowy!
Is this the legendary Ocean Star?
The Ocean Star has reached its limit for absorbing pollution.
The Ocean Star!
I’ve obtained the Invincible Overlord Bullets!
Wolffy,
the Ocean Star belongs to the seas!
Mr. Slowy!
It’s mine now!
It looks like it’s really powerful!
I’m scared!
Does it only glow?
How come my body’s moving by itself?
Mr. Slowy!
Why did Slowy get sucked over?
The Ocean Star
belongs to the seas!
It’s mine! Let go, Slowy!
Why is Slowy getting sucked over with it?
I’ll come back and deal with you guys
after I put it into my Invincible Overlord Gun!
The Ocean Star is in Wolffy’s hands;
this isn’t good at all!
Ouch!
That was so dangerous,
but it was worth it to get this treasure!
Wolffy,
put the Ocean Star back where it belongs right now!
Finders keepers, losers weepers!
How selfish!
Fishies, stop Wolffy!
Ocean Star, can’t you go a little faster?
He’s gone towards the amusement park!
Don’t panic;
let’s split up!
Paddi, take a quick scan of the amusement park
and then send the map to everyone!
On it!
Jonie, Sparky, Tibbie,
follow the terrain and plan an ambush!
Got it!
And I’ll take care of capturing Wolffy.
Let’s go!
Scan complete.
Now sending to everyone!
Locked onto Wolffy!
You can’t escape!
Stop, Wolffy!
It’s dangerous here!
I don’t care!
He fell for it!
Quick, capture him with the shield!
Okay!
Oh no!
Leave it to me!
Watch this!
Tibbie!
Here I come!
Fishies,
go!
Circular stereoscopic array!
Surround Wolffy!
You guys really think you can catch King Wolffy?
Oh no, the fishies went too far!
My treasure!
It’s falling!
Look out!
Don’t be afraid!
You’ve still got me!
Mr. Slowy!
Catch them!
Don’t worry;
I can do it!
I don’t need you to catch me!
Sirius!
What?
Apparently, Sirius was hiding nearby;
no wonder Wolffy was escaping in this direction!
Sirius, catch the Ocean Star!
I won’t let you take it!
Quiet!
It’s mine!
I got the Ocean Star!
Great job, Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy!
Don’t worry, I’m okay!
Quick!
Quick, take back the Ocean Star!
You guys don’t need to bother,
because the Ocean Star is now mine!
What’s going on?
The Ocean Star is detected to be abnormally differentiated!
Did… Did the Ocean Star break?
This is my first time ever seeing a meteor shower under the sea!
What’s this dark stuff?
Mr. Slowy,
what is that?
That stuff is called pollutants.
It’s all of the pollution that the Ocean Star has absorbed over the years!
What the heck is going on?
Danger!
Get away!
Places that the pollutants reach are all being destroyed!
Mr. Slowy, what now?
We can’t let it keep spreading!
Wolffy, give us a hand!
This is so dangerous;
I should… get out of here.
How could you just leave like that?
This is bad!
The pollutants are about to reach a nearby city!
If the pollutants reach the city, it’s game over.
Paddi, scan the area nearby
for a junkyard or something.
Okay!
There’s a shipwreck nearby;
I’ve detected a lot of scrap material that’s there!
Alright!
We need to use the scrap material
to make a giant fan machine
and stop the pollution from spreading!
Let’s go!
Alright!
Fishies, go!
Fan machine, activate now!
Jonie, now’s your chance!
Alright!
Rainbow Shield,
maximum output power!
We did it!
The pollutants are completely sealed within the shield!
Great job, everyone!
We can take a breather at last.
Although we’re safe now,
my Invincible Overlord Bullets are gone!
I have no way to take over the world now!
It’s okay, Daddy!
I’m still here!
I’m already a man!
Son!
Don’t worry, son.
For your
and Mommy’s sake,
I, Daddy, shall succeed!
What’s that button?
Could it be that the Invincible Overlord Gun
still has some hidden ability?
Alright!
I’m going back to try it out on the goats!
To be continued