The Goat–Wolf Cube
Mr. Slowy,
have you found a way to get rid of the pollutants?
Found it!
Look, everyone!
The scroll says
that when the Ocean Star is broken by an outside force,
the original solid outer wall
will shatter into fragments
and scatter all across the ocean.
As long as we recover all of the Ocean Star fragments,
we can restore the Ocean Star
and have it reabsorb the pollution.
Then let’s split up right away
and search for the Ocean Star fragments!
Oh no!
The shield is about to break!
What?
Is there really nothing else we can do?
Uh…
Little goats,
there you are!
Wait a minute, Wolffy!
We have to recover the Ocean Star fragments as soon as possible
to restore the Ocean Star and solve this crisis!
Okay!
Let me use my Invincible Overlord Gun to help you guys out!
Wolffy, you—
That Invincible Overlord Gun doesn’t quite live up to its name!
What’s happening?
Oh no!
We’re about to be sucked into the cannon!
Go the other way!
We can’t!
We don’t have enough power!
What’s going on?
What do we do now?
This is bad!
Apparently, he really did come to help.
What’s with all the noise?
How am I supposed to have a nap?
Wolffy, what the heck did you do?
Uh… Nothing, Wolnie!
We can talk later.
It’s not safe here;
go somewhere safer!
What the heck is going on, Sirius?
Excuse me, are you Mr. Wolffy?
This is your parcel.
Goodbye.
That’s odd; how come there’s a parcel for me?
Huh? A computer?
Wolffy!
Slowy?
What did you send this thing for?
The situation is dire right now.
I’m here to help you!
Help me?
Then do you know where the problem is with Sirius?
If I’m not wrong, it should be
right here in the chamber.
Why is it so red?
Just as I thought.
What the heck is going on?
You sucked all of the pollutants into Sirius,
and then they concentrated in this chamber.
The entirety of Sirius
has now become a pollution bomb!
What are you doing?
Since it’s a bomb,
I’ve got to get it out of Sirius!
Stop!
Its power is very terrifying!
If it’s messed with,
not only will it destroy Sirius,
but also
the entire ocean, too!
Why is it beeping now?
It’s counting down!
Counting down? What do we do now?
Don’t worry;
My Diamond Protective Cover invention
was delivered with me as well!
The Diamond Protective Cover you speak of
wouldn’t happen to be this parcel box, would it?
Not bad, Wolffy!
You actually noticed!
I suppose I’ll trust you for once!
It worked!
Time to eat!
Let’s celebrate this victory!
Yeah!
I never thought that Wolffy would come to save us!
We have to thank Wolffy this time!
Where’s Mr. Slowy?
I think I saw Daybreak headed
in the direction where Sirius crashed just now.
Mr. Slowy…
Slowy, the situation is getting worse!
Slowy? What happened, Slowy?
Wolffy, I’m right here–
“Right here?”
Where’s “here?”
Tell me!
Behind!
Behind?
Behind you!
Slowy!
Come help!
What’s that, Slowy?
This is my newly invented
Protective Cube.
Quick,
let’s put it around the pollutants!
We should be safe now.
You should have brought this thing out earlier.
Your invention isn’t working, Slowy!
Wolffy,
let’s collaborate.
Collaborate?
Right.
With my ingenuity and your inventiveness,
we should be able to rework the cube
and keep the pollutants under control!
You see my strengths, don’t you?
Then what are you waiting for?
Let’s start!
How’s it going on your end, Slowy?
We’ll be good once I add this part!
Oh no!
Sirius is going out of control!
I must place this part in!
The part!
Look out!
That was so dangerous!
This is bad!
The pollutants are about to explode!
But we can’t even stand up right now;
how are we supposed to get near it?
Mr. Slowy!
What’s the matter with Sirius?
Weslie,
we have an emergency!
Stabilize Sirius for me!
Okay!
Everyone,
let’s go stabilize Sirius!
Okay!
Weslie, are you okay?
We’re fine,
but our submarine power isn’t enough!
Kids,
assemble!
Let’s go!
Fire!
Full power!
Kids, hold Sirius down!
Slowy!
Here’s the part!
Catch!
Why won’t it close?
The pollutants are trying to counteract the cube’s suppression!
Mr. Slowy,
we can’t hold Sirius down for much longer!
For my family!
For the seas!
Slowy,
we’re okay!
Thank goodness.
We’ve finally succeeded.
Slowy?
What is it, Wolffy?
Do you know what I’m thinking of right now?
Don’t you think about eating me, Wolffy!
This Goat-Wolf Cube was made through our collaboration;
it needs us to press our hands at the same time!
Okay.
Once I destroy the bomb,
I’ll eat you!
Don’t even think about it!
Right now, the bomb and the Goat-Wolf Cube are one entity.
Destroying any part of it will cause the explosion.
What?
So we’re going to have a timed bomb in our house forever?
Therefore,
we can only work together and find the Ocean Star fragments
to completely solve this crisis.
Fine.
Find the fragments, restore the Ocean Star,
put it with my Invincible Overlord Gun,
and then…
Don’t worry, everyone.
Mr. Slowy,
how could you possibly stay on Sirius?
It’ll be fine.
Wolffy promised to not eat me.
But how could you trust anything he says?
Don’t worry.
He needs me,
so he won’t eat me for the time being.
It’s all your fault
for causing all this trouble
and making it so that Slowy has to live on Sirius!
These are a fragment container
and a fragment-searching radar.
Remember,
the more fragments you collect,
the more control we’ll get over the Ocean Star.
Control over the Ocean Star?
That can’t land in the hands of the goats!
Let’s go back to Sirius!
We’re leaving now!
I forgot Slowy!
Mr. Slowy!
Kids,
I’ll be fine!
Go search for the fragments!
We have to trust Mr. Slowy.
Magic Submarines,
here we go!
End