Buying and Selling
The fragment is somewhere nearby!
Undersea shopping streets are so lively!
There’s so many fun things here!
Here.
Paddi! Sparky!
What’s up,
Weslie?
Did you find anything fun?
Don’t forget that we came here to find fragments!
Grand opening!
Come take a look!
First come, first serve!
Come on!
How about we go look?
A fragment might just be there!
Excuse us!
Look at how beautiful this piece of cloth is!
It’s of terrestrial origin, too!
Aren’t these things we tossed out after we were done
using them on land?
I worked very hard to gather all of these things!
How could it be unwanted stuff?
But it really is our unwanted stuff.
Don’t go!
It’s all your fault!
All of my customers are gone!
We were just telling the truth, is all!
Don’t get in the way of my business!
Isn’t that a fragment?
What should we do?
Welcome!
Do you need anything?
Stop right there!
You haven’t yet paid back your credit debt from last time!
He has such a good memory;
he’ll recognize us for sure!
You guys are in the way of my—
So how are we supposed to get the fragment, then?
I have an idea!
You’re so heavy!
Don’t make a single noise;
otherwise, we’ll get caught!
Could you walk straighter?
Welcome!
I have all sorts of things here;
choose one that you’d like!
You want this one?
A bowl?
This one?
Or this one?
None of these?
Oh, you want this one!
It’s this one, right?
I want this one!
This one!
This is a piece of rubbish.
That’ll be one clamshell.
I’ll get it!
Paddi,
can’t you keep still?
So it’s you guys!
Don’t you guys hate my stuff?
What would you buy them for?
We’d like the fragment;
can we have it?
Sure,
for ten thousand clamshells!
You said it cost one before!
That was before;
the price has now gone up!
But we don’t have that many clamshells!
Then there’s nothing else I can do.
How about we trade with you instead?
That’ll depend on what kind of stuff you guys have to trade.
I’ll trade these with you, Uncle Crab!
How about these?
This is all we have, Uncle Crab.
Alright, it’s a deal!
Thank you!
Paddi, is the fragment secure?
Don’t worry; the fragment has been with me the whole time!
See?
This is a candy, not the fragment!
It’s okay; it’s here somewhere!
Perhaps I dropped it back there?
I just sold one,
and I’ve found another!
Our fragment!
Excuse me—
Don’t disturb me; I’m very busy right now!
Abyssal Elementary School lets out at four o’clock;
I can’t miss opening my store at that time!
Uh…
We dropped our fragment over here;
could we get it back?
I found this one.
But if you guys want it,
you can trade with me!
But
we’ve already given all of our stuff to you!
Then there’s nothing else I can do.
I must set up my store.
It won’t fit!
How about we help you move,
and the fragment works as our payment?
Is that okay?
It’s a deal!
If you help me move to Central Square by four o’clock,
I’ll give this fragment to you guys.
I’ll be waiting for you.
No problem!
Apparently, those goods can be traded for a fragment.
I’ve got to get those goods for myself!
I’m so tired; let’s rest for a bit.
Grandpa, are you okay?
Kids, could you help me out?
Grandpa, what’s the matter?
Today is my grandson’s birthday,
but I don’t have money to buy him a present.
Could you guys give me that stuff for a present?
That’s someone else’s stuff, Grandpa;
we can’t give it to you.
Looks like I’ll have to put some more into it.
Grandpa,
are you okay?
What should I do?
Without a present to give to my grandson,
he’ll surely be very upset!
I’m begging you guys!
Take some pity on me!
We’ll help you!
How could a birthday not have presents?
Awesome!
Thank you guys!
We can make a toy from scratch for Grandpa!
Grandpa,
the birthday gift is done!
We hope your grandson likes it!
Grandpa,
we’ll be on our way now.
I shed all of those tears for nothing!
It looks like
I’ll have to steal!
Excuse me, do you sell cakes?
My apologies, but we’re out of stock today.
Where the heck are they?
We’re here!
Your goods are here.
You guys didn’t bring my goods on time,
so I won’t give you the fragment!
Paddi,
how are you guys doing?
Have you guys found any fragments?
We…
Well, we’ve already found a fragment;
we just haven’t gotten it yet.
How about we come find you guys?
Okay!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
What happened?
My store got stolen!
Who stole it?
I don’t know;
I’ll draw it out for you!
It was him!
Well?
Pretty clear, isn’t it?
It’s Wolffy!
Let’s find him!
Yep!
Wait!
I’m coming, too!
The fragment is mine now!
That’s him!
Chase him down!
We’ll sneak up on Sirius.
Little goats,
come and get me!
Oh no, he saw us!
Then let’s get him together!
Go!
You really think you can get the fragment like this?
Are you guys okay?
We’re okay.
That bastard is running away!
Quick, chase him!
Paddi,
check to see if there’s a shortcut around here!
On it!
This way;
follow me!
Huh?
Wolffy,
drop the fragment!
How’d they catch up so quickly?
Watch this!
I’ll protect you, Tibbie!
I hate you guys!
Let’s distract him!
Weslie,
how dare you block my path!
Tibbie,
now’s your chance!
Got it!
My fragment!
So long, Wolffy!
What?
I’ll be back!
My store!
Is everyone okay?
Yep!
Weslie, here’s the fragment you guys wanted.
But we’re already out of things
to trade with you for it.
No need for that;
you guys saved my store,
so you’ve earned it.
Thank you!
Yay!
I still have to set up my store, so I’ll head off!
Goodbye, Uncle Crab!
I’ve found yet another one!
Uncle Crab…
One million clamshells!
End