Kind Mari
Paddi!
Mr. Slowy!
Wolffy has discovered the location of an Ocean Star fragment;
I’ll give you guys the coordinates!
Make sure to find the fragment before he does!
Okay! Where’s the fragment?
Got it!
The fragment is in a coral reef off of the Coral Hills Highway!
Here we go!
With Weslie, we’re the fastest!
What’s going on?
Look.
No vehicles allowed here; please stop and walk.
If that’s the case, we’ll have to walk.
Wolffy’s here, too!
Darn it, he’s going to get there first!
It’s fine;
don’t you see Mari blocking off the road ahead?
He can’t get through!
Mr. Wolffy,
this is where the coral reef fish spawn.
Right now, it just so happens to be
the reef fish spawning season.
In order to provide a quiet environment for the females to lay their eggs,
as well as to ensure the safety of these reef fish eggs,
I’ve closed off the road for the time being.
No vehicles are allowed.
I’m the most famous seafood chef on land!
I mean,
expert caregiver!
I’ll make sure to look after the reef fish mothers!
Time to show off!
Mama fish,
why don’t I help you?
I’m a papa fish.
But your belly—
I’m just fat because I ate too much, is all.
Aren’t you an expert caregiver?
How come you can’t even discern males and females?
Of course I knew he was a male!
I was just showing you how midwifery works on land!
We call it…
pro-production!
Terrestrial experts really are something!
However,
although I’m a gold medal expert caregiver,
I have my moments of distress.
Weslie and those guys are always bullying the fish
under the guise of love!
Seeing them bully the fish is so heartbreaking!
I despise those who bully fish!
I’m going to go teach them a lesson!
I can search for the fragment easily now!
By the way,
these sardines haven’t been bathed in a while.
Could you help?
Wait for me!
Fine.
Let’s rest for a bit.
Who’s littering?
Look, guys!
There’s an injured little sardine here!
He’s bruised.
That must hurt a lot.
I’ll bind him up!
All done!
He’s just bruised a little, is all;
he doesn’t need to be bound that much.
Let me do it instead.
Stop!
I can’t believe you guys are bullying a sardine!
Outrageous!
We were helping him remove his bandages;
you can ask him!
You’ve made the sardine pass out?
You’re truly a bunch of evil goats!
Sardines,
get rid of them all!
I’m not bathing you guys!
I should hurry and find that fragment while Mari isn’t here.
Wolffy, where are you doing?
I…
I heard something, so I came to open the door.
Thank you.
I’ve already gotten rid of those goats;
they truly do go around bullying fish.
By the way,
have you finished bathing the sardines for me?
Almost!
You’re the kindest!
I’ll head out for patrol, then.
You guys are so annoying!
I’m done pretending!
Hey, you!
Come give me a massage!
You, come beat on my leg!
You, come make me some tea!
Wolffy, you hypocrite!
Sardines, capture Wolffy for me!
Wait a minute!
What’s going on?
I’ll have to thank you for letting me bathe them
so that I could put electric current devices on their bodies.
You’re evil!
Thanks for the compliment.
Even without the sardines, I’m still going to arrest you!
Woah, I’m so afraid—afraid you can’t catch me!
Stop!
You have nowhere to run!
Watch this!
Sirius!
Wolffy,
let me out!
In your dreams!
There’s no way I’m letting you out!
Turns out that the fragment is under the reef;
I’m taking Sirius to dig for it right away!
We’ve finally escaped those sardines.
Isn’t this the same place from before?
I’m all rested;
let’s keep on searching for the fragment
It’s right up ahead!
Why are you guys so lazy?
Even I’m up already!
Are you guys not rested yet?
Help me!
That sounds like Mari.
She screwed us over so badly just now.
It might just be another trap this time.
Should we go, then?
We have to rescue her!
What are you guys doing?
Rescuing you.
I don’t believe you!
You guys bullied a sardine;
there’s no way you’re that nice!
What—What are you doing?
Here, stand.
Thank you.
Little sardine!
Apparently, you guys were helping treat my sardine’s wounds.
I wronged you guys;
I’m sorry.
Something must be happening in the spawning area!
These corals are quite tough!
Stop!
Don’t destroy the spawning area, Wolffy!
How perfect!
I’ll capture you all
so that nobody can fight with me for the fragment!
Don’t forget our agreement!
Well, Slowy’s out right now and won’t see it…
Are you okay?
If only the Magic Submarines were here!
For the sake of protecting the spawning area,
I permit you guys to drive your submarine here.
Come on over, Magic Submarines!
Your voices
are already being interfered with by my machine!
You can’t stop me!
This fragment is mine!
Good thing I prepared more than just one controller!
Magic Submarines!
I’ll be back!
This time, it’s truly all thanks to you guys
that the reef fish and their eggs are safe.
Here;
the reef fish found this fragment.
To thank you guys, you may have it.
Thank you!
End