The Goat Rescue
Oh, for goodness’ sake!
Slowy,
I’m going to eat you!
I’m sorry!
I told you I don’t need your help!
My hand just slipped, is all.
If it weren’t for the Wolf-Goat Cube, I’d have eaten you by now!
Getting hit on the head by this bowl hurts,
don’t you know?
I’m sorry.
Wolffy,
is my salad ready yet?
Yes, it is!
How about I get you a new bowl?
Hurry up!
I need to get more of my vitamins;
don’t forget to add a bit of mutton flavoring!
Mommy,
I don’t want to eat that weird-tasting salad!
You must, son.
We can’t waste food.
Fine.
Well, we’ll head out first, then.
Slowy,
won’t you have a bowl of mutton-flavored vegetable salad?
I’m fine with eating bread.
Oh no, the Wolf-Goat Cube is about to explode!
Slowy, hurry and press your button!
Don’t worry; it’ll be fine!
What’s going on?
This is a handprint simulator.
It simulates our handprints.
This way, we won’t need to keep an eye on the cube all the time.
Of course,
this simulator is still in its pilot phase.
In other words, with this simulator,
I don’t have to be afraid anymore!
That’s right.
And you finally don’t have to stay at my place anymore, right?
That’s right!
I can finally eat mutton now!
Wait, no!
You smell so good;
just like mango ice cream!
Ice cream?
Daddy, do you want to eat ice cream, too?
Uh, yes…
You can have this, then.
Wilie,
the Wolf-Goat Cube is under control for now.
Your dad says that I can go home now.
Really?
But Grandpa Slowy,
I’m going to miss you!
I will, too.
Stupid Slowy!
I didn’t realize just how easier life would be
now that Slowy’s gone.
It’d be even better if I could eat mutton right now!
Wolffy!
Oh, wow!
What did I just say?
Perfect!
Wolffy, I won’t allow you to do anything!
What’s going on, Mari?
Wolffy,
you ate Mr. Slowy, didn’t you?
What kind of joke is this?
I clearly accompanied him to the door yesterday!
You must have faked accompanying him
and ate him instead!
Don’t accuse me!
Who can prove that I ate him?
I can!
Who the heck are you?
Don’t steal the show, please!
I am a good-natured citizen.
I can testify
that yesterday, you wanted to eat Slowy!
For goodness’ sake!
Slowy, I’m going to eat you!
I’m sorry!
I was just bringing it up, is all!
Give Mr. Slowy back to us!
Take him away!
I really didn’t eat Slowy, though!
He drove Daybreak alone yesterday to leave!
No need to accompany me, Wolffy. Goodbye!
Accompany you? Pfft!
I only let you go today for the sake of my son;
you won’t be so lucky next time!
Afterwards, to celebrate the bomb getting cleared up,
I went and bought a whole bunch of snacks.
Where are the snacks right now?
That’s not important right now, Paddi!
Okay.
Then where’s Mr. Slowy right now?
How am I supposed to know?
I told you that I accompanied him to the door!
Wolffy is a prime suspect;
take him back for now!
Hold on!
Aren’t you a traffic controller, Mari?
Why are you arresting me?
Aside from traffic,
I’m in charge of everything!
Slip of the tongue.
Along with traffic, I’m in charge of everything!
Arrest Wolffy!
Uh…
Wait a minute.
Actually, yesterday night…
I’ve bought all these snacks;
we can have a nice celebration!
Celebrate?
Now that I think about it, if Wolffy ate Mr. Slowy
but still bought snacks to celebrate,
that would be a little strange.
Since there’s a gap,
then Wolffy—
Where’d he go?
Why are we suddenly leaving?
No time for explanations; let’s get out of here first!
Send out an APB right now!
We have a warrant against Wolffy!
I can’t believe King Wolffy has become a fugitive!
What’s a fugitive?
Daddy’s a fugitive,
so that means I’m the son of a fugitive!
No,
I can’t let my son become the son of a fugitive.
I’m going to prove my innocence!
I’m going to keep a sharp eye on you!
King Wolffy isn’t going anywhere! However,
do you really have to watch me so closely?
Of course I do!
I don’t believe you can keep up!
I’ll rest a bit before watching you again!
Oh, really?
Don’t rest if you dare!
Fake passing out?
I’ll scare you!
If you keep acting, I’ll eat you!
Mr. Slowy’s Daybreak’s signal
disappeared right around here.
Finding Slowy in such a big coral forest
would take quite a bit of time.
We better have the sardines come and help instead.
Wolffy, what did you do to Sparky?
I didn’t do anything, I swear!
He passed out himself!
Liar!
How could he just pass out on his own for no reason?
Exactly; why aren’t we passing out?
Why are you guys passing out, too?
I’m telling you that this has nothing to do with me, really!
You have to trust me!
Help—
Don’t!
This really has nothing to do with me!
You’re kidding me, right?
It looks like
you guys won’t believe anything that I say.
Weslie, do you still believe Wolffy right now?
I…
Take Wolffy away!
I really didn’t eat Slowy!
Captain Mari,
we’ve found Slowy and Daybreak.
How come Mr. Slowy passed out
just like the rest of them did?
Plus, there aren’t any bite marks on his body.
Well, that’s for sure! I’d know if I’d bitten him!
Nobody was hurt, but they all passed out?
This is way too odd.
There’s something else that I find a bit odd.
What is it?
How come they’re all affected, but you’re not?
That’s right, why is that?
What are you doing? Are you passing out, too?
No! You can’t pass out! You can’t!
Come on, let’s sing the theme song together!
♪ Weslie, Tibbie ♪
You don’t want to sing?
Then let’s do radio calisthenics together!
Do some stretches!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight;
two, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight!
Even Weslie’s passed out;
I can’t clear my name even if I were to jump into the sea!
I better just get out of here.
Do you trust that Wolffy is innocent?
Wolves can’t get rid of their goat-eating instincts;
I think he must have done it.
My dad is innocent!
There’s no way he’d lie!
It’s all your guys’ fault for passing out for no reason
and making King Wolffy save you!
My son is no son of a fugitive!
Nope… Nope… Why isn’t there anything?
Eat something for now.
Thank you, Wolnie,
but I have no appetite right now.
Just eat at least a little bit.
This is all we’ve got.
Go eat; I’ll go make something else.
Thank you, Wolnie.
It’s mutton-flavored salad!
Slowy couldn’t ever imagine such a wonderful taste.
Slowy’s stayed here for a long time,
but he didn’t seem to have eaten salad even once.
Is my vegetable salad ready yet?
I need to get more of my vitamins!
Could it be…?
Scurvy?
That’s right; this disease
is caused by insufficient levels of vitamin C in the body.
Just make sure to get enough vitamins,
and you’ll get better.
Remember to keep a balanced diet
and to eat vitamin-rich fruits and vegetables.
Speaking of which, our diets were very unhealthy
during the time that Mr. Slowy wasn’t with us.
I was afraid of the weird flavoring that Wolffy was adding,
which is why I only ate bread.
After I said goodbye to Wolffy that day,
I saw what looked like a fragment in the coral forest,
so I went in there.
That’s when I passed out.
In other words,
we wronged you earlier, Wolffy.
We’re sorry.
We’d like to make it up to you
if that’s possible.
Great!
How about becoming a mutton feast to make it up to me, then?
Help!
Yell all you want!
I’m going to eat you guys right now;
no one will know!
I knew you were eating goats!
Not you again!
What now?
Warning; the Wolf-Goat Cube is about to explode.
The Wolf-Goat Cube is about to explode.
What’s going on?
Weren’t we safe from the bomb exploding
now that we have the simulator?
That thing was just a test;
it looks like it failed.
What?
Open the cage right now!
If I don’t press my button soon, the Wolf-Goat Cube will explode!
Get out of here, kids!
Mr. Slowy…
With the Wolf-Goat Cube,
Wolffy won’t dare do anything to me.
Go press the buttons!
Then let’s get going.
I’m going to eat mutton for sure next time!
End