The Volcano Restaurant
The radar says that a fragment is around here somewhere.
What is this place?
Let’s go in and check.
There doesn’t seem to be anyone inside.
It’s so creepy in here!
Don’t be afraid;
I’ll protect you guys!
The circuit breaker tripped;
apologies for scaring you guys.
I’m Chef Octo.
Welcome!
Chef Octo?
You guys seem a bit hungry;
here, come eat something.
Yeah!
We’ve been searching for fragments for so long;
my stomach has been empty for a while now!
Come and eat, guys!
We’re super close to finding the fragment;
let’s find it first, then eat.
Alright.
Eating something first won’t take too much time.
Disgusting!
This is our new cold noodle dish at Volcano Restaurant.
How is it?
Is it good?
Uh…
A fragment!
So the fragment was right here!
Chef Octo,
where did you get this from?
Can we have it?
We can do anything!
We can work for you;
please give the fragment to us!
But I was planning
to give this necklace
to the person who eats the ten thousandth bowl of cold noodles.
How many bowls have you sold so far?
Five.
How about this;
if we help you sell ten thousand bowls of cold noodles,
could you give us the fragment?
Ten thousand?
Are you serious?
If you guys can help me sell ten thousand bowls of noodles,
this necklace is all yours!
Okay!
We’ll be sure to do it!
I’ve finally located a fragment!
Volcano Restaurant’s new cold noodles!
Come and try some!
Would you try our cold noodles, please?
Would you like a bite?
Could you try
our cold noodles?
Look!
I also sell noodles!
We’re sorry.
We haven’t even sold one bowl.
I sold some!
Really? How did you do it?
I told him that eating these noodles helps with weight loss,
so he took them!
I have an idea!
Order number nine hundred and ninety-nine!
Order number one thousand!
Order number one thousand and one!
It looks like people really do like my food!
I’m feeling young again!
As long as we find the things that people like,
we’ll be able to attract enough customers!
Eat the noodles, and you can play the games!
I’d like ten bowls of cold noodles!
Thank you for your order!
Have fun!
These cold noodles are disgusting.
I’d like twenty bowls of cold noodles!
Thank you for your order!
This is our complimentary gift.
Our cold noodles
give the body all the needed carbohydrates;
perfect for after the gym!
I’d like thirty bowls!
How did this restaurant get so popular
after such a short time?
Perfect; I can blend in with them
and steal the Ocean Star fragment!
Excuse me, sir,
this is not the ordering area.
If you’d like to order, you may wait in the dining area.
Please queue up.
You cut the line and got caught by the owner, didn’t you?
Nonsense; why would I cut the line?
King Wolffy shall disguise himself and try again!
Who put the garbage bin over here?
It must have been Sparky.
Just wait and see, little goats!
We’ve finally sold eight thousand bowls!
I’m still quite a good cook!
People still like my food!
Tibbie,
I’d like to swap this bracelet for a red one;
I don’t need to eat noodles to swap bracelets, do I?
Mr. Octo, I have a friend who also wants to lose weight!
I only succeeded in losing weight after eating this place’s noodles!
Bracelets?
Weight loss?
This is a restaurant!
I only sell noodles, not bracelets,
and I don’t help with weight loss.
Says who?
If it weren’t for me wanting these bracelets,
I wouldn’t have eaten such disgusting noodles!
But such disgusting noodles
are the best medicine for weight loss!
Apologies; we’re already closed for the day.
Could… Could you come tomorrow?
Wait a minute!
You guys said that my noodles are disgusting?
Yeah, I hate those noodles!
I do, however, like the complementary items here.
I don’t like the noodles, either!
If it weren’t for the significant weight loss,
I’d rather starve than eat them!
What about you guys, then?
We also find the taste to be…
not so great.
Apparently, nobody likes to eat my noodles.
Since that’s the case,
even if I sell more,
what’s the point?
How am I supposed to get the Ocean Star fragment?
I’m so hungry!
Is there a restaurant around here?
Where is there a restaurant?
I’m starving to death!
Exactly!
But I was planning
to give this necklace
to the person who eats the ten thousandth bowl of cold noodles.
Aha! I have an idea!
I apologized to Chef Octo
and also promised him
that we won’t ever uses those kinds of methods
to sell his noodles.
He must be very upset.
Now, not only did we not finish our task,
but we also hurt Chef Octo’s feelings.
What should we do now?
Fellow group members,
this is this city’s famous Volcano Restaurant!
You’re welcome to eat all you want!
Waiter, I’d like to order!
Come take our orders!
Hurry up!
Yay!
Chef Octo, there are customers!
A lot of customers!
Start cooking!
What does it matter if there are customers?
Nobody likes the food I make.
It’s good!
We want more!
Chef Octo,
they say it’s good!
They say they want more!
They say it’s good?
Finally, people who appreciate my noodles!
Coming right up!
Your city’s cold noodles are truly amazing!
Why do the tour guides here sleep on the ground?
We’ll head out now! Goodbye!
I hadn’t thought that while we don’t like these cold noodles,
there are other people who do!
Perhaps fish from other areas have different tastes.
Thanks to them,
we finished our task!
Don’t you guys feel like that tour guide looked really familiar?
Little goats,
thank you.
I promised to give this to you!
Thank you, Chef Octo!
Yay!
Little goats!
Chef Octo?
You guys didn’t like the cold noodles I made last time,
so I’ve developed a new type of noodles
and brought it for you guys to try!
How is it?
Do you guys like these noodles?
If you like them, have some more!
I’ve got a lot!
End