The Liar, Uncle Boulder
Stop, Wolffy!
Give the fragment back to me!
That’s odd.
I clearly saw Wolffy run this way.
Wolffy!
Give the fragment back to me!
Hello, are you looking for someone?
I’m sorry, I was mistaken.
I’ll be on my way, then.
Wait!
What is it?
Excuse me, have you seen Wolffy?
A stupid-looking, useless-looking,
no-good-qualities-looking wolf that passed through here?
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
I haven’t seen him.
Wait!
Why is there fur on your back?
That’s actually a sweater I’m wearing underneath!
Why is it so cold today?
Right now, it’s… summer, isn’t it?
Maybe you’re…
Darn it, I’ve been caught!
Maybe you’re sick?
Yes, I am;
I’m going to see a doctor now.
Goodbye!
Get well soon!
How could a fish have fur?
That was obviously just Wolffy.
Tibbie,
you’re a little too gullible, aren’t you?
I’m sorry, this was my fault.
I’ll make sure to find another Ocean Star fragment!
There’s something here!
Found it!
Thank you so much!
Hello, my name is Boulder.
Your gem is really beautiful;
could you lend it to me for a day?
I just need one gem,
and this crown will be finished.
What a unique crown!
Yeah, I made it out of scrap materials.
Can I ask what you’re making this crown for?
My daughter is taking part in a Children’s Day performance;
this is her first time being the princess.
It’s just that she’s still missing a complete crown,
so I’d like to borrow your gem for it.
Uh…
Never mind.
That seems like it’d be a hard thing to ask of you.
Since gem is truly very important,
are you sure you’ll only borrow it for a day?
Just one day is enough!
Okay, then!
Thank you!
What?
You lended the fragment to Uncle Boulder?
What if Uncle Boulder was sent by Wolffy?
That’s it!
I once saw Uncle Boulder
give a fragment to Wolffy!
Give it to me!
Tibbie,
why were you gullible yet again?
He’s definitely a liar!
Let’s hurry and take the fragment back!
Tibbie,
did he leave you any contact information?
He left me a photo.
Come on, let’s go find that liar!
Wait!
I feel like he’s a good dad;
he’s probably not a liar.
I’m sure he’ll return it to me!
Maybe we should wait one more day?
I knew that Uncle Boulder wouldn’t keep his promise.
We’ve got to track him down!
This place is too big;
how are we supposed to find Uncle Boulder?
I’ll go look over there.
Then let’s get out and ask around.
Excuse me, do you know Uncle Boulder?
I don’t know that liar.
Uncle Boulder?
Why are you guys looking for that liar?
Uncle Boulder really is a liar?
Can I ask how exactly he lied to you?
Uncle Boulder—
I can’t speak of such a painful memory!
That afternoon,
Uncle Boulder… he…
I’m going to get him!
Tibbie,
I found where Uncle Boulder lives!
But this place doesn’t even have the house from the photo.
There can only be one reason for that.
I know!
It must be because
we’ve gone to the wrong place.
Perhaps
Uncle Boulder gave me a fake location?
I knew it!
Uncle Boulder is a liar from start to finish!
I’m sorry, everyone.
I shouldn’t have been so gullible.
Otherwise, the fragment wouldn’t have been taken.
Don’t let me see him!
If I see him,
I’m going to tell him to hand over the actual location!
Is that Uncle Boulder?
It turns out they really are working together!
Wolffy!
You liars!
What are you doing?
Here!
Hurry up and go!
Are you guys bullying me for not having Sirius around?
Sir, please keep seated while we are in motion.
I’ll be back!
We’ve finally got you!
What is it?
Great!
Tibbie,
there you are!
I’m returning this to you.
Is that my fragment you’re holding?
What’s going on?
Didn’t you give Tibbie’s fragment to Wolffy?
Wolffy?
You guys misunderstood.
Here’s what happened…
Are you done looking?
I’m sorry.
Could you lend me this gem for a day?
This is my treasure, you know;
how could I just lend it to anyone?
Then what about just now?
Why were you with Wolffy?
He said his stomach wasn’t feeling so well
and asked me where the nearest toilet was.
I see.
But how come we couldn’t find your house
when we went to this place?
Because last night,
a waterspout came out of nowhere.
I was very frightened
and took my daughter as fast as I could to find shelter
while our house was destroyed by the waterspout.
Since I was looking for a new place to live,
I was late in returning the gem as I promised.
I’m very sorry.
I’m so glad that you weren’t a liar to me.
Hold on!
You might not have lied to us,
but
why does everyone say that you’re a liar?
What?
I… I’m a liar?
Says who?
There you are!
I’m asking you once more, so say it out loud;
am I
beautiful or not?
Auntie Swaddle, I’ve already said it many times.
You really look rather…
mediocre.
Mediocre?
I don’t believe you!
I’m also asking you once more!
Do you think I’m tall and powerful?
Sturdy,
you really aren’t all that tall and powerful.
What?
I don’t believe you!
You’re lying!
I understand now.
When they said “liar,” this is what they meant.
Thank you guys for helping me rebuild my house!
No problem; it’s the least we can do!
Uncle Boulder,
what are you collecting all that garbage for?
This isn’t garbage;
they’re all treasures!
Although they’re all other people’s scrap materials,
they can be turned into new things
after recycling!
Awesome; that way, it won’t go to waste!
By the way, if there’s anything you guys need,
I can help you guys make it, too!
Sure.
Maybe you can make Paddi a little more industrious.
Hey!
End