Repairment
Come have a look! Come see!
Newly released treasures! Get them now!
These aren’t available under the sea;
make sure to get yours!
Well?
Not bad, huh?
So,
how much do you think it’s worth?
How about ten clamshells?
Sure, it’s a deal!
Money first.
Aren’t you supposed to be paying me?
You called me to repair your store;
of course it’s you who pays me the clamshells.
How about five clamshells, then?
Absolutely not; we agreed on ten!
If repairing some small things is so expensive,
I might as well just do it myself!
Goodness!
What a stingy bastard!
The radar says that a fragment is around here somewhere.
But this place is so big; how am I supposed to search?
Daddy,
I can help you!
I’d like that, son!
Daddy, might it be in here?
Son,
how about you stay here and cheer Daddy on?
Okay, Daddy!
Go, Daddy!
Run, son!
Just hide for now, son.
Daddy’s going to distract that fish!
Big guy!
I’m right here; come and get me!
Daddy?
I’m not your dad!
Uncle, have you seen my dad?
Since you can’t find your dad,
you can stay at my store for now,
but you’ll have to be my little helper, though!
What’s a little helper?
A little helper is someone who helps me take care of things for the store.
Okay! I love helping!
Use the wood planks to repair the door first.
Got it!
Having a little helper is quite nice.
All done!
Already?
Pretty good!
However—
Why did you tear out my door?
It’s easier to repair it if it’s out.
You better help me with other stuff instead.
Go patch up the crevices and holes on the roof.
Okay!
Uncle Crab,
I report that all of the holes are patched up!
Stand right here! Don’t move!
Got it, Uncle Crab!
What are you waiting for?
Help me out!
But you told me to stand right here and not move.
I need you to push the ladder over to me right now!
Okay!
You better help me keep an eye on these merchandise instead.
There better not be any problems this time.
Finally done!
I knew that keeping Wilie away from my precious store
was the right choice!
My merchandise!
Uncle Crab, I report that a man wanted to borrow them just now,
so I lent them to him.
What?
Did he give you money?
No.
He was just borrowing it;
why is money needed?
Which way did he go?
I don’t know.
Don’t help me anymore!
Please, Uncle Crab, I’ll try harder!
Give me back the hat!
Is he bullying you, kiddo?
Uncle Crab—
No, no.
He’s my helper;
I was going to have him hand out flyers!
Is there anything you need?
Uncle Crab, did you say that you needed me to hand out flyers?
Wait a minute.
Alright, you can go hand out flyers now.
I’ll make sure not to mess up this time!
Everything’s on sale! Take a look!
Where in the world is Wilie?
I got rid of that big guy,
but then I found out my son disappeared!
Where in the world is my son?
Not you again!
If I hide in here,
that big guy shouldn’t be able to find me anymore!
That Wilie really makes me uneasy.
Emergency news coverage.
There have been successive submarine volcanic eruptions.
Those in the vicinity, please seek shelter immediately.
The volcanoes are so far; he’ll be fine.
How could anything go wrong with handing out flyers?
It’s fine;
Wilie won’t be that unlucky.
Run!
That big fish is coming!
Isn’t that the direction which Wilie went to hand out flyers?
I’m coming, Wilie!
Wilie, where are you?
Run!
There you are!
That big fish is ugly and mean; he’s not to be messed with!
Uncle Crab,
I found a lot of materials to repair the store with!
Help me, Daddy!
Daddy!
Son!
Why is it you again?
Sirius!
I made it!
It’s Daddy! Go, Daddy!
Daddy!
Wilie!
Hey!
Let him go!
How dare you bully my son!
Yay!
The big fish is gone!
Uncle Crab, we’re okay now!
But…
my store is completely gone.
Uncle Crab…
Uncle Crab,
I gathered all the pieces of your store back.
There you are!
Uncle Fish!
Thank you for lending me that stuff last time
so that I could complete my client’s requests on time.
This is for you!
I don’t want the gift, Uncle Fish.
Can you help fix Uncle Crab’s store?
Piece of cake!
Uncle Crab, look!
I have a surprise for you!
My store! My store!
What happened, Wilie?
Uncle Fish wanted to thank us for lending stuff to him,
so he fixed up the entire store!
You’re truly the best little helper!
Wilie, where are you?
That’s Daddy’s voice!
Wilie,
here’s my little helper badge for you.
Thank you, Uncle Crab!
End