The Lord of the Seas
With an awe-inspiring glare,
a strong and healthy posture,
and sharp, pointy teeth,
sharks are the lords
and the protectors of the seas!
Enough, Sparky!
Sharks are terrifying!
Exactly; just thinking about them makes me scared!
I’m going to prove to you guys
just how awesome sharks are!
Don’t go searching for sharks yourself!
Sharks are a very dangerous type of animal;
we must keep our distance from them!
Since they’re dangerous,
that means we don’t have to go search for the fragment, right?
What do you mean?
The radar detected a fragment
that’s right within the shark range.
That’s so scary; which one of us should go?
This expedition is on the dangerous side;
we must plan well and go slowly.
What?
The Goat-Wolf Cube is about to explode?
I’m headed back to Sirius for now;
when I come back, we’ll discuss how to get that fragment!
Where’s Sparky?
Since everyone’s afraid,
leave the fragment searching to me!
Who knows if I’ll get to meet a shark?
I can’t only think about sharks;
finding the fragment is more important!
Could the fragment be inside?
Whatever; I’ll just go in.
Who is it?
Mr. Slowy, there’s trouble!
Calm down!
Speak one at a time!
Sparky
went by himself
to look for
the fragment!
That’s a shark-infested area, though!
Stay where you are; I’ll go find him!
Let’s get going, Slowy!
What are you doing?
We’re friends, aren’t we?
You help me control the bomb, I’ll help you look for people!
Based on experience, you must have something up your sleeve.
There’s no way!
I, Wolffy,
am already noble-minded and pure,
a wolf of moral integrity!
Wolffy,
take advantage of Slowy when he goes for the fragment
and get a face mask for me, too.
Fine.
We’ll go together.
You know my plan, yet you’re still going with me?
As long as Sparky is safe,
I can deal with not getting the fragment.
Great! Then let’s work together to fight against the sharks!
A shark!
Come on,
let’s take a photo together!
Look at the camera!
One, two, three, say “cheese!”
Excuse me, who exactly are you?
Apologies, I got too excited.
Hello, my name is Sparky.
My name is Sawyer.
I almost forgot.
Have you seen this?
No, I haven’t.
Lunch break is over.
I have to go back to work.
You have a job?
A shark’s job must be to protect everyone!
Are you an agile police officer
or a heroic firefighter?
I’m neither.
Because my teeth are incomparably sharp,
I shred unwanted paper here.
He must be like those superheroes;
his job is just a disguise,
but when the time comes, he’ll switch into his hero suit
to rescue everyone!
Sawyer,
do you do anything else besides shred paper?
Of course I do.
—I knew I was right!　—Sawyer,
another one!
I’m also an apple peeler.
But you’re a shark, though! How could—
How could you just do what other people tell you?
Sawyer,
who is this?
Why are you messing around in here?
I don’t even know him.
I don’t care!
You cannot let him disrupt our work!
You’re right, sir.
I apologize.
I’ll finish peeling your fruits right away.
Outrageous!
How could the Lord of the Seas do this?
Let’s go!
Go where?
I still have work to do.
I’m taking you to do a different type of work!
What work?
Being a qualified Lord of the Seas!
You’re a shark;
You’re destined to be a Lord of the Seas,
protecting everyone!
Forget it; I’m not like that.
Do you really just want to stay weak?
I…
I want to protect my friends.
Please teach me how to become a Lord of the Seas!
That’s more like it!
Hand over the lollipop that you’re holding!
No!
It’s on you, Sawyer!
Protect the young and weak!
Okay,
watch this!
Let him go!
Let’s see if you still dare to bully others!
Yay! You got rid of the bully!
What are we training next?
No more training.
I think I’m pushing you too hard.
All done!
With this robot that you and I worked on together,
we won’t need to fear even the meanest shark!
Start up!
Search for fragments!
No;
go to the shark area and search for Sparky!
Fragment first!
Sparky first!
Rescue first!
Find the fragment first!
Destroy. Destroy.
Oh no!
Searching for sharks.
Destroy. Destroy.
Destroy all sharks.
Destroy all sharks?
Oh no!
I can protect the environment,
but how can I possibly protect my friends?
Destroy.
Sparky!
Sparky, you came back!
Run, Sawyer!
Destroy.
Sparky!
I can’t lose!
We’re here!
Let’s assemble!
Okay!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Amazing!
Activate self-upgrade program.
Hold on, I’m coming!
I’ve gotten the fragment; I’m leaving!
Wolffy, you bastard!
Darn it!
His attacking power is way too strong!
I have to help them!
What can I do?
Keep going!
Oh, yeah! My teeth!
The shield is about to break! What should we do?
Don’t hurt my friends!
Sawyer!
You’re incredible!
You’re a true Lord of the Seas!
Thank you for inspiring my potential!
I now have the courage to do my dream job!
Is it being a police officer or a firefighter?
I’ve always wanted to be a sculptor;
I’m going to become a sculptor!
End