Who Upset Jonie?
All clean!
What are you guys doing?
Bad news!
I lost a fragment yesterday!
Fragment?
Is it this one?
Where did you find it, Jonie?
Right on the ground.
You guys probably dropped it
when you came in here to play yesterday.
I see!
We haven’t seen you outside at all today, Jonie;
what are you up to?
I’m cleaning up Rainbow.
Sorry, Jonie;
we made it messy again.
It’s alright.
Why don’t we help you clean up?
Yeah!
Jonie, whose tie is this?
This is a limited edition signed Flat-beak Allen tie;
if I lose it, I can’t get another one.
Jonie, it’s our turn to do the shopping!
Okay,
but my room isn’t cleaned up yet.
Don’t worry, Jonie!
We’ll be done cleaning before you get back!
I’ll leave it to you guys, then.
Let’s go, Jonie!
I’m so tired.
There’s nothing all that special about this tie, though.
Be careful!
Jonie really treasures that signed tie!
I’m just taking a look, you know.
I can’t believe you guys got my limited edition signed Flat-beak Allen tie
all dirty!
What should we do?
Let’s wash it!
Weslie, I bought you the—
Goodness! You guys got Jonie’s most treasured tie
into that state?
We’re trying to fix it!
How come it’s still so dirty?
I bought a bottle of laundry detergent; maybe it’ll help!
Such a tiny bit isn’t going to do anything.
Let me do it!
Weslie, are you guys there?
Tibbie, the bleach that I just bought is gone.
Is it with you?
It might be in that bag over there.
I can’t find it.
Could we have dropped it on our way back?
I’ll go take a look, then.
Quick, see if the tie is clean yet!
It’s more than clean;
it turned white!
What kind of laundry detergent did you buy, Tibbie?
So this was the bleach.
Let’s go apologize to Jonie together.
Weslie, Jonie will forgive us, right?
There’s Jonie!
Jonie!
Did you guys see that?
Jonie’s crying.
Is it because she found out that her tie is missing,
and now she’s upset?
Then what should we do?
I think we should ask Mr. Slowy’s opinion.
So that happened, huh?
We were trying to fix it at first,
but we ended up just making things worse.
What should we do now, Mr. Slowy?
You guys should pay a visit to Sirius!
Huh? Why?
Because
Wolnie also has a signed Flat-beak Allen tie!
Wolnie—
Why are you throwing so many clothes out?
Because those are all old-fashioned now.
But your “old-fashioned” clothes and your new clothes are the same;
it’s such a waste to toss them out!
If I give these unwanted clothes to people who need them,
they won’t go to waste.
True, true…
Wolffy,
Weslie and the others are looking for you.
You guys want this tie?
Alright!
Really?
That is, if you trade Ocean Star fragments for it.
No, we’re not giving any fragments to you!
No?
Never mind, then.
Oh, my window is so dirty!
I’ll give it a wipe!
Stop!
It’s a deal!
Five fragments.
What?
Oh, my floor is so dirty!
No!
Alright, alright! Five!
That was the price before; I now demand ten,
or else…
Oh, how come the toilet’s also this dirty?
Perfect; I can give it a wipe!
This is evil!
We can’t let him win!
Let’s leave.
What did you say, Weslie?
How are we supposed to clear this up with Jonie?
Truth to be told, we can just apologize to Jonie.
She’ll surely forgive us,
so we don’t need that tie.
Hey, wait a minute!
The number of fragments is negotiable.
No thanks.
How about I lower it?
Still too high.
Look, we can negotiate a little longer!
One is the most we’ll do.
Not interested?
Then we’ll be on our way.
It’s a deal!
Thanks!
Jonie will be very happy when she sees the tie!
Jonie’s back!
That’s odd; how come Jonie didn’t even look at the tie?
Maybe she didn’t see it.
I’ll do it!
Look at me, Jonie!
Paddi, what—
what happened to the bib on your chest?
Jonie, I’ve been showing it off for so long;
how did you not see this tie?
Whose tie is that?
That’s your most treasured
limited edition signed Flat-beak Allen tie!
No, it’s not.
The stripes on mine go from left to right;
this one is from right to left.
They’re not the same.
Wait,
did something happen to my tie?
You didn’t know?
What in the world happened?
I’m sorry, Jonie.
I got your tie into this state.
We’re sorry, Jonie; it’s all our fault.
We kept trying to think of a way to fix it, but…
Jonie!
My signed tie!
Good thing it’s safe.
Jonie, where are you?
What now? Jonie’s definitely really upset this time!
It’s all my fault for fooling around
and getting Jonie’s tie dirty!
How could such a little thing
break up our friendship?
Paddi!
Jonie?
I already forgive you guys.
Are you not mad anymore, Jonie?
My tie might be valuable,
but I think our friendship is even more valuable, isn’t it?
But we saw you crying
when we tried to find you to apologize earlier.
You guys misunderstood.
I just had a bit of a cold;
you guys probably just happened to see it.
I see.
We’re glad you’re not mad, Jonie!
What are you looking for, Wolnie?
I’m looking for my signed Flat-beak Allen tie;
have you seen it?
Signed Flat-beak Allen
tie?
Yeah!
I clearly put it here!
Wolnie,
usually, you have to stop looking for something in order to find it.
Let’s eat first.
That’s true; then let’s eat first.
Wolffy!
What?
To thank you for giving the signed Flat-beak Allen tie
to the little goats,
I made you a seaweed salad!
Wolffy!
Wolnie, let me explain!
I’ll be back!
End