Quilly’s Job Search
What’s Tibbie doing over here?
Is it because there are Ocean Star fragments around here?
The more I look at it, the more I like it!
The luxurious yet understated
black studded sea urchin purse!
Black studded purse,
you’re the one I want!
Really?
I thought it was an Ocean Star fragment,
but it was just that thing.
It’s the black studded purse!
The black studded purse!
Yay!
Owner—
I want a black studded purse!
I want two!
I want five!
There’s no way I can beat them.
Apparently, Tibbie really likes the black studded purse.
Sea urchin?
If I have a sea urchin disguised as a purse sneak in with the little goats,
I can get all of their fragments at once!
I just want a job;
why doesn’t anyone give me a chance?
My friend,
what’s your name?
My name is Quilly.
Quilly, I’d like you to work for me!
Sure! Can I ask what it is?
Acting!
You’re now a professional actor;
do you remember what to do?
Director,
I am acting as a purse.
No matter what, I will not move.
What do you do if you’re caught?
Reveal myself immediately.
She’s here!
Black studded purses!
Come get your black studded purse!
I should be able to sell right here!
Great black studded purse sale!
Alright, we can stop here.
Is this actually where we stop?
It doesn’t look like it is.
Driver, could you drive farther ahead?
I’m sorry.
Why is selling a purse so hard?
Why?
Black studded purse?
Are you selling that black studded purse here?
Of course I am.
I didn’t think that Tibbie would be the one to buy me.
A purse with flowers;
perfect!
Oh no, I’m allergic to flower pollen!
Darn it!
Did the purse sneeze?
How come we have so little ramen left?
Don’t add so much black pepper, Sparky.
So it was Sparky.
It looks so good!
No, I’m an actor.
I can’t eat while I’m acting.
Is that a stomach growling?
Paddi, I can’t believe you’re hiding here and sleeping!
What am I doing here?
I clearly went back to my own room after stealing the ramen!
No wonder we lost all that ramen!
You stole it!
No, no, I was just testing it!
Testing it!
Paddi!
Working is so hard.
Time to check on the enemy!
There it is!
Quilly? Quilly!
Director?
Quilly,
there’s a spherical container on the table.
When they’re not paying attention, bring it back to me!
But I’m acting as a purse; I can’t move.
You did a good job,
so you’re a moveable senior actor now.
Hurry up and bring the container back to me!
After all this time, I’ve finally been promoted!
Director, I’ll make sure to complete my task!
What a simple-minded guy he is.
What—What did you see?
I lost my glasses;
I can’t see anything right now.
Scared me to death.
Wolffy’s response was so odd;
might he have something up his sleeve?
Paddi, you’re in charge of doing the dishes this time.
Why?
The container is right on the table;
the door is right by its side.
Okay!
I’ll grab the container that you want, Director!
I’ve had a rough job history,
but this time,
not only did Wolffy want me to be an actor,
he also promoted me!
Therefore,
no matter what I run into,
I’m going to work hard and complete this task!
I must
work harder!
What happened to my room?
All done!
How come the strap broke?
I’ll fix it with a needle and thread.
Tibbie’s so kind.
Quilly,
what are you waiting for?
Grab the container for me right now!
But this belongs to the goats;
why do I have to bring it to you?
Because…
Because there’s a bomb inside!
A bomb?
I have to tell Tibbie right away!
Only I can disarm that bomb!
Tibbie will get injured if she tries to!
Okay.
I’ll bring it over.
The fragments are all mine now!
Found them!
So my glasses were right here!
That Wolffy;
he was just over here.
I don’t know where he ran to now.
What’s going on?
Why is the fragment container outside of the Magic Submarine?
Could it be Wolffy?
Where’s the spherical container?
Right here!
Hurry over! We’re running out of time!
The radar says that the fragment container is right up ahead.
How did the container get all the way over there?
That was close.
You’re so clumsy!
Hey, are you okay?
I’m okay.
Enough nonsense, Quilly!
Get it to me right now!
Okay!
Wait!
Why is our fragment container with you?
He’s your black studded purse;
I hired him to sneak up on you.
That’s right.
There’s a bomb inside of the fragment container;
only Wolffy can disarm it.
You’ve been fooled.
Wolffy lied to you.
The fragment container is for storing Ocean Star fragments;
there’s no bomb.
Hey, Quilly,
as long as you give me that container,
you’ll get to be the Super Job King
and enjoy a lifetime of well-paid benefits!
No!
If the fragment container isn’t dangerous,
then no matter what, I can’t give it to you,
because it belongs to Tibbie!
You’ll be sorry, then!
These are the consequences for betraying your boss!
Hold onto my hand!
How about it?
My Solar Gun is cool, isn’t it?
If you guys don’t want to fall,
then hurry up and throw the fragment container over to me!
You have five seconds to decide!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
The Goat-Wolf Cube’s alarm went off again!
Come back right now!
Wait a minute!
If you wait, it’ll be too late!
Wilie’s still in Sirius!
I’ll be right there!
Consider yourselves lucky!
Thank you, Quilly!
Good thing the kids are alright.
Press your button, Slowy!
The Cube is fine.
Where’s the alarm?
I’m old, so my hearing isn’t great.
I probably misheard.
I’m getting older.
How dare you mess with me, you darned Slowy!
Don’t leave! Come back here!
End