Delivery Crisis
Mr. Slowy?
How are you, kids?
Mr. Slowy!
Is your cold still not better, Mr. Slowy?
I’m already much better.
Wolffy detected a fragment with his radar;
you guys better catch up to him!
Where’s the fragment’s location, Mr. Slowy?
The—The Lotus—
Got it; the Lotus Grotto!
You’ve worked so hard, Mr. Slowy; rest for a bit!
Here we go!
Slowy, oh, Slowy!
I can’t believe you snitched to the goats!
Thank goodness King Wolffy came as fast as he could
and got to the fragment first!
Using Slowy to come after my fragment?
Time for some sweet revenge!
Knowing Paddi,
he’ll certainly take this fruit home with him!
This lightning fruit can render a creature unconscious.
Take off the leaf,
and one hour later, the lightning fruit will explode!
That’s what you get for messing with me!
We can’t find the fragment anywhere.
It looks like we came too late,
and Wolffy got to it before we did.
It’s all my fault for rushing.
Weslie,
I was talking about Lotus Mountain, not Lotus Grotto!
I made us waste all that time;
I’m sorry.
Found it!
Paddi, did you find the fragment?
I didn’t find the fragment,
but I found a lot of tasty fruits!
Weslie,
you can’t be so hasty and impulsive.
I’m sorry, it’s my fault that we didn’t get the fragment this time.
Don’t be so impatient with things.
Finish listening first,
or otherwise, problems will happen.
Mr. Slowy, let it go.
We didn’t find the fragment,
but we found fruits!
Alright. Weslie,
just be careful from now on.
Mr. Slowy must be very disappointed in me.
Don’t think so much about it; let’s eat now!
By the way, how about
we give some fruits to Mr. Slowy, too?
Sure!
Paddi, be careful when you’re eating.
I can take the fruits to Mr. Slowy in a moment.
Why bother with all that? Just have it delivered.
Wouldn’t that be a waste of resources?
Yeah, that’s such a waste!
You think so too, Sparky?
So let’s also have some other necessities
delivered with it.
This way, it won’t be a waste!
What’s all this for?
Lightning fruit?
That’s right! Knowing Paddi,
he’ll certainly take the lightning fruit home with him!
There are only thirty minutes left
before the lightning fruit explodes!
Mr. Slowy?
You guys picked a lot of fruits, didn’t you?
Throw the picked fruits out, now!
Why?
Because Wolffy rigged up the fruits;
one of them is a lightning fruit!
There are only thirty minutes left before it explodes!
I’ll go after the bomb!
I hope Weslie comes back soon.
How—How did you get back so fast?
I… I forgot to take the delivery note with me.
Here’s the delivery note.
Oh, yeah, which way did the courier go?
He went west.
He said he was going to go to Mr. Sea Turtle’s house
to pick up the last delivery.
I see!
I’m sorry; I was driving too fast.
Excuse me, have you seen Courier Swordfish?
I have.
East?
Alright, thank you!
Goodbye!
He went west.
Sir, this is your parcel.
Please sign for it.
I’ve finally caught up!
Are you…
Do you need me?
Do I know you?
I’m Weslie!
I had you take a delivery not too long ago!
I didn’t.
Did you misremember the number?
It’s not six,
it’s nine!
Hold on;
does your company
have another swordfish courier?
Of course not.
We have another one thousand swordfish couriers.
Undersea Express is all ours.
More than one thousand?
Then how am I supposed to search?
You’re looking for courier number nine?
Do you know which way he went?
Our delivery system is very sophisticated, you know.
Each courier has a record of each stop.
That’s odd; Sea Turtle told me that he went east.
Weslie!
Hello, Sea Turtle.
You ran off before I finished telling you the direction!
That’s not okay, you know!
I’m sorry.
There he is!
There’s been a traffic accident ahead; please take a detour.
These are the consequences of reckless driving.
I wouldn’t want a second vehicle to meet the same fate.
There really is a second vehicle!
Weslie,
you must watch the road carefully from now on.
I’m sorry.
Oh no!
There’s not much time left!
Remember to come back to get your ticket!
A third?
Found it!
Number nine, stop!
What do you want?
Not you guys.
Not you guys, either.
You!
Mr. Swordfish, where’s my delivery?
It’s already been delivered;
no need to worry!
Finally done!
Are you juggling, Slowy?
No, no, I’m not.
Why do you have so many packages?
Mr. Slowy!
Weslie?
The lightning fruit is still in the parcel!
There are only three minutes left!
Then hurry and open the parcel!
What are you guys doing?
My parcels are still in there, too!
Don’t just open them!
No,
there’s no way we’ll have enough time!
Toss all of them out!
No!
Why are you guys throwing out my parcels?
There’s a lightning fruit in them, you know!
Plus, it’s about to explode!
Why don’t we evacuate instead?
Wait a minute!
Wilie’s still asleep in his room!
And my clothes,
face masks, shoes, hats,
jewelries, family photos, frying pans…
I have to take them all!
But we’re out of time!
There’s only one minute left!
I’ll go get Wilie!
Weslie, is there really nothing else you can think of?
I can’t think of anything!
Calm down, Weslie!
Think closely for any particular detail!
Detail?
Juice!
Hurry and find the parcel with juice on it!
Okay!
Found it!
Throw it out!
Time’s almost up!
What the heck?
Who would be so inconsiderate and throw stuff around?
What the…?
I’ll be back!
End