Sparky’s Tooth Filling
The Ocean Star fragment is right up ahead!
I’m also ahead of you!
The fragment is mine!
No, no, no.
What’s yours is this midnight black bomb!
Back to you!
Goodbye!
As long as I get rid of the coral in the way,
I’ll get to the fragment!
I forgot yet again that my Morning Sun can only repair stuff.
The Ocean Star fragment is mine!
There’s nothing I can’t break through!
I refuse to believe that this won’t work!
Wolffy,
you’re going to destroy the entire coral forest that way!
Why do you care?
I’ve dealt with Wolffy at last.
However,
without getting through the coral,
I still can’t get the fragment.
Sparky,
what are you doing?
Sawyer?
I’ve got it!
Sawyer,
I’d like you to help me chew through these corals.
You’re amazing, Sawyer!
Then I’ll keep going!
Your—Your teeth!
I lost a tooth.
It’s all my fault!
Don’t worry, Sawyer!
I’ll make sure to help you get your tooth filled!
It’s all that Sparky’s fault!
Thank goodness the fragment is still here.
However,
how am I supposed to get past these corals?
This is…
This is Sawyer’s tooth?
Aha!
His teeth are so strong;
if I can gather some more,
I’ll be able to break through the corals, won’t I?
I’m such a genius!
Sawyer,
just leave the tooth filling to me.
But Sparky,
can you really fill a tooth with this?
Sorry,
I grabbed the wrong tool.
Here, Sawyer,
open your mouth.
Ouch!
I haven’t even started yet;
how could it hurt?
It’s my foot that hurts!
Sorry.
Let’s start this over.
Open your mouth!
All done!
Really?
It’s just a fake tooth
attached with invisible tape, is all.
It’ll fall out with just a small touch.
I guess we have to find a professional dentist
when it comes to tooth fillings.
Dentist?
I have an idea!
Disguising myself as a dentist
is the best way to get Sawyer’s teeth!
Doctor!
Here they come!
Hey, you two!
You two,
do you have any tooth-related issues?
My friend here needs a tooth filling.
There’s an actual dentist?
My clinic just opened today;
tooth fillings are buy one, get one free!
Satisfaction guaranteed!
You must be a new dentist, right?
Today is Teeth Care Day;
all services today
at undersea dental offices
are free!
This bastard is stealing from me!
Right, right!
I forgot that today was Teeth Care Day!
Not only are our tooth fillings free today,
but they also come with a phone credit bonus, too!
Fill one tooth, get fifty!
Fill two teeth, get three hundred!
The more you fill, the more you get!
Sparky,
which dentist is better?
Let’s see.
Regardless of whether you have a cavity,
an overbite,
or wisdom teeth,
I guarantee that your problems will be solved
with me, the dental king, around!
Nothing to worry about!
Words don’t prove anything.
Sir,
your teeth require fixing.
All done!
Amazing!
We choose you!
I’ve lost.
Alright;
if you need the tooth filling, come with me.
I’m old; I’ve hurt my back!
Sir, could you help me get to a doctor?
Of course!
What about us, then?
I’m still here, aren’t I?
Doctor,
do tooth fillings hurt?
It’s just filling a tooth;
of course it won’t hurt!
But
how come when I look at you,
I…
I keep feeling super nervous and scared?
That’s just a misconception you have about us dentists.
I’m—I’m sorry.
I flail around when I get scared.
I’m good now.
You can go ahead.
Don’t worry;
it’ll be quick!
Here,
open your mouth!
I’ve tied up my entire body this time.
It’ll be fine this time.
Really?
Don’t lie to me this time!
Come on.
You seem way too nervous.
Here,
have a sour plum and calm down.
I’m very sorry.
Doctor,
I’ll be sure to control myself.
Tooth extraction is way too dangerous with regular methods;
now is the time to rely on technology!
My painless tooth extraction plums
will cause teeth to shed by themselves
as long as it touches them!
This way,
it’ll be a breeze for me to obtain Sawyer’s teeth!
This plum was so sour that all of my teeth fell out!
Wolffy!
If I turn these teeth into a weapon,
I’ll be able to break through the corals
and get the Ocean Star fragment!
I’m sorry.
No matter what,
I’m going to get your teeth back!
Sparky!
I just knew that Sawyer’s teeth were useful;
I dug to the fragment so quickly!
Wolffy,
give Sawyer’s teeth back!
Sure!
I’m giving you the teeth;
why don’t you want them?
Stop fighting!
Get away!
I’m going to get your teeth back!
Don’t hurt Sparky!
You—
You see?
Thanks to me,
all of your teeth grew back, Sawyer!
No need to thank me;
I have to go!
Goodbye!
Sparky,
I got the fragment back for you!
Sawyer,
how did your teeth grow back again?
We sharks have five or six rows of teeth.
The tooth I lost today was just from the outermost row.
Once the outermost row of teeth is lost,
the teeth from the inner rows will move into the empty spaces.
Then that means you don’t need tooth fillings!
Right.
I kept trying to find a chance to tell you.
The truth is, my teeth will be fine even if I don’t fill them,
but thank you, Sparky!
End