The Piranha Queen
This is the trending undersea dress!
Is it beautiful?
It’s so beautiful!
But what kind of fish is the pattern supposed to be?
Look out the window, you guys!
Such cute fish!
How come they eat everything?
It’s way too dangerous here;
let’s get out!
Those submarines are so particular;
they must be very tasty!
We’re eating those tonight!
Weslie, these fish run really fast!
They’re already catching up!
There’s also a bunch ahead of us!
Move out of the way!
Oh no, the submarine’s broken!
You have nowhere to run now!
Look!
I found an entrance here!
Go inside and look!
Look,
there’s movement!
This is…
a mermaid!
Mermaid?
Might she be the legendary mermaid
who lures in the enemy with her song
and then eats them?
Defeating the enemy without even moving?
Amazing!
You’re our idol!
Can you be our queen?
I… I’m not—
Your Majesty,
it’s all our fault for ruining your submarine!
We’re going to repair your submarine right now!
What should I do now?
Oh no!
We lost Tibbie!
Let’s go back to find her!
Wolffy’s coming towards us with a school of fish, too!
Get out of the way!
Wolffy, what are you doing here?
How would I know?
I finally had a chance to come search for fragments,
but then these fish started chasing me!
Here comes my oversized torpedo!
I can’t believe they ate my torpedo!
I’m going to capture all of you!
There’s no use!
These fish eat everything;
plus, they’re very speedy!
Why don’t we collaborate for now
and escape from here first?
Do you have any ideas?
Got it!
Wolffy, I’ve already distracted the piranhas.
It worked!
Wolffy,
what are you doing?
I said I would trap all of the piranhas,
but I didn’t say that I’d let you guys go!
Release us right now!
Uh-oh!
Goodbye, little goats!
Your Majesty,
this is our Piranha Village.
What a unique village.
I wonder how the repairs on my submarine are going.
Please wait;
our mechanic is checking it over right now.
Does repairing a submarine require that many fish?
You have no idea
just how much the people of our village
like to do things together!
We rest together,
exercise together,
and eat together!
Do you have to eat such a small thing together?
No, this is for you to eat.
It’s meal time!
Thank you.
What kind of food is this?
This is our most delicious food,
fish balls!
I don’t like to eat that!
Then what do you like to eat?
Goats…
Goats obviously—
Goats?
You like to eat goats?
No, no, I don’t!
I’m saying that goats obviously like to eat grass!
Fellows,
Her Majesty says that she’s eaten goats before!
What should I do?
Your Majesty, your submarine is all fixed up!
I have to hurry out of here to go find them.
I have to go; goodbye, everyone!
Your Majesty, wait!
You haven’t eaten yet!
I don’t want to eat;
you guys can eat alone.
Your Majesty, this is your favorite food!
Won’t you have some?
No.
Since Her Majesty doesn’t want to eat any,
then let’s split up these goats and eat them!
Eat goats! Eat goats!
Eat… goats?
Wait!
You guys can’t eat them!
You’re right;
Her Majesty must be full
before we can eat.
Look, Your Majesty!
This goat is plump and tender;
it must be very tasty!
Exactly!
No, no—
He…
He’s too fat;
I’m worried that I’ll get fat!
How about this one, then?
This goat is neither fat nor greasy; it must be very tasty!
Exactly!
He… He’s too thin!
I’m worried he won’t be enough!
How about this one, then?
This one is right in the middle;
it’ll surely fit your tastes!
Exactly!
He’s too firm;
I’m worried I can’t chew through him!
Then—
Stop!
I don’t want to eat!
Then what does Her Majesty like to eat?
I like to eat green grass cake!
Green grass cake?
Where’s the green grass cake?
We piranhas never eat green grass.
Who exactly are you?
I…
I’m a goat! I’m not a mermaid!
I won’t hurt my friends!
How dare you lie to us!
I just want to be together with my friends!
Tibbie!
I’m sorry.
I can’t rescue us.
That’s not true;
we saw everything just now.
You’re the bravest goat.
But we’re about to get eaten!
Even if we’re eaten,
we’ll still be together.
How touching!
So brave,
as well as undying loyalty to friends!
That’s exactly like the spirit of our tribe!
Release them!
Are you still willing to be our queen?
Apologies,
but I can’t be your queen.
I have to go with my friends to find fragments.
We need to go now;
otherwise, Wolffy will get to the fragments first!
Wolffy?
Is that the wolf who trapped us just now?
We won’t spare him!
Come on, we’re going to find Wolffy!
The fragment is all mine!
Drop the fragment, Wolffy!
Oh, it’s you,
Weslie.
Us, too!
Even if you guys attack together, I’m not afraid.
With my five cannons,
not one of you is escaping!
Let’s start with Tibbie!
Protect Her Majesty!
It’s you guys again?
What’s going on?
Now’s our chance, my friends!
Magic assembly!
I’ll be back!
We did it!
Thank you guys for helping us get this fragment!
Your Majesty, we made some treats for you.
Have them on the road!
Don’t worry, we know that you guys don’t eat fish,
so we made you guys seaweed balls.
Thank you!
It’s getting late;
we’re about to leave.
Come visit us sometime!
I will!
Goodbye, Your Majesty!
End