A Glutton’s Trouble
—My seagrass pancakes!　—My dried seagrass!　—My seagrass donuts!
Weslie, all of my snacks are gone!
Do we have mice here or something?
This has happened a lot recently;
good thing I set up mouse traps.
So you were the big mouse that ate everything!
I’m sorry.
Seaweed snacks are just too good.
You can have it back.
How am I supposed to eat it when you’ve bitten it?
It’s all about friendship.
A fragment discovery!
It looks like a fragment is around here somewhere!
Let’s split up and search for the fragment;
meet back here in two hours!
Usually, you and I are together, Weslie.
Why did you leave me behind today?
You always eat my lunch whenever I’m with you.
Exactly.
If we’re with you, we always come back hungry.
Fine.
I’m so hungry.
If only there were seagrass everywhere.
There really is seagrass!
Paddi, why did you bite me?
I’m sorry, I was eating
and didn’t notice you.
What’s there to eat?
Can I have some?
Seagrass.
This is bad!
You ate all of the seagrass I worked so hard to grow!
I won’t make the delivery on time.
Okay, okay,
I’ll help you grow some more seagrass.
Really?
Did you guys find the fragment over there?
No.
I wonder how Paddi is doing.
Is he okay?
I think he’s definitely okay;
don’t worry!
Since Paddi really likes seagrass,
let’s gather some for him!
I always run into you guys whenever I search for fragments.
Good thing I’m prepared this time!
This is the special deep-sea seagrass.
It’s different from ordinary seagrass.
Just throw it in mud,
and it’ll quickly take root and grow!
Not only does it grow fast,
it can regrow itself!
So cool!
I’ll go plant over there; I’ll leave this part to you.
Make sure not to eat these seagrass sprouts!
I won’t eat them!
No, no!
Eat me! Eat me!
No!
I promised Quilly that I won’t eat them!
They grow so fast!
This is so easy!
All done!
I wonder if Quilly is done planting yet.
Quilly, I’m done planting!
How about you?
You planted so fast, Paddi!
I’m almost done, too!
Let me help you out.
We’re back, Paddi!
We didn’t find any fragments,
but we brought a lot of food for you!
Why hasn’t Paddi come back yet?
Paddi isn’t in trouble, is he?
We should go look for him.
All done!
Yay!
My boss will be super happy!
Thank you, Paddi! I’m going to deliver it now.
You’re welcome!
I’ll go search for fragments now, too.
Goodbye!
Wolffy,
here’s the seagrass you wanted.
Pretty good.
Wolffy, what are you laying out this seagrass for?
You don’t need to worry about that.
Just help me keep an eye on this seagrass!
No problem; leave it to me!
Paddi, why are you back?
I came to look for fragments.
Did you?
Why are you holding my lunch, though?
I’m sorry, your seaweed biscuit smelled too good.
You ate my lunch!
How am I supposed to keep an eye on this seagrass with an empty stomach?
How about I keep an eye on it for you
while you go look for food?
Really?
Okay!
But you have to promise me that you won’t touch the seagrass
or worse, eat it!
Rest assured!
I’ll go, then.
Paddi!
Weslie!
It’s alright, everyone; this is just seagrass, is all!
Just bite through it!
Why is this seagrass so weird?
Think of something, Paddi!
Oh, yeah!
I can just eat it all in one bite!
When it comes to eating, Paddi’s still the best.
There’s an Ocean Star fragment near here!
It’s over there!
Let’s hurry and find it!
You lied to me again, Paddi!
The fragment is right there!
It looks like the fragment is stuck inside.
Seagrass cake!
I can’t get to it!
Can’t get to it?
Help me!
Don’t worry, we’re coming to help you!
Oh no, I dropped the fragment!
Paddi still can’t get rid of his gluttony!
Wolffy!
I’ll keep the fragment safe;
goodbye!
What should we do now?
I’m sorry, it’s all my fault for being a glutton.
It’s okay, we’re not blaming you.
Let’s think of a way to escape!
Quilly!
Paddi, why did you eat all of my seagrass just now?
You got tricked, Quilly.
That was a trap.
Paddi only ate the seagrass
to rescue us.
I see.
Since you did it to help your friends,
I forgive you.
Why don’t we have a feast?
Sure, I’ve been wanting to have a feast!
The fragment is all mine now!
What’s the matter?
Wolffy,
give the fragment back to us!
You’re already caught up?
Full speed ahead!
Darn it, we’re losing him!
Let’s assemble, Weslie!
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Don’t you run, Wolffy!
You think assembling is going to do anything?
Just wait until I fling you guys away!
Have a taste of my seagrass bombs!
Dodge it, Weslie!
I’ll be on my way!
With all this seagrass, the submarine can’t move.
Leave the seagrass to us, Weslie!
Then go ahead, you two!
Let’s start, Quilly!
I’m so full.
I can’t eat any more.
The seagrass is all cleaned up;
it’s time for revenge!
Yeah!
What’s going on?
He’s off balance!
Now’s our chance, Weslie!
Tibbie,
load up the seagrass missile!
Seagrass missile loaded!
Now!
Fire!
The whole thing is out of order!
I’ll eat, too!
I’ll be back!
Paddi,
we’ve prepared a secret gift for you two!
You can take your eye masks off now!
Okay!
More seagrass?
End