The Birthday Gift
I found another treasure!
What a great deal!
That Uncle Crab really won’t even pass up garbage, huh?
Wolffy, is the food done?
It’s done!
The goats’ decorating isn’t bad!
Alright!
We’ll truce for today
and throw an unforgettable birthday party for Wilie!
You’ve already said that more than ten times today.
Have it?
Daddy,
I’m back!
Happy birthday, son!
Thank you, Daddy!
Do you like the surprise we set up for you?
Yes!
Daddy prepared a secret gift for you;
Daddy,
what’s inside the gift box?
You’ll see very soon!
Wolffy, why is it empty?
I’m just kidding.
I’ll go get the actual gift right now.
Where did I put it?
Where? Where did I put it?
Wilie’s present is ready!
Looks like it’s time to clean up, too.
What a great deal!
The gift must be with Uncle Crab right now!
Wilie,
Daddy will get the gift very soon!
Daddy!
Open up, shell!
With all these treasures,
I should be able to make a good profit!
Uncle Crab!
Open the door;
I’m taking back my stuff!
All the stuff inside the shell is my stock;
do you want to buy it?
You still want me to buy it?
Yep.
Uncle Crab!
I threw away a shell flashlight this morning,
but now, I regret it and want it back!
Sure, that’ll be three clamshells!
Amazing; thank you!
Here’s three clamshells; give me the gift box!
Your gift box costs thirty clamshells.
How come others only need three clamshells,
but I need thirty of them?
They say that terrestrial items are more expensive than undersea items
and cost thirty clamshells.
How dare you!
Do you really think some stupid door can stop King Wolffy?
It won’t stop me!
Uncle Crab,
I must get my tennis shoe back today!
I support you!
Nobody can stop me!
Unstoppable! Unstoppable!
I know how this door opens!
Open up, shell!
It’s “Open up, shell,” right?
I better find some other switch instead.
Found it!
My store only listens to me.
Just give up.
I won’t give up!
Then don’t blame me.
Well, Wolffy?
Do you want to give it a go, too?
You think King Wolffy would be afraid?
However, I suddenly remember that I have some other stuff to take care of,
so I’ll let you off the hook today!
How am I supposed to get inside the shell?
Uncle Crab loves to collect garbage!
I’ll just disguise myself as “garbage” for him to collect!
Lovely!
It worked!
I’ve found a treasure!
This will definitely work!
I’ve never seen such a big bottle cap before!
Even “You win a free drink” is written inside!
I’m so lucky today!
I can’t anymore.
This rock is so unique!
I can turn it into a toilet and sell it!
I’ve finally done it!
Mr. Slowy, it’s been a while.
The ice cream cake is slowly melting.
Melting?
What now? The ice cream cake is melting!
Why are you more worried than Wilie is?
How about
we cut the cake now?
No!
I want to wait for Daddy to come back!
I’ve finally made it inside!
What the heck?
The inside of this shell is so weird!
Calm down, calm down!
What’s important right now is finding the gift!
Found it!
How do I open this door?
Open up, shell!
But…
What should I do?
It should be okay if I stand a little farther back.
Open up, shell!
It worked!
If we don’t cut the cake soon,
it’ll melt completely.
So now what?
Don’t worry, everyone.
I’ve already put the ice cream cake into the refrigerator!
It won’t melt now!
Refrigerator?
Wolffy already turned our refrigerator into an oven!
What?
It’s all my fault.
What now?
How do I get out of here?
The door’s open!
Wilie, Daddy’s gift is coming!
I’ve collected a lot of treasures today!
Oh no, my store!
Wilie’s gift!
Got it!
I got out!
That was dangerous.
My store!
Wolffy?
What are you doing down there?
I… I can explain!
Did you fall down there because you tried to recover my stuff?
You’re such a kind person!
Yeah, yeah.
Throw me a rope!
Okay!
I’ll throw you a rope right now!
Catch!
Why did you throw the entire rope down here?
You’re supposed to hold the other end!
Oh, yeah.
Don’t worry!
I’ll make sure to hold on to the other end this time!
Catch!
Come on up, Wolffy!
Hold it securely!
Okay!
Securely!
Wolffy, are you okay?
Wolffy, what’s wrong?
Wolffy, answer me!
I don’t want to speak to that crab ever again.
Wolffy!
Wolffy, why are you ignoring me?
If you don’t answer me,
how am I supposed to know how you’re doing?
How am I supposed to rescue you?
Now that you’re down here, who’s going to rescue us?
Don’t worry, I have a solution!
There we go!
I’m never trusting you again!
Didn’t expect this, did you?
My shell can fly, too!
That’s cool,
but could you fly a little bit higher?
Alright!
Where do you want to go, Wolffy?
Right now, I just want to go home.
It’s Sirius!
Just stop right up ahead!
Stop?
My propeller doesn’t stop!
Then… Then what?
We’re crashing!
You’re back, Daddy!
Yep, Daddy’s back!
Can you let me get up first?
Oh, my… my back!
Why did it take you so long to get back?
The cake’s already melted!
Don’t be mad!
I’ve recovered the gift for Wilie;
it’s a Super Cake Maker that I made especially for Wilie!
Let’s all work together
to make Wilie a birthday cake!
Okay, let’s make a cake together!
What an awesome cake!
Thank you, everyone, for making me such a beautiful cake!
I hereby declare
that Wilie’s birthday party shall now begin!
Happy birthday, Wilie!
End