Little Conch, Big Tornado
Don’t—
Don’t stop!
What a thrill!
How cool!
How—
How dirty!
Who did that?
Tell me what flavor of banana chips these are;
they smell so good!
It’s not good that people keep littering.
Weslie,
is the tornado fun?
The ride operator is sick,
so it’s closed today.
That’s unfortunate!
Jonie kept saying that she wanted to go on that ride.
By the way, where’s Jonie?
Didn’t she get back on her submarine to get her ticket?
Why isn’t she back yet?
Don’t worry;
the parking lot isn’t far.
She should be back soon!
Careful!
Thank goodness you didn’t bump into them.
Look.
Just now, you almost bumped into
these little newborn fish.
Thanks for stopping me.
You’re welcome.
Are you sick?
I’m okay.
I’ll get better once I find the whirly grass from Lotus Mountain.
But Lotus Mountain is very far away from here.
It’s okay.
Goodbye!
I’ll give you a ride!
Daddy, are you here yet?
The photo studio opens at eleven!
It’s only ten o’clock;
we’ve got time!
Wolffy,
Wilie is really looking forward to today’s family photoshoot.
You can’t be late!
Got it; I’ll be right there!
A fragment?
Might there be a fragment on Rainbow?
There’s still an hour left; that’s enough time to get the fragment!
I’ll be there a little later;
you guys have fun for now.
Okay, then.
Actually, I can get to Lotus Flower by myself.
It’s okay;
when I’m done giving you a ride, I’ll still have time to go to the amusement park.
You’re so kind.
Tibbie and the others are surely having a lot of fun.
Run!
Conch, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I’m okay.
My shell is very tough.
That’s good.
We better get out of here.
The fragment should be in this direction!
Help me!
What a thrill.
The whirly grass is right at the top.
Then let’s get up there!
Let me do it instead.
Wait right there for me;
I’ll climb up and get it for you.
Thank you!
The fragment is right up ahead!
That’s odd;
is the radar broken or what?
Move, please.
Not here?
Maybe…?
So the fragment is on you!
Why isn’t Daddy here yet?
Daddy promised you, so he’ll be here.
Son!
Daddy!
Who are you?
Sorry!
Daddy, I’m over here.
Son!
Daddy will definitely come!
Conch,
I found the whirly grass!
Conch!
Where’d he go?
Are these…
Oh no, they’re Wolffy’s footprints!
I don’t know anything about “fragments!”
I have a way to make you hand over the fragment!
Well?
Where’s the fragment?
My foot—
Your foot?
Don’t kick your feet!
Where on your foot is it?
If you kick one more time,
King Wolffy is going to be mad!
You’ve gone too far!
I really don’t have any “fragments!”
Still making excuses?
What the heck
is happening?
Conch,
I’m here to rescue you!
Jonie,
you’re here to steal the fragment?
Sirius!
The final shot!
Conch!
Conch, how are you?
Are you okay?
Don’t worry.
Like I said,
my shell is very tough.
I got the whirly grass.
Eat it!
A fragment!
I feel much better!
Conch,
how did you eat a fragment?
I must have accidentally swallowed it
while I was working or something.
I’m always choking on random litter.
What do you work as?
—I—　—I knew there was a fragment!
Hand it over to me right now!
My cough is gone now;
I’ll show you what I can do!
What—What’s going on?
This—This doesn’t make any sense!
I’ll be back!
Conch,
how did you do that?
The truth is,
I’m the tornado ride’s operator at the amusement park.
Would you like to try my tornado?
I can’t take any more; I had too much fun today.
I swear,
I’m not going on any more rides, no matter how fun they are.
Sadly, Jonie couldn’t make it.
Surely, she’s not happy.
Awesome!
Jonie?
This is so fun!
We want to ride, too!
Our family photo
turned out so well!
What’s the matter, Wilie?
Why isn’t Daddy here yet?
Did he forget the time?
It’s okay, Wilie.
Daddy will be here soon.
Wolffy,
how dare you be late
and miss our appointment!
Help!
Daddy,
you’re finally here!
That’s for sure; your old man always keeps a promise!
Come on,
get ready for the photos!
Here,
look at the camera!
Ready?
One,
two,
three!
End