The Mystery of the Sea Monster
It’s Tibbie’s voice!
Tibbie, what happened?
Weslie,
some garbage got my submarine dirty!
Look,
it’s right here!
It’s too dirty!
I just wiped my submarine yesterday;
now it’s gotten all like this!
I thought something bad had happened.
There’s a sign of fragments!
Let’s go!
I want to clean my submarine before going.
Alright; I’ll head off, then.
Finally all clean!
What happened?
The sea monster is coming!
Sea monster?
That’s right! He’s terrifying!
What does it look like?
He has a pair of eyes that shoot fire,
two nostrils that shoot water,
and a ten meter long tail!
No fish that has seen him
has ever come out alive!
Then how did you escape?
I haven’t seen him.
There’s the fragment!
My fragment!
Weslie said that the fragment is somewhere around here.
Where is it, though?
The fragment!
Stop!
I found that fragment first!
Trying to steal my fragment, huh?
There’s no sign of any fragments over here.
I wonder how Tibbie is doing.
Wolffy?
Thank goodness I was quick enough.
Wolffy, what are you doing here?
Have you got something else up your sleeve?
I’m not going to let you succeed!
You think?
Says who?
My friends aren’t far!
You’re talking about Tibbie, right?
She’s probably already been eaten by the sea monster!
Sea monster?
Tibbie!
Don’t worry!
I’m here!
Thank you so much just now.
Tibbie!
Who is this?
Wolffy just told me that—
That I got eaten?
What exactly happened?
Well,
Lightning Angel!
No!
So he was there to help you?
Yes, but unfortunately, I lost the fragment.
I’m glad you’re okay!
I’ll be on my way.
Where are you doing?
I don’t know,
but whenever people see me, they get scared.
I don’t want to scare them.
That’s odd;
why are you covered in garbage?
Actually, I’m an undersea cleaner.
I clean the garbage that’s under the sea.
Because of some mishaps,
I turned into this.
Is that why everyone thinks you’re a sea monster?
Oh, yeah!
Why don’t we help you clean up the garbage on your body!
Tibbie,
aren’t you afraid of getting dirty?
I am;
I can’t stand even a tiny bit of dirtiness.
That’s why I think he must be even more uncomfortable.
I want to help him!
There wasn’t even a sea monster to begin with, I see!
Wolffy?
It’s all you guys’ fault that I couldn’t get the fragment!
King Wolffy is very angry!
What do you want, Wolffy?
Of course, I’m going to—
The fragment!
Could it be…
It must have fallen onto him just now!
What’s up with Wolffy?
I was wrong.
Cleaning up garbage is everyone’s responsibility;
let me help you guys!
Why is Wolffy so motivated all of a sudden?
What are you guys waiting for?
Hurry up and come help!
Alright.
Now’s my chance!
Labor makes you feel good!
The fragment is mine at last!
Sorry.
Why?
I just want to get a fragment, is all!
Why is it this hard?
I can’t just give up now!
What are you guys looking at?
Go clean the garbage!
Why do I feel like Wolffy’s acting weird?
Weslie, look!
There’s some force sucking the garbage back!
Maybe you guys found the location of the converter?
What’s a converter?
It’s a machine that suck up garbage
and converts it into renewable energy.
Since it broke,
and I couldn’t take it off,
my body got covered in garbage.
But the converter’s been covered in garbage for some time now.
We need to find out where it is first.
My foot is stuck!
Wolffy,
the suction power where you are is super strong,
so the converter is likely to be right there!
Take a look!
What kind of joke is this?
Why must I listen to you?
Didn’t you say that cleaning up garbage is everyone’s responsibility?
For the sake of getting the fragment,
I suppose I’ll help you out!
There’s a button here; it’s vibrating, too!
The converter is probably right here!
Your mechanician skills are so good;
maybe you can fix it?
That’s easy for you to say!
There aren’t even any tools here; how am I supposed to fix it?
There happen to be a lot of mechanical tools here!
Catch!
Slow down!
Don’t—
Finally fixed.
You’re… You’re the sea monster?
Actually, I’m a manatee.
The converter is all fixed now;
it shouldn’t turn you into a sea monster again!
Thank you guys so much!
And Wolffy, too!
Where’s Wolffy?
I don’t know where he went just now.
The fragment!
Give me the fragment now!
Right now!
No,
we can’t!
We can’t give the fragment to you!
Then you’ll be sorry!
I’ll say, Tibbie,
you’d be better off just giving me the fragment.
Put Tibbie down, Wolffy!
Brave enough to follow me, huh, Weslie?
As I said before,
you’re no match for me!
But I am!
You guys are so annoying!
You stupid Weslie!
This uneasy feeling…
This malice of the underworld against me…
Don’t tell me…?
Wolffy, you can have this missile back!
I knew it!
The ending is still the same for me!
I’ll be back!
Eyes that shoot fire?
Nostrils that shoot water?
And a ten-meter-long mouth?
Who told us the sea monster was scary?
The sea monster was fake;
Mr. Manatee is actually an undersea cleaner
to clean up the ocean’s garbage!
Your gadgets are so cool!
Can we help you clean up garbage, too?
Of course you can!
Yay!
Where are we going to clean first?
How about this way first?
Okay!
End