The Frigid Icicles
I didn’t think they had ice shops down here, too!
I really want some shaved ice!
Paddi,
we’re here to get information on the fragments’ whereabouts.
According to the radar,
there’s a fragment on this icy mountain.
We have to find it as fast as possible.
Okay, I’ll get a waiter and ask!
Waiter!
A cup of shaved ice, please!
Didn’t you say you’d ask about the fragments?
Won’t it be great if we eat shaved ice
while asking about the fragments?
Your shaved ice is ready.
What kind of “shaved ice” is this?
Sawyer!
Sawyer,
what are you doing in Volcano Restaurant?
In order to become a sculptor,
I decided to learn ice sculpting first,
so I’ve become an ice shaver here!
This shaved ice is so hard;
how are we supposed to eat it?
No wonder why there’s not a single customer in your shop.
It’s not my fault that there are no customers.
It’s because every year, around this time,
terrible icicles appear on the icy mountain!
Therefore, there won’t be any customers for now.
When the temperature here drops to a certain level,
the salt in the seawater dissolves
and the seawater freezes like an icicle.
Plus, these icicles move with the currents.
Wherever they go, every living being freezes to ice.
That’s why they’re now known as the “frigid icicles.”
How dangerous!
With such big icicles,
we can make lots and lots of shaved ice, can’t we?
Why are you always thinking about food?
Based on what Sawyer said,
the icy mountain has frigid icicles; that’s too dangerous!
We can’t go.
However, I saw one of the blue beads that you guys want to find
on the mountain yesterday.
What?
At the time, I was on the mountain collecting ice,
and I saw a blue bead on a block of ice.
I was going go grab it,
but…
but a frigid icicle was starting to form,
so I had to leave it.
I really want some shaved ice.
Kids,
I’ve heard about the frigid icicles.
Wolffy over here is also fearing them;
you guys set up camp and rest for now.
Wait until the frigid icicles are gone before going up to find the fragment.
Okay!
I really want shaved ice!
But Mr. Slowy told us to not run around.
Oh, yeah.
I’m just going to eat shaved ice;
I won’t be running around!
Yeah, that works!
Time to eat shaved ice!
I’m not doing anything!
I just came here for some shaved ice!
It was just an ice sculpture.
This cake ice sculpture isn’t bad.
These are the ice sculptures I made.
The one next to you
is a TV set that I carved.
That’s a TV?
I know that my ice sculptures are really ugly;
go ahead and laugh.
Actually, everyone has their failures.
As long as you keep working hard,
you’ll be just like this airplane,
flying towards your dreams!
That’s a shark.
I’ve been making ice sculptures all night,
but not one of them worked out.
I’m really just not fit to be a sculptor.
Don’t lose hope.
Let’s start with baby steps.
Try making an ice sculpture in the shape of a cup of shaved ice!
Oh, yeah!
Shaved ice is super simple;
surely I’ll be able to do it!
Just wait!
This way, not only can I encourage Sawyer,
I can also eat shaved ice!
Two birds with one stone!
I’m out of ice blocks.
I also threw out those other ice sculptures.
Now, there are also frigid icicles on the icy mountain,
so we can’t go up and collect ice.
Then let’s look in places near the icy mountain.
As long as we don’t climb up the mountain,
we’ll be fine, right?
That’s right!
Then let’s get going tomorrow morning!
Oh no!
My shaved ice glass is missing!
My jam is missing!
Paddi is missing!
What does Paddi’s disappearance have anything to do with jam?
I’ve detected that the icy mountain’s temperatures are dropping rapidly.
None of you went to the icy mountain, did you?
We’re all here,
but Paddi’s missing.
Jam, a shaved ice glass…
Wait!
Could Paddi have gone up the icy mountain to get shaved ice?
Why do I feel like it’s getting colder?
We’re right next to the icy mountain,
so it’s extremely cold here.
Let’s quickly find some ice and then go back!
There’s not a single block of ice here!
Don’t worry; we’ll walk ahead,
and we’ll see ice very soon!
For the sake of our dreams,
we must keep going!
Didn’t you say that there’d be ice up ahead?
How come we haven’t seen any after walking for half an hour?
I’m sorry.
I’m not walking any more.
I want to go back!
We’re actually already at the top of the icy mountain!
What? The top?
What now?
The frigid icicles are going to arrive, aren’t they?
It hasn’t frozen here yet;
let’s hurry up and go back!
Okay!
Then let’s hurry—
Our path back is already frozen!
What should we do?
Are we trapped here?
Are you sure you’re actually a shark?
How come you’re more scared than I, a scaredy-goat?
I’m sorry.
It’s the frigid icicles! Run!
It’s coming again!
Oh no!
Oh, yeah; we can still summon the submarines!
Come on out, Hurricane!
I was summoning Hurricane, but Thunderbolt showed up!
Does this mean that Thunderbolt likes me better
and thinks that I’m better suited to be its owner than Weslie is?
We came to rescue you, Paddi.
Paddi!
Yay! We’re rescued!
What’s going on?
It’s a frigid icicle!
Darn it, the submarines are stuck!
If you don’t get out now, they’ll break, Weslie!
Weslie!
It’s all my fault!
If it weren’t for me sneaking out here,
you guys wouldn’t have been frozen!
Paddi,
I’ll help you rescue them!
What can you do to help?
Making me a cup of shaved ice would be good enough.
Shaved ice?
That’s it!
I’m going to chew through this ice like I’m making shaved ice!
This way, we can rescue Weslie and the others!
I can’t believe you chewed through such a big block of ice!
You’re amazing!
Thank you, Sawyer
Paddi, summon your submarine!
Hurricane!
Full speed ahead back to the shaved ice shop!
Alright!
Shaved ice is actually super tasty!
Is it? Add some jam to the shaved ice,
then try it!
So sweet!
Paddi,
get on the submarines!
The frigid icicles are gone now;
let’s go up the mountain to find the fragment now!
Sorry,
I’ll join you after this bite.
Isn’t this one of the beads you guys are looking for?
It’s a fragment!
Thank you for helping us find this fragment!
I have to thank you, too.
It was your encouragement
that led me to making this first successful ice sculpture.
Really?
Where is it?
It’s these cups of shaved ice!
Look at this shaved ice; it’s just like the real thing!
It looks like I’m still fit to be a sculptor!
How could shaved ice count as an ice sculpture?
End