Paddi’s Persistence
Keep searching, everyone!
The Ocean Star fragment is right around here somewhere!
It’s just a glass bead.
Why are these all just some shiny garbage?
Found it!
Did you find the fragment, Paddi?
No,
I meant that I found fruits.
Paddi!
Everyone is working hard to look for the fragment,
yet you’re slacking off!
But it’s hard to search around here when there’s so much garbage;
besides, Weslie can find it himself.
Found it!
See?
I told you that Weslie could find it himself.
Why do we have to keep trying?
Paddi,
why would you say that?
I’ll try harder!
Please give me one more chance!
Nope.
You’ve already been fired!
See?
Who said that hard work is rewarded?
Stop making excuses!
Go search for fragments!
Fine.
Garbage again!
Don’t people have any sense of decency?
Ouch!
I’m sorry, Paddi!
I was too busy reading and didn’t see you.
Yay!
I’m injured now,
so I don’t have to search for fragments.
Oh, yeah;
I have to tell Weslie right now
that I can’t help him search for fragments anymore!
Fragments?
You mean those beads that you guys have been looking for?
Have you seen any?
I saw one this morning.
Where?
Go straight east of the coral forest for three nautical miles and turn right,
turn left through the kelp forest,
then turn right and immediately left.
Why don’t you take me there?
But I have an interview at six this afternoon,
and I have to review right now.
It’s alright; just give me directions.
It won’t disturb your review!
Let’s go!
Which way do we go now?
Right.
Quilly!
What?
I feel like we’re not being productive at all right now.
What do you think?
Didn’t you say this wouldn’t disturb my review?
You don’t have much time to review anymore, anyway.
Now you don’t have to worry about me going the wrong way,
and I can rest for a bit.
Isn’t that great?
Only for you.
Quilly, why did you hit the brakes?
That cliff behind us is following us!
What are you talking about?
This one.
This one is following us!
Quilly,
don’t be so suspicious.
This is just a normal piece of mountain.
Don’t believe me?
I’ll have Hurricane check for you.
What?
It’s Sirius?
That Wolffy!
I can’t believe he’s sneaking behind me
and trying to steal my fragment!
What are you planning to do?
Of course I’m going to
run!
Could Paddi have seen through my disguise?
Come here!
Wolffy’s going to catch us!
Let’s get out of the submarine!
Let me get something first.
What are you taking a white flag for?
To surrender.
Aren’t we getting out to surrender?
No.
We can do this…
Like this…
Paddi is definitely hiding somewhere around here.
There he is!
Come here!
I told you so.
Putting Hurricane on autopilot
and having it distract Wolffy
is foolproof!
You’re so smart, Quilly!
Although we got rid of Wolffy,
we don’t have a submarine anymore.
I’m so tired.
We’re almost there; keep going!
I’ve walked for too long; I’m so tired.
I can’t walk any more!
But we’ll be there very soon.
It won’t be hard to get through, will it?
Of course it won’t be!
Look, it’s right down there!
That was easy, wasn’t it?
We found an Ocean Star fragment!
Yay!
Now you trust that hard work is rewarded, right?
Of course I do!
Wolffy!
Good thing I quickly realized that nobody was in Hurricane
and immediately backtracked!
Otherwise,
you guys would’ve been the ones to get to this—
lightbulb?
Are you serious?
Lightbulb?
I spent three days adding a disguise to Sirius
and chased an empty Hurricane for so long!
After all this time,
all I get is a lightbulb?
I’m going to teach you guys a lesson!
You’re the one who chose to follow us!
Why are we to blame?
Outrageous!
How dare you cause trouble on Golden Barbel’s territory!
Are you out of your mind?
Who are you?
I, Golden Barbel, am famous in the district,
yet you don’t know me?
Back in the day, I—
Go away!
What do you mean, “Golden Barbel?”
Don’t just jump in and steal the show!
Outrageous!
Security!
Brother Barbel, who did this to you?
He did!
Outrageous!
I know I was wrong!
Can we have a civilized conversation
and not fire shots, please?
No!
We’re…
safe now, right?
It looks like we are.
Look out!
This is bad.
We’re trapped under the rubble!
The only thing we can do is wait for Weslie and the others to rescue us.
But then I’ll be late to my interview!
Forget it.
Doing an interview doesn’t guarantee you’ll get the job.
But what if I do?
You’re not trying to dig a tunnel to escape, are you?
Just give up.
How could you possibly dig your way out?
No pain, no gain!
What do you mean, “gain?”
Look!
Not only did we not find the fragment,
we’re trapped here!
Don’t you work super hard at your jobs
and still get fired all the time anyway?
Yes!
But if I don’t work hard,
I’m going to regret it!
If there’s even the slightest bit of hope,
I’m going to reach for it!
Paddi…
Fine.
I just want to see what kind of “gain” there is.
We did it!
Good thing we listened to you and dug a tunnel out of there!
Paddi, look!
We actually found a fragment this time!
Good thing we listened to me and dug a tunnel to escape!
Oh no, your interview!
There are only thirty minutes left;
I probably won’t make it.
You’ll have to work hard
to know whether or not you’ll make it!
Hurricane!
I’ll take you back!
A fragment?
Paddi,
how did you find it?
As long as you work hard,
you’ll be rewarded!
Did you get the job, Quilly?
Let’s go celebrate!
No thanks.
Did you not get the job?
It’s okay;
keep trying!
It’s not that.
I’m saying that I don’t have time to celebrate.
I have to go to work!
Really?
Yay!
End