A Different Kind of Treasure
A long, long time ago,
there was a group of pirates
who waged a fierce battle for treasure.
The battle raged all day and all night.
At last, it was a pirate named Big Mac
who obtained this invaluable treasure.
Suddenly,
their ships were caught in a storm,
eventually sinking to the seafloor.
What happened next?
As for what happened next,
please pay first.
Weslie, let’s go look for fragments.
This story must be fake.
Hold on!
How about fifty percent off?
Is there really a lost treasure?
Of course
there isn’t.
I’ve already followed the map and looked for it;
the treasure map is fake.
I knew it was fake.
Wait!
Look, you guys!
Look,
there’s a hidden path here!
There really is a treasure!
I’m going to be rich!
Wait a minute.
The treasure’s location
is very close to the fragment’s location!
Then let’s go treasure hunting at the same time!
Two birds with one stone!
No!
I can’t let them get to it before I do!
I’m a pirate! The treasure is mine!
No, it’s mine!
I have to think of a way to get rid of them.
Oh, yeah! I’ll lie to them that I have to use the restroom!
—Hey, uh—　—Uncle Crab,
we’re going to use the restroom.
Let’s go together!
You have to go to the restroom together?
Right now, we’re adventuring.
No matter what we do, we’re doing it together!
The restroom idea didn’t work.
Oh, yeah! I can say that I’m hungry and will look for food!
Hey—
Weslie, I’m hungry.
Great, I can help!
I just knew you would be!
Look, I’m prepared!
Uncle Crab, what did you say you were helping with?
Helping with eating!
What’s goin on?
It’s likely an earthquake.
This is very normal.
Let’s hurry and finish treasure hunting.
How unlucky; there’s garbage all over the place here.
Even my radar is broken.
What now?
It’s Weslie and the others!
Here we are!
Let’s go!
Why is the photo in the middle different from the others?
This is creepy!
We better… We better get out of here!
No!
The treasure must be right up ahead!
It’s a pearl!
Wait a minute! There might be a trap!
A trap?
How could that be?
So there is a trap!
Hurry, think of something!
Check
to see if there’s a switch!
This is so creepy; the statue moves!
It stopped?
It’s going faster!
Do we have to find the correct pose
for it to stop?
Hurry!
Hurry, we can’t hold on anymore!
How in the world does it work?
Why is the photo in the middle different from the others?
Might it be the one in the photo?
It looks like we’re safe.
What is…?
Might this be
where the treasure chest is?
I have to find the treasure chest before they do!
Look out!
This place is very dangerous;
you have to stay with us, Uncle Crab.
Right, we’ll protect you!
This place is a huge mess;
finding it is hard!
The radar shows that the treasure and the fragment are both here.
Just search!
My beloved treasure,
I’ve finally found you!
I can’t let the goats know!
Oh no!
It looks like my flying setting is broken!
Give me the fragment!
I found the fragment!
Great!
Let’s keep looking for the treasure!
Where’s Uncle Crab?
Give it back!
The fragment inside is mine!
Wolffy,
let Uncle Crab go!
The fragment is with me!
So it’s with you guys!
If you don’t want me to hurt him, then give the fragment to me!
Alright.
You can have it.
Weslie…
You’re our friend.
But he doesn't think of you guys as his friends!
Nonsense!
He found the treasure and didn’t tell you guys.
Does that count as a friend?
Is he telling the truth?
No matter what,
we can’t just not care about him!
Here you go!
My fragment!
Let’s go.
What should I do now?
Weslie, you threw the fragment off of the cliff!
Don’t you leave!
What are you doing?
If you don’t want me to hurt him, then—
Again?
Go down and get the fragment for me,
or else I’ll toss him down there!
Wait a minute!
I’ll go get it.
Don’t! I’ll do it!
Go get it!
Be careful, Uncle Crab!
I got it!
Hang on, Uncle Crab!
Wolffy?
My fragment!
You’re too heavy, Uncle Crab!
Throw some stuff out!
Still too heavy!
Throw out everything except for food!
I can’t hang on anymore!
Uncle Crab, your treasure…
It’s okay.
Let’s go.
Wait a minute!
Give me the fragment!
Otherwise,
you’re not leaving this place alive!
Run!
Uncle Crab must be very upset that he had to sacrifice the treasure.
Then let’s cheer him up!
You have an idea?
Watch this!
Uncle Crab,
you’ll cheer up with some ice cream!
That’ll only make you happy.
No thanks.
Well, let’s not waste it.
I’ll eat it.
Uncle Crab, it’s your treasure chest!
I really want to know what’s inside!
Open it, Uncle Crab!
If it weren’t for you guys,
I wouldn’t have gotten the treasure chest.
This is our treasure of friendship.
Let’s open it together!
Yeah!
Are you kidding me?
End