Sawyer’s Badge
This place is so creepy and scary.
There’s nothing to be scared of.
You’ve got me!
There’s nothing scary here.
Scaredy-cats.
It’s a fragment!
It’s a sea roach!
Scared of a roach, huh?
Scaredy-cat.
Scared to death from just this, huh?
Monster!
Who’s that?
What was that sound just now?
It’s Sawyer?
Return my fragment!
I only came to collect rocks!
This is truly the most perfect sculpture in the world!
Master Sawyer,
could I get your autograph?
No problem!
Autograph, please!
I want an autograph, too!
Ever since I started wearing this gem,
everyone has started liking my sculptures!
I’ve already failed a thousand times.
What’s this pretty gem doing here?
I can’t get distracted!
I have to work harder and practice!
All done.
I can’t believe I did it!
What happened?
How did I suddenly get better?
Was it this gem that made me better?
From now on, I’m going to wear it on my chest!
It should be around here somewhere.
Sawyer!
Sawyer?
It’s the fragment!
Sawyer!
Sparky!
Sawyer, I’d like to ask you for something!
No problem!
Here you go; my autograph!
Actually, I want—
Here’s two!
Can I have the gem on your chest?
It’s very important to me.
No problem!
Wait,
without it, I won’t be able to sculpt.
Sawyer, autograph, please!
Autograph, please!
Autograph, please?
I want an autograph, too!
Autograph, please!
Sparky has helped me before;
I don’t want to let him down,
but…
Autograph for me, too!
Where’s Sawyer?
It should be around here.
I’m stuck!
There you are, Sawyer!
That gem is very important to me.
Can you give it to me?
But it’s very important to me, too.
I could only become a master sculptor because of it.
How could that thing possibly make you a master sculptor?
But how come when I wear it,
I’m able to make beautiful sculptures?
That must be a result of your hard work.
Even though you say otherwise,
I still think it’s because of this gem.
I’m not talking to you ever again, Sawyer!
Bad news, Sparky!
Mr. Slowy,
what happened to you?
I’m very well,
but your friend Sawyer…
With this weapon,
I can snatch over Sawyer’s fragment!
I’ll think of a way to delay Wolffy.
What are you doing, Slowy?
I can’t talk to you anymore!
Go help Sawyer!
Oh no, Sawyer’s in danger!
Can I actually make a fishtail without the badge?
How could that thing possibly make you a master sculptor?
That must be a result of your hard work.
Can I still make good-looking sculptures
without wearing the gem?
So it turns out I haven’t been wearing the gem at all,
but even without it, I succeeded!
Sparky was right;
I’ll give the gem back to him!
What a cool creation!
You have nowhere to run!
Hand over the fragment right now!
Wolffy?
I’m here to save you, Sawyer!
I did it!
But
I’m still here!
I’ll rescue you, Sawyer!
Let Sawyer go, Wolffy!
Stop, Wolffy!
It’s your turn now, Sawyer!
Right here!
What do you want?
What do you think?
Help me!
Give the fragment back to me!
I got it!
Goodbye!
Wait a minute!
That fragment is very important to Sparky!
Sawyer!
Sparky!
Thank goodness I made it.
Sparky,
Wolffy stole the fragment.
That’s alright!
Let’s go get it back right now!
Darn it!
Morning Sun’s battery is too low!
Then what?
Aren’t you a sculptor?
Why don’t you sculpt out a catapult?
But I only know how to sculpt fishtails.
Fishtails work, too!
I got the fragment!
What happened?
It’s Sparky!
Don’t you try to stop me from getting the fragment!
Have a taste of my weapon!
In the end, the fragment is still mine!
Oh no!
This plan isn’t working on Wolffy!
I’m not so sure about that!
My robotic arms!
You can’t block my attacks anymore!
Oh no!
I’ll be back!
You see how good I am?
Wait for me outside;
I’ll be right back!
Okay!
I treated Sparky so badly earlier,
yet he still came back to help me.
I’m sorry, Sparky.
I wronged you.
You’re right;
all masters relied on their own hard work!
Finally, you understand!
Sparky,
do you blame me?
We’re friends;
how could I blame you?
I don’t want the fragment anymore; you can take it.
Really?
I’ll go get the fragment right now!
Sea roach!
How about I help you get the fragment?
You can successfully work hard and sculpt out beautiful sculptures.
I believe that as long as I have courage,
I can also overcome my fear of cockroaches!
So many roaches!
Sparky!
I did it!
Master Sculptor, can I get your autograph?
I became a master sculptor even without my badge!
Master, Master,
can you make a sculpture of an entire fish?
Of course I can!
Finished!
Apparently, this master can only sculpt out exquisite fishtails.
Sea roaches!
I’m still very afraid of cockroaches.
If I want to be a master sculptor,
I’ve still got to work even harder!
Keep it up; you can do it!
End