The Light at the End of the Tunnel
Wolffy,
the TV is broken!
I’m coming, Wolnie!
I didn’t realize you could do that, Slowy!
It’s nothing.
Daddy,
my toy broke.
Daddy’s the best at fixing toys!
Wait for me to go get my toolbox, okay?
You fixed it already?
You’ve done a lot, Grandpa Slowy.
Have a cup of tea!
Thank you, Wilie.
Can’t you let me show off, too, Slowy?
What’s with the blackout?
I’m scared, Mommy!
Is it because the light bulb burned out?
I’m the best at changing light bulbs!
We’re out of spare light bulbs.
Don’t be afraid, Wilie!
Daddy will go buy a new light bulb!
Just wait!
Sir,
do you sell light bulbs?
Yes.
Nope, too small.
Nope, still too small.
Nope.
Nope!
None of those!
Bring me the biggest light bulb you’ve got!
This one’s too big!
What kind of store was that?
They don’t have a single light bulb that fits.
Are you okay, sir?
If we had that at home,
we wouldn’t have to worry about blackouts!
It’s okay!
Can I borrow the thing on your head?
That’s not possible!
If I give it to you,
the tunnel won’t have light.
I’m sorry, I have to get going.
Looks like I’ll have to think of some way to get it into my hands.
The radar says that there’s a fragment inside the tunnel.
But it’s so dark inside.
Exactly.
It’s already so late;
why is there still no light in the tunnel?
It’s way too dark in there.
Since you’re all so afraid of the dark,
just let me
get the fragment this time!
What’s the matter, Sparky?
Nothing;
I’m going in!
Why is it so dark in here?
Who poked my foot?
Help!
A big sea monster in there poked me!
Is that the big sea monster you were talking about?
Sparky, what are you doing?
I’m going to get the fragment for sure this time;
wait right here for me!
I won’t be afraid of the dark this time!
How are we supposed to get out of here if it’s so dark?
Why are you guys following me?
The tunnel’s too dark;
could you lend me a flashlight?
Of course I can!
I still have a lot more!
Thank you, big brother!
Could you give us one, too?
Oh… Alright.
Let’s hurry out of here!
It’s an Ocean Star fragment!
The fragment is stuck on something.
Don’t eat me, big sea monster!
I only came in here to get a fragment!
I’m not a big sea monster.
I’m sorry, I was mistaken.
It’s okay.
Why are you so sad?
It’s a long story.
I’m the tunnel’s lightkeeper.
Many people pass through this tunnel each day.
My job is to place my glow stone right here
before it gets dark
to light up
the entire tunnel.
But today,
when I was making my way here,
a pair of hands suddenly covered my eyes!
When I opened them,
my glow stone was missing!
I see.
And the one on your head is…?
I found this one around here.
If I help you find your glow stone,
can I have the one on your head?
Of course!
This place is so dark;
how am I supposed to find the thief?
Is that…?
Come here,
thief!
It’s so dark!
Help!
I’m not scared of the dark!
You’re the one who stepped on me, yet you’re calling for help?
I’m sorry!
I’m just too scared of the dark!
So you’re scared of the dark, too?
My son is also pretty scared of the dark;
he’s still waiting for me to return.
My friends are waiting for me to return, too.
In other words,
we can’t just stay here.
Then let’s collaborate and get out of here!
Oh no!
I lost a very important item!
I’ll help you look for it!
—Found it!　—The glow stone!
—Wolffy!　—Sparky!
Stop, Wolffy!
Give me back the glow stone!
No way!
I’m a wolf! I should be the one chasing you!
If you dare bully me,
I’ll tell Village Chief!
How dare you bring up that Slowy!
He was the one who threw the light bulb at you.
He’s lying!
What should we do now?
How would I know?
I have a great idea!
Hey, big octopus!
Come get me!
We did it!
Good thing
I was quick enough for us to not get hurt.
What’s important is that the glow stone is alright.
Give me the light bulb!
You have nowhere to run!
Thank you, Sparky!
The tunnel can finally be lit up again!
Sparky’s here!
Look, everyone!
I found the fragment!
You’re amazing, Sparky!
For me, that was a piece of cake!
The radar says that there’s a fragment in that tunnel over there.
We’ll leave it to you again, Sparky!
Another tunnel?
Daddy,
you’re awesome!
The tea you made smells great, son!
I didn’t make it.
Your mom’s tea is Daddy’s favorite!
Wolffy,
if you like it,
I’ll make a few more cups next time.
There’s no way I’m drinking your tea!
End