Slow and Steady Wins the Race
Welcome to Undersea Radio.
It’s the morning news hour.
Here are today’s highlights:
The Central Park whale is surfacing.
Paddi, lock on to the whales!
Okay!
The whale is two degrees ahead of us!
How long until the whale surfaces?
Let me check.
Five minutes left!
How did you know, Tibbie?
Because Undersea Radio reported it just now.
It looks like this Undersea Radio
is even better than Hurricane.
Can we get to the whale’s head and get the fragment
within five minutes?
Yes, we can!
The fragment is mine!
Not necessarily!
Can you outrun my missiles?
That’s nothing!
Magic Submarine,
speed up!
Hey, Captain Mari! Come here!
Someone is vandalizing public facilities here!
Oh no!
Mari’s coming!
I better get out of here!
Why did you slow down, Weslie?
The whale is about to surface!
At our speed,
we’ll have time to clean up the broken corals
before catching up to the whale.
The corals are all fixed; the road is clear!
Weslie, there are only thirty seconds left
before the whale surfaces!
That’s alright!
Found it!
That was so fast!
What fish was that?
That’s a sailfish;
it’s the fastest fish in the ocean!
Look, you guys!
The fragment is on his body!
Sailfish are so fast;
how exactly
are we supposed to get the fragment from him?
Let’s go back and think.
Apparently, that sailfish is even faster than an assembled Magic Submarine.
All done!
With this Ion Accelerator
that we got from Uncle Crab,
we’ll surely be able to match Sailfish’s speed!
Uncle Crab’s stuff
just isn’t high quality.
Don’t think too much, Weslie.
That’s right; there’ll be a way!
Do you have any good ideas?
I know!
Let’s—
Let’s eat first!
Tibbie,
why are you always stealing my lines?
I’m sorry.
Have some bread and calm down.
The bread is so good today!
This is a new recipe I learned from Undersea Radio;
nori bread!
Such delicious bread
means I have to open a bottle of my treasured soda
and eat them together!
How quick!
I’ve thought of an idea!
Ocean Academy
is next, right after this advertisement.
I might not compare to Sailfish in terms of speed,
but no matter how fast he is,
there’s no way he can escape my dragnets!
Just an experiment.
None of your business.
Go on.
Sailfish is coming!
Let’s see what you can do!
What was that just now?
Whatever.
Even my dragnets can’t handle Sailfish!
Welcome back to Undersea Radio,
back again at our Ocean Academy.
Listeners,
do you know why sailfish
are the fastest fish in the ocean?
Why?
That’s because they have a strong, powerful tail fin
to help them generate a lot of propulsion.
Plus, their long, pointy mouth
breaks through water
to help them speed ahead.
I know a way to make Sirius faster!
It was him!
I have to think of a way
to get this fragment first!
Use the upgraded ion accelerator with the soda’s propulsion!
Sailfish is coming!
Ready,
go!
We’re finally caught up to Sailfish’s speed!
What’s wrong?
The soda ran out.
Now we’ll replace it with this giant soda container.
It’ll surely last longer!
Wolffy!
Just leave the Ocean Star to me!
Oh no!
Where’d Sailfish go?
There he is!
Weslie,
you can’t come up with anything on an empty stomach.
Have some bread!
Thanks.
It tastes…
funny.
It really is disgusting.
Why is the bread this time around
so different from last time?
It might be because I was impatient to bake it
and didn’t give it enough time to ferment,
so it’s not as good as last time.
Maybe that’s what it’s about; slow and steady wins the race.
I have another way to get back the fragment!
You’re currently listening to Undersea Radio’s
interactive session.
Let’s hear from this listener.
Hello.
I’m Weslie.
I have something to say to Sailfish.
Me?
Mr. Sailfish,
a very important item of mine is with you,
but I can’t catch up to you.
If you hear this,
please come to the undersea forest.
I’ll be waiting there for you!
Is Sailfish really going to come?
Sailfish listens to undersea broadcasts,
so he’ll definitely come!
He’s actually here!
Wolffy!
Mr. Sailfish is in danger!
Let’s use the Magic Submarines to rescue him!
Why aren’t you coming, Weslie?
They’re going too fast.
We have to think of something else!
Give me the fragment!
Got it!
Up next, let’s hear from our last listener.
Hello.
I’m Weslie!
Weslie, you’re such a loyal listener!
I’m sorry,
I have something urgent for Mr. Sailfish!
Mr. Sailfish,
the submarine that’s chasing you
is very fast,
but
you can use the undersea forest terrain to escape it.
Follow what I say!
Right now, turn right!
Now go up!
Oh no!
It’s a dead end!
Mr. Sailfish,
charge through!
Nowhere to go, huh?
Let’s see what you’ll do!
Just charge through?
Isn’t that a dead end?
Charge through!
When I tell you to U-turn, do so immediately!
Okay!
U-turn now!
Yay!
Thank you for rescuing me, Weslie.
This is yours.
I have to thank you as well, Mr. Sailfish!
I learned that slow and steady wins the race!
Weslie,
come have some bread to celebrate!
Tibbie baked these fresh,
and they were fermented for enough time!
Try some!
It’s so good!
My friends,
I’m busy, so I’ll get going.
Goodbye!
Our fragment container is on Sailfish’s body!
Wait!
Weslie!
Slow and steady wins the race…
End