The Boys’ Hero Dream
Help!
Give me the fruit basket!
Stop!
The Warriors of the Sea?
Mind your own business!
My friends, we attack together!
I overestimated myself.
Are you okay?
Thank you,
heroes!
You’re welcome;
protecting everyone is our duty!
So cool!
We want to be heroes, too!
Tibbie’s in danger!
What’s the matter, Tibbie?
I accidentally broke a cup.
According to the radar,
a fragment is somewhere around here.
Let’s work hard together!
Wait;
why are you three dressed up like that?
Oh… Nothing.
Alright!
Let’s split up and go search for the fragment!
Okay.
Starting now,
we must discreetly ensure the safety
of Tibbie and Jonie!
Warriors of the Sea, let’s go!
Weslie, Weslie,
have you noticed any danger on your side?
We’re safe for now; no sign of danger.
How about your side, Paddi?
Safe.
Sparky!
Start up, Morning Sun!
Scary!
Oh no, Tibbie is currently in danger!
Don’t hurt Ti—
So it was just a little fish.
Help me!
There’s air spewing everywhere;
how am I supposed to get through?
Let me help you!
Not every hole is spewing air;
watch me find a safe path!
You’re amazing, Paddi!
Follow me!
I didn’t count on it spewing oil!
Watch this!
Hero’s Pike!
Hero’s Armor!
Watch this!
Seaweed Baozi!
Their gadgets are so cool.
I finally know why we can’t be heroes!
I know why, too.
It’s because
I’m hungry.
It’s because our gadgets aren’t big enough!
Now, our submarines have both offense and defense;
incredibly powerful!
We Warriors of the Sea,
here we go!
I wonder where Tibbie and Jonie went.
Could they be inside the cave?
Then let’s hurry inside and check!
Look, it’s their submarines!
Tibbie and Jonie are in danger!
Oh no!
It took Tibbie and Jonie away!
Why are there so many?
Leave it to me!
I’ll distract them;
you two go after Tibbie and Jonie!
The armor is too heavy;
Thunderbolt can’t accelerate!
Sparky,
could you please take off my armor quickly?
Okay!
I forgot I’d changed Morning Sun’s mechanic abilities
to destructive abilities!
Don’t go!
Oh no, they’re already gone!
Paddi, activate search mode!
I removed the search antenna
to add new gadgets.
What?
Now what do we do?
It’s all our fault for being impulsive
and causing Tibbie and Jonie to get kidnapped.
I don’t want to be a “hero!”
I just want Jonie and Tibbie to come back!
Thank you guys for saving me!
No need to thank us;
it’s what we’re supposed to do.
When I grow up,
I want to become a hero like you guys!
As long as you have a desire to protect others,
you, too, can be a hero!
That’s right!
We have to get it together!
We have to protect our friends!
Alright!
We Warriors of the Sea,
here we go again!
This is another one of the devil rays’ caves;
Tibbie and Jonie are right here!
Then let’s hurry up and get going!
Any more delays,
and Tibbie and Jonie will be in even more danger!
Alright!
Proceed as planned;
I’ll distract them,
you two go and carry out the rescue!
Come get me!
What do they mean by that gurgling?
I’ll translate.
Apparently, they don’t understand what you’re saying.
Now what?
Watch this!
“Gurgle, gurgle!”
What did you say to make them so mad?
I said that one of their friends is in your submarine.
Let’s hurry inside and search!
Which way do we go now, Paddi?
There’s too much interference here;
I can’t search!
Then let’s split up!
Okay!
Paddi and Sparky should be doing well by now.
I have to hurry back!
They’re already caught up again?
Did you find anything, Paddi?
No, this place is too big.
What should we do now?
Out of the way!
How did you get back so quickly?
I didn’t mean to!
It’s a dead end!
U-turn!
It’s too late!
Is everyone okay?
We’re okay.
Weslie!
Tibbie! Jonie!
We’re here to rescue you!
Actually, you guys misunderstood the devil rays.
Don’t!
This whole thing is a misunderstanding!
I was helping a devil ray
extract a fragment that was stuck in its teeth!
Fragment?
Then why did the devil rays take you guys away?
They probably thought that we were in danger.
The devil rays have warmly welcomed us.
But due to the language barrier,
we couldn’t leave when we wanted to.
So it was our fault all along.
If only they could understand me talk.
Oh!
Paddi,
translate the situation to the devil rays!
“Gurgle, gurgle!”
Yay!
They understand!
We’ve brought snacks for you guys!
What are you guys watching?
As long as you have a desire to protect others,
you, too, can be a hero!
I guess it’s not that easy to be a hero after all.
So the reason you guys did all that stuff
was because you wanted to be heroes?
We might not be able to become the kind of heroes that they are,
but
as long as you do the best that you can do,
you’re a hero, too!
Alright, come have some snacks, everyone!
Okay!
Leave some for me, Paddi!
End