The Super Radar
Wolffy threw me out again
to fight with the kids over fragments.
I wonder if the kids can get to the fragment first.
Isn’t this the Magnetic Valley?
The magnetic fields here will disturb the accuracy of radar readings.
I can’t believe Wolffy is finding fragments so quickly!
Is his radar not affected by magnetic disturbances?
I found another five fragments!
How is Wolffy
able to find fragments so easily?
I have to get things clear!
Thank goodness he didn’t hear that.
With this super radar,
even the strongest interference
won’t get in my way!
The fragments’ locations are clear as day!
So Wolffy’s been using
a super radar that’s not affected by magnetic fields?
Nope,
I have to help the kids make a radar that’s just as good!
The next fragment is right at the top of Magnetic Mountain!
Alright; Sirius, let’s go!
Finished!
I did it!
They all failed.
It looks like Wolffy must have had some kind of trade secret
while making that super radar.
Aha!
This time,
I have to find out the trade secret behind the super radar!
Ouch!
Slowy, don’t press so hard!
Apologies; is this level of pressure better?
It’s good.
I’m willing to anything
to help the kids make a super radar!
Don’t stop!
Oh, yeah!
My throat is a little dry.
Your drink.
The house is a little dirty.
And,
look.
The window hasn’t been wiped in a while.
It’s very dirty underneath the sofa, too!
Also, the toilet is clogged!
However,
I’m just so busy!
Oh, what should I do?
I’ll do it!
Not bad!
Wolffy,
as said with the promise earlier,
can you teach me how to make the super radar now?
Of course!
The instructions are right here!
What do you mean by this, Wolffy?
Nothing.
Just telling people
that you wanted me to tell you how to make the super radar!
Stop your dreaming!
You’re not keeping your word!
How could you trust the words of a bad guy?
Slowy fell for my pranks yet again today!
Since Wolffy won’t tell me,
I’ll just have to take his radar
and reference it!
With this optical camouflage helmet,
I can become invisible!
No matter what Wolffy does,
he can’t stop me from going invisible!
So he’s sleeping?
I wouldn’t have prepared all of this if I knew.
Is that Wilie?
Is he sleep talking?
Come here, Wilie.
Here, son.
Daddy hugs you.
I’m not your son!
Here!
Don’t touch me!
Here, Wilie!
I’m not Wilie!
Son?
Son!
Wake up! I’m not your son!
Wolnie, don’t be mad.
I’ll go catch goats immediately!
The radar’s right here!
Why are there two super radars?
There’s one here, too.
There are so many!
Which one of them is the actual super radar, then?
Great!
New fragments have been discovered!
So that one is the real one.
Nearby magnetic fields are interfering,
so we’ve lost the fragment location yet again!
Recently, Wolffy has always been able to find the fragments before us.
Exactly!
It’s like he’s not getting interference from the magnetic fields!
Why is that, though?
We’ve left the magnetic field!
This time, we can’t lose to Wolffy!
Here we go!
I’m coming, fragment!
I have to find a chance
to test out Wolffy’s radar!
What is Slowy sneakily following me for?
I must get rid of him!
Let’s see if you can still follow me!
That’s odd.
Where did Wolffy go?
You can’t see me.
You can’t see me…
You can’t see…
Help!
Is that…?
Slowy,
help me!
Okay!
I’ll go find some rope!
Just wait for me!
Hurry, Slowy!
My super radar!
What’s taking you so long, Slowy?
Alright, I’m coming!
Ready!
Oh, yeah,
I have to get another one for Wolffy.
Hurry
up,
please!
Can’t you hurry up?
I can’t hold on anymore!
Coming, coming!
This one isn’t long enough.
I’m getting another one; just hold on!
I just knew that Slowy isn’t reliable!
Oh, yeah!
I almost forgot about Sirius!
Sirius!
No, don’t summon Sirius!
There are so many corals here;
the kids’ submarines can still manage to get through,
but your Sirius is too big!
It’ll get caught on the corals!
Why didn’t you say so?
What are you doing?
I’m helping you grab your radar.
Can you let me try it out once we get back?
You’re still worried about the radar right now?
The fragment is nearby!
Help!
That’s Mr. Slowy’s voice!
You guys, Mr. Slowy is in danger!
Then let’s hurry over there and rescue Mr. Slowy!
Okay!
Hold on, Mr. Slowy!
I’ve got the radar at last!
You’re seriously still worried about the radar right now?
My strand of seagrass is about to break!
Then what now?
If I’d known better, I would have used that thicker piece of seagrass!
If there was a thicker piece, why didn’t you use it?
You’re the one who rushed me!
Oh no!
Paddi!
On it!
We’re okay.
Thank goodness we made it on time.
I crushed the radar!
Although Wolffy’s radar shattered,
I went by what was left of it
to figure out the trade secret behind its immunity to magnetic fields.
So
I’ve turned our radar into a super radar!
You’re amazing, Mr. Slowy!
We don’t have to worry about magnetic fields anymore!
Who knew that Slowy would’ve broken my fifth generation radar?
I’ll have to just use my sixth generation.
End