The Great Body Swap
What’s the matter, Wolnie?
If you’re going to look so ugly,
don’t sneak up on people like that!
You scared me to death!
You darned viperfish!
Stop scaring my Wolnie!
I was just passing through!
I’ll get rid of you!
Don’t hit me!
Wolffy!
I’m sorry!
He looks so mean!
You scared my child!
I’m sorry.
Wolnie, if he ever scares you again,
use this pepper grenade against him!
What if he still doesn’t leave?
Then use this ultra-high-power fan to blow him away!
What if that still doesn’t work?
Then use my ultimate plan,
the high-pressure water cannon to blast him away!
With all of these ways to defend against him,
I feel safe now!
The radar says that an Ocean Star fragment is nearby.
Why have I run into that viperfish again?
A fragment?
Wait!
Don’t hit me!
Stop!
I’ve got the fragment!
Oh no!
Look, it’s an undersea shooting star!
It looks like it’s coming towards us!
What are undersea shooting stars?
Undersea shooting stars are a special phenomenon here.
It’s said
that scary things happen
wherever the meteor lands!
Isn’t that where we are right now?
What’s the matter?
Wolnie?
Wo—
What’s wrong, Wolnie?
Ultra-high-power fan!
I—
I’m Wolffy!
Wolffy?
Still trying to fool me?
Look in the mirror and see for yourself!
What…
What the heck?
Undersea shooting stars are a special phenomenon here.
It’s said that scary things happen
wherever the meteor lands!
Could it be that I swapped bodies with Viperfish
because of the undersea shooting star?
Looks like it’s time for Wolffy’s ultimate plan!
Wait—!
Oh no;
where the heck did the fragment go?
Hello.
Wo—
Wo—Wolffy!
Don’t eat me!
I saw that you dropped this earlier.
Be careful next time.
What’s wrong with Wolffy?
You’re so mean that you scared my son!
You’re lookist!
I’m suing you!
Still talking back even after scaring my son?
I’ll take care of you!
You—
Wolffy,
where have you been all day?
Come home with me right now!
Wolnie!
Where’d he go?
I saw him run that way.
All clear; he’s gone.
Come on out.
May I ask what happened, sir?
Please help me, kids!
Here it is.
So you’re saying that you and Viperfish swapped bodies
after being struck by a meteorite here?
Goodness;
that’s unbelievable!
Do you guys trust that he’s actually Wolffy?
I trust that he’s actually Wolffy.
Mutton…
Sorry,
it’s a wolf instinct.
I just can’t resist when I stand too close to you guys.
I’ll be more aware next time.
Found it!
The record book says
that if two people are struck by an undersea meteorite at the same time,
they’ll swap bodies.
However, if they’re struck again by another meteorite,
they’ll go back to normal.
According to the undersea phenomena forecast,
the next appearance of meteors is tomorrow.
But that viperfish has already taken my handsome body;
there’s no way he’ll be willing to switch back!
You guys have to help me out!
There’s no way we’re going to help you;
you and we are enemies!
Sparky’s right;
you always ruin things for us!
Hey, don’t be like that!
If you guys don’t help me,
what if that viperfish uses my body
to wreak havoc everywhere?
Even if you hadn’t swapped bodies with Viperfish,
you’d still go around causing trouble.
Let’s just help him out.
It’s not like we can just leave the two of them like this.
Thank you, Weslie!
And that’s the deal, Mr. Viperfish.
Therefore, as long as you’re struck by a meteorite again tomorrow,
you guys can swap your bodies back.
I promise you guys
that come with you tomorrow.
Great!
You better keep that promise!
What’s with all the noise here?
Why are you back, you viperfish?
Wolnie!
♪ Oh so sweet / Your smile is oh so sweet ♪
♪ Just like the flowers that bloom in the spring ♪
How do you know that song?
It’s the poem I’d written for you
on our first date.
Do you remember the question you’d asked me back then?
If your mother and I fell both into the water, which of us would you save?
I’d said that we wolves are born able to swim,
so you guys can just swim to shore!
That’s right!
Only Wolffy could give
such an unromantic answer!
Are you actually Wolffy?
Of course it’s me, Wolnie!
Because of an accident,
I got turned into a viperfish!
But tomorrow,
I can go back to this attractive, intelligent self!
Mr, Viperfish,
try this ball!
Mr. Viperfish,
how about you play this round?
Not covered well enough!
What if you cause my body to catch a cold?
It’s time, Viperfish!
Let’s go!
Where’s Viperfish?
Viperfish?
Viperfish!
Darn it!
Viperfish escaped!
We’ve split up to look for him;
if you have any updates on your end,
tell us right away!
Got it!
I just knew that that viperfish was up to no good!
Without my original body,
I can’t even drive Sirius anymore!
Once I find you, I’ll make you see—
Oh, there you are!
Come back here!
You have nowhere to run,
you fish liar!
I’m sorry!
Help me!
Hold on tight!
I’m not going to let you escape again!
I’m sorry!
Of course you’re sorry!
You don’t keep your word!
I look too mean,
so everyone gets scared when they see me.
I want to play with everyone, too!
I see.
Looks like I have to help him regain self-confidence
for him to be willing to swap bodies with me.
Actually, looks don’t matter.
You coming back to rescue me
proves that you have a beautiful heart!
I’m sorry.
If I hadn’t escaped,
I wouldn’t have gotten you into this trouble.
Forget all of that!
Just get me out!
I’m not strong enough!
There you are!
It’s almost time.
You don’t have to hold onto me;
I really won’t run off this time.
Here comes the undersea meteor!
Who’s playing ball in such a time-tight situation like this?
Who?
Show yourself right now!
I’m sorry, Uncle!
The ball is ours!
No need to be so mean; we’re sorry!
Since you guys are kids,
this time,
I’ll let you go.
Undersea meteor!
It’s actually the undersea meteor this time!
Get ready!
Oh no!
This isn’t the meteor’s impact site!
What now?
Don’t worry!
There’s still a way!
I’ve got my gorgeous, handsome face back!
I just can’t stop looking at it!
Wolffy,
it’s time to eat!
Coming!
We’ve made too much lunch yet again;
if anyone wants to eat, come on over!
Mr. Viperfish,
come and eat with us!
Thank you!
End