The Boy Like the Wind
Wolnie bought so many perfumes;
I must not break them!
Daddy,
come play with my toys!
Dear son,
Daddy is busy right now.
Alright.
Catch it, Slowy!
Okay!
I’m so sorry.
You’re such a slowpoke! You’re no help!
Back in the day…
I left my backpack in the car!
Let me help you!
You’re amazing; thank you!
You’re welcome!
Someone over there needs my help;
I’ll be on my way!
I’m old.
I’m not as good as my past self.
Help!
It’s these waste fishing nets again;
they’ve gotten me so many times!
These waste fishing nets
not only destroy the marine ecosystem,
they also endanger our safety.
I’m in a hurry; I have to go!
Uncle Crab, you dropped something!
What is this thing?
Look out!
What kind of breeze is this?
I’m suddenly feeling a strong power
infuse into me,
like my whole body is full of energy!
Are you okay, Mr. Slowy?
What happened, Weslie?
There’s a fragment on that taxi!
Really?
I’ll help!
I can’t keep up;
it’s too fast!
Mr. Slowy?
That’s odd;
why am I running so fast?
Mr. Slowy,
you ran so fast just now;
how did you do that?
Could it be…
Mr. Slowy?
What is it?
It’s…
I can’t let them know that I used that thing.
It’s actually the result of hard work!
You’re amazing, Mr. Slowy!
Look like I’ll have to exercise, too!
What should I do?
What’s wrong?
I have a very important contract
that I need to get to a suburban company right away.
I’ll help you out!
Rest assured, ma’am!
I’ll make sure to have it sent on time!
Thank you! Goodbye!
My new coral tiara!
Let me help you!
Thank you!
What should I do?
So many orders;
when am I going to finish delivering them?
I’ll help you!
Shooting star fish!
But it’s too late to make a wish.
I’ll help you!
My skateboard is gone!
Can anyone help me?
Isn’t it right here?
You’re standing on it!
Oh no!
I’m too late!
Your glasses.
Why do I feel fatigued all over?
That’s because you used too much of the Super Fan.
Super Fan?
Good thing you didn’t keep using it.
Otherwise…
What’ll happen?
Death
won’t happen.
Then—
Paralysis
won’t happen, either.
Can you just tell me all at once?
Actually, you’ll get a runny nose,
chills,
hot flashes,
a sore throat,
and generalized muscle pain.
In short,
a
severe
cold!
Therefore, you must not use it ever again!
Oh, it’s just a cold.
Getting severe colds is very dangerous at your age!
Fine, then.
Mr. Slowy,
Wolffy stole our fragment container!
Thanks for the fragment container!
You’re cheating, Wolffy!
What kind of hero are you?
I’m not trying to be any sort of hero!
Fellow kids,
I’m headed out!
Weslie!
Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy,
Wolffy stole our fragment container and ran off!
I’ll chase him down!
All the fragments are mine now!
Stop, Wolffy!
Slowy, with how slow you are,
do you think you can catch me?
This world now belongs to the young wolf!
What the heck?
Wolffy, give me back the fragment container!
Wolffy, you have nowhere to run!
Really?
You guys can’t catch me!
Goodbye, goats!
What’s going on?
It looks like he’s lost control!
This is too dangerous!
We have to find a way to stop him!
Let’s hold him down!
But he’s moving too fast;
we have no way to hold him down!
Then what should we do?
Well, I have an idea…
Using this.
You’re crazy!
You can’t use that fan again!
What’s the matter, Uncle Crab?
Mr. Slowy will face very severe consequences
if he uses the Super Fan again!
Take care of your body, Mr. Slowy!
But there’s nothing else we can do.
You’re right;
I have to rely on my own strength to solve this!
Weslie, Paddi, Uncle Crab,
you guys go to the left!
Jonie, Sparky, Tibbie,
you guys go to the right!
Now!
Great job, Mr. Slowy!
My fragments!
End