The Restaurant’s Eruption
Fragment, fragment,
where in the world are you?
I’m getting something!
The fragment is located… under Volcano Restaurant?
Great!
The fragment is mine!
Why is there a button here?
Don’t press that!
Chef Octo?
Why can’t we press it?
My grandfather said
that he placed this button here
while building the restaurant,
and it’s very, very important.
You can’t just press it!
It can’t be that pressing it causes a volcanic eruption, right?
That won’t happen.
Although this restaurant
is built on top of a real volcano,
my grandfather said that this is an extinct volcano.
So rest assured, everyone.
Stop it, Weslie!
I’m sorry;
whenever I see these kinds of buttons,
I can’t help but want to press them.
Focus, everyone.
The food critic will be here any minute now.
As long as we get this critic’s approval,
then my volcano shaobing
will surely be loved!
But so far, the food critic hasn’t come yet.
I heard that this food critic has a poor sense of direction.
Don’t worry.
I’ve already sent him a map.
What’s going on?
This is bad!
There’s a big hole outside of the restaurant!
Could this be the volcano top?
Is this volcano going to erupt?
Then what?
We better find Mr. Slowy for help.
One piece of kelp,
two drops of sesame oil,
and three scoops of broth.
A good bowl of noodles!
What an expert!
Want a bite?
Maybe next time.
I’m here to ask for directions.
Do you know how to get to Volcano Restaurant?
Volcano Restaurant
is two kilometers north of here.
Thanks!
By the way,
which way is north?
This way.
Thanks!
The volcano is going to erupt soon, isn’t it?
Why hasn’t Mr. Slowy arrived yet?
My grandfather said that this volcano won’t erupt!
What now?
Chef Octo,
why don’t we get away from here first?
No.
If I leave, what about this place?
This is my home, you know!
Let’s go.
Home is a people,
not a place.
Let’s go!
You guys don’t get it.
This place
is full of memories.
My grandfather made this table by hand.
My favorite place for hide-and-seek
was this cabinet.
Look,
a childhood drawing of mine is on the inside!
It’s this one!
Therefore, the restaurant is my home.
Even if the volcano erupts,
I’m not going to move!
What now, Weslie?
Let’s see if there’s a way to stop the volcanic eruption.
Is it really possible to freeze lava with this big fan?
Looks like that didn’t work.
Let’s try ice this time.
Did it work this time?
It seems to be even worse now!
What should we do?
The problem must be inside the volcano.
Who wants to take a look inside the volcano?
Mr. Slowy!
Good thing I activated the Magic Submarine’s heat resistance
ahead of time.
For us, entering the volcano
is no problem at all.
That’s odd.
How come so many tunnels appeared
inside the volcano?
Why are there so many holes?
It’s so hot down here!
Village Chief Slowy,
didn’t you say that the Magic Submarine is heat resistant?
The submarine can function under high temperatures,
but I forgot to fix the inside temperature problem.
I can’t take anymore!
Paddi,
where do you not feel well?
His heart is unwell,
because all of his ice cream melted.
That’s odd.
The radar is obviously saying
that the Ocean Star fragment is nearby.
Wolffy?
Goats?
So you guys also found out that there’s a fragment under the volcano!
There’s a fragment under the volcano?
Did you guys not know?
Wolffy,
were you the one who dug all these holes?
Of course!
For the sake of getting the fragment,
what does digging a few holes cost?
So you’re the one who’s causing the extinct volcano to erupt!
It’s all your fault, Wolffy!
My restaurant is about to be destroyed!
How is your restaurant any of my business?
What?
How dare you say such a thing!
Believe it or not, I’ll—I’ll—
What?
Believe it or not, I’ll never give you a discount again!
Have I ever patronized you?
Waste of time.
I’m not playing with you guys anymore; out of my way!
Wait a minute!
It’s all because of you
that the volcano is about to erupt!
How are you going to fix it?
What can you do
if I don’t fix it?
Trying to distract me
and take the fragment, huh?
No way!
What’s that noise?
It’s my stomach growling.
No, it’s not.
Listen closely.
It’s the sound of an eruption!
I’ll be back!
He did it to himself.
All this lava will swallow the city!
I have an idea!
I’m hungry and tired; where in the world is Volcano Restaurant?
“Volcano shaobing;
“it’ll make you feel like you’re flying.”
This restaurant’s got a lot going for it!
The volcano’s lava has been directed away with the holes we dug.
Volcano Restaurant is safe!
Yay!
Weslie,
what a great idea!
By directing the lava elsewhere,
I won’t need to move!
However, directing lava to a safe place
isn’t an easy task.
Isn’t it just directing it away?
How hard can it be?
Watch this!
How did that happen?
Again!
Another location!
There better not be anyone here!
What a cool fish!
Come look, everyone!
What’s your name?
How old are you?
Where’d you get your glasses from?
This can’t be.
The ocean might be big,
but every place has its own wonders.
Directing the lava to reasonable places
isn’t easy at all.
I know where we should direct the lava to.
Let me lead the way.
This is the volcano shaobing?
It tastes very average;
how does it give me a “flying feeling?”
Chef Octo,
are you sure you want to do this?
The best place for the lava to erupt
is, in fact, the volcano top.
But what about Volcano Restaurant?
That’s your home!
Didn’t you guys say
that home is a people, not a place?
The lava is about to erupt!
What’s going on?
Chef Octo, look!
I really am flying!
What’s happening?
I can’t believe it landed on the shopping street by itself;
that’s incredible!
Turns out that this button is a safety mechanism!
Chef Octo’s grandfather must have had the foresight
to include a jetpack
so that the restaurant could fly away when the volcano erupted.
Great, Chef Octo!
Your restaurant is okay!
Yes,
but I missed the food critic.
What a thrill!
Critic,
you came!
Just like the flyer said,
it felt as though I was flying!
Really?
Amazing!
My volcano shaobing finally received a critic’s approval!
I meant that the restaurant made me feel as though I was flying,
not the shaobing.
How was the shaobing, then?
It’s hard to explain.
That’s why, while we were flying just now,
I wrote about its shortcomings.
All of the things you need to adjust
are written here.
That can’t be.
All of that?
This is just the table of contents;
the rest are over there.
Chef Octo, are you okay?
Wake up!
End