Conquering Pickiness
The kelp balls here are the greatest;
even food critic Paddi says they’re good!
Queue up!
Can’t you see that everyone is waiting?
I didn’t think that Paddi would become the current food critic!
As long as I get Paddi’s approval,
my noodles will become trendy, too!
This is my newly crafted dish.
please try it out, Paddi!
My kelp noodles are going to become the highest-selling dish!
They’re disgusting!
I hate kelp!
You… You hate kelp?
But everything I’m making right now is made of kelp ingredients!
Then that’s unfortunate.
No!
Is that a fragment?
Who are you?
So it wasn’t a fragment.
I recommend that you let go of me right now.
The radar clearly shows that there’s a fragment around here!
I’d like to tell you
that we jellyfish’s tentacles are poisonous.
My hand!
I’m sorry!
Good thing I had an antidote on me.
My handsome face is swollen this badly?
Oh, yeah.
I’ve heard that Chef Octo’s restaurant is full of kelp ingredients;
I’ve got to go get some kelp to bring down the swelling!
Volcano Restaurant, here I come!
Where did all the kelp go?
Come on, try some of my new dishes!
Strawberry cake,
banana split,
and cotton candy!
Chef Octo,
how did you make land-only food
underwater?
This is amazing!
Last time, Paddi said that he hates kelp.
I thought about it;
it must be that my kelp isn’t tasty enough,
so this time, I specially formulated
new seaweed dishes for him to try.
Paddi loves banana splits;
he’ll definitely like it this time!
You can use kelp to make so many different dishes?
Amazing!
They’re all made of kelp?
Just what I needed!
Paddi isn’t here yet,
so I’ll put these dishes in the fridge for now.
How come they’re all made of kelp?
Paddi!
Since Paddi doesn’t like it,
there’s no use in keeping this food anyway.
Goodbye, my kelp.
No!
Paddi’s way too picky.
The truth is, I think Chef Octo’s kelp dishes are pretty good.
Recently, his skills have improved quite a bit!
Wait!
Chef Octo, what are you doing?
Without Paddi’s approval,
my restaurant can’t run anymore.
I better transfer it to someone else.
We have ideas for getting Paddi to approve your dishes;
don’t transfer the restaurant yet!
Really?
You guys really have ideas?
Rest assured and leave it to us!
Then I’ll go prepare, Weslie!
Weslie,
how are we supposed to get Paddi to like kelp?
For the sake of helping Chef Octo,
there’s only one solution left.
If I disguise myself as Paddi,
I’ll get to eat kelp noodles!
If I wear this newly formulated Paddi hat,
others will mistake me for Paddi!
What’s wrong, Paddi?
I have a cold; I really want to eat noodles!
Alright; I’ll go make some right now!
I’ll help you send it over, Chef Octo.
Thanks!
How is it, Paddi?
Bad!
I can’t believe there’s no kelp in here!
How… How could there be no kelp?
Sorry; for the sake of helping you get approval,
we secretly swapped it with seagrass noodles.
You guys aren’t helping me!
That’s disrespecting me!
I respect you!
Please give me a bowl of kelp noodles!
Wolffy,
what are you doing here?
Where’s Paddi?
Paddi is in my hands!
If you want to see him, use kelp noodles to trade with me!
Don’t try anything!
You can have kelp noodles,
but you must hand over Paddi first!
Okay.
Give the noodles to me with one hand, and I’ll give him to you with the other.
Oh no!
Paddi rolled all the way over there!
Paddi!
My critic!
Wait!
Give me the kelp noodles!
What is this place?
I’ll ask for directions!
Excuse me—
Why did they run?
Paddi!
Split up and look!
Hello!
Have you seen him?
Chef Octo,
I’m begging you to give me a bowl of kelp noodles!
With how pitiful you are,
alright.
Wolffy’s in danger!
This must be a kelp noodle!
Don’t eat it!
It worked right away;
my handsome cheeks have returned!
Chef Octo!
It’s Paddi!
What are you doing in here?
I ran into the waterspout,
so I hid inside the clamshell.
After I got blown into this cave,
I was too scared to come out of the shell.
I see.
I haven’t even eaten lunch yet;
I’m so hungry!
I do have food with me,
but
it’s kelp noodles.
Noodles!
Paddi, do you not hate kelp anymore?
This taste…
The feeling of freshness like never before is just amazing!
You finally believe that my noodles are good?
Chef Octo, you made me realize
how tasty kelp can be!
Thank you for the compliment,
Paddi!
I should be thanking you for helping me overcome pickiness!
Oh no, this place is about to collapse!
We have nowhere to go!
Paddi!
Chef Octo!
There you are!
Thank goodness Mr. Slowy was quick enough
to be your substitute for the Magic Assembly!
Otherwise, we wouldn’t be able
to get inside this waterspout and save you guys!
Yay, Chef Octo!
We’ve been saved!
There are so many customers!
Congratulations, Chef Octo!
Congratulations for what?
They’re not customers;
they’re all just here to use the bathroom!
Even food critic Paddi’s endorsement doesn’t work?
It doesn’t.
“Food critics” are a fast-changing business;
there’s a new one now.
At least you, Chef Octo, have Paddi’s support!
Paddi, didn’t you hate kelp?
Nope! This is my favorite flavor!
End