The Undersea Grassland
Watch this super shot!
Let’s play badminton!
Jianzi should be fine!
I’ve found a treasure!
There are too many creatures under the sea.
It’s hard to play soccer,
and there are no fruits to eat.
I really miss life on the grassland.
This is bad!
Nothing could be worse
than how we’re feeling right now.
The Magic Submarines are almost out of oxygen!
What?
Everyone, hurry up, gather everything, and search for oxygen!
Sparky!
Where are the fragments?
Wolffy,
the starfish got my clothes dirty again!
How am I supposed to wear it?
Just bear with me.
Once I collect all of the fragments
and we head back to the grassland, it’ll be clean!
Daddy,
there’s jellyfish all over the place;
I can’t fly my kite at all!
Just bear with me.
Once I collect all of the fragments
and we head back to the grassland, you can fly it!
Wolffy,
Sirius is almost out of breathable oxygen!
Just bear with me!
Once I collect all of the fragments
and we head back to the grassland, we can breathe!
What?
Found the nearest supply point.
Let’s go!
Go right!
Slowy, what are you doing?
The path on the right is shorter;
go right!
The path on the right is too dangerous;
going left is safer!
Right!
Left!
Look in front!
Fruits!
They’re so good!
The air is so fresh!
Come look, everyone!
Beautiful!
Is this Green Green Grassland?
This doesn’t look like a grassland.
Mr. Slowy, what are you doing here?
What is this place?
Weslie, you’re here, too?
Wolffy’s here, too?
We ran into some trouble.
It was all your fault, Slowy!
I can’t believe there’s such a place under the sea;
this is so cool!
This must be just a regular cave.
Because the oxygen generated by undersea plants has gathered,
a dry area has accumulated in the cave.
Over time,
the conditions become right for all kinds of plants to grow here,
naturally forming an undersea grassland.
Does everyone understand that?
It’s wonderful here!
Let’s go play!
Are we going to play soccer first?
Brother Goats,
let’s play together!
Okay!
It feels like we’ve returned to Green Green Grassland!
This is bad!
This place is so good; what’s bad about it?
The oxygen here can’t charge the submarines!
What?
We have to find a different supply point.
We were lucky to find such a good place!
Plus, the submarines are almost out of oxygen.
Going out is very dangerous!
Why don’t we stay a few extra days?
I don’t want to leave this place!
But this place isn’t our grassland to begin with.
Only once—
Only once we collect the fragments
and solve the undersea crisis
can we return to our own grassland!
This place is so relaxing!
Going out without oxygen is indeed dangerous.
You guys, don’t take the risk.
I’ll go search for oxygen.
Mr. Slowy,
we’re coming too!
Kids?
We’re a family!
We’re all in this together!
Daddy, they’re leaving.
Are we not going?
It’s so dangerous out there;
of course we’re not going!
This cave is so creepy!
The supply point is near the cave;
let’s keep looking.
Mr. Slowy,
why have we still not found the supply point?
Let’s keep going ahead and see.
Mr. Slowy,
the submarine’s oxygen is almost out!
Uh…
Maybe we should just go back!
We don’t have enough oxygen to go back.
Let’s keep going!
The map shows that it’s right here.
Let me do it!
Not quite!
Oh no, the cave is collapsing!
Charge out of here!
We can do it!
Staying here is so good;
who’s venturing outside?
Daddy,
come help me!
What’s wrong?
My kite is stuck.
That’s easy; watch this!
Daddy!
Don’t worry, it’ll be alright!
Look, Daddy!
The kite fell off!
Daddy’s amazing!
See? It’s easy!
Son, be careful while playing.
Flying! Flying!
The kite is flying already?
Son!
How is Wilie flying as well?
Sirius!
Mommy! Daddy!
Son, don’t be afraid!
Daddy’s coming to rescue you!
Wolffy,
drive faster!
Even faster!
Just a little more!
Keep going!
We did it!
What’s going on?
Oh no, Sirius is out of power!
Mommy! Daddy!
Son!
What’s happening?
Wolffy,
we’re back!
Save my son!
Leave it to me!
Yes!
The oxygen is almost finished charging!
The big undersea grassland is gone;
what a pity.
Don’t be sad, everyone.
The faster we collect the fragments,
the sooner we can return to Green Green Grassland,
our actual home!
A fragment has been detected!
It’s eight hundred nautical miles southeast!
Let’s go!
The fragment is ours!
End