The Housekeeping Battle
Wolffy!
What’s the matter, Wolnie?
Why is the house so messy?
You better clean up the house
by the end of today!
Yes, understood!
Wolnie, all done!
Are you?
Is this how you do housekeeping?
Do it again!
Yes.
What’s with all the mess?
You old goat,
you’re in charge of housekeeping now!
I’m busy with my experiments!
So clean!
How are you doing the cleaning, Slowy?
This is a housekeeping workout I just learned!
Not only can I do housekeeping, I can also work out!
Why don’t you give it a try?
We’ll go look for fragments this time!
You guys are in charge of housekeeping, then!
No problem;
leave it to us!
Let’s get cleaning!
Alright!
Why isn’t it coming off?
Here comes the stain remover!
Why is cleaning up so hard?
When Mr. Slowy does it, he looks so relaxed.
Housekeeping is so exhausting.
Why don’t we go to Mr. Slowy for help?
Yeah!
Hands in the air!
Circle your left hand twice!
Circle your right hand twice!
Great job! One more time!
Wolnie,
look!
I made this corset just for you!
If you weigh yourself while wearing it, you’ll lose twenty jin!
Go on, try it!
What’s the point of false weight?
I don’t want it!
I’m learning the housekeeping workout!
Didn’t I ask you to do the housekeeping, you old goat?
Why is Wolnie doing them, too?
This housekeeping workout is actually very effective!
Why don’t you give it a try?
No way!
Daddy!
Wilie, you want Daddy to play with you, right?
Look, Daddy!
Grandpa Slowy gave me these scrubbing skates!
They’re so much fun!
Daddy!
What is it, my son?
I’m going to help with housekeeping!
Mommy, look at how clean I swept the floor!
Isn’t it just housekeeping?
I, Wolffy, can do that, too!
Even doing the dishes can produce such a wonderful melody!
What’s the big deal?
I can do it, too!
Out of my way, you old goat!
Wolffy,
all you do is mess things up!
Wolnie, give me another chance!
No.
Your way of housekeeping is just stuffing things elsewhere
and covering up dirty places.
It’s nowhere near as good as Slowy’s.
Just you wait, you old goat!
What a big, big robot!
Scared, huh, old goat?
This is my housekeeping robot invention,
Super Cleaning Buster!
Clean up the kitchen!
Daddy, your robot is amazing!
Old goat, your housekeeping workout is already outdated;
my robot is the actual King of Housekeeping!
Robot?
I have one, too!
What?
Come on out, Scrub-Scrub!
What can such a small robot do?
Concentration is the essence!
Then let’s go to another place and compete!
Go, Daddy!
Go, Grandpa Slowy!
Who are you rooting for, son?
I’m rooting for both!
Bring it on!
Go! Go!
You’re going to lose!
I’ve still got another plan.
Hyper-speed scrubbing mode, activate!
Amazing!
It cleaned everything so quickly!
Looks like Slowy’s robot isn’t all that bad,
but neither is mine!
Is there anything we missed?
I can’t let Slowy find it first!
There’s still a dirty stuffed animal!
Super Cleaning Buster!
Scrub-Scrub!
Super power mode, activate!
No matter what, get it back!
Mr. Slowy is in danger!
Kids, don’t!
I got it!
How about that, Slowy?
Have you given in?
Where’d they go?
Mr. Slowy, why did you guys start fighting?
We weren’t; we were just having a housekeeping battle.
Housekeeping battle?
What’s wrong?
Just for you guys, I made
this housekeeping robot!
All the housekeeping problems can be dealt with one by one!
This is great; we don’t have to do housekeeping anymore!
Start up, housekeeping robot!
Getting ready to start cleaning.
Yay!
You three, hurry up and scrub the window,
sweep the floor,
and wipe the table!
This can’t be!
End