A Dreamy Honeymoon
How beautiful!
Wolnie!
Wolnie,
this is my gift for you.
Wolffy!
Wolnie,
Wolnie!
Wolffy?
Wolnie,
it’s time to eat!
You ruined my good dream!
What… What kind of dream?
A honeymoon dream.
Ever since we got married,
you tell me every year that we’ll go on our honeymoon!
Where is it?
Well, uh…
We’re adventuring under such a beautiful sea;
isn’t that basically a honeymoon?
Look at those beautiful fish!
I don’t want this!
I want a real honeymoon!
Wolnie,
there are a lot of honeymoon destinations in here.
Choose one!
Dreamy Forest?
I choose this one!
The name makes it sound like a perfect place for a honeymoon!
“Ten Forbidden Places in the Ocean Where You Can Enter but Not Leave:
“Dreamy Forest!”
This place is too dangerous, Wolnie!
How about we go to another place for our honeymoon?
No! I want to go there!
Wolnie,
how about we watch some TV
to see if there are any good places?
Dreamy Forest,
the unforgettable honeymoon spot!
What a nuisance.
Let’s look online instead.
Look,
there are so many honeymoon packages online!
Hello, sir.
Our company has recently added
some great deals on Dreamy Forest honeymoon packages!
Recently, there’s been a lot of random people
coming here to advertise.
Let’s keep looking to see
if we can find other suitable honeymoon places.
Wolffy,
do you not want to go on a honeymoon with me?
It’s not that!
But that Dreamy Forest really is very dangerous.
Whatever! You just don’t want to go!
I’ll go by myself!
Wolnie!
Dreamy Forest?
I can’t believe there’s such a beautiful place under the sea!
Why don’t we go check it out?
Don’t.
The magazine says that that’s the most dangerous place in the ocean!
We’re just going for a look!
But we have more important things to do!
It’s just around the corner, anyway.
We’ll look for fragments on the road.
Wait!
You want to stop us, too?
No!
We have to go together.
What did you say?
Because there’s a fragment in Dreamy Forest!
According to the information,
the first dangerous place on the route to Dreamy Forest
is the coral bushes.
Although Dreamy Forest is beautiful,
it’s dangerous!
A variety of corals will trap nearby targets!
There’s no easy way to escape.
How beautiful!
It’s just like my dream!
Wolnie!
Did you finally decide to come along, Wolffy?
Where’d he go?
Maybe it was just me?
Wolnie,
I’m over here!
I can’t believe Wolffy said
that such a beautiful place is dangerous!
The truth is, he just didn’t want to go on our honeymoon!
Don’t you dare hurt Wolnie!
This coral is so unique!
How cool!
There must be even more interesting things up ahead!
You think I can’t call for help if I can’t defeat you on my own?
Sirius!
Looks like the signal is too weak here;
I guess I’ll rely on myself.
Watch out, everyone!
Up ahead are the dangerous coral bushes!
What?
It’s so beautiful;
how is it dangerous?
This is different from what the information said.
From the looks of it, someone else has already been here.
Let’s still keep our guard up following this.
I think, following this, we’re going to…
fill our stomachs first!
You only think about eating;
can’t you check the information first?
Next up, we’ll run into a smack of jellyfish.
Jellyfish tentacles are highly poisonous.
If you get stung, you’ll get poisoned!
Should we still keep going
if it’s that dangerous?
Maybe we should just go back.
We should be okay as long as we’re careful.
Plus, we’re already almost to the destination;
turning back now would be awful!
Alright, then; let’s keep going.
How beautiful!
They’re so pretty!
Wolffy, look!
I forgot that Wolffy didn’t come with me.
Wolnie!
Look, it’s me!
I think someone called me just now.
It’s so cool that these jellyfish chase and play with each other!
It looks like the destination is up ahead!
But…
Wolffy’s not here;
would it still count as a honeymoon?
There are jellyfish all over the place;
be careful as we’re going ahead.
I’ve been poisoned!
Ouch!
Paddi, are you okay?
Where’s Tibbie?
How cute!
They’re not dangerous at all!
I’m fine?
Aren’t these jellyfish poisonous?
How come they’re also different from what the information stated?
These jellyfish look like they’ve been knocked out.
Weslie,
didn’t you say that it’s very dangerous here?
I don’t know what’s going on,
but there really is danger coming up!
Right, Paddi?
Right.
Next up is the center of Dreamy Forest.
The center must be the most dangerous part, right?
According to the information,
the forest’s center is a beautiful and safe place.
It’s so beautiful!
But unfortunately, Wolffy isn’t here.
Wolnie, I’m here!
I happened to pick up a gem, too;
it’s yours now!
Why did you only come now?
What were you doing earlier?
Sorry, Wolnie.
I had something to do and ran late.
Wolffy?
Wolffy,
why are you injured all over?
Could it have been Wolffy
who subdued those dangerous creatures?
That’s unbelievable!
So it really is very dangerous here?
No wonder we didn’t run into any
of those dangerous creatures our entire way here.
So it was you who was secretly protecting me the whole time!
How am I supposed to wake him up?
The information states that there is an antidote nearby!
Let’s split up and look for it!
Madam Wolnie,
stay here and wait for us.
We’ll be right back once we’ve found the antidote!
I’ll leave it to you guys, then.
What?
All of these could be the antidote?
We could confirm the antidote’s location,
but we didn’t know which plant it was,
so I brought back all of the ones that could be the antidote.
Is there any other information about the antidote?
The information states that the antidote tastes sweet.
Then we can taste them one by one!
But there are some plants that are poisonous;
it’s too dangerous to do it that way!
I’ll do it!
Wolffy did so much for me;
I just need to save him!
Madam Wolnie, do you feel unwell at all?
This one tastes very sweet!
Great!
I didn’t think we’d find it that quickly!
But I accidentally swallowed all of it by accident.
Quick, everyone! Look for an identical plant!
Found it!
Wolnie, why are you crying?
Why are the goats here, too?
Wolffy!
Careful! I can’t breathe!
We seem to have forgotten something.
Oh, right! We still have to find the fragment!
Then let’s hurry up and go!
Wolnie,
are you sure you want to have our honeymoon right here?
Really?
You don’t regret it?
As long as I’m with you,
it’s a honeymoon wherever I go!
But,
Wolnie…
I would really prefer a different place!
End