The Mystery Box
Weslie,
come here!
Come get me!
Come on!
Why did you guys turn Jonie’s room into such a mess?
Exactly.
Aren’t you guys tired of running around?
Paddi,
you need to keep clean, too!
Whenever Mr. Slowy isn’t here, you guys are always fooling around.
Tibbie,
you’ve done so much already;
let me take it from here.
Jonie is so good at housekeeping!
You three should at least give her a hand.
It’s almost Children’s Day;
can’t we relax a bit?
Jonie,
what’s with this box?
That’s Mr. Slowy’s box;
he said that we can’t touch it!
But I really want to know what’s inside of it!
Maybe there’s food inside!
Mr. Slowy?
Kids!
Mr. Slowy,
are you not busy today?
Why is everything such a mess?
The house belongs to everyone;
when I’m not around,
Jonie—
Jonie, from now on—
Why did it suddenly cut off?
Move, Slowy!
Why don’t you go somewhere private to make a call?
You’re blocking the TV!
My communicator is malfunctioning;
can I have ten minutes?
I mean, you could.
Thank you!
You have to do the chores for me first, though!
You think I can’t find another communicator?
This one is so cheap!
This one is so beautiful!
Wolnie?
Wolnie!
Go away, Slowy!
I’m busy trying to get deals!
Go!
Get rid of the bad guys!
Wilie,
could I borrow your tablet for a second?
Grandpa Slowy,
how about I give it to you after I’m done watching this cartoon?
How long will that be?
Not that long;
just an hour!
Slowy,
you could have just agreed earlier!
What did Mr. Slowy want Jonie to do just now?
He must have wanted me to watch over everyone!
Let’s clean up the rooms.
Okay!
Paddi, what are you doing?
I really want to see what’s inside of that box.
But Jonie’s right here;
we can’t get close to it.
Let me try!
Didn’t I just get rid of this cardboard box?
What is the trash can doing over here?
Don’t go near the box again!
Mr. Slowy said not to touch it!
Are you guys really that curious about that box?
Well, aren’t you curious?
There must be a delicious cake inside!
A cool robot!
A celebrity-signed soccer ball!
Then let’s only take one look.
Do we really want to open the box?
Why not?
What… What’s this?
All that secrecy.
I thought it was some kind of food.
Why did Mr. Slowy put an egg-shaped thing
inside of here?
We better put it back.
I want to see, too!
Thank goodness.
Could it be food?
What? It’s not edible?
Oh no!
What happened?
Did you guys touch Mr. Slowy’s box?
Sorry.
What’s making that noise?
It looks like we activated a bomb!
There are thirty minutes before it explodes!
What?
Let’s hurry and throw it out!
What I meant was
to throw it out to an empty place.
No,
there are too many civilians here!
Then let’s go find some other empty place.
Jonie, what are you doing?
We’re out of time!
I’ll take Rainbow to dump it in some middle of nowhere!
We’re coming too, Jonie!
No!
The bomb is too dangerous;
you guys just wait for me here!
Finally done cleaning!
I’ve finished cleaning;
can I borrow the communicator now?
So quickly?
Did you clean up everything?
Not even a speck of dust!
Nope;
I can’t give in to Slowy just like that.
Look, it’s Weslie!
Where?
I don’t see him.
I must have been mistaken,
Also, look.
You haven’t fully cleaned the place yet!
Do it again!
You cleaned up so well, Wolffy!
Of course I did!
I do my best to give my wife
a comfortable environment, you know!
I haven’t finished wiping.
Fine, fine.
Go somewhere else!
Kids!
Mr. Slowy!
Jonie!
What’s wrong?
Uh…
Jonie drove off alone with Rainbow to take the bomb elsewhere.
The bomb?
Why didn’t you guys go with her?
Jonie obeyed your orders
where you said for her to take care of us,
so she went alone.
When did I say that?
Jonie—
I wanted her to supervise you guys while you’re housekeeping.
How could I let Jonie alone to—
I’m not finished yet!
There’s not a single person here;
I’ll let it detonate here!
Come and see!
You can’t miss it!
There’s a big sale going on!
Big discounts!
Why did so many people suddenly show up?
I’ve got to… I’ve got to get back to Rainbow!
Excuse me!
Free snacks!
Jonie, we’re here to help you!
Didn’t I tell you guys
to wait there for me?
We’re a family, though!
We can’t let you face danger alone!
Exactly!
Let’s work together to get rid of the bomb!
Rainbow!
Watch this!
Oh no!
It’s counting down!
It’s going to detonate soon!
There’s a chasm up ahead;
let’s throw it to the bottom!
Then let’s assemble and speed up!
Magic assembly,
unmatchable energy!
No, we’re out of time!
Is everyone okay?
We’re okay.
Good thing we got rid of the bomb in time!
Mr. Slowy?
Kids, are you okay?
We’re okay!
We worked together with Jonie
to throw the bomb down a chasm!
That’s good,
but why did you guys have a bomb?
We wanted to ask you
why you left a bomb with us.
What?
Didn’t I tell you guys not to touch that box?
Those were my Children’s Day gifts to you!
What?
I wanted to make it a surprise.
Where’d you go?
We’re getting them back right now!
My Children’s Day gift!
Mr. Slowy?
Did everyone get the gifts back?
Mr. Slowy, all our gifts got broken!
Could you send another one to us?
Alright, alright!
Thank you, Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy’s gift arrived!
Let’s open it and see!
How come they’re all cleaning supplies?
You guys got the gift, right?
Mr. Slowy,
what did you send us these cleaning supplies for?
Didn’t you say you’d send the gifts again?
Just wait, everyone!
If you want your gifts,
you’ll have to clean up your rooms!
This can’t be!
End