Electric Eel Power Bank
Finally, Slowy’s gone for the time being!
I can peacefully search for fragments now!
Is that a fragment?
It’s so far away, though.
Not enough power?
There’s no way I can get to that place!
It’s Uncle Crab.
Oh, yeah!
He might just have some kind of charger!
Wolffy,
what are you doing here?
My Sirius is almost out of power,
and I wanted to see if you’re selling anything I can use to charge it.
Oh, so you came to buy?
Well, that’s great!
This is a terrestrial solar-powered charger.
As long as there’s direct sunlight,
it can generate lots of electricity!
Charging your Sirius with this will be a piece of cake!
Great!
Hold on…
What about under the sea, where there’s no direct sunlight?
Well, then…
Then…
it’s certainly not going to work.
Don’t worry!
Try this wind-powered charger!
As long as there’s wind, you’ll have infinite power!
We’re under the sea;
there’s no wind!
Oh, you’re right, Wolffy.
Why hadn’t I thought about that?
Never mind.
I’ll just think of something by myself.
Wait, I also have this!
It’ll definitely be useful when there’s no power!
This looks quite promising!
Of course it is!
Once your Sirius is out of power,
just turn it on
and watch cartoons.
That way, you won’t be bored.
It’s dead?
Bob!
Come here!
It’s dead!
Can this fish produce electricity?
Bob is an electric eel;
of course he can.
I’ll take him, then!
My friend,
I see the fire inside of you.
It’s time for you to show us what you’re made of!
Why don’t you work for me?
Let’s get started right now!
Come on!
Mr. Wolffy,
can I eat first?
I’m very hungry!
Oh, Bob,
when it comes to work,
one does not simply think only of what they can receive.
One must first consider what they have given.
The power is not yet fully charged,
yet you want this and that?
That’s not the proper mindset of a young man!
But I didn’t even eat breakfast today;
I’m so hungry right now!
If you’re hungry,
think about your dreams.
How can you reach your dreams if you don’t persist?
Here.
Keep it up!
You can do it!
Why did you stop?
Is he actually out?
But Sirius should already have enough power by now.
That means you’re useless now!
I have some bad news.
We’re almost out of power!
Then let’s hurry and find a place to charge!
I have some good news!
What is it?
It’s lunch time!
Paddi,
look around for a charging station!
We need to charge the Magic Submarines first!
Fine.
What’s the matter with him?
I’ve checked him over.
There are no signs of injury on his body.
But why does he look so faint?
In my professional judgment,
it must be that he
hasn’t eaten lunch yet.
Don’t just think about food, Paddi.
Paddi actually guessed it.
Then let’s hurry and start cooking!
The submarines are already low on power;
if we use the power on cooking,
Hurricane might not be able to travel any farther.
But this fish is already so hungry to the point of passing out!
Exactly!
I’m almost about to pass out, too!
Oh, yeah!
Let’s put the submarines together
and share the power evenly!
Good idea!
Now,
the fragment shall belong to King Wolffy!
What’s going on?
We’re stuck!
I’m so full!
Thank you guys!
No need to thank us;
Mr. Slowy is always teaching us
to help out others in need!
By the way, why were you passed out on the road?
It was all thanks to Wolffy.
Wolffy?
Yeah.
He asked me to work inside his submarine,
and I said that I was hungry.
He just told me to follow my dreams.
In the end, I was too hungry to keep going,
so he left me on the side of the road.
That Wolffy is evil!
On the submarine, he treated me as if I were a burden,
like I was delaying his fragment search.
What?
Fragments?
Apparently, Wolffy found the location of some fragments!
Then let’s catch up to him and look!
But because of cooking,
the submarines are almost dead.
Do you guys also want to find that fragment?
I’ll help you!
You want to help?
Of course!
You guys treated me to eating,
and now, I’ve got energy!
I can help you guys charge!
Speed up! Let’s get out of here!
Here I come, fragment!
Darn it!
I used up too much power trying to clear the road!
The goats?
They’re definitely trying to snatch that fragment from me!
What?
Wasn’t Bob out?
Why is he helping them charge now?
I’ve got an idea!
Great!
Even Hurricane’s power is fully charged!
Then it’s full speed ahead!
Mari?
I’ve received a complaint
that someone here is breaching a contract.
No way!
How are we breaching a contract?
The one who’s breaching a contract is Bob!
This is the contract that Bob and I signed.
We both signed it!
His job is to fully charge Sirius,
but he never finished it
before running over to you guys!
Is that now a breach of contract?
But you didn’t even feed Bob!
The contract says that he’ll be compensated
once Sirius is fully charged.
It doesn’t say that he gets food!
But if I don’t eat, how would I have energy to charge?
I don’t care about that!
Either way, according to the contract,
you don’t get to leave until you finish charging Sirius!
Weslie,
what should we do now?
We can’t just let him bully Bob!
Follow them!
My Sirius has power again!
The goats really dare to follow us, huh?
Watch this!
Let’s speed up as well!
This won’t work!
Bob,
finish charging Sirius immediately!
I need even more power!
I’m already charging!
Then try harder!
Right now, it’s like you’re not eating!
How dare you bring up eating!
Am I not supposed to?
The contract didn’t say that I have to feed you.
The contract also didn’t say that I have to finish charging immediately!
Oh, really?
Now, with this electricity sourcer,
you’re going to charge for me
whether you like it or not!
This way, I’ll have enough power
to activate my super acceleration setting!
Since you want it,
don’t blame me!
Oh no, there’s too much power!
Stop, Bob!
Stop it!
Now!
I’m not working for you ever again!
Goodbye!
I’m so glad that Bob is safe!
Wolffy really had it coming for him this time!
But the fragment is gone now, too.
Everyone, look what I found!
It’s the fragment!
I’ll be back!
End