Magic Department Store
Weslie!
What happened?
Have you seen our game consoles?
We can’t find them!
Could it be that you guys took them outside to play
and forgot to take them back inside?
How is that possible?
Those are our treasures, you know!
There you guys are!
What are you doing with our consoles?
I saw that the consoles were a bit dirty,
so I went and washed them.
What?
Tibbie,
game consoles will break if they’re washed.
But they were too dirty!
I’m afraid that we’ll get sick from the germs if they’re unwashed!
Found it!
The fragment is in that coral forest up ahead!
Hold on.
I think this road is too narrow;
the submarines might not be able to get in.
Then let’s proceed on foot.
It’s so busy here!
Let’s hurry in!
Okay!
Wait!
What’s wrong, Tibbie?
There must be a lot of germs in that garbage over there!
Tibbie the germaphobe is at it again.
How about you guys go in and look for the fragment?
I’ll stay here and clean up the garbage.
Alright, then.
We’ll come back to help you once we’ve found the fragment.
Found the treasure!
A monster!
Tibbie, it’s me!
Uncle Crab?
What are you doing here?
I was looking for this!
Tibbie, what are you doing?
I’m getting rid of all this garbage!
You can’t!
I was planning on selling these treasures for money!
But this stuff is all junk;
they’ll attract germs if they’re not rid of!
These are my treasures!
Your shop isn’t filled to the brim
with this kind of stuff, is it?
Uh…
I’ll help you clean all of these
before you sell them.
Clean?
But you have to promise me
that you won’t pick up junk anymore!
What’s wrong, Paddi?
This chocolate ball is so hard!
Why does this piece of candy look a bit weird?
It’s the fragment!
Darn it!
I can’t believe the goats got to it first!
Let’s head back, then.
I’m starting to worry about Tibbie now.
Are you worried about Wolffy going to her for fragments?
No.
Tibbie’s so hygienic
that I’m afraid one day, she’ll think a fragment is dirty
and will throw it out!
Then let’s hurry back!
That garbage wasn’t here when we came in.
Someone must have dumped it just now.
Then let’s clean up this garbage first.
Take your time cleaning it up!
Great!
The last item is finally clean!
I wonder how Uncle Crab’s stock
is doing with sales.
Uncle Crab, are you not worried
about your stock not selling?
I’m not in a rush,
because I—
You have an idea?
I’m used to it.
This stock might take about half a year to sell out.
What?
Half a year?
That’ll attract a lot of germs!
Nope, I have to think of something.
Got it!
Uncle Crab,
let’s organize your shop!
All done!
Magic Department Store’s new opening!
Come take a look!
Why don’t you look around, ma’am?
Choose whatever you’d like!
Are these things useful?
Of course they are!
Done!
Something’s going on over there!
Let’s go over there and see!
Uncle Crab, we really like this hat!
Here!
I’m glad you like it!
Come back anytime!
Uncle Crab,
is this stuff useful, too?
Uh…
Of course they’re useful!
Uncle Crab, I need your help!
What a unique qipao!
I’m very satisfied!
Thank you!
Come back anytime!
You’re incredible, Tibbie!
We earned this by working together!
Uncle Crab,
I want this one!
Okay!
I want these!
—I want this one!　—Okay!
I want all of these!
Come back anytime!
You’re amazing at selling things, Tibbie!
Thanks for the compliment!
Uncle Crab!
We finally sold everything;
no more gathering this stuff!
Tibbie, what’s that over there?
Uncle Crab,
if you keep gathering junk like this,
you’re going to get sick!
Sick?
My health is so good;
how could I possibly get sick?
Uncle Crab, what’s wrong?
Uncle Crab!
Why am I sick all of a sudden?
The germs must have infected you.
Treasure!
What “-sure?”
Uh…
Nothing.
I meant to say, I assure you that I won’t pick up junk again.
My stomach hurts!
Are you trying to gather—
Who’s inside of Lightning Angel?
Thanks! Goodbye!
Wolffy!
All of the fragments are gone!
I have to notify everyone!
Tibbie, are you okay?
I’m okay.
I’m sorry, everyone.
Tibbie,
what happened?
I’m sorry.
I lost…
the fragments.
Did you actually throw it out as garbage?
No,
Wolffy stole them.
What?
A little trickery is all it took to get the fragments!
Give the fragments back to us!
You’ll have to catch me first!
Wolffy!
Bring it on!
Tibbie, are you okay?
We’ll take it from here!
Look out!
Get out of the way!
Darn it, he escaped.
Trying to mess with King Wolffy?
I don’t think so!
Uncle Crab?
Gathering junk at a time like this?
Out of the way!
I’ll be back!
What a beautiful treasure!
Score!
What happened?
Is that…
Uncle Crab!
What are you doing here, Tibbie?
Didn’t you say you wouldn’t pick up junk again?
I meant that I wouldn’t do it the way that I used to!
Now, I’ll wear a protective suit while gathering junk, so I won’t get sick!
I have to go; I’m busy!
I can’t believe him.
Wait a minute!
Did Uncle Crab just put the fragment container
into his shop?
Uncle Crab, wait!
It’s so busy here!
Here you go, guys.
Thanks to Tibbie teaching me new methods,
my profits are growing!
No need to thank me!
Remember, don’t just gather every piece of junk!
Uncle Crab, how much is this?
Coming!
Just one clamshell; thank you!
End