The Third Reunion Cake
Of course we must eat the Good Family reunion cakes
during the Reunion Festival!
The small one goes to the son,
the medium one goes to Mom,
and of course, the big one goes to Dad!
The whole family deserves a Good Family reunion cake!
I want one!
Daddy!
Today is the Reunion Festival!
Mommy and I prepared reunion cakes!
I can’t believe Wolnie and my son prepared reunion cakes for me!
How touching!
Son,
Wolnie,
I love you!
Wolffy, what are you doing?
What are you doing here?
Daddy,
you said to honor our elders during the Reunion Festival.
Oh, son!
You remember my words so clearly!
So,
I’ll honor you with this reunion cake!
Thank you, Wilie!
It’s my fault
that there aren’t enough reunion cakes.
I only had enough ingredients to make these three.
Daddy!
It’s not that there aren’t enough cakes;
it’s that you have an extra me.
I’ll just go back to the Magic Submarines.
Poor Grandpa Slowy.
That darn Slowy!
My son gave you a reunion cake,
yet you still dare to act so pathetically?
You help us control the pollution while on Sirius;
why would we think of you as a burden?
Here, sit down!
Daddy,
my cake;
you can have it!
There’s no need;
I don’t like to eat them.
You eat it instead.
Oh, you don’t like them?
Then I’ll go ahead!
Oh, go ahead, Slowy!
Wolnie and my son made that reunion cake for me!
I must eat it!
Today is the Reunion Festival.
I really want to spend it with the kids.
The submarines need to charge again?
What a nuisance.
If only Mr. Slowy were here.
Today is the Reunion Festival;
if only Mr. Slowy could spend it together with us!
We’re spending this year’s Reunion Festival under the sea;
we can’t even see the Moon!
Says who?
Isn’t that the Moon?
I didn’t think the Moon was under the sea, too!
The radar shows that there’s an Ocean Star fragment there!
Slowy,
you should go back and spend the festival with the goats!
The bomb could detonate at any time;
how can I leave?
The goat-wolf cube is perfectly fine;
the way I see it, it won’t detonate!
I mean, it’s the Reunion Festival!
Don’t you want to spend it with the kids?
Of course I do!
Slowy’s gone;
the reunion cake is mine now!
I have to stay here!
I can’t let you guys be in danger
just because I’m with my loved ones!
Time for plan B!
To thank you for what you’ve done for the family,
I’ve prepared these Reunion Festival exclusive dishes for you!
Thank you, Wolffy!
Bon appetit!
You won’t have room for the reunion cake
after eating all of that!
Now, the reunion cake is all mine!
This is too sweet.
Elderly people can’t have too much sugar.
This is too salty.
Elderly people can’t have too much salt.
This is too oily.
Elderly people can’t have too much oil!
Apologies, I’ll get you something else.
“Middle-aged and Elderly People’s Cookbook”?
“One Hundred Dos and Don’ts of Eating and Drinking”?
“Nutritional Dietary Guidelines”?
Alright!
Outrageous!
This dish is outrageously tasty!
Go ahead, then!
Keep eating!
Even more!
I’m so full.
The reunion cake is mine now!
Now, I can eat the reunion cake for dessert!
The big fish swallowed us!
What now?
Why is there so much garbage in the fish’s stomach?
The radar says that the fragment is around here!
Is the radar broken?
No,
it might be that the Ocean Star fragment
is hidden among this garbage.
Why don’t we get off and search?
Instead of the fragment,
shouldn’t we be worrying about how to get out of here?
We just got swallowed by the fish, you know!
Well, uh…
That’s in the “Undersea Survival Manual”
that Mr. Slowy left us!
Look!
If you’re swallowed by a big fish,
just tickle its throat,
and it’ll spit us back out!
Mr. Slowy has a lot of books, huh?
Since we have a way to get out,
let’s hurry up and get off the submarines to find the fragment!
We’ve gathered all of the garbage,
but we still haven’t found the fragment.
Help!
It’s a monster!
Don’t be scared, Paddi!
I just blew a shell, is all!
Just a shell?
I didn’t think the fragment would be in there!
No wonder we didn’t find it earlier!
Oh no!
Our oxygen is low!
We have to get out of here!
The submarines are out of power!
What now?
We can’t get out!
Let’s send an SOS to Mr. Slowy right now!
My reunion cake!
Kids,
happy Reunion Festival!
What?
I’m heading to rescue you right away!
Now’s my chance!
I’ll eat the cake right now,
and no one is going to know!
Where’s the reunion cake?
Why did I bring this with me?
Whatever!
Slowy,
at least leave the cake!
What’s taking Mr. Slowy so long?
Hypoxia alert.
I’m so sleepy.
Hang in there, Sparky!
If you fall asleep, you won’t wake up!
Weslie!
Everyone’s asleep?
I must make it through!
Stop!
Slowy,
you could have let me hold on to the reunion cake
before going to do your thing!
Let’s talk about that later.
I have to rescue the kids!
They’re getting hypoxic inside of the big fish’s stomach!
I can’t stop!
Oh, for goodness sake!
I’ll help you rescue the goats,
but you have to give me back the reunion cake!
Here’s a black pepper bomb!
Kids, here I come!
You darned Slowy!
Couldn’t you at least give me the reunion cake first?
Magic assembly, unmatchable energy!
Thank you guys.
My stomach feels much better now.
Because my stomach hurt before,
I was attacking people everywhere.
I’m very sorry.
I’m just glad everyone’s okay!
Remember not to eat whatever you see from now on!
Here,
Wolffy.
Have this reunion cake back.
Great!
I can finally eat the reunion cake
that Wolnie and my son made for me!
Wait.
You gave the cake to me, but what about you?
Me?
Of course I’m going to eat reunion cakes with my loved ones!
Happy Reunion Festival, kids!
Happy Reunion Festival, Mr. Slowy!
Come have some reunion cakes, everyone!
End