Paddi’s Great Adventure
The fragment is right around here;
let’s split up and look for it!
With so many people searching, they don’t need me!
I’ll go take a nap on Hurricane instead!
I forgot to clean again.
Who’s littering?
Finally, I can sleep!
They should be back by now, right?
I’m telling you guys, I used to be very cool!
What the heck is this place?
Excuse me…
What?
Uh, nothing!
How did I get here?
Someone help me!
How am I supposed to get out of here?
Don’t leave!
There’s food and drink in the Coral Circle;
it’s a great place to loaf around!
Who is that?
I’m under you.
Could you help flip me over?
Like this?
Who are you?
Could you help me out?
Thank you. Hello.
Everyone calls me Tortie.
You’re this old, yet you have such a childish name?
I was about your age when I first came here.
In the blink of an eye, a hundred years have passed.
What?
A hundred years?
Why were you locked up for a hundred years?
I was a litterbug and got arrested.
A litterbug?
Am I going to be locked up for a hundred years, too?
No!
Here is it!
The radar says that the fragment is right behind the coral!
But how am I supposed to get in?
There’s a hole!
I’ll help you!
I’m in!
Did I ask you to pull me out?
I’m trying to get in!
No trespassing allowed in the Coral Circle.
Mari, he ran a red light!
How should we take care of him?
Lock him in the Coral Circle and have him reflect.
You better get out of here.
Ran a red light?
I don’t want to be locked in here for a hundred years!
I have to get out!
That’s a piece of cake.
I’m close to getting out!
I want to leave!
I’ve heard that Mari likes cleanliness;
you might just be able to leave if you clean up the Coral Circle.
Really?
Then let’s hurry up and clean!
We’ve got a lot of time; I’ll take a nap for now.
I’m so tired.
Working needs energy, too.
I’ll take a nap for now.
Paddi, come have some cake!
It’s cake!
We’ve been waiting for you!
How come you guys are all old?
Everyone will grow old after a hundred years!
I’ve grown old, too!
I don’t want to be old!
What’s the matter?
So it was just a nightmare.
I have to get out of here!
It’s just the statue left.
Once I pull it back up,
the Coral Circle will be all cleaned up!
Don’t you know that running a red light is very dangerous?
I ran a red light, so what?
Wolffy!
Mari?
I ran a red light; arrest me!
Thanks to Wolffy,
you guys narrowly avoided hitting a child.
Good thing Wolffy reacted quickly!
That statue is too heavy; just give up.
No, my friends are waiting for me!
Friends?
Grandpa Tortie, there’s an old photo here.
Is this you in it?
Ready, set,
go!
It’s starting!
I remember now; I also have a friend.
He must be out there waiting for me, too!
Let’s work hard to get out of here!
Okay!
We’re finally finished!
Let’s go, Grandpa Tortie!
Great, I finally snuck in!
Who was that?
Paddi?
Never mind; I need to find the fragment.
Why is the fragment moving?
So it’s on them!
Stop right there, Paddi!
Who’s calling me?
Paddi, hand over the fragment!
Wolffy!
Hurricane!
Sirius!
Hand over the fragment right now, Paddi!
You have nowhere to run!
You’ve been cornered!
Hand over the fragment, and I’ll let you go!
Let me go!
The fragment is with me!
What?
So it’s on you!
Found it!
What? It’s a flashlight?
You lied to me! I’ll get my revenge!
Wolffy,
how dare you cause such a mess in this place!
It’s Mari.
Mari, I finished cleaning up the Coral Circle.
Could you not lock me up for a hundred years?
A hundred years?
I was only planning on giving you one day to reflect.
Then how come Grandpa Tortie was locked in here for a hundred years?
It’s because he’s lazy and wants to eat, but not to work.
He just didn’t want to leave.
I’ll get out!
Have you found the fragment?
Weslie!
I missed you guys!
Hasn’t it only been a day?
What are you so excited for?
Paddi, did you find the fragment?
Well…
You weren’t slacking off again, were you, Paddi?
Is this the fragment that you guys want?
Yes, it is!
Then I’ll give it to you guys.
Thank you, Grandpa Tortie!
Grandpa Tortie, where are you going?
I’m going to find my friend, too!
End