Strength, All for You
Amazing, Sparky!
Where’s Jonie?
She’ll be here soon.
Let’s take Mr. Slowy’s call.
Mr. Slowy!
Listen up; Wolffy has discovered a new fragment,
but that fragment is stuck under a massive conch.
Wolffy can’t get to it.
Great!
Let’s drive the Magic Submarines there right now to get it
Wait!
Mari is patrolling over there,
and vehicles are off-limits.
Then what do we do?
Mr. Slowy,
how about I just lift up the massive conch?
The massive conch is extremely heavy;
I’m afraid that you guys can’t lift it.
I…
can…
do it!
Woah, Sparky,
are you okay?
Jonie, you’re so strong!
Alright, then the two of you go together!
Okay!
Go where?
With these Super Strength Gloves,
the one who’s getting the fragment under the massive conch will be me!
Darn it!
I need to think of something to buy time.
Wolffy!
Wilie has a lot of homework that he needs you to sign!
That’s easy!
Wait!
Today is Valentine’s Day, you know.
Do you not celebrate Valentine’s Day?
Wolnie wants to celebrate Valentine’s Day every day;
I’m so sick of it!
Just say you haven’t seen me, okay?
Poor you.
Go on.
Hey, what are you doing?
My robot is malfunctioning;
help me stop it!
You could just turn it off.
Kids, this is all I can do for you.
This road is blocked;
let’s move the rock.
Let me do it!
How could I let a girl do such rough tasks?
Moving them one at a time takes too long;
it’s much faster to move them together.
Do you need help?
I’ll help you open it!
I’ll help you!
Leave it to me, Jonie!
Sparky, what the heck were you thinking?
I knew these gloves would work!
That guy who loves to show off his strength is over there!
Get him!
Apologies, we got the wrong person.
Why am I always the one who gets hurt?
I need to become even stronger
if I want to lift up the massive conch and get the fragment.
Why are there so many rocks?
King Wolffy has places to be!
Sir Hercules, could you teach me how to be even stronger?
I have a very important treasure
that’s stuck under a massive conch!
I need to lift it up to get it!
You mean the Ocean Star fragment?
Alright; since you look strong,
I’ll take you as my pupil!
Let me see you lift up that rock.
Of course!
Now, all I need is a little trick,
and Sparky will be crushed!
Master, what were you doing behind me?
I’m fine.
Try lifting up this one.
Okay!
Leave it to me!
Once I use this, Sparky will be crushed!
Bullseye!
Where’s Master?
Did Master leave these gloves just for me?
Someone help me!
Turns out these gloves are quite powerful!
Jonie, look!
I’ve become boundless in strength,
all thanks to this pair of gloves!
Sparky,
I think you’re very strong even without the gloves!
What do you mean?
Because you’re always looking out for us!
You’re always the first to step up when something happens.
No matter who’s in trouble, you put all your effort into helping.
Therefore, you’re very strong!
Aw, thanks…
We better keep looking for the fragment.
We’re here! Let’s go!
Only the true Hercules
can lift up this massive conch bare-handed!
Would anyone like to give it a try?
How is anyone supposed to lift up such a big conch?
I’ll go!
Go! Go!
Would anyone else like to give it a try?
He’s so brave!
I can’t believe he actually went for it bare-handed!
I won’t use gloves to lift up the conch, either!
If you won’t, I will!
Wolffy!
Wolffy’s going to get the fragment!
What do we do?
The fragment is mine!
The big conch is angry! Run!
Oh no!
It’s you guys?
I’ll hold it up!
You two, grab the fragment and go!
What the hell are you talking about, Jonie?
On a count of three,
we’re all making a run for it together!
One,
two,
three!
Jonie!
Are you okay?
I think you’re very strong!
Jonie, I’m coming to rescue you!
It’s no use, Sparky.
Even my Super Strength Gloves can’t counter it;
how could you possibly lift it up?
Even if I can’t, I’m going to do everything to save her!
I’m not letting go!
Jonie,
are you okay?
Thank you, Sparky!
End