The Love of Old Clothes
Next.
Wolffy, that’s Wilie’s clothing!
You’ve been trying on clothes for an entire day!
What in the world do you want to wear, Wolnie?
This one!
Buying new clothes yet again?
Wolnie, look.
There’s no room in your wardrobe!
I’ll just throw out the old clothes, then.
Are you sure?
You literally bought this one yesterday!
You haven’t even worn this one yet!
Clothes become old when they become old-fashioned!
I’m a fashion goddess; how can I settle for less?
There’s no use in keeping old clothes that I won’t wear!
You can have these clothes!
With this box,
I finally have a place to stay!
Who should I give these clothes to?
Oh, yeah!
Why don’t I just leave the clothes here
and let someone who wants them take them?
Hey, Wolnie!
I didn’t mean to litter!
You dropped this.
Get down!
Arrest him!
You are driving dangerously;
take him away!
Madam Wolnie, are you okay?
Mari, your clothes are ripped!
Oh, yeah!
These just so happen to be my old clothes;
you can have them!
Really?
I do, in fact, need old clothes!
Finally, the old clothes are gone!
Look, you guys are all dirty!
My silk scarf!
Let me clean you up.
That’s not how you use that!
I’m really sorry.
It’s okay.
Just remember that clothes are for wearing!
You’re speeding! Stop!
Be careful with the clothes!
Take him away.
Mari!
Don’t worry, I’m okay.
It got ripped again;
how am I supposed to feel comfortable giving the clothes to her?
Different occasions require different clothes.
That way, the clothes will last longer.
Got it!
Athletic wear is for working out,
formal wear is for parties,
and sleepwear is for sleeping.
Looks like you’ve got it!
I’ll head back, then.
These clothes are so small, though;
how do I wear them?
Wait!
Are these little ones worn like this?
No, no,
not like that!
Like this?
Is this right?
This is how to wear accessories with your clothes.
It looks so good!
Seeing you in this outfit
makes me think of myself back in the day.
Now, I feel comfortable leaving my old clothes
to you.
I almost forgot;
the buttons on that pajama set are a little bit loose.
Don’t button them together super hard.
Also, never use a washing machine
to wash the red robe!
That’ll ruin it.
Alright,
goodbye for real this time!
Wait!
What is it? Do the clothes not fit?
It’s not that.
Here’s your bag back.
I thought you might want to keep it.
Right, that bag is super useful.
Well, goodbye!
Wolnie, the seashell dress you ordered has arrived;
I put it on the table!
Does it look good?
Yes!
Great!
Another goal!
Wolffy!
Wolnie,
do you still remember the time we went for a walk on the beach,
and your dress got all wet?
Of course I remember!
I also remember the time where Wilie was super naughty
and wouldn’t sleep for the whole night!
Now that you mention it, Wolnie,
I actually kind of miss the clothes you wore before.
How nostalgic they are!
Did I say something wrong?
How am I supposed to explain this to Mari?
Just say it!
Mari,
I want to talk to you about something.
Really? I wanted to talk to you about something, too!
What is it?
Does she want to give the clothes back to me?
Ever since I started wearing your clothes,
I’ve gotten a lot of compliments!
I really like your clothes,
especially this set of athletic wear!
I can’t thank you enough!
I’m glad you like them.
By the way, what did you want to talk to me about?
I…
I want my clothes back.
What did you say?
I want my clothes back!
Look out!
How dare you drive while drunk!
You have committed a serious traffic violation!
Stop right there!
My clothes!
Here, let’s get your clothes back together.
Mine?
Of course they’re yours!
But I gave them to you,
and now I’m asking for them back.
I know that old clothes are very important to you.
You can always buy more clothes,
but you can’t buy memories.
Take him away!
My clothes!
What now?
I’ll climb down!
I’ll go down with you!
What’s that sound?
Wolnie,
look out!
Danger!
Look, I got the clothes back!
That was incredible, Wolnie!
Oh, goodness!
Hurry, come over here!
Give me your hand!
Wolnie!
Don’t be afraid, Wolnie!
I’m here!
You’re just in time, Wolffy!
I think this should go back to its owner.
Well, if there isn’t anything else,
I’ll head out.
Wait!
As a symbol of friendship,
I want you to have it!
Wolnie,
didn’t that used to be your favorite athletic wear?
You always said
that it was limited edition and very valuable,
so you never had the heart to wear it!
Shut up!
Sorry!
I’ll go sweep the floors!
Thank you so much, Wolnie!
End