The Best Food
We’ve been here for so long,
yet we still haven’t found the Ocean Star fragment that’s on the radar!
It’s not broken, is it?
Be patient, Paddi!
We’ll find it eventually!
Then how much longer do we have to wait?
Lunch time!
What are we eating today?
We made a lot of food!
Stewed seagrass soup,
stir-fried seagrass,
and sauteed seagrass!
But I don’t want to eat seagrass;
is there anything else?
We’re in the wildest part of the deep sea, Paddi.
Seagrass is the only food around here.
Yeah, don’t waste food;
come and eat!
I don’t want to!
I want a feast!
But there’s only seagrass here!
If you don’t eat, how are you doing to have enough energy
to look for Ocean Star fragments?
Ocean Star fragments?
I found it!
During my long, hard search just now,
I finally found the Ocean Star fragment,
so…
let’s get out of here!
Let’s leave!
Paddi, this is a fake!
I can’t believe you tricked us!
I’m not eating seagrass anymore!
I’m going out to find different food!
Food? Food!
Where the heck is the food?
I’m so hungry!
What’s that sound?
There are so many fish gathered around;
they must be having a potluck!
Feast time!
Can I have a little bit of your potluck here?
Uh, nothing!
Bye!
What are you doing? Let me go!
Chief, we’ve found a suspicious creature!
Who are you? Are you one with those guys?
What? What guys?
He’s back!
Out of the way, everyone!
Little goat,
I didn’t think you’d be here, too!
Wolffy!
Did you come to get the Ocean Star fragment as well?
Fragment?
I see greed in your eyes!
Security, escort me!
Yes, Chief!
There’s no way I’m going to give my precious gem
to strangers like you guys!
Then you’ll be sorry!
Stop!
Don’t attack me!
I was just passing by, is all!
I’ll give you the fragment right now!
Why did he just give it to me like that?
If you don’t want it, you can give it back to me!
No way!
Thank you, Paddi!
Who are you?
Why did you give the gem to that bastard?
I’m Paddi; I’m from—
I didn’t ask you who you are!
I only asked you why you gave the gem to that bastard!
Chief,
you did, in fact, ask him who he is.
Did I?
Actually, I still have your gem.
How come the gem is still here?
Because the “gem” that I gave to Wolffy
is a rock that I painted.
You know, what’s-your-name, you’re quite smart!
Chief, his name is Paddi!
I know; I don’t need your reminder!
Yes, sir!
But what kind of gem is this, anyway?
Everyone wants it!
It’s not a gem, it’s an Ocean Star fragment!
My friends and I
are also looking for it!
I won’t give such a valuable thing
to a stranger!
I’m so hungry!
Empty stomachs are not allowed here.
I’ll allow you to dine at my palace.
Do you have food at your place?
Of course we do!
Our food is the best food in the world!
The best food?
Wolnie,
I’m back!
Look, I got a fragment!
Forget the fragment.
Look at my new clothes!
Why is your hand so dirty?
Why is the fragment losing its color?
Paddi, how dare you trick me!
I’m going to get you!
Wolffy!
I’ll just go and look for the fragment.
Wolffy, I’m going to get you!
This is my palace!
Your palace?
So this is the palace you spoke of?
Well? Beautiful, isn't it?
When are we going to start eating?
Security,
take Paddi to dine!
This way, please.
Aren’t you hungry, Paddi?
Eat!
The food you spoke of
is seagrass?
That’s right!
But I want to eat candy, chocolate, and chips!
We’re rabbitfish;
we only eat algae plants!
Don’t you guys get bored of eating only one type of food?
How is that possible?
Algae plants are the world’s best food!
Look!
Behold, our people are hard at work farming!
See?
Our people are harvesting kelp for the winter!
Look over here!
A rock?
Oh, yeah.
Who put this rock here?
Chief, it has always been here.
I don’t care! Move it!
But it’s too heavy;
we can’t move it in two shakes.
Then take three shakes to move it!
Yes, sir!
Three Shakes!
Here comes Three Shakes!
That’s amazing!
It’s all Chief’s wisdom!
Chief’s wisdom!
Finally, there you guys are!
Wolffy!
That guy looks so familiar;
where have I seen him?
Chief,
he’s the dog who came to steal your gem this morning!
Hey, I’m no dog!
I’m a wolf,
Wolffy the wolf!
Did Wolffy already find out that the fragment is fake?
How dare you bring that up!
Watch this!
Chief, he says very loudly that he is a wolf!
Outrageous! How dare he speak to me so loudly!
Forget it! Just run!
I heard Chief’s cries!
Help!
Are you okay?
I’m okay; thank you.
Chief, our seagrass fields!
Your food…
We have to think of a way to get closer to Wolffy
and take his gun!
That’s easy! I have a way!
What kind of way is this?
Hand over the fragment!
Chief,
we’ve seized his weapon!
Well done!
Watch this!
Is it broken?
This is garbage!
Garbage! Garbage!
What is this place?
What am I doing here?
Oh no!
The swordfish controller broke!
The swordfish seem to have gone back to normal.
Guys, he’s the one who used a machine to control you!
That’s not at all what happened!
I can explain to you guys later!
Help me!
I’ll be back!
All of your food is gone.
We’ll just plant it again!
I finally understand!
It turns out that growing food takes such hard work!
I’ll never waste food again!
Such hard work?
You city people are so pretentious!
Take this.
Didn’t you say you wouldn’t give such a valuable thing
to a stranger?
But you’re one of us!
Thank you!
Goodbye, my friends!
I brought the best food back!
The “best food” you speak of is seagrass?
This isn’t any ordinary seagrass;
I grew it by myself!
It’s very tasty!
You guys are hungry, aren’t you?
You really want some, don’t you?
Come on, let’s eat!
End