Don’t Worry, Daddy!
Are you okay?
Wilie!
Wilie, what happened?
Daddy!
Don’t worry, son!
I’ll bandage it for you right away!
Who threw this can out here?
How old are you guys?
What species are you?
Where do you live?
Where do your parents work?
You made my son fall over; what are you going to do about it?
We’re sorry!
Daddy,
what are you doing here?
I was taking out the garbage and passed by.
Here, son.
Let’s go home.
Slowy!
Wilie’s injured;
help me out!
Is it really that bad?
He fell over while running around just now.
Isn’t that a small thing?
Sit down, Wilie.
Daddy, I—
Huh?
Are you hungry?
Here, I’ll feed you!
Here.
Tell me what you were doing running around.
I—
You should speak even if you know you did wrong.
How is Wilie supposed to talk with you shoving food?
I wanted to sign up for the Deep Sea Environmental Adventure with everyone,
and I was preparing!
Adventure?
You can’t go!
But…
I’ll get a souvenir scarf for entering the contest.
I wanted to get the scarf and give it to you, Daddy.
So it was for me, Wilie?
Alright,
I’ll let you go!
Yay!
Daddy says I can go on an adventure by myself!
What?
By yourself?
No,
I have to follow him!
He’s not going to grow if you puppy-guard him like that.
Why do you care?
The annual youth Deep Sea Environmental Adventure
is starting now!
Participants, please pick up a garbage bag.
During the adventure, our objective
is to pick up stray garbage.
Afterwards, you can get a souvenir scarf.
With this costume,
no one will recognize me!
Wolffy,
are you here to accompany your son?
I’m not Wolffy!
Wait for me, you guys!
Are you okay, Wi—
I mean, kiddo?
Thank you, big brother!
Kiddo,
how about we work together?
Can we do that?
Of course!
What’s your name, big brother?
Uh… My name is Billy.
What a coincidence;
my name is Wilie!
Your name is just like mine!
Our competition is about to begin!
Participants, please take your mark!
Get set,
go!
Wilie,
do you want to rest for a bit?
No, I’m not tired!
Actually, we can rest for a bit.
Wilie must be hungry;
I need to have him eat something.
Look, Wilie! This sea anemone tree has fruit growing on it!
Good thing I’m hungry!
It’s so good!
Why does this fruit look so much like bread?
This is a peculiar plant called a bread anemone.
If only there were a place to sit.
Look, there are kelp chairs over here!
I keep thinking you’re very similar to my family, big brother.
Is it… your dad?
You’re not like my dad at all!
My dad is always scared of me being in danger
and never lets me do anything.
No one wants to be friends with me.
Brother Billy,
you’re my first fish friend!
Wilie,
we’ll reach the finish line after exiting the undersea forest!
Wilie?
Wilie!
I’m over here!
Why did you climb up there, Wilie?
I found something important!
This time,
not only did I ensure Wilie’s safety,
I also found a fragment!
Great!
Wilie!
We’re almost at the finish line!
Brother Billy!
Are we?
That’s great.
Let’s hurry over there.
I’ll go and check how to get there first.
Wilie, it’s dangerous!
Wait for me!
Brother Billy!
Where are you?
Don’t bully Brother Billy!
Wilie!
Brother Billy!
Don’t worry, I’m okay.
Don’t be scared, Wilie.
I’ll think of a way to get you out of here!
Brother Billy,
you’re hurt very badly!
I’m okay; I’m doing just fine,
see?
Look at my eyes!
Don’t they look good?
Oh no, I have to think of a way to get out of here!
Look, Brother Billy!
There’s a hole over here!
I’ll climb out this way
and find my dad to come and rescue you!
Don’t! That’s too dangerous!
Don’t worry, I can do it!
Wilie!
Don’t go, it’s too dangerous!
It’s Daddy!
I’m sorry, Wilie.
Billy was just me in a costume.
Don’t worry, Wilie.
I’ll definitely think of something!
Daddy!
Daddy, leave it to me this time!
I’ll find Grandpa Slowy to come and rescue you!
Don’t, Wilie!
Wilie!
It’s okay, Daddy!
I’ll definitely rescue you!
So you’re father and son?
No wonder you’re attacking me!
I understand how you feel.
If my son were hurt,
I’d be very angry, too!
However,
I think we’re in a civilized society now,
and we shouldn’t use violence.
Wolffy, we’re here to rescue you!
Daddy!
Wilie!
Daddy,
you’re finally awake!
You’re so brave, son!
Thank you for rescuing me!
Daddy,
I’ll be the one to protect you from now on!
I’ll say, Wilie,
you really have grown up!
Let’s go play, Wilie!
Daddy, can I—
Go ahead!
Thank you, Daddy!
By the way, son,
don’t you have something to give to me?
That’s right!
Daddy,
this is the Deep Sea Environmental Adventure souvenir;
it’s yours now!
Thank you, son!
Isn’t there also a fragment or something like that?
An Ocean Star fragment?
I gave it to Grandpa Slowy!
I didn’t think that Wilie managed to find a fragment;
I must get it to the kids quickly!
Slowy,
give the fragment that my son found back to me right now!
End