Sparky’s Decision
Stop!
Wolffy,
give back the toy car right now!
Uh…
What toy car?
I haven’t seen it.
That’s my toy car!
Let’s get this straight;
I found this thing five minutes ago,
so it’s mine now!
Give back Sawyer’s toy car right now!
Too late!
Sirius!
With Sawyer’s tooth,
I can once again make powerful weapons!
See you later,
you two!
Goodbye!
What now?
Follow him!
So that’s what happened.
Wolffy’s so evil!
What should we do now?
How about…
How about we…
How about we eat first?
Actually,
you could just buy another toy car.
Yeah!
Buy a higher-tech one!
I made that toy car
out of a tooth that fell out.
We sharks never stop growing new teeth;
I’ve turned all of my lost teeth
into interesting things.
The car that Wolffy stole
was the best one I made.
Come on, don’t be so sad!
Here,
eat first!
I’ve lost my appetite;
I don’t want to eat.
Poor Sawyer.
I’m going to teach Wolffy a lesson right now!
Sparky,
isn’t this Wolffy’s radar?
Why do you have it?
I found it on the road.
Goodbye!
Follow him!
A radar?
And so,
I took it back with me.
Won’t you give it back to Wolffy?
Wolffy’s so evil!
Why would I give it back to him?
I think we should return things to their owner.
But
he also took Sawyer’s toy car,
yet he didn’t give it back!
Mr. Slowy wouldn’t want you to do this.
Yeah.
Fine.
Since all of you insist so,
I'll return it right now.
The radar has detected an Ocean Star fragment!
It’s really close to us!
Then let’s collect that fragment before returning the radar!
Sparky,
the magma is about to erupt!
Hold on,
Paddi!
I’ve almost got it!
Got it!
The fragment!
Sparky!
Rainbow Shield!
Magic assembly,
unmatchable energy!
We’re safe.
Sparky, look!
The fragment!
I didn’t think I’d find a fragment by accident!
This is great!
Wolffy again?
Let’s get him!
Oh no!
We used up almost all of the Magic Submarine’s power
for the magma heat resistance earlier!
We may have escaped the magma,
but we couldn’t escape Wolffy!
Where’s the radar?
Where is the radar?
I swear I put it on the bookshelf!
Daddy!
Come play with my remote control airplane!
Where’s Daddy?
I’m right here.
Daddy, why were you hiding behind the door?
Did you want to play hide-and-seek with me?
Wilie,
I’m looking for my radar.
Play by yourself for now.
Radar?
My radar is missing;
how am I supposed to find fragments?
Found yet another fragment!
Finding fragments really is easier
with Wolffy’s radar!
Wilie!
Thank you, Brother Sparky!
Wilie,
what are you doing over here?
I came out here to find Daddy’s radar.
Radar?
I lost Daddy’s radar,
and he’s really upset!
You lost the radar?
I was playing in his room.
See you later, you two!
Goodbye!
Stop!
I don’t know where the radar is now.
I’ll go take a look over there.
Goodbye, Brother Sparky!
Should I give it back to Wolffy or not?
Of course you should!
Weslie,
what are you doing here?
I saw that you were out for such a long time,
so I came to look for you.
Sparky,
you better hurry up and give the radar back to Wolffy.
But Wolffy’s so evil;
he takes other people’s things and doesn’t give them back!
So how come I have to give his things back to him
if I take them?
There’s no way I’m giving it back!
Good thing I send out a guardian robot
every single time Wilie goes out!
Otherwise, I never would’ve known that it was you, Sparky,
who took my radar!
Aha!
It’s time to eat!
Mari?
Wolffy?
What are you doing here?
We’re here to arrest a thief!
Arrest a thief?
All I did was take a bite of a vegetable pancake;
why does that need an arrest?
Not you!
I’m saying that Sparky stole my radar!
Sparky,
don’t you know that theft is a very serious crime?
Sparky did pick up Wolffy’s radar,
but he returned it a long time ago!
Sparky,
did you, or did you not, take Wolffy’s radar?
Uh…
Enough!
Just search!
All of the submarines have been searched.
We did not find Wolffy’s radar.
There’s no way!
The radar must be in here!
That box hasn’t been searched yet!
I told you, the radar isn’t in here!
What’s inside of this?
Don’t open that!
Too late!
See? I told you not to open it!
Don’t say I didn’t warn you!
Then where’s my radar, huh?
Daddy,
the radar is with me!
Son,
how did the radar end up with you?
I lost the radar;
it was Brother Sparky who helped me find it.
Sparky?
So what happened?
Wasn’t the radar on you the whole time?
After you and I split up,
I ran into Sawyer on the road.
Sawyer,
what are you doing?
I was thinking that I could make another toy car,
but I just can’t.
None of these are as good as the one that Wolffy took.
It’s all Wolffy’s fault!
Right!
I hate those bad people who take other people’s things
and don’t give them back!
Well, not all of those people are bad people, right?
But if they take other people’s things and don’t give them back,
are they any different from Wolffy?
You’re right;
am I any different from Wolffy in this case?
I think I know what I should do now!
Sawyer’s words reminded me,
so I gave the radar back to Wilie.
I was wrong;
can you guys forgive me?
Of course not!
Unless
you clean up the Magic Trains!
Here you go.
Yay!
If it weren’t for Wilie forcing me by not eating,
I wouldn’t give it back to you, you know!
Sawyer,
let’s go!
Wolffy,
give it back!
No way!
It must be something good!
Why is it black pepper?
Wolffy,
what goes around, comes around!
End