I Have an Opinion
There are six paths to the fragment.
Why don’t we take the most exciting route, the volcano?
Let’s take the shopping street route!
We could buy some clothes along the way!
It’s better to take the stadium route!
We can exercise and stay fit!
All of your guys’ routes are so boring.
Paddi,
what’s your opinion?
Obviously, I choose
the amusement park route!
There’s stuff to play and ice cream to eat!
We’re adventuring; there’s no time for ice cream.
Amusement park!
Hey, guys—
You guys, it’s been an hour.
Let Mr. Slowy decide!
Mr. Slowy, who do you agree with?
Mine’s better!
No, mine’s better! No, mine!
Looks like I’ll have to choose a leader within you guys
to make important decisions when needed!
But…
Who?
Why don’t we do rock, paper, scissors?
How could I decide something so important
through such an unserious manner?
We’ll draw straws!
The person I draw
will be the one making decisions!
Any objections?
Nope!
The one I’ve drawn is…
Jonie!
Me?
Jonie’s so lucky!
Really?
Jonie,
which route are we taking to get to the fragment?
Well…
How about this one?
Great!
Everyone, listen to Jonie’s orders and get going!
Okay!
This place is so cluttered.
The fragment is buried,
so the signal is very weak.
The fragment must be down one of the paths.
Weslie, which path do we take?
You’re the leader now, so you decide!
Then… How about the one on the left?
As you wish, Jonie!
Darn it, the goats are ahead of me!
The fragment must be down one of these paths.
I’ll go right; if I don’t find it,
I’ll turn back and go down theirs!
This path looks very safe!
Good thing I made the right decision!
Look, everyone!
What? What’s wrong?
Look at that rock!
Doesn’t it look just like me?
Look!
There’s one here, too!
Over there, too!
Look out, Paddi!
What the heck happened?
Could it be that we’re too loud,
causing the rocks to fall?
I don’t want to look for the fragment anymore!
I want to go home!
Get into a hole, everyone!
Let’s get out of here!
Be quiet when crossing!
Paddi!
Sorry, that was me.
Another fork?
Which way should we go?
—Left!　—Right!
Stop arguing!
Mr. Slowy said to listen to what Jonie says!
Okay.
Then… I’ll choose right this time.
We should be safe now.
So many fish up ahead!
They’re so cute!
Get behind me, everyone!
Shield!
Is everyone okay?
Jonie,
I don’t think so.
I’ll distract them!
Fishies,
come get me!
Run, everyone!
Alright,
maximum speed!
This path is so dangerous.
If only I had chosen the other path
at the first fork.
It’s alright!
It should be a breeze from here!
Don’t say that;
what if the other path was even more dangerous?
If we had taken that path instead,
we might just be calling for help right now!
Help!
This movie is terrifying!
Why haven’t I found it
after all this time?
Where the heck is the fragment?
Two paths again?
Jonie, which way do you choose?
I choose left.
Wait!
Maybe right is better?
Jonie!
Okay, then left.
What are all those holes for?
Go!
Are you okay?
This is too tough to get through!
So now what?
Let’s not be reckless.
Analyze them closely
and see if the geysers have any patterns.
Patterns?
Look, guys!
When the geysers erupt,
they go every other row!
They do!
If we follow this pattern, we can get through!
Let’s go!
We did it!
Look, guys!
It’s the fragment!
Yay!
We finally got the fragment!
Those paths just now were so dangerous!
I put everyone at risk with my decisions;
I’m sorry.
Didn’t we safely get out, though?
I’m hungry.
Let’s find a safe place to stop and eat!
Let’s race!
Wait for me!
Wolffy!
I know that you guys have gotten the fragment;
hand it over to me!
There’s no way we’re telling you where the fragment is!
Exactly, Jonie!
You better not hand it over to Wolffy!
So the fragment is with Jonie, huh?
Hand it over to me!
If not, I’ll…!
No!
I’m still young! I don’t want to die!
Don’t give it to him, Jonie!
And your decision is?
Jonie!
I know what to do!
What, you choose escaping?
Stop!
I can do this!
Hand over the fragment!
Jonie!
You can’t run from me!
Hand over the fragment!
Mr. Wolffy, watch out!
Oh no.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Charge past them,
Sirius!
Here I am, Wolffy!
Jonie,
you can’t run from me!
Wait,
there must be a trap.
Oh, it was just a bluff!
Goodbye,
Wolffy!
I’ll be back!
Jonie,
I didn’t realize it was all part of your plan!
I was bad at making decisions earlier,
so I put you guys at risk.
But don’t worry, everyone!
I, Jonie, have grown!
The radar has detected another fragment!
Let’s go get it, then!
Can we take the shopping street route this time?
I think the stadium route is better!
No, we should take the amusement park route!
Jonie, what do you think?
End