Have a Hug
I have to leave now.
The Wolf-Goat Cube inside of Sirius could explode at any time.
Mr. Slowy!
Today is the city-wide undersea Hug Day!
Give a hug to those next to you
and wish them well!
Oh, today is Hug Day!
Kids,
let’s have one last farewell hug!
Mr. Slowy!
We’ll miss you, Mr. Slowy!
—Come back frequently!　—There, there.
Weslie,
it’s your turn!
Mr. Slowy, I’m already all grown up!
I’m a man,
so I don’t need a hug!
Since when have hugs been restricted to age?
Even if you’re a man, you need hugs, too!
See?
I don’t want you to leave, Mr. Slowy!
Come on, Weslie.
Let’s hug!
Slowy,
the Wolf-Goat Cube is about to explode!
Get back here right now!
Okay, I’ll be right there!
I’ll head back then, Weslie.
The Goat-Wolf Cube is about to explode!
That was a close call.
Weslie,
the fragment is somewhere in the western suburban basin.
Weslie, you ran a red light.
Really?
It’s obviously a green light!
Fine.
I accept my punishment.
So what’s my punishment?
Well,
your punishment is a hug!
Since today is the annual Hug Day,
we should hug others when we meet them!
Captain,
can I take any other punishments?
You dropped your stuff, Grandma;
I’ll pick them up for you!
Thank you!
Come here, child!
I’ll give you a hug!
Uh,
no thanks—
Thank you so much for helping our grandma!
Let's hug!
Stay away from me!
Everyone has to hug on Hug Day!
You have to follow the rules!
Child, wait!
Stop right there, Weslie!
Get out and accept your hug!
Where’d Weslie go?
Let’s look over there.
Hug Day is so scary!
I better hide in here for a while.
What’s that sound?
Stay away!
Ouch!
I hate hugging!
Quilly?
Weslie?
What are you doing here?
Today is Hug Day;
everyone is just way too excited,
so I had to hide in here.
Me too!
I really don’t get what’s so good about hugging.
Then let’s hide in here for the rest of Hug Day together!
Okay!
The Cube crisis has been averted!
Wolnie, son,
let’s hug!
What do you want, Slowy?
Today is the undersea Hug Day.
Shouldn’t I get a hug, too?
Don’t even think about it.
Why the heck would I hug a goat?
An Ocean Star fragment has been detected!
Apparently, it’s around the western suburban basin’s cave!
That fragment is mine!
What’s wrong with a hug?
Wolffy is so stingy!
Oh, yeah.
Wolffy discovered an Ocean Star fragment.
I must notify the kids!
This cave is our hideout;
we can’t tell anyone else!
Therefore, no matter what happens,
we can’t leave!
I understand,
but
you don’t need to tie me up!
Oh this? This is just in case.
We’re hiring!
We’re looking for a goodwill ambassador!
Limited position available on a first-come-first-served basis!
Me, please!
I just knew that as soon as you hear about employment,
you’d lose all self-control!
Me, please!
Hire me! Hire me!
Only someone who agrees to hugging sea ​​urchins
can become our goodwill ambassador!
Don’t hug me!
You’ll get pricked!
Sea urchin!
Where’d that sea urchin go?
I’m sorry, Weslie.
I should have listened to you.
Quilly,
you don’t actually hate hugging;
you just don’t want to prick others, right?
That’s not true; I’ve always hated hugging.
I won’t leave this cave again today.
Quilly—
Mr. Slowy?
You’re saying that Wolffy discovered a fragment in…?
I’m at that place right now!
I’ll go find it right away!
Quilly.
I have to go find the fragment now.
I can help, Weslie!
But if you leave…
I have a way for you to not prick others!
Really?
Where the heck is the fragment?
I found it!
Look!
Great!
Thank you!
You’re so smart, Weslie!
This way, I won’t prick others anymore!
Unfortunately,
he’s not as smart as King Wolffy!
Wolffy!
Oh no!
The Ocean Star fragment is mine!
My sponge!
Quilly!
Well, that was easy!
Have fun, you two! Goodbye!
The fragment is mine!
Oh no!
If Quilly falls like that,
he’ll get hurt!
I got you, Quilly!
Don’t, Weslie!
You’ll get pricked!
Careful!
Quilly,
why aren't your spines sharp anymore?
What’s going on?
When I saw you dropping everything to rescue me…
Could it be that my spines got dull
after that?
Now, you don’t have to worry about hurting others
when you hug them!
Yay!
By the way,
Wolffy hasn’t gone too far yet.
We still have a chance at getting back the fragment!
You messed up, Mr. Wolffy!
How dare you follow me, Weslie!
Well, since you’re inviting me to a mutton picnic,
don’t blame me!
Look behind you!
Today is Hug Day!
I’ll give you a hug!
Do you want another hug?
Just you wait, you two!
I’ll be back!
Thank you, Weslie!
Because of you,
I can now control the sharpness of my spines!
You’re welcome!
Mr. Slowy!
Weslie?
Mr, Slowy,
I didn’t realize hugging was so joyful!
It’s because hugging is full of love!
Give me the Ocean Star fragment, Weslie!
I didn’t think you’d hug me as well, Wolffy!
I don’t want to hug you?
Let go of me, Slowy!
I’ll come back to visit soon, Mr. Slowy!
Today is truly such a wonderful day!
Let go!
End