A True Chef
We’ve arrived at your destination, Chef Octo!
Who’s that?
He’s my idol,
Guo Jing!
Guo Jing?
Can he…
Can he do kung fu?
Nope.
He’s the new cooking god,
Guo Jing!
If only I could meet Guo Jing
and get some advice from him!
You’ll definitely be able to!
By the way,
thank you for taking me to find deep sea snow lotuses.
This is for you!
How is it?
It’s… It’s not bad.
Actually, I’d like for you to be fully honest.
Alright; they’re very disgusting.
I just knew that I’d fail yet again.
Still, thank you for telling me the truth!
I’d like everyone to be honest!
It must be around here somewhere.
I knew it!
The fragment is mine!
It’s ours!
You’re so evil, Wolffy!
The fragment has gone flying!
Get it!
I’ve finally found a deep sea snow lotus!
The fragment dropped somewhere around here.
The goats are still following me?
I’ve got the upper hand!
It’s too dangerous! Stay away!
You see how strong I am, huh?
All of the fragments will be mine!
Savory kelp cake!
I welcome you all to Volcano Restaurant to give it a try!
Volcano Restaurant?
How despicable of Wolffy to steal our fragment like that!
Chill out, you guys.
Although we lost the fragment,
at least
we didn’t lose our meal time!
What kind of kelp cake is this?
Why would you even run a business
with such a disgusting dish?
There’s no one who likes my food.
Am I really going to have to give up my dreams of being a chef?
Chef Octo,
how can you give up on your dreams?
Just keep going,
and one day, you’ll make something that people like!
Will you guys support me?
Of course we will!
That’s great!
I’m making snow lotus mushroom soup right now.
Why don’t you guys help me taste it?
It’s a fragment!
So it was with Chef Octo, huh?
Soup’s ready!
If this attempt fails as well,
perhaps
I’ll have to give up
on my dreams.
Actually, Chef Octo, your food—
Don’t say that it’s gross!
If you do, you’ll ruin Chef Octo’s dreams!
Come on over, you guys.
Try my soup!
How is it?
It’s… It’s good.
It’s… It’s not bad!
Since you guys all like it,
you guys can eat the rest of this soup!
We should just tell him the truth.
We can’t!
Didn’t you guys see how happy Chef Octo was just now?
If we tell him the truth, Chef Octo will give up on his dreams!
Why aren’t you eating, Sparky?
Do you not like the soup?
Actually, I think…
Actually—
It’s not bad.
Yeah, it’s just a little too salty!
It actually tastes pretty good!
Yeah, and we want more, too!
No problem!
Coming right up!
Paddi!
Sorry, I just wanted to play along, too.
Is this enough?
No!
Remember to eat it all!
Why can’t I find it?
Why isn’t the radar doing anything?
Enhanced radar, go!
So the fragment isn’t over here?
Chef Octo’s food is so bad;
I can’t believe he’s still being patronized!
It should be around here somewhere.
What are these fish doing here?
Move!
My radar!
Chef Octo,
what’s the matter?
Guo Jing said that…
he wants to meet me tomorrow!
He wants to try my food!
If a master chef eats his food,
it’s all going to come crashing down!
My friends,
does this look good for meeting the master chef?
Or is this outfit better?
This one looks a little more casual!
Do you guys like it?
Yes.
I think it’s pretty good, too!
Chef Octo,
the truth is, we all lied.
The truth is, your soup
really doesn’t taste that good!
I thought I’d succeed this time.
If we had said it earlier,
Chef Octo wouldn’t be so heartbroken.
What if the master chef likes Chef Octo’s food?
But it’s really not that good.
How about Chef Octo buys something tasty for the master chef to try?
Wouldn’t that work?
No! That’s cheating!
I’d like everyone to be honest!
When will the radar get a signal?
Excuse me,
how do I get to Volcano Restaurant?
Thank you.
I wonder how Chef Octo is doing.
Chef Octo, are you choosing to meet the master chef?
I’ve canceled on him.
I’m going to make a dish that tastes better
before I meet him!
That’s right.
A true chef must face his failures and never give up.
That customer just now…
He…?
He left without paying!
No, that was the master chef!
Thank you, master chef!
I’ll continue working hard on my dreams!
I won’t give up!
Thank you guys!
Will you guys keep supporting me?
Of course!
Great!
With a sudden surge of inspiration, I made another batch of soup!
Care to help me taste it?
There you guys are!
You guys already know where the fragment is, don’t you?
In there?
Here, here!
Help me taste it!
There’s no Ocean Star fragment in this soup, is there?
Remember, you have to eat it all!
End