Integrity
Let’s go search, you guys; it should be around here somewhere!
Are they looking for fragments?
Over here, everyone! This must be it!
They must have found a fragment!
The fragment is mine!
I’m free at last!
There you are, Mr. Slowy!
How did you get locked in the bathroom, Mr. Slowy?
I went inside without realizing that it was closed for maintenance.
What?
So you were just locked in the bathroom?
What a waste of time!
I should head back to Sirius.
By the way, Mr. Slowy,
I made cream cakes;
take it with you!
How come there’s only one left?
Paddi!
I didn’t eat it, really!
It’s not scary to make mistakes, Paddi.
What’s scary is refusing to admit it.
I’m sorry, I stole them.
Everyone makes mistakes.
Let’s forgive him.
Oh, really?
I’ve never seen you make mistakes, Mr. Slowy!
It’s getting late; I should head back.
Your cake, Mr. Slowy!
This restaurant is pretty well-kept!
Quilly, have you mopped the floor yet?
It’s all clean, Chef!
The health inspector will be here soon;
they’re going to inspect every last thing!
Yes, sir!
Surface-level efforts aren’t enough.
While the dining area is very clean,
dumping all of the garbage here
is very unhygienic!
My apologies;
I’ll have Quilly clean it up right away!
What’s more,
customers are likely to fall over if they step on cream on the floor!
You call this “mopping” the floor, Quilly?
But I swear I got every spot!
Good thing we had Village Chief Slowy to remind us this time!
Quilly, you don’t take your work seriously.
It looks like I’ll have to let you go!
Is it that serious?
Here’s your pay for today.
This much?
Nope; I don’t have any clamshells for change.
I need you to get me some.
You’re back, Grandpa Slowy!
Stay away from my son, Slowy!
Son, go do your homework.
I’m already done with my homework, Daddy!
You’re done with it?
Then you can go find something meaningful to do.
Like what?
Like sleeping?
Fine.
That was fun!
Where’d this cream come from?
Come on, Daddy will help you get cleaned up.
How come there’s cream over here, too?
Oh no!
Does that mean the cream…?
Customers are likely to fall over if they step on cream on the floor!
But I swear I got every spot!
Quilly, you don’t take your work seriously.
It looks like I’ll have to let you go!
Doesn’t that mean that I got Quilly fired?
We’re not hiring currently.
Not hiring.
We’re not hiring here!
But I’m just here to eat!
Then why didn’t you say so? Come on in!
I’ll find a job someday!
Who?
Village Chief Slowy?
Quilly, I want to talk to you about something.
Thank you, Village Chief Slowy!
I thought about it,
and I think I was just being careless.
So, thank you for pointing out my mistake!
Actually, Quilly, I—
I’m sorry.
At the time, I actually thought
that you, Slowy, were the one who left the cream.
Well, I was!
Village Chief Slowy!
There you are!
What is it?
Thank goodness for your reminder about the garbage behind the restaurant
and the cream on the floor!
Now, the Volcano Restaurant has achieved
a five-star restaurant status!
Village Chief Slowy,
your fairness and persuasiveness are recognized by all!
We’d like for you to give the opening speech
for tomorrow’s Candor Day!
Uh…
Village Chief Slowy,
you’re the first guest of honor to be invited to speak on stage, you know!
Well, uh…
By the way, Slowy,
didn’t you say you wanted to talk to me about something?
It’s nothing.
Why is it so hard?
Why is it so hard to come clean?
I’m sorry!
I’m sorry, Wolffy.
I just couldn’t resist ordering another piece of clothing online yesterday.
Wolnie,
I’ve already canceled your order.
Although you canceled it,
I bought it again later.
Plus, it’s already been shipped.
Although it was already shipped,
I already refused the parcel when it was delivered.
What did you say?
What’s going on?
Mommy and Daddy say that today is the Candor Day.
On this day,
we sincerely and honestly apologize for doing something wrong,
and the other party will forgive it, no matter what it is.
I mean, you did it to save me some money.
Of course I did!
You’re usually such a big spender,
having absolutely no sense of moderation!
You always buy a bunch of stuff you’ll never use!
Even Wolffy and his wife are coming clean;
I have no excuse.
The Candor Day is such a great holiday!
Don’t you think so, Wolnie?
I want to ask:
can a previously refused parcel be sent back?
Quilly!
And now,
let the nine hundred and ninety-ninth Candor Day
begin!
I’d like to welcome everyone to Slowy!
Today, I’d like to say that…
I’m sorry.
I’m sorry, Quilly!
Village Chief Slowy, what exactly are you saying?
Because I did something wrong.
I wanted to take this opportunity to come clean.
That day, when I went to Volcano Restaurant…
But I swear I got every spot!
It was me who wronged Quilly!
Apparently, Slowy came today to apologize?
I’ve once said that making mistakes isn’t scary;
what’s scary is refusing to admit mistakes.
I guess I was confused, too.
I can’t believe
that Village Chief Slowy is coming clean to me in front of an audience!
Thank you for telling me, Village Chief Slowy!
It’s Quilly!
Do you…
Do you accept my apology, then?
Of course I do!
Apologizing in front of so many people
requires a lot of valor!
Thank you!
The truth is, the Candor Day is actually about honesty.
What Village Chief Slowy did
has fulfilled this holiday’s purpose!
Let’s continue to be honest, everyone!
I’m sorry, little brother.
I was the one who broke your toy.
I’m sorry, I’ve been hiding money in my shoes.
I’m sorry… I’m sorry…
It feels so much better to get it out.
Mr. Slowy had a lot of valor during yesterday’s Candor Day!
I’m very sorry, Tibbie.
I was the one who stole the snacks you made.
Didn’t you already apologize to me last time?
I’m not talking about that time.
I’ve stolen something every single time.
Fine.
Since you’re coming clean, I’ll forgive you.
The flavors, however,
have some room for improvement.
For the sake of not wasting food, I had to force myself to finish eating them.
Paddi!
I won’t forgive you!
I don’t know whether Quilly has found a job or not.
Stop!
Quilly?
Village Chief Slowy?
What’s going on?
They…
Stop!
Don’t worry, I’ll help you!
Why are they chasing you?
They’re all saying that I’m good at cleaning,
so they want me to clean their stores.
Isn’t that a good thing?
Let’s get out of here, then!
Why isn’t the door opening?
Anyone? Help us! We’re stuck!
End