The Fish Egg Guardian
The fragment is right around here somewhere!
Let’s split up and search!
Okay!
So this is where hermit crabs live!
What if the fragment happens to be in here?
Apologies!
I’m sorry!
I’ll help you fix all of your houses!
Finally done.
Hey, kid,
don’t you know that you’ve done something wrong?
I do.
I ruined all of the hermit crabs’ houses.
I’m not talking about that.
You’re sitting on my tail!
Sorry!
Whose baby is this?
Where’s the mom?
Just stay right here, okay?
Your mom will be back soon to pick you up.
The fragment is right here!
This is a neighborhood, Wolffy!
You can’t cause trouble here!
Leave!
Don’t get in the way of King Wolffy’s fragment search!
No!
Stop!
Hand over the fragment!
Come here!
Hide here for now, baby fish.
I’ll come back to get you once I distract Wolffy!
Oh no!
These clams are so dangerous!
Don’t worry, baby fish.
I’ll protect you!
Have you two found the fragment?
Nope.
I wonder if Sparky and Paddi have found it?
Paddi!
Don’t steal my cake!
I really can’t win with you, can I?
I wonder if Sparky, all alone, might…
Don’t worry;
he’ll be okay!
But he’s usually so careless;
I…
I’m actually kind of worried about him.
Here comes the cake!
Excuse me,
have you guys seen my child?
Your child?
Where did you lose them?
Here’s what happened…
I was taking my children out to play today.
Suddenly, the weather changed.
It wasn’t until I got home
that I realized I was missing one of my children.
I don’t even know where I lost them!
I don’t know if they’re in danger or not!
Don’t worry, Mother Fish;
we’ll help you search,
okay?
That was close!
Wolffy’s caught up to me again!
Clams?
Trying to stop King Wolffy?
I don’t think so!
The fragment must be right here!
That’s odd;
it clearly says it’s right here.
Sparky!
This statue…
Who carved such an ugly statue?
Finally, I’ve escaped Wolffy.
What am I doing back here again?
Hand over what you’re holding!
I’m not giving it to you!
Then you’ll be sorry!
I found the fish baby!
Paddi,
that’s just a pretty rock.
Don’t worry, Mother Fish!
We’ll definitely find them!
Help!
Sparky!
Come help me!
Wolffy’s trying to snatch the fish baby that I’m holding!
My child!
Don’t you stop me from my fragment search!
Look out!
Look out, Sparky!
You have nowhere to run!
The fragment is mine now!
My child!
Oh, so you’re the baby’s mom?
Great!
I can finally return the baby to you!
Here!
What the heck?
Mommy!
So it was the baby hatching!
I’m not your mom;
your mom is over there.
My child!
Yay!
The mother and child are reunited!
Thank you!
Thank you for your help, everyone!
Goodbye!
So it turns out the fragment was right here;
no wonder Wolffy kept on chasing me!
Let me out of here!
I’ll be back!
End