Sweet Mari
Sweet in the mouth,
sweet in the heart;
With the Meigan Birthday Cake,
let love and friendship melt together
on this most special day of the year!
What a pretty cake!
My birthday is in a few days.
Hey,
why don’t we have a birthday party?
Who should I invite to my birthday party?
Tomorrow is my birthday—
Your garbage fell out;
be more aware next time!
Where’d they go?
I’d like to invite you to my—
You’re in violation of overloading;
overloaded passengers, get off immediately!
Be more aware next time!
Why do people run the moment they see me?
Slow down!
You’re speeding!
Apparently, I look so mean!
No wonder everyone is afraid of me.
Stop yelling!
Hand over the fragment!
Stay away!
I won’t give you the fragment!
You can run all you want,
but I’ll get it no matter what!
Help me!
Stop!
Don’t bully Tibbie!
Tibbie’s such a sweet girl;
how could you possibly treat her like this?
Sirius!
Wait!
Still not giving up, huh?
Ma—Mari?
Tibbie,
are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I’m okay;
thank you, Sister Mari!
Tibbie…
Could you teach me to be a little sweeter?
Huh?
I usually act so serious,
and everyone is afraid of me.
I want to become sweeter
so that people will want to come to my birthday party.
Birthday party?
Well, I can give it a try!
Thank you!
Then let’s get started!
You think I can’t go fragment searching myself
if I can’t snatch it?
The fragment is right up ahead!
Out of my way!
I… I’m just passing by!
Is Mari planning a birthday party?
What a coincidence; we’ve crossed paths again!
Apologies for the wait!
How beautiful!
Stop right there!
Don’t you know that you were speeding just now?
Looks like relying on appearances isn’t enough.
I know!
Mari, I think
you should change your serious facial expressions
and smile a little bit more.
Like… Like this?
Smile naturally!
Just like this!
Like this?
Just like that!
Don’t forget to smile!
You were speeding just now;
be more aware next time!
Look, guys!
This is bad!
Mari is definitely going to punish them!
Are you…
okay?
Don’t skate on the road next time;
that’s very dangerous!
Is that actually Mari?
She seems different!
I’m planning a birthday party;
would you like to attend?
Sure, I’d love to!
Would everyone like to come to my birthday party?
There’s going to be delicious cake!
I want to come!
Me too!
I’m going to get an invitation, too!
I want to come to your birthday party, too!
I’m going to get an invitation!
I want to come!
Remember to show up!
I want to come, too!
Without an invitation,
how am I supposed to get in?
Tibbie,
thanks to you,
I was able to invite so many friends!
You’re welcome!
We’re almost all set.
Where are the sardines?
I saw that they were tired after working for so long,
so I let them rest.
I see!
Then let’s get ready
to welcome the guests!
Okay!
The sardines are gone,
and the now-sweet Mari isn’t scary anymore!
Happy birthday,
Mari!
Thank you, everyone!
This gift is for you!
Thank you!
Wolffy!
How could you have a birthday party without me, Wolffy?
Out of my way!
Don’t try to stop King Wolffy from his fragment search!
Stop!
I ask you to please leave my birthday party!
I’ll leave once I find the fragment!
The fragment might just be in there!
Stop it!
Wolffy,
I won’t let you ruin Sister Mari’s birthday party!
Do you really think you, a single little goat, can stop me?
Don’t underestimate me!
Don’t panic, everyone!
Tibbie!
Wolffy,
please let go of Tibbie,
would you?
I’m not afraid of you anymore!
Tibbie!
Don’t hurt my friend!
I’ll be back!
Are you okay?
I’m okay,
but
all of the guests got scared off.
There’s no one to celebrate my birthday with again.
There’s me!
Thank you, Tibbie!
Us, too!
Didn’t I scare you guys off?
You keep the seas in order;
how could we possibly be afraid of you?
We just went and hid the cake!
Thank you, everyone!
Let’s have some cake!
Yeah!
Here!
It’s a fragment!
Mari,
can I have this fragment?
If you like it, you can have it!
Thank you, Mari!
You’re welcome!
End