Brainy and Brawny Wilie
Watch, Wilie!
What’s this called?
Iron Wolf Punch!
How about this one?
Iron Wolf Clap!
What’s this one called?
It’s the Iron Wolf Weapons!
Well done, son!
Remember,
if you encounter bad people,
you must learn to defend yourself with kung fu!
Understood!
Alright,
Daddy will teach you a few more!
You’ve got a lot of nerve, huh?
How dare you throw stuff in my face!
Daddy,
why is he so small?
You think I’m small?
I’ll finish you off!
Son, we’re in for a real doozy.
Let him have a taste of our strength!
Throw a punch!
What a great punch, son!
I’ll treat you to candy!
Son, what kind of “punch” is this?
It’s a Friendship Punch!
Don’t think that I’ll forgive you guys
just because you gave me a piece of candy!
Son, throw a clap!
I know this one!
Go, son!
Go!
Again?
One,
two,
three,
four!
Son, what kind of “clap” is this?
It’s a Friends Forever Clap!
Looks like you guys aren’t that much at all!
Not so fast!
I haven’t used my weapons yet!
I’ll use weapons, Daddy!
What kind of “weapon” is that?
The Weapon of Knowledge!
Son, just watch me fight him!
Don’t, Daddy!
The book says that pufferfish
have spines!
These are our Wolf Clan’s weapons.
Choose one for self-defense!
Daddy, I want this one!
What a good eye my son has!
The wonders of folding stools
are that they can be tucked away and be readily available.
It’s definitely the number one weapon on the list!
Please sit, Grandpa Slowy!
What a good kid!
The method you teached me yesterday worked so well!
Then today, I’ll teach you—
Don’t teach my son weird stuff, you old goat!
Let’s study together!
The seas are full of danger;
what use is there in reading?
We must know kung fu
in order to defend ourselves!
Reading is useful!
Studying will help you learn to defend yourself even better!
So then which one is more useful?
—Well, of course kung fu is better!　—Well, of course knowledge is better!
Slowy,
how about we do a challenge?
Whoever finds an Ocean Star fragment in this part of the sea first
will be correct!
Alright!
I’m going to make my son know the greatness of kung fu!
Don’t worry;
Daddy is here!
Daddy,
our path is blocked.
To get past this kind of stuff,
I’ll just throw a punch!
I don’t want to hurt you, Wilie;
stand back!
Wait!
Daddy!
Help!
Don’t worry!
I have an idea!
Wow, Grandpa Slowy!
The books say to us
that the best way to counter enemies
is to give them what they want!
This is my specially-crafted fish food!
Wilie,
Daddy forgot to use weapons,
which is why I failed.
But with weapons, that changes!
Wow, Daddy!
I’ll show you just how powerful Daddy’s kung fu is!
Daddy has chased him off!
Let’s study from Grandpa Slowy instead.
There’s no way I’m studying from him!
I can’t let Slowy find the fragment first!
I have to hide it somewhere!
Daddy, what are you doing?
My son,
Daddy’s hungry;
can you go get some food?
Okay!
Aha!
Slowy!
Look what I found!
What is it?
Who did that?
Who dares to throw something at my face?
It was him.
He was here just now!
I didn’t throw the rock, little puffer!
I hate when people call me “little!”
Ouch!
Don’t you dare call me “little” again!
Help!
Wolffy, pull me out!
I hope you don’t mind staying here for a little bit.
Once I’ve found the fragment, I’ll come back to rescue you!
Wolffy, that’s cheating!
Daddy!
I brought food, Daddy!
Where’s Grandpa Slowy?
He’s elderly, and his back was hurting;
he said he was going to rest for a bit.
So I can’t study today?
How about Daddy teaching you some other stuff?
What are you going to teach me, Daddy?
Daddy is going to teach you
the power of wolves!
I’ll see if the book has it!
Forget about reading; just listen to Daddy!
Wilie!
Daddy!
Don’t worry, Daddy’s coming to rescue you!
Daddy, why don’t we get Grandpa Slowy to help?
Even without Slowy,
I can still rescue you!
Why are these jellyfish so difficult?
Do I really need that old goat to help me?
Are you looking for me?
You… Weren’t you stuck?
I’ll never be stuck if I keep reading!
I’m telling you—
Enough, Slowy!
Think of a way to rescue my son!
Let me think.
For how long?
The book says that there are many of them;
if touched by their tentacles, you’ll experience a sharp stinging sensation.
Just get to the point!
The book says
that there’s only one thing we can do.
So this is the “thing” that you speak of?
Dressing up as jellyfish?
Exactly!
Son!
Daddy!
Daddy,
I found this!
It’s the fragment!
They look very strange!
Think of something, Slowy!
There’s one last thing we can do!
What is it?
Run!
What? Is that all?
Stay—Stay away!
Daddy, help me!
Daddy!
It’s alright, son!
I’ll use state-of-the-art weapons to fight them!
Super Iron Wolf Punch!
Super Iron Wolf Clap!
Here comes my Iron Wolf Weapon,
the Super Iron Wolf Weapon!
Wow, Daddy!
Raise your hands higher!
It looks like learning some kung fu is actually pretty good!
Daddy, I want to learn even more about the power of wolves!
Daddy’s thought about it;
keeping in shape is important,
but
studying is very important, too!
Don’t fall behind!
Study well with Grandpa Slowy!
Okay!
End