Defender of the Seas
What should we do?
It’s not coming off at all!
Mine isn’t coming off, either.
Ever since the dark smog arrived yesterday,
this place has become more and more polluted.
Where am I supposed to find the kind of
cleaning agent spokesperson that my boss wants?
My boss says that they need to look clean and like to be clean.
If it’s not coming off, just forget it.
No, it’s just too dirty!
Looks clean…
Likes to be clean…
You’re it, Tibbie!
Quilly?
I’ve gotten yet another fragment!
Where’s my fragment?
Which one of them is my fragment?
Why isn’t it coming off?
I have to think of something!
Huh?
A cleaning agent spokesperson?
But I’ve never been a spokesperson before.
Just say yes, Tibbie!
I think you’d be perfect as a cleaning agent spokesperson!
Exactly!
Alright.
I’ll try it!
Yay!
My manager will definitely love
you being the cleaning agent spokesperson!
So what’s the first thing that the spokesperson does?
My manager says to wear this cape
and make a beautiful promotional video!
Why doesn’t this cleaning agent clear stains?
Don’t worry, use mine!
It’s the Cleaning Heroine!
Try out Universal Cleaner!
It gets to the root of the stain,
effectively removing even the stubborn ones
and leaving no trace!
It’s so clean!
There’s not a single stain at all!
Universal Cleaner,
the stain remover
that keeps you clean for life!
It’s been a whole day;
how come there still aren’t any people?
Yeah.
Why isn't it coming off?
What kind of cleaner is that?
It’s so cool!
This is our Universal Cleaner!
Universal Cleaner?
Then I’ll buy a few bottles!
Us, too!
Come on in and buy, everyone!
Okay!
Give me one! I want Universal Cleaner!
Just wait! Everyone gets one!
This cleaner works so well;
it removes every stain!
Removes every stain?
Tibbie?
Oh, right.
She probably won’t recognize me with all this mud on my face.
I’d like a box of Universal Cleaner!
We only have this one bottle left.
I’d like this bottle, then!
I claimed that bottle first!
Plus, I need it more than you do!
Liar!
I’ve been soaked so badly by the dark rain
that I can’t even stand up!
Oh, I don’t feel so good!
The pollutants have already entered by body;
I can’t take it anymore!
Outrageous!
Let's duel!
Bring it on!
Who’s scared of who?
I win!
The Universal Cleaner is mine!
If it weren’t for the pollutants gluing my hand,
I would have won!
I still have half a bottle here;
you can have it!
Thank you!
I’ll get rid of the fragment’s stain first.
It’s not the fragment?
Could the fragment still be in the mud?
It’s the cleaning agent spokesperson!
It’s Tibbie! Tibbie!
The city is clean all thanks to you!
Thank you, Sister Tibbie!
The dark smog is back again!
Don’t worry, everyone!
You’ve got me!
Wow!
You’re incredible, Tibbie!
It’s the dark smog again! Run!
Why is the smog worse now?
Forget it;
let’s go indoors for now!
What’s with all the smog recently?
It’s so unusual!
I don’t know, either.
Let’s go figure out what’s causing it.
Okay!
Look, Quilly.
Apparently, that factory is producing all of the smog!
We must stop them from polluting the environment even further!
Isn’t this the cleaning agent company’s logo?
What is our company’s logo doing over here?
Could it be
that our cleaning agents were all manufactured here?
What? There’s no way!
My manager wouldn’t do such things, like polluting the environment!
He gave me a job when I was at my most helpless.
He helped me.
My manager is a good guy;
someone must be impersonating our company!
But…
Okay!
Let’s go into the factory and explore
so we can get to the bottom of this!
Alright!
I’m going to prove my manager’s innocence!
Why is there a trap?
What now?
We can’t get in if there are traps!
Oh, yeah!
Why don’t we ask Weslie and the others for help?
The fragment must still be in here!
What are you doing?
I’m taking a mud bath.
Not this one!
You’re taking a mud bath, too?
Says who? I’m playing hide-and-seek!
Go somewhere else to play, little fish.
It’s so round; it must be the fragment!
Oh, yeah.
Clean off the mud with the cleaner!
It’s empty?
It’s the goats?
Oh, yeah!
I’ll ask Tibbie for some of the cleaning agent!
What are the goats doing all the way over here?
After analyzing,
the smog that was polluting us
did, indeed, come from here.
There’s no way!
This can’t be my manager’s factory!
Either way,
we have to shut down the factory’s machinery first.
No, the main door is way too strong;
we can’t get in.
Let me try!
Watch this!
Sparky, wait!
Super Overlord Morning Sun Punch!
Sparky!
There’s simply no way to get in through this door.
What now?
Who are you guys?
What are you doing at my factory?
This voice…
Quilly!
Did you guys come to mess around at my factory?
Manager, what are you doing here?
Quilly, instead of promoting the cleaning agent,
you brought strangers here to mess around?
The smog from your factory is polluting the living environment!
For the sake of the people, stop your processes right now!
Well, I don’t care about the environment.
The factory is mine;
if I don’t stop, what can you do about it?
Disturbing the environment for your own profits is not okay!
Quilly,
I can’t believe you’re helping others refute me!
I shall
let
you
go!
Quilly,
you dodged a bullet.
We can’t let him continue polluting!
Paddi,
do a full scan of the factory.
Alright!
Find its weak spot.
Found it!
The chimney leads directly to the inside of the factory!
Alright!
Let’s get inside of the factory through the chimney!
Go on, fishies!
Oh no,
the smog is too thick!
You guys can’t bring down my factory!
No!
Tibbie, use these cleaners!
Quilly?
I understand!
Manager,
I can’t just let you keep doing wrong!
All set!
It’ll work this time!
Go on, fishies!
Darn it!
All of my cleaning agent has escaped!
All of my cleaning agent is gone!
After analyzing,
the factory’s machinery is broken,
unable to produce smog again.
We did it!
Bubble rain of the cleaning agent!
At last, I can get clean!
A fruit shell?
Is the fragment still in the mud pit?
Tibbie,
it looks like there’s something stuck on Lightning Angel.
A fragment! It’s a fragment!
What?
Really?
It must be the universe rewarding Tibbie!
I can’t find it!
End