Paddi’s Marathon
Get up, Paddi!
Stop slacking off!
Everyone’s working hard to find fragments!
But we’ve been walking for so long and haven’t noticed one;
I’m so exhausted!
Haven’t we only been walking for five minutes?
Five minutes is still tiring!
Whatever; I’ll search over there.
That smells so good!
Grandpa, where did you get your baozi from?
Just sign your name over there, and you’ll get some.
Really?
Apparently, there’s such a thing as getting baozi
from just a signature!
I’d like kelp baozi, too!
Sure.
Just sign your name.
Okay!
Here.
They smell so good!
Great!
Congratulations on winning
the Undersea Marathon’s last entry!
Here’s your ticket!
What do you mean, “marathon?”
The Undersea Marathon!
This is our long-distance race here in Ocean City.
No, no, no!
I wasn’t trying to get into the marathon!
An Ocean Star fragment?
Paddi,
are you taking part in the marathon, too?
You’ll have to try hard!
Paddi
cannot possibly win!
You’re taking part as well, Wolffy?
Of course I am!
I’m determined to win the fragment!
Paddi,
have you found any fragments?
There’s a fragment inside of the marathon champion’s medal.
So that means that if we were to get the fragment,
we’ll have to win the marathon title first?
But Wolffy signed up for the marathon, too!
Let’s go back and ask Weslie for help.
You guys want the title, too?
Laughable!
Who are you?
He’s Lightning Marlin;
he was the champion of all of the past Undersea Marathons!
He’s that good?
You terrestrial creatures
are undeveloped in all four limbs
and simple-minded.
Just give up the race!
How the heck are we undeveloped?
Look at Sparky
and how strong his arms are!
Exactly! You think we’re simple-minded?
Look at Pa—
What are you saying, Sparky?
Whatever; don’t underestimate us!
If that’s the case,
let’s see what happens during the race!
The title will certainly be ours!
Let’s go!
What’s so good about the title?
I think the runner-up trophy
is more valuable, with how shiny it is!
Paddi,
you’re the only one who is qualified for the marathon right now.
Getting the fragment is entirely up to you!
But there’s no way I can complete
something as exhausting as a marathon.
I don’t want to participate.
Alright; you have two choices.
What choices?
One,
you participate in the race;
when the race is over, you’ll get to eat your favorite,
pine nut chocolate.
Two,
you participate in the race;
when the race is over, you’ll get to eat your least favorite,
carrot dumplings.
Of course I’m choosing to eat pine nut chocolate when it’s over!
So that means you’re agreeing to the race!
There’s no time to waste;
let’s start training!
Wait a minute!
How come something doesn’t feel right?
Come on!
I’m so tired!
Can I rest a bit after running so far?
How is this far?
You’ve only run one hundred meters!
That’s because I’m very hungry!
How am I supposed to have energy to run if my stomach is empty?
Keep it up, Paddi!
You’re close to getting the cake!
I want the cake!
Mmm!
Really?
Keep training once you’re done eating!
I know, I know.
I just remembered that Mr. Slowy was looking for me;
Sparky, why don’t you keep running with Paddi?
Alright!
Come on, let’s continue!
Fine.
I’m so tired.
Look,
I can’t even outrun a sea turtle!
How could I possibly win?
How about I run with you?
Training is so exhausting.
I’ll just tell them that I won’t do the race.
Weslie, are you okay?
Weslie,
why didn’t you tell us earlier
that you got injured while training with Paddi?
This is just a scratch;
Sparky, though, kept running for the whole time.
He worked even harder than I did.
You guys did a lot today.
Hopefully, Paddi can keep it up.
[CHEERING]
Go, Paddi!
Lightning Marlin is so handsome!
He is, he is!
Take your mark,
get set,
go!
The marlin is at it again!
He’s taken the lead once again!
It looks like he’s secured the title again this year!
Didn’t Wolffy sign up for the race, too?
Where is he?
What’s the use in running fast?
The title is mine, and mine only!
What are those things?
Oh no, Wolffy must have something up his sleeve!
I’ve hit the jackpot!
Affected by unforeseen circumstances!
Now, many of the runners have stopped running!
Paddi won’t be affected like the rest of them, right?
We have to trust him!
Right!
Take your time, everyone! I’ll be on my way!
Tornado Shoes!
Oh, yeah!
I almost forgot about my runner-up!
It’s so good!
No need to run, Mr. Sea Turtle.
They’re already so far ahead;
there’s no way we can win!
That’s fine!
I didn’t sign up for the race
just to win!
Go!
Go, Paddi!
Run, Paddi!
Go!
Right; for the sake of everyone,
I must keep racing!
But I can’t waste food, either;
I’ll finish eating first!
It’s time to speed up!
So there are traps?
Who’s doing this?
Of course it is
the celebrated Mr. Wolffy!
The title is mine!
Here comes a stink bomb!
Wolffy,
we’re taking this together!
I’m at the finish line!
I’ll stand right here
and wait for the first place person to pass
so I can get second place!
I’m so tired.
Run, Paddi!
The title is going to be yours!
The title?
Great!
Help! It stinks in here!
Lightning Marlin is in danger?
Sprint, Paddi!
Help!
Are you okay?
You…
Where’s Wolffy?
Great, the title is mine!
Oh, come on!
It stinks so bad! Someone help me!
Let’s have a fair competition!
Okay!
Congratulations to contestant Marlin
for winning the marathon title once again!
I went to the bathroom and returned in third place; what a loss.
This trophy…
I’ll give it to Uncle Crab instead.
Here.
Really?
You’re so kind, Paddi!
I’m the one with the title.
While you guys are undeveloped in all four limbs
as well as simple-minded,
at least you’re caring and righteous.
Let this be a thank you gift to you from me.
Thank you!
End