Never Giving up on You
Good news!
Jonie,
how did you suddenly lose so much weight?
Found it!
This is my last band-aid;
be careful when walking next time!
Paddi,
have you found the location of any fragments?
I detected a fragment that’s in the Algae Pool
of the Undersea Forest!
The other goats are all far away looking for fragments,
and it’ll take them a long time to get here.
I’m leaving this to you.
No problem!
I’ll make sure to find the fragment before Wolffy does!
Don’t even think about it!
Here I go!
Don’t worry, I’ll chase him right away!
Come and get me!
You have to be careful while driving.
Stop!
Due to the rapid growth of seaweed,
the terrain and environment
have become extremely difficult.
Therefore, when entering,
please ask a guide to show you the way.
And what if I go in without asking?
These are the consequences of entering freely.
I have to find a guide, then.
King Wolffy needs no guide!
A gold-level guide?
I need your help!
She’s our custodian, Auntie Goldfish.
I’m the gold-level guide and manager here.
In the Undersea Forest, there are places you can’t think of,
but no place that I can’t go to!
—Great! I’m—　—I’m filing a complaint!
I’m filing a complaint against Quilly!
He took the wrong road one too many times!
I’m sorry.
Quilly, you…
You’re fired!
Please give me one more chance!
You’ve received thirty complaints within three days!
Who’s giving my agency a chance with that, huh?
Hold on.
Are you willing to give me a chance?
Give me back your guide badge.
Sir,
you can’t fire Quilly!
Why?
Because I’ll take him!
So you won’t choose me, a gold-level guide,
but you’re choosing this embarrassment of a guide?
I trust
that Quilly will be able to take me to my destination!
Thank you, Jonie!
Fine.
If he can complete his task,
I’ll give him one more chance.
I’ll give it my all this time!
Why didn’t she choose me?
I need a gold-level guide!
I’m available!
Wait.
South is the danger zone.
It’s safest to go north.
To get to the Algae Pool, it’s safest to go north.
This way!
Are you sure?
I’m sure!
Okay!
Quilly,
are… are you sure this is the place?
I have a…
bad feeling about this!
I…
should be right.
What’s going on?
Help!
Run!
Jonie!
Look, it's a fragment!
This isn’t a fragment.
It’s a pearl.
Help!
You’re incredible!
You helped me find the fragment right away!
I, a gold-level guide, do live up to my name!
All done!
It’s time to lead me out, right?
That’s right!
It sure is time!
What did you take me here for?
I helped you find the fragment,
so it’s your turn to help me!
This is the souvenir shop;
it’s almost out of business.
Please buy some stuff!
I don’t have time.
Let’s
just
hurry up
and leave!
If the shop goes out of business,
my heart will be broken.
I just want to sit here for a while.
I could make some time.
Let’s head inside for now.
I’ll help you carry them.
I’m broke now!
You’re quite fervent
to buy so much at once!
Take me out of here!
Okay!
Next stop, the jewelry shop and the clothing shop!
Thank goodness we escaped.
Jonie,
have you gotten the fragment?
I’m almost at the destination.
We’re at the Undersea Forest entrance,
but we can’t get in without a guide,
so we’ll have to leave the fragment search to you.
Make sure to not let Wolffy get the fragment first!
Don’t worry;
with Quilly,
I’ll get the fragment!
Alright, then!
We’ll be waiting for you!
Quilly, let’s go!
Where’s Quilly?
Auntie Goldfish?
What are you doing here?
Quilly resigned; he asked me to come and give you directions.
Aren’t you a custodian?
I look like a custodian on the surface,
but through my efforts to learn about guiding,
I’ve now become a professional guide!
Either way, I’m better than him!
Jonie, have you gotten the fragment?
I’m almost at the destination.
Sir, I resign.
Have Auntie Goldfish lead the way for Jonie.
Alright, then!
We’ll be waiting for you!
Jonie only let me be her guide
because she pitied me.
I can’t let her get lost because of me.
What are you doing here?
Didn’t I have Auntie Goldfish to help you?
I told her to go back.
Why?
Because you’re my guide!
But I take the wrong roads.
Mr. Slowy once said that mistakes aren’t scary;
what’s scary is being afraid to never try again.
Are you not afraid of me letting you get lost?
Nope,
because I believe in you!
I’ll do it just for you!
Let’s go!
The next left is the Algae Pool!
What… What’s going on?
It looks like you held the map upside down.
Common sense says that the top of the map is north,
and the bottom is south.
I’ve failed again.
Roads are made by people;
let’s just go again!
The fragment is right here!
We’ve found the fragment!
Thank you, Quilly!
Stop it!
Wolffy!
Give me the fragment,
or else you guys will end up just like him!
Help me, Quilly!
The manager?
You added your own tourist locations
as compulsory purchases
while ignoring the feelings of tourists!
I hate guides like you!
No!
Sir!
He’s already been launched up to the surface!
Help me!
What a terrible spring chair!
I’m filing a complaint with the Consumers Association!
Get on, quick!
Come with me!
Trying to run?
I don’t think so!
Why did you stop?
Nowhere to run, huh?
Hand over the fragment to me!
It looks like giving the fragment to Wolffy is all we can do.
No! The fragment is very important to you!
But we’ve already been cornered!
You’re right.
Roads are made by people!
Trying to run?
Got you!
What the heck?
Oh, goodness!
Wolffy’s been tangled;
let’s go!
What’s taking Jonie so long?
She didn’t run into Wolffy, did she?
There she is!
Jonie,
great job!
I can’t believe you were able to find the fragment in such a difficult maze!
We were only able to get out
thanks to Quilly coming up with a plan!
Well, I only succeeded
because you didn’t give up on me, Jonie!
End