Striving for Excellence
Hey, thief!
This goat with the bell on his chest is incredible!
He’s the recently trending Weslie!
Soda cans are recyclable waste.
Expired medicines are hazardous waste.
A medal?
Who threw this out?
Doesn’t this medal belong to Tetra?
Do you know Tetra?
I met him once during a competition.
Then could you please return this to him?
Look, that silhouette looks a lot like Weslie!
That is Weslie, isn’t it?
Weslie?
What is it?
We need your help, Weslie!
Could you help me take a photo of a playbill, please?
Could you be our restaurant’s spokesperson, please?
Uh…
Help me first!
Help me first! Me first!
Excuse me, do you know Weslie?
I don’t,
but I’ve heard that he has a bell on his chest.
Okay, thank you.
Hello.
Can I ask why you’re looking for Weslie?
I have something very important to give to him.
Actually, I am Weslie.
Don’t believe me? Look at my bell!
Replica Weslie’s bells for sale!
Wear the bell, and we’re all Weslies!
For sale!
I’ll just go look for the real Weslie.
Your medal!
Uncle Mustache told me that it was Weslie who found it,
so I wanted to personally thank him.
Oh, yeah; Uncle Mustache knows me,
so we can ask him to prove that I’m Weslie!
By the way, what’s your name?
My name is Tetra.
Tetra?
Thank goodness it’s still here.
You seem to care a lot about that medal.
That’s because this is the medal I got
from my very first competition.
Did you win the title?
No,
it was a consolation medal.
There must be some meaning behind it, right?
Wait!
Did you not see that it’s a red light?
I can’t see.
What?
He’s blind?
Apparently, he can’t see anything at all,
yet he wanted to find me to say thank you!
I must protect him!
My plane!
I’m sorry!
Wait!
What’s wrong?
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
I saw that you were about to—
Actually, you don’t have to worry about me.
Ever since I came here from the underground tunnels,
everyone wants to protect me
because I can’t see.
Just like you just now.
But not being able to see really is very dangerous!
I’m fine.
A long time ago,
our ancestors were driven into dark underground tunnels
by flooding.
As time passed,
because they couldn’t use their eyes,
they eventually lost their vision.
However,
this doesn’t affect
any of our other senses.
Therefore, we can protect ourselves!
It’s just that other fish don’t believe me.
Oh, I see.
I’m sorry.
After all this time, I still haven’t found the fragment.
I’m so tired.
Could the fragment be on them?
Alright, I’ll just attack them from behind!
Wait, something’s not right.
Have I been caught?
Let’s go this way.
The fragment is mine!
Never mind; to the left.
Going right then left; what are they doing?
What’s that sound?
It’s a waterspout!
We avoided the waterspout back there thanks to you!
Thanks!
No need to thank me.
By the way,
wasn’t there something you wanted to give to Weslie?
I want to give this to him to thank him.
An Ocean Star fragment!
What’s that sound?
Wolffy!
I just knew that the fragment was with you guys!
Run, Tetra!
Hand over the fragment!
How come he wants this fragment?
It’s a long story;
I’ll explain later!
Run, Tetra!
I’ll distract him!
You want to run,
but you didn’t ask King Wolffy, did you?
My medal!
The fragment is mine now!
You’re not getting it!
Give it to me!
You can’t get away, Weslie!
How about now, huh?
Go away!
Are you okay?
I’m..
o—
—kay.
Look, I got it!
When did you pick up the medal?
Isn’t this medal super important to you?
Thank you.
Then the fragment is mine!
Again?
Come on, at least let me touch it!
I’m not giving you the fragment,
because you’re a bad person!
Hand over the fragment right now!
I don’t believe that I can’t catch you!
It looks like you guys treat me like I’m Wilie
if King Wolffy doesn’t do this the hard way, huh?
Super Mode,
activated!
Keep hiding!
I’ll get you guys soon!
How’s your injury?
It’s okay.
Let’s get out of here.
I didn’t realize you could do all this.
That means you believe me now, right?
We’re almost at the exit!
You guys have nowhere to run!
I have an idea!
Hand over the fragment right now!
It’s our turn to fight back!
What the heck is going on?
Oh, come on!
I’ll be back!
Uncle Mustache’s house is right up ahead!
“I’m not home at the moment.
“Please come back for me in a few days.”
Oh, Uncle Mustache isn’t home.
Look, everyone! It’s Weslie!
Weslie, can I get an autograph?
Can I get an autograph, Weslie?
Weslie!
So it turns out he is the real Weslie!
Hey, Weslie, your gift!
End