A Skincare Event
My face!
No!
I don’t want pimples!
What’s wrong, Wolnie?
How horrifying!
I can’t believe I dreamt that I had pimples on my face!
Wolnie, your face…
What’s wrong with my face?
Pimples!
Where are the skincare products I just bought?
Where in the world did they go?
What’s wrong, Madam Wolnie?
My skincare products are gone!
I threw them all out.
Don’t take my skincare products!
Pay back my skincare products, Slowy!
Those are all harmful products!
They were so expensive;
how could they be harmful?
Here’s the test report on those items;
read it.
Apparently, they contain all these harmful substances!
It’s better that they’re gone, Wolnie!
My skin growing pimples is what’s harmful!
Go get my skincare products back to me
right now!
Stop, Madam Wolnie!
Health is the most important thing!
Let go!
Wolnie, you and Slowy can just talk about it.
It’s none of your business!
Well, I’ll just go retrieve the skincare products.
Poor Slowy.
It must be around here somewhere.
What a creepy swamp!
The radar says
that the fragment is in the swamp.
How are we supposed to get into such a dangerous place?
Forget it!
Let’s go!
No!
That’s too dangerous!
Don’t worry;
I’m prepared!
Let’s take a nap before thinking of a solution.
Is sleeping all you care about?
I’ve got it!
Let’s…
Where is Uncle Crab?
Are they searching for fragments?
I’ll follow them and see!
I’ll make some natural skincare products for Madam Wolnie.
One pearl,
two pieces of seagrass,
and three drops of tears.
Three drops of tears?
I’ll have to do it this way.
Ouch!
All done!
The recipe also requires deep sea swamp mud.
Looks like I’ll have to head out!
It’s all Slowy’s fault for throwing out my skincare products!
But good thing
he didn’t notice this place!
You’re still here;
thank goodness!
“Madam Wolnie, health comes first.”
Slowy’s message?
This was my last skincare product,
Slowy!
I hate you!
It’s Wolffy!
Keep it up, everyone!
The fragment is right up ahead!
The fragment is mine!
The fragment is ours!
That wasn’t me!
It really wasn’t
me!
We’re sinking!
Help!
It’s the fragment!
It’s mine!
Come here, Wolffy!
Stop moving, Wolffy!
The more you move, the more you’ll sink!
Why didn’t you say so?
With this deep sea swamp mud,
I can help Madam Wolnie with her skincare!
Slowy!
There you are!
Madam Wolnie,
perfect timing!
Keep still.
Ew!
Slowy,
today I’m going to
fight you!
Stop chasing me!
Madam Wolnie, I can explain!
I don’t care!
I’m not letting you go today!
Stay away!
Help!
Slowy,
stop!
You can’t run from me, Slowy!
Madam Wolnie,
let me explain!
Stop running!
I… I’m not running.
Slowy!
Stay away!
Danger!
Quiet!
This is bad.
What is this?
Oh no!
It’s a swamp whirlpool!
I don’t want to die!
Don’t worry;
we still have the submarines!
Daybreak!
I don’t want to die!
My pimples aren’t gone yet!
Grab onto that rock!
Madam Wolnie!
Wolnie!
Wolffy?
Mr. Slowy?
You guys are here, too?
Summon the submarines!
We tried to,
but the submarines are stuck in the quicksand.
Then what should we do?
Think of something, Mr. Slowy!
Now, we can only rely on the submarines assembling for escape.
But how are we supposed to assemble in this situation?
We can use the whirlpool
to gather the submarines together!
I can’t hold on anymore!
Help!
Wolffy! Wolnie!
Weslie!
Kids, assemble now!
Magic assembly,
unmatchable energy!
Kids!
We’re alright, Mr. Slowy!
Save my Sirius!
We’re safe at last.
Wolffy!
Wolnie, the pimples on your face!
What happened?
The pimples on my face are gone!
It must have been the clay skincare mask that I applied to you.
Clay skincare mask?
Slowy, why didn’t you say so?
You were so mad
that I didn’t get a chance to.
I’m so pretty!
Slowy!
There are another two pimples on my face!
Help me get rid of them, quick!
Hold on.
Let me see them first.
Where are they?
Here.
Look at how big they are!
Don’t worry;
we’ve got the Health and Beauty Code!
You only need to apply this clay skincare mask once.
It’s comfortable!
Wolnie,
I’ve made a batch of
a naturally beautifying skincare product!
Really?
Based on my experiences,
this doesn’t look so good.
What do you know, Slowy?
I made this according to my Health and Beauty Code, you know!
Have you tried it, then?
You’re going to test it for me!
No way!
End