The Best Choice
Sweeping the floor is gross,
wiping the windows is tiring,
patrolling is hard,
and cooking is overstimulating.
Is there not an easy choice?
Little goats,
hand over the fragment!
Paddi,
find an escape route!
Roger that!
Hurricane, search for
the best escape route!
Found it!
Alright!
Paddi,
lead the way!
Okay!
What’s wrong?
Go!
It’s too dangerous up ahead; we can’t go!
But there’s even more danger behind us!
Let’s just go for it!
Why isn’t it working?
Help!
Danger ahead. Please scatter.
What’s going on?
If we had kept going ahead…
Thank goodness…
Hurricane is so accurate!
With Hurricane, I don’t need to worry about anything!
Hurricane, which way do we go?
Let’s go left;
there’s a waterspout on the right.
There really is a waterspout over there!
Danger ahead. Take cover.
Take cover, everyone!
Your Hurricane is amazing, Paddi!
Of course it is!
Then can Hurricane detect where any fragments are?
Hurricane,
locate a fragment.
Found one!
There’s a fragment in the canyon below!
Alright!
Full speed ahead to the fragment!
Okay!
Why did you stop?
Danger ahead. Take caution.
Danger!
It doesn’t look dangerous at all here.
My Thunderbolt is quick,
so I’ll go down there and check.
Stay up here and wait.
What if Weslie runs into danger
and needs help?
I must go down with him!
Don’t go!
Tibbie,
wait for me!
Hurricane says it’s dangerous down there;
why aren’t you guys listening?
Jonie,
look at them!
Jonie?
Wait for me! I’m coming, too!
Weslie, where are you guys?
What is this?
I’ll try one!
These are golden seagrapes.
Is there more food?
What’s going on?
I… I guess it’s…
actually quite dangerous down here.
Look, guys!
There’s a fragment in his mouth!
I’ll grab it!
We’ll help you, Sparky!
Yay! We got it!
I told you guys it’s dangerous down here,
but you didn’t listen!
It’s your fault!
Hurricane,
what's the best route to escape the big fish?
It is suggested to hide in the seagrass bushes up ahead.
Hide in the seagrass bushes!
Look,
the big fish is tied up in the seagrass!
But we’re all tied up, too!
The fish is breaking out!
Hurricane,
how do we get the fish to calm down?
It is suggested to find something to distract the fish.
The fish is angry because of the fragment.
Oh, yeah!
Can’t we just give the fragment back to him?
No!
It took so long for us to get it!
But we can get it back later!
Here!
Good thing we have Hurricane.
Paddi!
The submarines are broken!
Don’t worry;
I’ll fix everyone up in a moment!
I can help, too!
Wolffy?
Let’s assemble!
Magic assembly, our force is unending!
Hurricane,
how do we escape this crisis right now?
Paddi, what are you doing?
Come assemble!
Hurricane, what should we do now?
Based on analysis,
it is suggested to run.
Don’t assemble right now!
Let’s run!
Huh?
You guys keep running;
I’ll take care of him!
Got one!
Weslie!
Got two!
Tibbie!
What’s going on today?
A special offering?
Don’t even think about running!
Run, Paddi!
Jonie!
It’s all my fault
that everyone’s been captured!
I can’t just run off like this;
I’ll be back to rescue you guys!
You guys…
You guys just wait for me!
Overweight? Slowed down?
Alright, Paddi;
I’ll catch you next time!
It is suggested to retreat.
I’m going to make my own decisions this time!
Come with me, big fish!
Tell me,
where’s the fragment?
The fragment is on Hurricane.
Then where’s Hurricane?
Behind you!
Huh?
Here I come!
Go, big fish!
The fragment?
Help me! Help!
We’ll be on our way, Mr. Wolffy!
Goodbye!
Don’t leave!
Help me!
Thank you for saving us, Paddi!
Your Hurricane is amazing!
I think I can’t rely on Hurricane too much.
In a pinch, I have to rely on myself!
End