The Undersea Chef
Wolnie! Wilie!
It’s time to eat!
It’s been hot outside lately;
having some cold kelp is perfect.
Mr. Slowy, your food is so good!
I want more!
Slow down!
Don’t choke!
What’s so good about
some basic cold kelp?
I’ll demonstrate my high-end chef skills!
How about it?
Don’t waste food, Wolffy!
We can’t eat any more!
I made some sour plum drink to take the edge off;
who wants some?
Me! Me!
I need to hurry up and gather all of the fragments
and get Slowy out of here!
Undersea Chef Cooking Competition!
Paddi,
we’re here to look for fragments,
not for food!
Don’t slack off!
It’s not that;
I…
I just wanted to see
if there were fragments here or not.
There is a fragment!
The fragment is embedded in that trophy!
How come residents under the sea
are always putting fragments on the champion’s prizes?
It looks like
if we want to get the fragment,
we’ll have to compete.
Leave it to me, then!
An Ocean Star fragment?
Turns out, it’s on this trophy!
It’s the goats again!
I’d like to participate!
Your name is…?
Wolffy!
What-ffy?
Wo-what?
Wolffy, Wolffy, Wolffy!
Old man, my name is Wolffy!
Oh, Wolffy!
Our sign-up time concludes at four;
come back next year!
How am I supposed to get into the competition?
I left my frying pan at my kitchen;
could you go over there and get it for me?
Sure.
Got it!
Contestants, please enter the venue!
We’re about to enter;
where is he?
Your frying pan is here!
Finally!
Who are you?
I…
I’m your assistant!
How… How did you get so much darker?
Uh… It’s because it’s very sunny out,
so I got tanned after being out here.
Then how did you get so much fatter?
Forget about that;
let’s enter the venue!
One, two, one, two…
What a great pose!
It looks like Chef Octo might have a chance!
Try it!
I made this before the competition as practice.
Okay!
How is it?
This xianbing has a rather unusual taste.
That’s for sure!
Its filling was made from seafloor mud;
a full flavor of the sea!
It’s good, right?
Seafloor mud?
Great!
You’ve never been this happy before!
I’ll make a few more!
One, two, one, two…
He’s going to lose the competition this way;
I have to stop him from making that dish!
I know!
Chef Octo, your Volcano Restaurant is on fire!
What?
My restaurant!
These disgusting xianbing should be thrown out.
The restaurant isn’t on fire!
What are you doing?
This xianbing is so good
that I couldn’t resist eating a few more!
If you swapped in some normal fillings,
such as cheese, garlic, or something like that,
it’ll be even better!
Thank you!
You really do love my dishes,
and you’re giving me such good advice!
With your chef skills, Chef Octo,
there’s no way you’re winning the title!
Assistant,
since you liked my xianbing so much,
I made these especially for you!
Why don’t you take them with you before the competition ends?
There… There’s no need!
Come on, go ahead!
Take them!
There’s really no need!
Sorry!
Are… you okay?
It doesn’t really taste the same as before.
It tastes so much better!
Really?
I specially made these xianbing to thank you!
I considered your preferred tastes this time,
using the cheese that you like!
As it turns out,
I realized, thanks to you,
that being sensitive to the feelings of customers
is the true meaning of using our hearts!
Could it be that the reason why Chef Octo’s food before was so gross
was because of the weird ingredients he used?
Where’d he go?
Chef Octo,
what are you doing in here?
I don’t know why,
but I feel very safe in this barrel.
What the heck?
Let me check the encyclopedia.
Apparently, all octopuses have a hiding instinct.
Don’t sleep, Chef Octo!
The Undersea Cooking Competition begins now!
Contestants, please take your mark!
The competition is starting!
Chef Octo!
Get up, Chef Octo!
I’ll have to do it!
The competition begins now!
Let’s take a look at how our fellow contestants are doing!
Our contestants have begun to prepare their own dishes!
Contestant Four isn’t doing anything!
There are so few ingredients left;
it’s not enough at all!
Chef Octo is so careless.
He brought so little ingredients.
Good thing I brought more for him.
But…
Where is he?
Where’d he go?
Chef Octo?
Add some jade seaweed!
And add some golden kelp!
Our ocean stew
will definitely win first place!
What should I do now?
It’s been hot outside lately;
having some cold kelp is perfect.
I made some sour plum drink to take the edge off;
who wants some?
Use your heart.
Daddy!
I know what to make!
Wolnie,
eggs are good for your skin.
Son, have some mushrooms
to balance your health!
Time’s up!
The judges will taste the contestants’ dishes in order.
Why is there a barrel here?
The cover isn’t even on!
Why is it dark?
What time is it?
I can’t get out!
Assistant,
where are you?
This is my proud dish,
golden kelp soup!
So good!
Great job, Tibbie!
Now, let’s see the final contestant’s dish!
What?
Just instant noodles?
Go ahead.
I didn’t realize that ordinary noodles could be so elastic!
Not too soft, not too hard, but just right!
Plus, it sucks in the essence of the soup’s flavor!
The egg is cooked just right,
the sweet yolk melting in the mouth!
When I was little,
I was always picky and never ate mushrooms,
so my father put a seasoning that I liked on the mushrooms,
and it became my favorite food.
I didn’t think that I’d get to taste
such a familiar flavor outside!
How touching!
Thank you
for allowing me to taste such a wonderful dish!
The results are in!
Our champion is
Contestant Four’s assistant!
Finally!
A barrel?
Is it Chef Octo?
Congratulations, sir!
This trophy is yours!
Even though I’m a villain,
I’m a villain with senses!
The trophy can be claimed later,
but I have to rescue Chef Octo now!
Darn it, I can’t catch up!
Just in time!
I didn’t notice
that my assistant was just you, Wolffy, in a costume.
Thank you for rescuing me!
It’s you who made me understand
how to make food that people like!
I should thank you, too!
By the way,
how did the competition go?
Oh no!
The trophy!
What?
Yes.
I’m very sorry.
Since you left during the award ceremony,
we gave the trophy
to the second place, Tibbie.
My own trophy got taken!
Don’t worry; although you might have not gotten the trophy,
we got the secret to making delicious food!
You’re right.
Time to head back and cook!
Wolnie, son,
dinner is ready!
Daddy,
the noodles you made smell so good!
Slowy, you—
They smelled so good
that even I couldn’t resist eating some!
End