The Last Fragment
Paddi,
have you found the location of the fragment?
Paddi’s room is all messy again!
What are you guys doing here?
The radar sounded;
we came to check the fragment’s location.
Radar?
Actually, it was just my alarm clock.
It’s been so many days;
why hasn’t the radar
found an Ocean Star fragment yet?
Good news!
Mr. Slowy?
You guys and Wolffy
have collected all of the fragments!
Really?
Great!
Tomorrow, we’ll come over and reform the fragments with you!
Get ready!
I’ve got to get ready, too!
I’ll be able to move back tomorrow!
See you tomorrow, kids!
Goodbye, Mr. Slowy!
Wolffy is voluntarily agreeing to reform the fragments with us?
Oh, yeah.
Based on what he’s done in the past one thousand episodes,
something must be wrong!
Then what should we do now?
Grandpa Slowy!
Grandpa Slowy,
I’m going to miss you!
Wilie…
Wolnie.
There, there.
You can come to Goats’ Village whenever you want to find me!
Also, I’ve prepared a gift for you!
They’re safety glasses!
You love watching TV;
just wear the safety glasses, and your vision will be fine.
Thank you, Mr. Slowy!
Wolnie, I’ve prepared a gift for you as well.
Me, too?
I’ve been a bother for the time i’ve been here,
so let these gifts be thank you gifts.
These are labor-saving gloves;
from now on, no matter how many things you buy, they won’t be too heavy.
Thank you!
Slowy!
Why are you still here?
Go!
The ceremony is about to begin!
Alright, I know!
By the way,
I also prepared a gift for you!
A gift?
Look, Daddy!
Village Chief Slowy gave these gifts to us!
Yours is over there!
I didn’t think that Slowy would prepare a gift for me!
How dare you mess with me!
Slowy,
just wait and see!
In a moment, I’ll touch my cup,
and the helpers I hired will jump in
and snatch the Ocean Star!
That way, I can activate my Invincible Overlord Gun!
When the time comes…
Wolffy smiling like that must mean that there’s a trap.
Don’t worry;
Uncle Crab has already found us a helper!
When they hear the burp signal,
he’ll jump out to help!
Leave the burping to me!
By the way, what’s our objective this time?
It’s to help Wolffy snatch an Ocean Star.
What’s an Ocean Star?
It’s a big, blue ball.
Mr. Slowy,
how are we supposed to reform the Ocean Star?
Just put the fragments close together,
and they’ll automatically reform.
Oh no!
Wolffy,
we, the Undersea Trio, are here!
A big blue ball!
The big blue ball is ours!
What?
Why are you taking Paddi?
Burp, Paddi!
The name is Master.
What seems to be the problem?
Can you help me pick up all of the fragments on the ground?
No problem!
Bro,
this big blue ball seems to have lost its color!
Let go of Paddi!
Slowy,
why couldn’t the Ocean Star reform?
The book says that if there are one hundred fragments,
it’ll reform!
You don’t have one hundred.
You obviously only have ninety-nine!
Since my job is done,
I’ll take my leave.
Mr. Slowy, how come we’re missing a fragment?
Wolffy,
why are we missing one?
Didn’t you say that you gathered fifty?
Uh…
Well,
it’s possible
that I miscounted.
Since that’s the case,
let’s immediately go look for the last fragment!
Okay!
Wait a minute!
Wolffy,
you haven’t paid us yet!
Uh…
Can I do it later?
Mr. Slowy,
the radar has already located the fragment.
Look!
Let’s get going right away!
I think you should clean up your room right away;
you’re not coming with us for the fragment search!
Let’s go.
Look, the last fragment is right there!
There’s no time to waste;
let’s get it and go back!
Thanks for leading the way!
Wolffy followed us!
The last fragment is mine!
We got it!
How did we succeed so easily?
Forget it;
let’s go back and reform!
Don’t think that you guys will get to reform just like that!
That was just my remotely-controlled Sirius!
The best
is yet to come!
Cleaning my room is exhausting.
Waiting for you to come out is exhausting, too!
Wolffy!
We’ve got the last fragment!
Weren’t you at Bubble Canyon?
How did you get back faster than us?
That was my remote-controller;
I was here the whole time.
What?
We’ve been fooled!
Let’s cut to the chase!
Paddi is in my hands right now;
I’ll trade him for the last fragment!
How does that sound?
You’re evil!
Mr. Slowy, what now?
We can’t leave Paddi.
Let’s trade!
Slowy gets it!
Reform,
Ocean Star!
No need for this Cube anymore!
It worked!
The pollutants are gone!
Alright!
Ocean Star, load up!
The Invincible Overlord Gun is back to life!
Onto the submarines, everyone!
Trying to run?
Sirius, fire!
Danger!
Keep firing! Don’t stop!
Oh no!
Wolffy is shooting the residents!
Sir, how can we help you?
The Invincible Overlord Gun paired with the Ocean Star
really can make all creatures listen to me!
Go capture those submarines for me!
Yes, sir!
Wolffy has possessed the residents!
Oh, yeah; the more, the better!
I’ll shoot even more fish to help me catch goats!
Wolffy,
the Ocean Star is still in its transformation stage;
its energy is very unstable!
Take it out right now!
I’ll have time to take it out once I’ve taken over the world!
Boys,
go!
Darn it, we’ve been surrounded!
Mr. Slowy, what now?
They’re all innocent residents that have been possessed;
we can’t hurt them!
Then you’re coming home with me!
Wolnie, we’re eating mutton today!
Really?
Yes!
We must celebrate my achieving my dream of taking over the world!
What are you doing?
I need to vent!
I need to vent, too!
No more venting! Get out!
Yes, sir!
I’ll say, those fish are rather hyper, huh?
Wolffy,
the Ocean Star is still in its transformation stage
and is easy to be overloaded!
You have a lot to say, huh? I’m eating you first!
Wolffy,
Slowy has lived with us for so long,
and he even gave us gifts.
I just feel like it’s not right.
They’re just gloves after all; I can make more for you!
Daddy, you’re hurt!
I’ll help you patch it up!
What a nice son;
he even prepared a first aid kit for me!
Actually, Grandpa Slowy was the one
who gave this smart first aid kit to you.
So Slowy really did prepare a gift for me?
Don’t think you can just change my instincts like that!
I’m eating you for sure today!
Who’s venting now?
Huh?
It’s Sirius’ Invincible Overlord Gun!
To be continued