The Heroes’ Return
Oh no, the Overlord Gun is flying away!
The city is descending into chaos!
This isn’t good.
Wolffy,
we have to work together!
Saving the world is up to you guys;
I’ll be on my way!
You’ve got to at least let us out first!
What now?
We can’t just stay trapped here!
I have an idea!
Hey, guys!
Before your master left, he told me
that he’s giving you this cage for venting!
Now’s our chance! Get on the submarines!
Let’s head downtown right away!
Help!
Taxi!
Go!
Don’t you guys know how to ride in a civilized manner?
Help me!
Don’t push!
Whose foot is this?
Sorry, that’s my seventh foot!
Let’s find a safe place before thinking of a solution.
On the surface, we’re safe!
Daddy,
what’s that?
The Grassland Trio?
What are you guys doing here?
Ever since the goats left,
there’s no one to clean up the grassland,
and it’s getting dirtier and dirtier.
So we decided to move to the undersea city.
The undersea city?
Wait a minute!
Oh no!
The Grassland Trio have been corrupted!
Is everyone okay?
Stay back, Wilie!
They’re so scary!
The goats are still in the dirty sea;
aren’t they in lots of danger?
They’re out of here at last.
Where’s our son?
Son!
I’m coming to save you, goats!
Hurry!
Hurry after him!
The Magic Submarine!
That was very dangerous, Wilie!
Good thing we made it in time.
I want to fight with you guys!
Wolffy!
Son!
Don’t go out alone, son!
I just wanted to be a hero like Daddy!
Now that you’re here,
let’s resolve this crisis together.
Alright!
I’ll do it!
Wolffy and I have analyzed it.
The Overlord Gun’s loss of control
was caused by the Ocean Star’s dark energy erosion.
We just need
to switch the Overlord Gun to absorb mode
in order to activate the Ocean Star’s energy reverse transformation.
With this, the purification power will skyrocket,
sucking up the pollutants
and return everyone back to normal!
But the entire city is filled with corrupted fish right now;
are we supposed to go in there
and capture that flying Overlord Gun?
That’s impossible!
It’s our last hope for saving the ocean;
no matter how slim the chances are,
we must do it!
Weslie’s right!
I’m coming with you guys, too!
Me, too!
Us, too!
Slowy,
let’s go!
We’ll maintain this speed
and head into the city center!
Wolffy,
there’s a bunch of corrupted fish coming up!
Bring it on!
You’re no match!
This is bad!
A massive corrupted fish is nearing us,
and it’s not the only one!
We’ve been surrounded;
what should we do?
No matter what, we can’t stop!
Let’s speed through!
That’s right.
We’re fighting them!
Although we successfully entered the city center,
the submarines are completely broken now.
Take these, kids.
We’ll have to go on foot from here.
The corrupted fish are coming again!
We’ve escaped those corrupted fish at last.
But everyone’s split up;
what now?
Forget it!
The only thing we can do now
is to get to the Overlord Gun and get rid of it!
What’s that sound?
Is it the corrupted fish again?
No,
it’s the Overlord Gun!
Wolnie!
Son!
Daddy!
Wilie,
run!
Daddy!
Go!
Wolffy!
Wolffy,
why did you lock me in here, too?
I’m out of Sleepy Bullets!
I’ve only got one left, too.
We can’t keep this up for much longer!
The Overlord Gun is flying over here!
The corrupted fish are coming again!
How are we supposed to take care of the Overlord Gun like this?
Sparky!
Make the Overlord Gun fly this way!
Sawyer!
Weslie,
look for the power switch!
Mr. Slowy,
I don’t see a power switch!
The switch must be on the other side!
What now?
Weslie,
when I count to three, jump!
One,
two,
three!
They did it!
“After this series of twists and turns,
“the Ocean Star’s transformation period
“ended smoothly.
Remember to visit!
You guys still owe me a lot of shells!
Goodbye!
“Now,
“because the traffic is no longer jammed,
“Mari took a long vacation to travel.
“Uncle Crab has started to sell marine items.
“Sawyer has recently done a sculpture showcase
“in Central Park.
“Chef Octo stopped using weird ingredients in his food,
“and Volcano Restaurant’s ratings are getting better and better!
“As for me, I’ve finally found a suitable career!
“Come visit when you’re free!
“—Your good friend, Quilly”
I miss them, Mr. Slowy!
Let’s go under the sea right now to play with them!
Not now.
Have you forgotten that we still have a job to do?
Return Green Green Grassland to its previous state!
This is a massive task;
do you have the heart to do it?
Yes!
Then let’s begin!
Alright!
Here we go!
End