Catch her and can’t let her out
ah
Just pass through this waterfall and it will be safe
Oh no, my kirishi
Well done Curiosity
Take her back
Princess Luna
Fulai?
How did you be here?
Ah your hand...
Run quickly
He actually jumped down
Report Team Leader
I got the magic stone
OK Let’s go back to report to the Queen
Let’s prepare your picnic
good
OK I’ll open the sun
Ah, finished
Help
Paddi
What can you do without us in the future
You’re fine
I’m fine
Or do you go and pick apples
Yes OK
You’re fine
Or I’ll come
You go and help them get the pads first
good
I can always get the slap
My wall, don’t run
Let’s help you
Come and have something to eat
cake
Brother Yangyang
This is the greatest amount to you
Cake My favorite
oops
How about my cake...
Paddi
It’s okay
There’s also here
you…
Thank you very much
Haha I’ll find some water to wash
Really
The goat always makes people so uneasy
- ah…
What’s wrong? Goat
There are two people...
Falling on the river
what…
- You’re awake
Who are you?
Where is this?
Here is the green grassland
I just realized that you were lying on the river
You’re fine
Green grassland?
It seems that we have escaped from the Catland?
Uh uh…
Fulai
He suffered a heavy injury
Although urgent treatment was done
But the situation is not very good
Are you doing me
This is...
The wounds disappeared
Can you tell me you are a monster?
Don’t be so unpretentious
This is Qili
Qili
Yes, actually I...
Luna is in danger, leave quickly
You’re fine
Don’t be afraid that they are not bad people
How is it possible
How do goat and wolf get together
This is a long time...
I didn’t expect that the wolf and the goat could become good friends
Then why do you fall on the river
This is because...
My name is Luna
The place where I live is called the Cat Country
People there use different powers
And my dad and mom
It is the king and queen of the strange cat country
I also have a sister named Levana
But it’s not good since the small body
And he is our good friend
To please my sister
We often go out to play secretly
But one day...
We missed the forbidden area
Meet a mysterious person
He exuded the dark energy sealed by his father
My sister is protecting me
Being hit by dark energy
Fortunately, Dad arrived with the soldiers
Catching the mysterious man into prison
However, the sister who woke up from a coma
A big change in temperament and a big increase in power
She asked everyone to listen to her
Because of dad and mom’s stopping
My sister also attacked her father and mother
Finally, Dad is widowed
Give me the magic stone
And use the final power
Let me escape from the Imperial Palace
And that’s the case...
Why did your sister suddenly become like this?
I don’t know either
She wasn’t like this before
But I want to save my dad and mom
They should be able to help their sister restore their original state
But Princess Luna
The palace is too dangerous now
We don’t have the time to get close
Let’s help you
Thank you
But everyone in the Cat Kingdom will use the Cat
It’s hard for ordinary people to fight
I’m grateful for your kindness
no problem
We are not ordinary goat and wolf
- Ah when did you prepare
This doesn’t matter
What is important is to have more people and more strength
We are also guardians of Yangcun
There is absolutely no problem with ability
Are you...really willing to help me?
Of course
Control item movement
It’s Qili, who I am mainly good at
Magic power is really convenient
Come on now
Wolffy
Come here
Ah, I almost forgot
Wolffy
Catch it quickly
Hanging wall
Must come back safely
Red
We’re leaving
See you again, brother and sister
Where is this place?
Sexy
It’s so big afog in front
Everyone is relieved
Wow, what a big waterfall
Next we’re going to walk through this waterfall
Aren’t your cats afraid of water?
Don’t worry
Leave
etc…
You’re not afraid of me
Goat
Do me, I can’t hold it in
Can’t hold it in, you can still say?
Yes
oops! My sling...
Now the red is going to get angry
Wow…
This is the same as the dream
We can only get here
There is boundary here protected
From here is the Catland
Then let’s go in quickly
What’s it?
What a big rat
This is the miracle that guards the gate of the boundary
Will attack the invaders from outside
Everyone, let’s go
No need to see me!
Everyone, run away!
Luna…
No effect at all
Weslie: Use a squid to make it
- Success
ah…
magic stone?
Could it be that it fell here before?
Weslie
Catch the magic stone
After absorption, you will have the ability
Strange...power...stone
What happened