Paddi
See if you can use amazing power
good
Nothing to feel
Help
Paddi
Stopped
Give me a
We’re here to help, too
We can’t hold on
Quickly concentrate and use amazing force
- Weslie
It’s about to be shut down
Everyone, hold on
Focus quickly
Concentration Concentration
Oh, why can’t I get it out?
ah…
Everyone…
- Run quickly with the goat
Don’t remember
Let’s go and help
ah
Luna
The ground is about to collapse
Stop your mouth quickly
Come here
The Paddi, wake up the strange clouds
I can’t make it
Do you want to do
I don’t want to… let everyone suffer
Give me a gift!
You may harm my friend
Paddi
Leave it to me
It’s time to me
Paddi…
Come on
Um
Win
You’re just stunned
Fear and tired
Thank you
No thanks, old man
Everyone’s injuries have been cured
Does everyone in the Cat Country have Qili?
There was originally
But my sister prevented the villagers from helping me
Use only the remaining seal powder
Eliminate everyone’s power
So scary…
Sorry, I’ll take you to such a dangerous place
It’s okay
We will definitely help you protect the cat country
you…
Let’s go out quickly
Um
Wow
This is the Catland
Where should we go?
above
So high, how do we get up?
We can get there by taking the train
You follow me
I’ll take you to the station
Enemy invasion
I’ll sue the Queen immediately
Wow, it’s so beautiful here
Hello
strangeness
Do you feel the residents here
Very scared
That’s my ball
Give it to you
thank you
What’s your name?
I have lollipops for you
My name is…
What’s going on
Since my sister became the queen
No one dares to talk to people anymore
It turns out to be like this
But as long as we turn our sister back
Everyone can live happily like before
Um
It’s almost time to arrive at the station
Everyone, get down
It’s a soldier, be careful
Catch them
So many soldiers
With our ability, we can’t deal with them
Only use the big move
You shouldn’t be…
Run quickly
Everyone, let’s go
What about the Slowy
Oops
Stop and don’t run
Here
It seems to be taking them off
Let’s take a break first
OK
Ahhhhh…
Be careful
How could this be…
Wolffy
The wolf fell off the cliff
Don’t worry
Wolffy…
Don’t run and stop
stop
Stop and don’t run
They’re about to catch up
stop
Here
- Don’t run
Why did you stop suddenly
Let’s run
Will be discovered here
Hey, what are you going to do
-Catched
Where is the person?
Where have you gone?
I just saw that I was still here
Let’s find it separately
good
call! Here is…
This is our secret base
before
My sister and I always like to come here to play secretly
ah
Do you want to eat fruit?
There are a lot of them here.
We also met Fulai here
Playing together often
Xiao Mingri will be the eternal good sister with Xiao Luna
good
Levana Luna
I’m a little tired
Let’s go out to pick the fruit and eat it
You know how to eat
Sister, let’s pick the fruits
Xiao Luna said she was tired too
Oh well
But my sister is now like this
Luna who doesn’t have to worry about
Weslie must have a way to turn her back to what she used to be
Just trust us
Um
Are you looking for it there?
No
But I received a notice from the team leader
Say goat were caught there
Then let’s go quickly
Catch the goat
Weslie
Wolffy
Where are you?
Let’s go look for it separately
good
Weslie Hot Hot Hot
Slowy Tibbie
Village Chief Big Wolf
Help…
I just heard Wolffy’s voice
Let’s go ahead and take a look
Help… Help
I’m here
Big Wolf, why are you there
Say it
Save me up, it’s so scary here
Save me up, the branches are almost broken
I’ll help you
Big Wolf Are you okay
I’m fine
Right, what about the village chief?
Isn’t he with you?
Why don’t you say anything?
Slowy he… was captured
what!
No way out!
I can’t run anymore…
It’s so far away, it should be fine, right?
I don’t know where the 海官网网站s and others have gone
Let’s go find them again soon
Who are you looking for?