Who are you
presumptuous
How can I talk to Queen Levana like this
Are you the sister of Princess Luna?
You are the help my sister has come to
I wonder if there is anything wrong with you
misunderstanding?
Princess Luna is actually very concerned...
Jonie
Not enough
What happened?
- Jonie, are you okay?
We’re on...
It seems that I underestimated you
But...that’s the end
Be careful, everyone
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Will be crushed
Is this her Qili?
What to do
The village chief was caught
There is no news about Weslie and the others
Since my sister’s personality changed drastically
I’ll pay for it
Weslie and the sister will not be caught by their sister too
I’ll go find them
Don’t walk if you stay here
But there are soldiers everywhere outside
You’ll definitely be caught
I’m the big wolf, the transformer.
I’m going
Wow...
This won’t be discovered
Meow…
- Wow, great
I’ll find everyone
Alas
It doesn’t matter at all
That’s right
He hadn’t caught a goat before
No, I’m going to help
Princess, wait for me
I want to go, too
Have you ever seen a goat like me?
No, no
Could you ever see a goat like me?
no
I’ve seen it
Ask for a while...
It’s you
What did you just say
I saw the soldier escorting Lao Yu to the side
thank you
Is Luna’s helper still somewhat capable?
Lord Queen, how many have not been caught
Maybe they can catch it
But, I need to strengthen it
now…
You are mine
Work as much as possible
Village Chief
What should I do now
I can only save the village chief myself
But how can I do it alone
No matter
Keep up first and then talk
who?
It should be just a mouse
Meow…
You have to control yourself
You have been trained professionally
sorry
Do cats like light spots?
There is a way
Meow
You can’t be a high-level soldier
True failure
Can’t help it...
I’ve failed too
Meow Meow Meow Meow…
Village Chief, I’m here to save you
Why are you the only ones
What about others
Let’s run first
Um
Meow Meow Meow Meow…
The goat escaped
Stop and don’t run
I don’t know if Big Wolf and the others succeeded
Catch him
Stop and don’t run
This is...
- Wolffy
Oh, I’m dressed up like this
How can it be recognized
Wait
The ears are all gone, why can’t you tell me
It seems to have failed
We want to help him
Stop and don’t run
stop
Oops, no way to go
Depend on where you’re going
Let you see my power
Explode
Hehe...a joke
superior
Cough cough cough...
I really have the power
Cough cough... grab him...
Ahem...
Wolffy
It turns out that it is Luna’s ability
Where is the car
Can’t explain it now, get on the train
Don’t run
Help
It’s Weslie and the others
Great, finally found you
It’s fine if you’re fine
Let’s run, there are chasers behind.
you…
Like...
How could he dress up like a cat?
Is it hard to hide from the pursuit?
Then hurry up and get the two pursuers behind you
What happened to you? Nothing is said
Why do you ignore me?
Let me go!
Village Chief
Weslie, are you catching me and doing me
I’m going to save the village chief...
We are ordered by Queen Levana
Come and catch you
Catch me? Why?
We are good friends
Hahaha…
This scene is really good
Who are you
Queen Levana
It’s you?
What did you do to my friends
Your friend?
Then do you still know him?
Don’t recognize
How could it be...
OK, take him away
What are you talking nonsense
Why don’t you recognize me? I’m a goat
A goat?
Don’t recognize...
I only know that we are the subordinates of Queen Levana, Zhongli
You wake up quickly
Magic Cloud!
He actually has amazing powers.
Could it be that it was the magic stone that Luna gave him?
Why do you become like this
They must be controlled
You run away quickly
Escape quickly?
But…
Everyone is still controlled
What should I do?
They are my best partners
Let’s change everyone back soon
It depends on your ability
Is that only level?
I’ll tell you the real power
Paddi...
Too weak
snort! Even if you have Qili...
stop
Let go of goat
Small tricks of carving
what
Is this... flour?
Let’s run away with rush
Luna You can’t fight mine
Wake up quickly
Where are you going?
Don’t leave...
No...don’t let me go
Luna What’s going on with the slept goat
I didn’t expect my sister to do so hard
I don’t have the ability to cure the goat now
Then...Next...
What should I do?