Everyone is controlled
Nowadays, the same is true for the goat
Wolffy
If you catch up with us, you will win
Ha ha ha ha
This simple
You’re running too fast, too
You’re too slow, too bad
Really can’t catch up at all
It doesn’t matter
You no longer need to chase us
Because we will always be by your side
Um…
What to do now
actually…
There is a way to save the goat
What method
On the nearby Thunder Valley
There is a kind of saccharine that can cure all diseases
A thousand years can produce a piece
Maybe it can be used to save goat
Very good I’ll go up right away
- etc
But the Thunder Valley will keep falling thunder
No one has ever been able to come out safely after entering
My sister and I haven’t been there
Very… very dangerous
Such a dangerous
We’ll be around you all the time
I must go
But you have no ability
Not familiar with the environment
It doesn’t matter
I have strong body
I also have agile skills
Or I’ll go
No, someone must take care of the goat
Let me do this dangerous thing
All right
But you must be careful
Don’t worry, hand it to me
Can he really do it?
I felt a strength in him
He might be able to do it
By the way, how to get to Leihu Valley?
You’re all over the city
You must catch Luna and the others as soon as possible
Lord Queen
I’ve always wanted to ask…Why do I need to catch Princess Luna?
Isn’t she your sister?
ah…
Does anyone else have any questions?
no!
You don’t have to go
Any more instructions? Queen Levana
I have other tasks to arrange for you
Other tasks?
I want you to help me guard every city
Help me look at the dissatisfied residents
Once Luna and others are discovered in the middle of the way
Just catch them for me
yes!
In order to give you enough ability to deal with them
I want to give you these kiwi stones
Wow…
Don’t disappoint me
yes!
How do you look at this map?
Look at this
Look…
What are they looking at?
Tongzhi!
you! Not like the residents of this town
Yes…yes
I’m traveling
Please… Please ask how to leave the Thunder Valley?
There is the Thunder Valley
Thank you
Wait a minute.
No! Can’t you see through?
Thunder Valley is very dangerous
You have to be careful
good
Fortunately, I was not discovered
It’s a criminal, catch him
Why am I so unlucky
I won’t give up!
Is this the Thunder Valley?
Can’t run!
The slept with the goat is waiting for me!
stop
It seems that the Thunder Valley is not that scary either
Why does it smell like barbecue?
This is a violation
He ran into the Thunder Valley, are we still chasing?
But if the queen knows
We let the criminal run away…
Our Cat Country’s Maintenance Unit
Not a person who is afraid of death
superior!
ah…
That’s…living grass!
Finally found you
Why are there so many thunders here?
Can this pass?
You’re going with us
You go with us
Maybe I can survive
But you step into that heavy mine area
It can only turn into a piece of ashes
Why…you’re catching up with me so soon?
All are here
I must go
what
Running in?
Does he want to die?
I will definitely not let you have any trouble
Get it!
ah…
Wolffy Help me…
By the way, Wolffy hasn’t come back yet
mother
When will dad and the others come back
I don’t know either
But Dad and the others will definitely come back
Um
I’ll ask what happened to Wolffy
The number you are calling is not in the service area
But don’t worry
The flash seems to have stopped
Go and catch him
Isn’t this the most common herb that can cure all diseases?
We can give it to Queen Levana
It’s obviously all down
How could it be so powerful
Don’t think about it!
Still alive?
Brothers!
That’s right! Someone is waiting for me to go back!
ah…
I have never heard of him having such a powerful power
Is this Qili?
I just chased me like a wolf
Can you please give me my qi
Power of electricity!
Could it be that I’m wrong with my name?
Lightning Strike!
Lightning Strike Lightning Strike Lightning Strike…
It turns out that you can’t control your own power
what
That’s the herb used to save Paddis.
don’t want
Hahahahahahaha…
Think about it quickly, that’s the only surviving grass
This is a violation
If a thunder is not hit, then…
What are you muttering about?
Just hit until the hit
Lightning Strike Lightning Strike Lightning Strike…
Have you been crazy?
You’ll be struck
Some things are more important than life
This guy is crazy. Run…
You must be fine
Find details
If this continues, you may find us!
The texture of this big tree is more detailed than others
What’s going on then?
Thunder is coming. Is it raining?
Have you found it here?
No, let’s finish work and go home to collect clothes
good
Wolffy is back
Have you been injured?
I’m fine. Please save Xiaoyangyang.
Living grass?
I didn’t expect you to succeed
I’ll make a pill
Um
Have a good rest, he’ll be fine