Paddi
You finally wake up
What do you mean
Big sound
I’m fine…
what
Very…
It’s indeed a goat
I’ll find you something to eat
What about Weslie and the others
them…
Weslie and the others…what happened
I have to ask
You’ve been in a coma for a month
Weslie and others don’t know where to go
I can’t find the Slowy
Now there are soldiers chasing us
Mr. Slowy and everyone…
I’m tired everyone
Don’t cheer up
Everyone still needs us!
Found the Princess Levana and I will definitely save everyone
Um
So you have to go to the station right away
There will be trains there to the palace
But now there are many soldiers looking for us outside
What are you afraid of? I have Magic power now
You have it too?
But there is a problem
Your Magic power has no control yet
Hum What is this problem
Just practice a few more times
Lightning Strike!
Go and take a look
It seems…it’s indeed a problem
Um?
Let’s go there and have a look
Ah, grab the mosquito
Um
It’s the same as Qili
Why is Wolffy out of control
Because the strange power of the strange cat country is divided into three types
The first one is our strange cat country villagers
The innate power
The second type is the goat
Magic power obtained by using the precious magic stone
The third type is Big Wolf
The magical power obtained by pure natural
Because it is a pure natural and wild power
So it will be more difficult to control than the first two
-That…
Then you can’t use it
I had to do this
Ahhhh…
You can’t move your hands, I’ll help you
Be careful of fire
ah!
Let’s go quickly
Wait a minute.
We can’t just go out like that
I have a way
Report to the Queen
Weslie and the others
Already guarded in various towns
The villagers are not different at all
Good students are so efficient
Their teacher, Slowy, must be even more harmful
Maybe the plan to catch the bright moon has been deployed
Uh… Queen
The military officer is still visiting the palace
Sue the Queen
It took three days and three nights
I finally finished visiting the palace
Three days and three nights, but just visiting a palace?
Three days and three nights are almost done
I used to spend ten days and a half months
A funny ball?
Take a stunning ball to find someone who is suitable
Turn it into a sensational
This miracle will win you in the future
The stronger the person you are looking for
The more powerful the miracle he became
My scoundrel…
Take it yourself
Right
If I use these scoops
Hit the few rebels of the queen
Then they will hear my life
Still, Luna has a way
oops!
ah…
Wait a moment
Did you wear your helmet in the opposite direction?
That’s right, it’s backward
and
You two go with me to move something
How to do it
The station is right in front
You’ll go first
Fu and I will be there afterwards
But you…
Don’t worry, they didn’t doubt us
Go
- Um
Come
Where did Yakang and Wolffy go?
That back…
Mr. Slowy…
Slowy…
Mr. Slowy, I miss you very much
Slowy I miss you so much
Hahaha…I finally found you
ah?
Mr. Slowy Why did your tail change
Mr. Slowy Your face…
I miss you so much…
Run quickly, Slowy are also controlled
Don’t even want to run
Now I’ll catch you back and give it to the queen
Stunning ball
Avoid
ah
You can’t escape
Take the call
Take the goat
Run now…
But…Mr. Slowy…
Run
If we continue to waste, we can’t save it
Mr. Slowy, I will definitely come back to save you…
Take the call
Ah, amazing
Someone was sucked into the ball…
It actually made them run away
Finally, I didn’t catch up
Why didn’t you see Luna and the others
…
The train is coming soon
We need to think about how to break through the scope
Had to be forced
Lightning Strike!
Wolffy!
Oops
It’s them
Catch them quickly
Ah, everyone get on the train
Let me come
Magic Cloud!
Not good The trousers were opened
Haha I know that Magic Cloud has changed a lot
Good luck with goats
What a coincidence, have you eaten?
Take them away
The train is about to open
Please check the time to get on the train
No…
Since that’s the case… I can only…
Must hit
Lightning Strike!
ah
Really, they ran away again
Very rare
Fortunately, curiosity has been used
Dear passengers, please sit down and support your feet
Next stop, the strange flower town
Strange Flower Town?
Wow!