Wow…
Look, is the town of Strange Flowers in front of it?
Well, my sister and I used to visit Qihua Town
There are seas of flowers everywhere here
A peaceful and beautiful
And that unique flower is called Seven Colors...
Ah...Help...
You can take the clouds to catch everyone
Yes Magic Cloud
Where are we?
Has arrived at Qihua Town
Thanks for riding
Is this a peaceful and strange flower town?
Look, that vine did it
Why is it the only one moving?
Oh no, I forgot to be in the water
Who are these people
Then where are we going now
The train is broken
The car stands in the town, let’s wait for the next trip
Then let’s go quickly
Um
Don’t step on plants
sorry
What’s up
Be careful
Injuring plants here will be caught
And you can’t touch them
What happens if you touch it
Will be bitten
- Ah how did you know
Ah, run quickly
Ahhhhh…
Isn’t this a peaceful and strange flower town?
Hit the vine and it will drop the explosive seeds. It’s very dangerous
Oops lightweight...
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Hello, horrible
Uh-huh
These are mammoths
Wake up will be very fierce
You are not like residents of Qihua Town
Actually, we traveled from another place
My name is Big Wolf
Fulai
My name is Xiaoyue
Paddi
Hello
My name is Xiao Zheng. I am a resident here
Hello, Xiaozheng, I want to ask
How did Qihua Town become like this now
oops!
Weslie, you kicked me in the head again
Playing football is difficult to avoid mistakes. Do you want to come again?
You’ll kick it out for Sparky
Playing football? I don’t want to sweat
- You’ll kick it out for Jonie
I just want to lie down
Visit the Queen
Haha...why are you so embarrassed
Military officer
Military officer, how are you here
Let’s show you these two new scoundrels
Military officer, do you have a miracle? Two more?
Let me see you
Cough cough cough cough cough...
Wow! Is this the military’s miracle?
That’s right, and they hear it very much
oops…
Really good to hear
Um? Visit the Queen
Tibbie and Luna have arrived at Qihua Town
You go and greet them
Yes, I will not disappoint you
The Qihua Town was not like this before
But since the princess becomes queen tomorrow
Just let a man named Tibbie control the Qihua Temple
After Tibbie arrives
Plants are beginning to grow wildly
Huge vines and strange flowers have emerged
Make the villagers uneasy
The strange flower town has gradually become this current model
It also stipulates that we cannot destroy any plants
Otherwise, it will be closed
Tibbie...will not be like this
Tibbie and Goat also let everyone have seven-color flowers
Speaking
Seven-colored flowers only have seven colors of petals
You can realize your wish
well! Don’t know whether it’s true or not
It’s true
ah?
The seven-color flowers are indeed real
It really opened up seven colors
Sister, please give me your wish
I want Luna’s fish doll
Can go back to her
Sister, you should...
Close your eyes
Wow! Fish doll
The seven-colored flowers can really realize their wishes. Sister, please see
Luna, are you sure that your sister was not cheating on you?
My sister won’t cheat me
You... Are you Princess Luna?
Yes
Wait a moment Since the seven-color flowers can realize their wishes
Can you give me the seeds of the seven-color flower?
The seven-colored flowers are only in the back garden of Tibbie
Only those who have withered will be wiped out
Tibbie taught me how to grow flowers
I think I can save it
All I have produced seven-color flowers
I’d like to restore everyone to its original state
Which would be so easy
We’ve been using it for so long
That...that’s...
Go quickly!
What’s up
- Tibbie
Ah... Escape quickly...
So loud
Run separately
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Danger
Fulai
Paddi
ah
Hide quickly, Paddi
ah…
Thunderbolt
Wolffy
Help
Look quickly
There is a cave, let’s hide in it
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
It’s safe at the moment
Is it really safe?
snort! Self-submission network!
Tibbie
This... This is the virtual illusion of one of the strange powers
A illusion?
Yes, as long as you have a close eye to her eyes
You’ll fall into a illusion
Luna
Don’t worry about us, run away
run? Do you think you can run away?
Tibbie It’s me
I’m Yuyangyang, don’t you remember me?
Ah, you don’t remember?
You are the ones you catch
The Goat, the Blessed Moon, the Blessed
There is also a Wolffy
Um
Where has your companion Big Wolf gone?
Everyone…
Try again Thunderbolt...
Tibbie Be careful
Paddi
You want to save me
Catch him up
It’s good that Tibbie, you’re fine
Fortunately, there was no pressure
Seven-colored flowers? Another color
Will you have seven-color flowers?
ah?
Just you come and help me with the seven-color flowers
A variety of seven-color flowers...
Yes, as long as the seven-color flowers are produced
I can only hope to restore everyone to its original state
OK My kind
Take these two first and close them
Take him back to the flower field
Also, catch the missed wolf
- yes
Levana’s Queen has announced all trains to be suspended
No matter how you can’t escape the strange flower town
Hehehehe...
Ah, the train is stopped?
Then how can we go up to find Princess Levana
The wolf should be nearby
Report No target was found here
Go search there
yes
Now I can’t escape the strange flower town, and I’m the only one left
What should I do next