Your mission is to make it come out with seven colors
It seems impossible to escape from here
Right
If Tibbie can remind you of the past...
I remember everything
Very good
What a silly smile, you won’t be happy
Give him milk
Thank you, I’m so thirsty
Not for you to drink, but for you to drink
Can you be gentler?
You used to be very gentle
It smells so good
Then give you drink
Really thanks
Don’t worry, drink slowly if you have some burns
You’re so good
It’s not for you to drink
Go to the flowers quickly, don’t steal it
Singing must be sung to the seven-color flowers
All right
Well, don’t look at me just a goat...
Stop and stop How can you sing so hard
Come again
You weren’t like this before
You used to say that I sing well
Don’t look at me just a goat...
It’s too hard to sing, I can’t stand it
Then what should I do tomorrow’s music test
It’s okay, I think you sing well
Really
Well, it would be better if I could have a little more relationship
I’ll teach you
Um
-The sky has become because of me
…More blue
Forget it, don’t sing
I don’t care what method you use
Must bring out the seven-color flowers
Tibbie
This is the residence of Tibbie
There are not many soldiers
It should be easy to get in
Prepare to hand over the shift
yes
So there are so many soldiers, how can I get in?
Ah, there is a way
Cats like to play with light spots the most
This...this is...
Hey, come on
Ha ha ha ha…
What are you doing
No...it’s impossible
We have been trained by professional training
How bad did you practice
whee…
We rely on our firm beliefs and training
Training begins
Nothing to see it Nothing to see it Nothing to see it...
Is this not possible? Do you want to give up?
No I can
Increase difficulty
Take it away
We are carefully selected high-level soldiers
Hurt
Catch him
Tibbie can’t remember anything
It seems that only seven-color flowers are produced
Only then can you wake up Tibbie
Lalalala...
What happened? This is a big noise
What should I do if I get the seven-color flower in a scary way
You’re even louder
It’s too hot today, why don’t you give them some rest
They’re too tired
No, Master Tibbie said
Can’t stop for a moment
But you can’t even have seven-color flowers like this
So how can I get it out?
Is this one
In fact, the most important thing about the seven-color flower is
energy
energy…
Energy is the energy of the heart
Let everyone have enough fun
The seven-colored flowers will open
But if everyone is unhappy
The seven-colored flowers will wither
Look at everyone is so tired
The seven-colored flowers will definitely not be produced
Then what should we do
simple
- This is obviously a rest
I’ve said it all
You need to find happiness from the heart to let the flowers bloom
Get more milk
this…
You won’t give
Don’t blame me if you don’t have seven-color flowers at that time
We’ll go now
It’s the first time I’ve heard this way to make a flower
You’re so philosophical
Nothing, read more books in normal times
stop
It’s you
Where did the fugitive go?
Then
Chase
thank you
What happened? Where are your partners?
them…
Being caught?
Yes, I’m going to save them
But I have no way to go in
There are heavy troops there, it is difficult to get in.
No matter how difficult it is, I have to find a way to save them
Because they are my friends
What else is there?
I have a way
What method to do
Maybe you can mix in with the gardener
This is too simple
Not dressed as a gardener
Go in and see cats and you can’t dress up at all
Then what should I do?
Mix in the straw and follow the gardener in
But you can’t act
This easy
It’s you again! Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
What sound
Let’s go I know where the gardener who sent straws
How does this plant grow like the residents
I’m a resident here
Wow! You’re here and don’t move for a while
I’m trapped by the plants and can’t move
Then why don’t you come to save you?
Because if he is saved
It is possible to be caught for damage to the plant
No, you don’t need to save me
Otherwise, the plant will be broken
You will be tired of being caught
I don’t care about being caught. It’s necessary to be nervous about saving people.
Because I’m afraid of seeing you and not saving you, I can’t do it
I’m here to help
Thank you
Meaning
Go home quickly
Your family must be worried about you
Yes, you go quickly, too
Otherwise, it would be bad if Queen Levana discovered it
Please save Qihua Town
What’s wrong with you?
Seeing you go to ask someone without hesitation
I’m really touched
So I decided to rescue the villagers.
But I can’t do anything if I’m the only one
So so...
Hope you can save this strange flower town together
No problem, give it to me
Thank you so much
But before that you have to save me...
What are you doing!
Seven-colored flowers...
Send it to rescue
Didn’t I let you have a seven-color flower?
I...I’m consuming flowers
A flower? Do you call this a flower?
It turns out that you won’t have seven-color flowers at all
Come close him
Tibbie Don’t
Do you want to go to prison, too?
Wait a moment
You’ve lost something
Is it yours or yours?
Oh, it’s mine
- Let’s go
Straw is coming again?
- Yes
Go in
Wait for surprise inspection
Because there is a major criminal who is in charge
Lord Tibbie gave instructions
Things coming in must be very cautious
What’s in there?
- Just a bunch of straw
Let me check
Go in
Mixed in
I’m here to save you