Tibbie, what did you tell us to do?
How easy it is to come out
Are those seven-color flowers that are truly desirable?
Um? I’ve heard of this flower, too
Really... can you really realize your hope?
It doesn’t matter to you...
The Queen will arrive tomorrow
Queen Levana
What’s wrong
I caught Princess Luna and the others
Oh, that’s so bad!
It’s true that you didn’t have any trust in you
How will the Queen deal with them tomorrow?
Never release
Obey orders
Oh
Tibbie I’ll go back with you too
I want to see what those prisoners look like, too
Don’t follow me
Don’t be so stingy
Don’t walk so fast, you will sweat
ah…
It’s a hundred keys that can’t be opened...
Our prison here
You can’t open
snort! I want to use the original method of
Pry it open!
ah…
You’re too noisy
You’re fine
My good brother Sparky, save us out...
This goat is so dirty. Don’t touch me...
I’ll recognize you with your mask
Why can’t you recognize me...
Ahhhhh…
Let me go, it’s so dirty...
Ahem! The Queen has ordered tomorrow
Keep you in the dungeon forever
Princess Luna, don’t even think of it
Princess Luna…
- Princess Luna…
Ah...so dirty. Let me go...
Oh, let me go, dirty...
Ahhhhh…
Cockroaches...
What a big reaction
Hum, let’s go
yes
Sparky  remembers that she is afraid of cockroaches, but she can’t remember me
Paddi...
Are you really Princess Luna?
Who are you…
I’ll save you
Who are you going to save?
I...I’m a new gardener
I want to save the seven-color flower, but I’m lost
Go and have fun, don’t run around again
good
Escape from this
Otherwise, it will be troublesome to meet Tibbies
Tibbie
Did it cost you to succeed?
Still... only five colors
No use!
It’s almost here
He finally opened the six colors and was destroyed by him
I’ll supervise you today
I must give me seven-colored flowers
good
You help me win
yes
Have to find a way to leave here
Tibbie
I’ll go to the kitchen to get some drinks for you
Not thirsty
Tibbie
I’ll go to the kitchen to help you get some food
Not enough
Then I’ll help you get the sun
Not silly
What do you want to order
It turns out that the seven-color flowers are here
well…
Lord Tibbie, I’ll help him
Go
Hehe...I’ll help him move something later
Then I accidentally fell down as a dress
oops…
Oh, so dirty
It seems I’m going to take a shower
Go quickly and go quickly...
Hehehehehehehehehehe...
I’ll help you move
Where are the seven-color flowers?
So heavy, I’m not going to be able to handle it
Alas...
Um? It doesn’t seem to be this one
Wow wow wow wow wow...
Alas I...
I’m so dirty...
Why didn’t Sparky go?
Sneaky to see what you’re doing
Sparky
- You’ll be on the spot early
Do you want to take care of it?
Now I can finally slip away
I didn’t expect Queen Levana to be so cruel
I believe my sister will come back
Then why are you here
well! We’re all because of accident
The plants were caught due to damage
Have you been injured?
Just a minor injury
I’ll help you with treatment
Haha...Princess Luna...
alright
Wow, your wood carving is so beautiful
this
This is for my son
I don’t know when I will see him
I really hope that Xiaozhen can return to its former appearance
Be able to gather with your family
I want everything to return to its original state, too
You can eat the green grass cake made by Tibbie
So I have to go out quickly
Have to find a way to find the goat
Where are you?
Finally washed the soil, it was much more comfortable
Paddi...
Who is this big
I actually knocked off my mask
Who are you…
Princess Luna’s party…
How to expose it
It seems I have to use that trick
Hahaha Do you want to kneel down and beg for a gift?
OK I’ll approve it
Wolffy Escape Method
Stop me
Look at my power
Ah, no, you will sweat
stop!
Can’t beat
Don’t run
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
I won’t be caught
Pain and pain
Makeup room?
Huh? What is this
There is a way
Hahaha
Now I’m not afraid of being recognized. Hehe...
Could it be recognized?
Hello, Master Sparky
Just please don’t have to react so much
good
Who are they?
They’re in the cell there
Just keep moving forward
You retreat
good
You can’t cheat me
Tibbie
I already know your true face
You...how did you know me
Oh! I knew you when you were in the flower field
She actually knew my identity
All I can do is to open
Sparky  Goat, I still want to hit someone if I can’t steal flowers
Come and see the prisoner is an excuse. You want to steal flowers
Stealing money!
It turns out that the true face she said is
Oh, I suddenly remembered that I was going to apply a facial mask
So come to the makeup room
I got lost and entered the flower field
Look, haven’t I just come out of the makeup room?
All right
There are cockroaches!
Aren’t you afraid of cockroaches?
Am I afraid of cockroaches?
Oh oh oh... Oh I’m so scared...
snort! A strength
I’m here
oops…
How can I get out
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Paddi
If the wrench doesn’t work, then use it to smash it
Ah, goat
Alas...
Who is it
Paddi
I... come... save you
Wolffy...