Oh, Haitaro
Wolffy Big Wolffy Wolffy…
What sound is it
Someone has come
What arguing
Master Sparky What’s wrong with you
Lord Sparky, wake up
Who am I, where am I? Am I doing
Paddi
Ah, I remembered
Sparky
Cough, right, Tibbie asked me to come and mention someone
They have discovered it here
Not safe
Then please show the certificate of Lord Tibbie
Prove
You must have a certificate to release someone according to the rules
That’s how I’ll look for…
Tibbie You’re here
grown ups…
- Success
Why would I lie here?
Oh, my face hurts so much
Ah…my face…
How did my face turn out like this
Oh my God, what should I do
It’s you again, why haven’t you left yet
this…
What’s wrong with your face
Face Face…
By the way, Big Gray Wolf
Wolffy is here
Wolffy? Where is he
he…
This matter cannot be told to Tibbie
Of course he…he was beaten away by me
Killed away
Of course
But he might be going to prison to save people
You need to pay attention
Save people?
How can he save someone if the key is in my hand?
- Ha ha ha ha…
Go quickly!
Meow
What’s going on? He doesn’t have a key?
Don’t worry, I’ll dig the tunnel to save you from
Don’t…
ah…
- ah…
We’ve tried all the methods
Only use keys to open the door
Oh…my claws…
Someone is coming again
Tibbie!
By the way, she might have a key
What about the soldiers
I’m here
Did Wolffy come here?
No…no
It’s Lord Sparky
After drinking a cup of tea here, he said he wanted to go back
go back?
I just met him in the makeup
not good! Could it be that he just pretended to be Big Gray Wolf?
What are you doing?
Have been discovered
Save me Save me
Look at my ultimate
Be careful, Mr. Tibbie
What are you doing…
He wants to steal you with a stolen slap
I want to protect you
You give me some peace
you! Watch them well!
yes
I have to go outside and take a look
Call everyone and search for me here
Must find out the gray wolf
yes
Tibbie
If Wolffy has already mixed in
I’ll definitely go to the prison to save people
Should I transfer the princesses and the others?
Makes sense
What about the key
not good!
Run!
Surrounded, what should I do
Thunderbolt
Ha ha ha ha…
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Catch them
- yes
Magic Cloud
Seven-colored flowers?
That may be the only hope of awakening Tibbie
Oh, hurry up
Don’t try to escape
It’s a Tibbie
Stop watching, run
Ah, the door was closed
Oops, it’s been surrounded
Paddi…
Tibbie
Didn’t he even get back?
How could I do anything to Tibbie?
what?
careful
For…why should I save me?
What are you talking about
When a good friend encounters danger
Even if you change it, you will do it
good friend…
Remember it quickly
The kind and gentle thing in the past
Tibbie who has been taking care of and helping everyone
Please remember it quickly
We’ve always been good friends
Paddi
I…I remembered
I remembered it all
Tibbie…
You finally remembered
Yes, the goat, I miss you too much
So hard that you tried so hard to wake me up
But it’s a pity
Everything that just happened was a illusion
Catch him up
Wolffy
Chase me quickly…
You wake up quickly, wake up quickly
This is…
You just got the power of Tibbie
Qili?
You’re here soon
I won’t explain it to you now
Let’s go and help us
Quickly don’t let them run away
Successful, everyone run away
Too bad
superior!
Protect the Princess’ Retreat
You go first, let’s hand it over to us here
you…
Please help me bring it to my family to protect the curious flower house
Don’t worry, I’ll definitely come back and take you out
Go and have a look there
Oh no, they’re catching up
What to do
Here
Searching me from house to house
- yes
Open door Open door