Ordered to search the fugitive
None here
Search for points of interest
good
This is...
It turned out to be a cockroach
What sound
cockroach
Let’s go, I don’t have it here either
good
They’re leaving
Thank you for helping us again
You should leave here soon
Alas, wait
This one has not been sent out yet
dad!
ah?
I’m not your dad
Mistakes...
I mean this is a wood carving made by my dad
well…
It turns out that the uncle in the prison guard is your father?
My dad is a wood carving
But after Tibbie came
Say... he hurts plants
So I closed him
Have you seen my dad?
Yes, it’s too much for your dad and others
We can escape
They are heroes
My dad will always be a hero in my heart
Let’s go back and save them
although…
Saving people is important
But is it better to go to find Princess Levana first?
That’s right
It’s not a good idea to fight Tibbie here
If you find the Princess of Levana
Maybe everyone will be restored
Um
Yes, go
I’ll take you to the station
But every time you are discovered...
To save everyone, I’m not afraid
thank you
Seven-colored flowers, please open it quickly
I want everyone to restore it
what?
Run away?
Tibbie I’m so disappointed with you
Her Majesty the Queen, please calm down
I won’t let them escape from the strange flower town
I’ve sent heavy troops to find them
Her Majesty, please drink milk
Her Majesty, please give me another chance
I’ll definitely catch them back this time
I can’t tolerate a second failure
Do you want me to help you?
Need not!
You will be able to get to the station soon after passing through here
Huh? The flowers are about to wither
That’s all?
Light or it will...
Plants are about to grow. Run...
careful!
ah…
What’s going on?
It’s Xiaoqiang, he’s stuck
Oh, what should I do now?
If we go and help, we’ll be caught.
I’ll save you
Magic Cloud
Don’t harm plants
Will be punished by Lord Tibbie
You go first I want to leave myself
No, we won’t give you up
I’ll help you
Come and help
No matter
Exercise force
Thank you and thank you everyone
No thanks for leaving
Thank you for your help
Since Tibbie came
I’m not so happy
Yes, it’s so heartbreaking to help others
Um!
Catch them!
ah…
What’s going on
I want to know the whereabouts of those people
Don’t be afraid
As long as you tell me where they went
I guarantee that you will never need to have seven-color flowers again
I...I don’t know
I don’t know either
If everyone doesn’t say
You know what the consequences are
Say good boy
I...I want to go to the bathroom
Tibbie
Discovering plant fertilization in the eastern region
There are wool and wolf hair on it
East District?
That’s on the way to the station
Humph As long as you are there
They definitely can’t escape
Paddi...
Paddi
Tibbie
Where is it
They’re not here
The sound is sent from the trumpet flower
If you don’t come back
I’ll take the entire residents of Qihua Town
All went into the thorn forest
No...
Just get there when you turn around
I’ll save everyone, you go quickly
It’s too dangerous for you to go alone
No matter how big the danger is, I will go
Because my friend is there
You taught me these
No matter how big the danger is, I will go
Because my friend is there
Don’t worry, I’ll get yours soon
Are we going to the station again?
Xiao Qiang is also our friend
well! It’s been so hard that I got here
Oh, don’t care...
Go and save people!
Princess?
As a princess
It’s hard for the people. I can’t stand by and watch
I will go wherever the princess goes
Why do you have footsteps?
Is it hard to say that Tibbie and the others have caught up with him?
Run so fast I almost couldn’t catch up
Wolffy?
Wait for us
you…
One more person, one more strength
We’ll help you too
OK OK OK Don’t be too touched
I’ll count the last 10 sounds
10 9…
3！
How can you jump directly?
This is not fair to us
Less talk less!
2！
1！
Put them in the thorn forest
yes
Tibbie Stop
Finally arrived
Ah, be careful...
What a big smoke
Be careful
careful!
Thank you
ah!
Be careful, princess!
Fulai!
Don’t go past
Want to steal
Oh!
It’s me!
Sorry, this fog is too bad
Blow this fog with a fan
good
Magic Cloud
- Let them go
Think beautifully
Then don’t blame me for being rude
Don’t rush Big Wolf
Must win
Lightning Strike!
Lightning Strike Lightning Strike Lightning Strike…
Haha...you’ve already gone
Ahhhhh…
It’s the sound of Tibbie
Let’s go while you’re now
But…
Go and chase
Where is the style?
You’re good
- Weslie
Weslie...
Why are you here?
Humph...