You’re good
- Weslie
Weslie What are you here to do
Of course I’m here to catch people
Wait a moment
This is my mission, you don’t need to interfere
I’m just doing it on orders
This is my place
If you can complete the mission
I don’t want to come here
I’ll stop messing with me again
Oops
- Tibbie
I’ll catch the prisoner
Of course I was arresting the prisoner
I’ll catch it
The prisoner ran away
Weslie, thank you for your help
They’re catching up
We need to speed up our pace
Um
ah
Ah Princess Luna
Give me a slap
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Fulai
What’s wrong with Tibbie?
Who told you to interfere
Go quickly
Everyone is fine
Don’t want to run
No!
Ah, he actually brought the explosive bean
ah…
We’re here to help you too
Run quickly
ah…
Ah, blessing!
Here is the sacred thorn forest
He was hit by the poisonous thorns
Have to suck out the venom tightly
Otherwise, life will be in danger
Leave it to me
Want to escape
Not that easy
ah…
Help, howl...
Magic Cloud
Don’t be afraid, I’m here
Um
ah!
Princess, we have to hurry
Explosion beans are gone
I need more time
So what should I do? This smoke won’t last long
I have a way
I’ll lead them out
You take everyone away first
Then how can we get along
Go to the exit
Wait, you don’t know where the exit is
Wolffy catch
This is...
This is the guide bean
Follow the direction it points to find the exit
good
Have to attract their attention
Just give the Goat to the Goat to get some time
Thunderbolt
Ahhhhh…
There
Don’t try to escape
He is mine
Tibbie, you’re like this
I’m not polite to you
snort! I’m not polite to you...
Very strong...
I was so tired that I couldn’t move all over my body
I didn’t expect that Tibbies had such a powerful beast
Tibbie...
I won’t be there
ah…
It’s indeed fake
oh? Are you awake now?
cut! Small carvings
Isn’t it fake to just the pain in the illusion?
Don’t worry, that’s the poison of my thorn forest
You just need to be good and not to act
When my mission is completed, I will come back to save you
Always feel a little uneven
Where is Princess Luna?
You... dare to fool me!
She can’t run away even if she is injured
Come back and calculate with you two
Don’t go...
I didn’t expect that I would be discovered so soon
You’re fine
Have to suck out the venom tightly
Otherwise, life will be in danger
Wolffy...
Don’t...want...run...
Who is the evil one? Report the name
Is it really Wolffy?
My friend, you’re so awkward to wear
It’s not just to help you suck out the drugs
It became like this
cut! Do more care!
I’ve saved your life at least
Isn’t there a word of thanks?
Um?
Taste good
All of them have been cured
Then let’s get out of here by tight time
Um
It’s Tibbie!
quick! Everyone find a place to hide!
I just heard a static
Why is there nothing left
It seems that everyone is hiding
I didn’t hide it at all.
This grass line should be
Go and hide there
Fortunately, I found out earlier or otherwise...
I’m stuck...
Can you have some self-knowledge?
What to do...She has walked over
Don’t panic...
The lawns are more indifferent
There is also a line of life if you are unmoved
I beg you little fat
Don’t move, okay
Who comes to save me
Can you stop moving
Why there is nothing
Could it be that I’ve heard it?
Have good luck
As long as you hide in peace and leave Tibbie...
Stand up...
Princess Luna
Are you sure Fulai is really our teammate?
Waste my time so long
Nothing Hum!
Great!
Finally came out
Everyone is safe and has nothing to do. It’s great
Fortunately, you are here
Uh-huh
Paddi...
It turns out that you are coming out so soon
- 未…
What are you talking about? That’s so small
They say
Don’t be so loud
Otherwise, I’ll be discovered by Tibbie
Yes, thanks for the reminder
Take down Princess Luna and others
yes
Don’t be afraid, look at me
Lightning Strike... Alas...
Take it away
How do they deal with it?
It’s useless to catch Princess Luna
Let’s go
I used this hand to push it
Just rescue Princess Luna and the others
Go in!
Hello everyone
Princess Luna Why are you caught back
Um
I think…
I want to save Princess Luna and the others
Are you going with me?
I’ll go with you
My brother saved me
I want to save my brother, too
Yes, let’s go together
I’ll go too
They risked their lives to save us
Now we’re reporting it
Let me go with you
That’s right!
Now the princess is in trouble
We can’t stand by and watch
I want to save them
Yes, save them...
Save them...