There is no abnormality on the right
There is no abnormality on the left
According to the information
In order to prevent Princess Luna and others from overwhelming.
To transfer them to the cliff cell
ah…
- That’s the one who’s in.
- Can’t even escape the cliff?
so
The last chance we can rescue them on the way
Everyone is ready
yes
Don’t look at me just a goat
Goat’s cleverness is hard to imagine
What’s the quarrel
It’s not letting people sleep
Don’t look at me just a goat
Don’t worry about the energy
Such seven-color flowers cannot be produced by many gardeners
Why not think about what is the way to escape
I have a way
The sky became blue because of me…
Wolffy, let me take my seven-colored flowers
Huh?
How did you create the seventh color
How is it? It looks real
As long as we take this fake seven-color flower
The siege shouted Tibbie and goat over
While they opened their cells to get the seven-color flowers
We can all take advantage of the opportunity to get out
ah? Very darn
Nothing to do
The seven-color flowers are blooming
Opened Opened Opened…
Seven colors…flower
Look at the seven colors
Go and call…
Hahaha…Thank you
I’ll go find Master Tibbie to ask for credit
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
The seven-colored flowers are being taken away…
Ah hahahahahahaha…
The seven-color flower that is impossible is now in my hands
Then why don’t I be willing to be a Warrior?
Seven-colored flowers, let me become a warrior
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
How to do it…
It should be able to save it
Um? Fake?
How to do it? How to do it…
You actually cheated me with fake flowers
Don’t think I’ll be there
Then what should I do now
We also have seven-color flowers
As long as we work hard to produce the seventh color
It will definitely save the entire cat country
Yes, let’s work together
Um
Work hard together
Work hard all night, no results
Take them all out and send them to the bottom of the cliff
Wolffy
Wouldn’t it be better to knock them down with your Lightning Strike?
No, my thunder flicker is not fully controlled yet
Will hurt yours
That’s it
Just now
ah…
Oh wow…
snort! How dare you come to save someone?
Catch them for me
Ahhhhh…
Cough cough cough…
What’s going on?
The soldiers were attracted by the attention
We went over to save people while we were rushing.
Um
Rush…
Could it be that we saved us?
right
Come with us quickly
Here!
The person who wants to kill me
No door!
Everyone…where are you
Where are you
Here is…whether
ah…
It hurts so much…
snort! Not enough!
There must be something wrong with her eyes
ah
I won’t let you die in vain
We’re slapping
ah…
- ah…
Wake up quickly This is a illusion
Princess, go quickly
We’ll go and slap the soldiers
No, how can I destroy you
Go quickly
Walk
We can’t put them down
Let go
Don’t…Don’t hurt them anymore
Seven-colored flowers…
The seventh petal is open
Seven Color Flowers, please restore everything to its original state
Let’s go back to that kind Tibbie
Paddi
Tibbie…
Great, you finally come back
What’s up? What happened?
Tibbie finally changed back
Now that I’m back, you don’t cry anymore
Tibbie? How do you feel strange?
Wolffy, what’s wrong
I think this should be…
These are all fake
What…what
Ha ha ha ha…
I didn’t expect you to see through my illusion
All are fake?
The seven-colored flowers…
How did this happen…
That’s because you’re too stupid
Only then will it be repeated
What’s wrong with believing in friends?
friend? Less self-indulgent
The Goat can only…
Lightning Strike…
careful!
Paddi!
All…it’s all my fault
Ah, you look at it
Um?
Tibbie was knocked down
Oh wow ah ah ah ah…
- Run quickly…
Oh wow… run away quickly…
Very good
Princess, let’s go while we are now
You… don’t want to escape one
No, she’s going to use the illusion again
quick! Stop her quickly!
Wait a minute…
Tibbie…
It’s you?
You’re fine, Tibbie?
Let it open quickly
Don’t beat her down
Everyone will be confused by the illusion again
She was just controlled
Everyone is calm
There must be a way to make Tibbie come back
ha? You’re not a fool
You’re injured yourself, and you’re going to protect the enemy?
I don’t need your sympathy
But I can’t watch you get hurt with silence
We are our best friends
No…No. Don’t get close to me…
Oh no, her Magic power seems to be a little out of control
Illusion and reality are recurring
Come back soon to take Paddi. It’s too dangerous
Then I will break it all
I’ll definitely remember it
Remember those who work together…
shut up!
It’s hard to go together…
Nothing…
Nothing
Can erase the time we are in contact with each other
Come back Tibbie
I’ve remembered it all. Thank you for taking Paddi
Hey, I just said you won’t forget me
All the illusion of the illusion disappeared
Sorry, it caused such a lot of damage to everyone
Do you think apology is useful?
Turn the town into this
We also imprisoned our parents
No matter what punishment I’m willing to accept
- We are willing to bear it together
Everyone…
Yes, no matter what the punishment
I’m willing to take it with Tibbie
Is it really okay to punish any money?
That…that…
Then you can rebuild the town with us
Um
Hahahahahahaha…
I didn’t expect that the seven-color flowers really let you come out
Wow…1234567…
Ah…I really created the seven-color flowers…
Give it to me
I’ll give it to you when I’m done
ah? etc…
The seven-color flower that cannot be done
Let me be a warrior in the cat country
ah?
This time I watched it grow
It can’t be fake
Have you finished your wish?
Don’t come here…
ah…
sorry
How about it…
It’s absolutely fine
Why can’t this seven-color flower realize hope?