Can this car move?
danger!
I’m here to save you… Alas…
Wolffy!
Let’s fix the car
But now all trains are stopped
Even if it is repaired, the train will not be able to leave
Then we don’t have the opportunity to go to the palace?
Trains are stopped because they cannot provide energy.
But just borrow the energy from the power stone
Power stone?
The appearance of the power stone is the same as that of the crystal
Its growing power provides energy to machinery
Then let’s go find this power stone
It is hidden in the thorn forest
Not many people have seen it
Thorn Forest…
Don’t worry, we’re not afraid if we look at each other
Yes, this time the delicate goat
We will definitely be able to safely enter and exit the Thorn Forest
Tibbie, I will give you more advice in the future
Let’s give advice together
Ha ha ha ha…
You go out quickly
Let’s hand the train over to repair
Yes OK!
Yes, how many times have you been secretly going out for fun?
I’m going to punish you today!
Haha… are you scared?
well! OK OK OK Don’t punish
Let’s come and practice, right? OK?
OK I’ll agree
Come on, you practice spraying first
You want to inhale like me
Against the opposite…
Very good, that’s it
Chi…
Why do you want this to me
I’ve suffered!
What to do? Let me down quickly!
Stop quickly…
ah…
Slowy Military Master, the Queen is looking for you
ah!
OK Wait a moment
Did you practice hard today
Punish you to think about it in front of the wall
Don’t look at me?
Please, please perform a thoughtful thought in the face of the wall
That’s right, just face the wall here
Please take me to the Queen
I’ll bring you something delicious
Haha…Let’s go
How do you do
Can’t even catch a bright moon
It also made Tibbie rebellious
It’s Tibbie that is too weak
Especially you
Let you help
You got married to Tibbie
Uh…that was an accident
But the queen restsatisfied
They’re going to pass the ice town next
I’ll catch them.
It’s best
yes
If I took the magical beast to capture Princess Luna
- The Queen will be very happy
whee…
Humph, wait until I arrive at Qihua Town
Just grab Princess Luna and the others
Ah… Alas…
Where are you going?
Is it good to hear me?
Let’s look for the power stone
I and Tibbie
Princess Luna and I
I and…
Children are children and need someone to accompany them
Don’t come back to find me if you’re scared
Haha I’ll come back to find me soon
Miracle…
Tibbie helps…
Didn’t catch up?
But why are there strange beasts here?
And this miracle is smaller than the miracle I encountered before
Why don’t I come to patronize him as my rider?
Cat Cat Country
Good to be good to be…
Oops Why…
Hello, please have lollipop
We are good friends
Very delicious
Eat it, eat it…
I’m here
Ahhhhh…
If it’s soft, it’s hard
Success
belch…
oops…
What’s going on?
Why did he suddenly run?
Come back
Tibbie, have you found the power stone?
After searching for so long, I still can’t find it. Very tired
Finally stopped
- Give me some rest first
- It’s you
Look at my illusion
I don’t watch I don’t watch…
It’s worthy of being Mr. Slowy
Don’t be afraid, look at my strange clouds
Strange
This miracle is so terrible…
Run quickly
Big Swords We’re on
What do you want
You’re out for a walk again…
Why does Slowy also have a strange beast?
- Wolffy Help
Don’t hurt them
Thunderbolt
It’s really dangerous
The thorns are poisonous. We’ve gone
Can you hit this lightning?
I’ve gradually become familiar with this ability
You see, I didn’t hurt you this time
Oops Oops…
You’ve hurt yourself
ah…
Help…
- Wolffy
Magic Cloud
ah…
- This miracle is too powerful
Keep up with the little beast
Chase quickly
Ahhhhh…
Alas, finally came down
finally…
Stopped
You get up quickly
The entire cave is a power stone
There is no time to feel sad, let’s go
Um
Hum, I will convince you next time
Meet again?
No!
My clouds can’t resist this fireball…
Who is the good thing that hurts me?
ah?
You’re coming out soon
It’s Princess Luna and Fulai
Haha, it’s so tidy
Just catch them
The Queen will definitely look at me with admiration
Oh, two fire together, how to do it
Protective shield
Come on, Luna
But this will continue to be consumed
The shield will disappear soon
You’re about to catch
ah…
superior
Magic Cloud
Say the net to catch the strange beast
oops…
what
Success
Good luck with goat
I’ve missed the goat
They were just dragged down for a while
Let’s run quickly
Stop biting, chase them
Stop me…
Please chase them
Stop quickly Stop…
Oh, oh…why is this happening
ah…
Hahaha…
Fixed
Strong dad is awesome
hehe
And the final work
Depart!
See you again
- See you again
See you again…
Take care of Princess Luna
You will definitely restore the cat country
You should take care of yourself, too
We’ll come back to see yours
- goodbye