Ha chi!
Very cold…
We’re in Ice Town
It’s winter all year round
I remember it
Weslie is Queen Levana
Sent here to guard
Weslie is here
But now he only hears Queen Levana
Don’t be afraid to meet him
We can restore you
It will definitely restore Weslie
- Um
Wow…
oops! Are the pursuits coming?
careful! I’ll go and see
Not a pursuer…
Not good!
The snow is too heavy, the car is crushed by the snow
We need to open the snow lens before we can continue to move forward
Magic Cloud
Please go there and go to the mirror
- Don’t be
oops…
It’s avalanche. Run…
ah…
Fortunately, it ran fast
Ha chi! So cold…
ah? It’s ice and snow town
The snow is too heavy
Let’s go there and avoid it
There are no movies in this town
It’s so cold, I guess I’m hiding at home
Could anyone please ask
Is anyone
Where to go?
Of course, I went in to avoid the snow
It’s not right to go to other people’s houses
It’s very unpretentious
The princess said
I’ll take some warmth
I’ll apologize to the master when he comes back
But it’s really cold now
Why doesn’t this family come back yet
So strange
Yes, I think it’s too disgusting
Very strange Very strange
One piece of squid in the fire pot is missing
I knew it was you
I’m not talking about this
Maybe the master has come back
I’ll open the door
Maybe the door was blown up by the wind. I’ll open it.
ah
It’s a bit strange
Open the door quickly
Weslie, is it you? Open it quickly
It feels so comfortable after washing your face
Hello, Sparky
Not good at all
Why did you come here again?
Of course I’m playing with you
I’ve gotten my stuff every time I come
You have to take him away as soon as possible
Actually
I want to…repair my carpet today
It’s not convenient to entertain you
Is it bad?
Uh…yes
You see, there are so many lines
Too serious
You should go back soon
Alas, no hurry
Let me help you repair it
ah?
ah…
OK I know what you want to say
No thanks
What exactly do you want to do
Isn’t Princess Luna helping others?
Go and catch them
No hurry
Why not hurry? What should I do if I run away
Someone will catch it for me
Where did Princess Luna and Fulai go?
Have you been caught?
Weslie, is it you
Come out quickly I’m so scared
Let’s go find them
Walk
Princess Luna…
Fulai…
oops!
- Tibbie
ah…
ah? Where is Tibbie?
- I’m missing
Ah… I don’t see it anymore
I’m so scared…
Don’t run around and change your hair quickly
We are not afraid of leaving if we tied each other together
Paddi…
ah…
Magic Cloud!
Very rare
Who has so many traps here
Rely on…
But is it really possible
Let’s try
not good! oops…
Tibbie, Luna, Fulai
Wake up
Uh…Goat goat…
Or your method is better
Fake down
Weslie really brought us
Bringed to Tibbie here
Let’s leave here quickly
If they come back, we can’t run away
Run!
Wow…
I won!
Ah…you go back quickly
They may have run away
Not so quickly escaped
The whole ice and snow town is a trap
The trap I dug
You will definitely catch Weslie
The end of Weslie has arrived
They all want to catch me
If you see the slept goat, help others
I must have thought we were one
I don’t need to do anything
Someone will catch the Goat and the others
Who is it? Why did they catch you?
Because I was in charge of the ice and snow town
Those innocent villagers who want to catch me are
The snowman will move!
Don’t want to run
Will talk!
Catch them!
You’re so cruel
No, it’s really clear
But it seems that it’s time to go back and look forward to it
Isn’t this the few snowmen who just stood at the door?
Magic Cloud
They’re about to catch up
Don’t think it’s easy to catch up with me
I’ll deal with them
Lightning Strike!
Lightning Strike Lightning Strike…
Haha… I can’t fight…
Can’t you win once?
Lightning Strike…
sorry…
Sitting at ease
Wow…
ah? Let me go
Who are you
Where have the residents of this town gone
Have you been caught
Nonsense we are residents of Ice and Snow Town
what?