Princess Luna
You have never said before that there are snowmen residents in the country of Weird Cat
It’s so amazing
I don’t know much, either
Princess Luna Are you Princess Luna?
Yes
I’m really sorry
We saw that they looked like Weslie
I thought you were a guy
I’ll do something as unforgettable as before
It seems you don’t like Weslie
We are all caused by Weslie and Goat
A month ago...
Hearing that Princess Levana is sending soldiers to capture Princess Luna
It’s so too much, we want to protect Princess Luna
right!
What happened?
Let’s go back to the city to take a look
Who is this?
My name is Weslie
Levana the Queen sends me to manage the ice and snow town
It’s too boring here
Let’s have some fun things
Go quickly!
All the people in the town have become snowmen
We can never eat the fire again
Can’t soak in a hot spring
and
Weslie also let us make various ice sculptures for him
then…
It’s mostly clean, how about it...
So have people in your town become snowmen?
this…
Meow Meow…
This is not what we saw in the photos
That cat
This is our son Coco
It’s also the only survivor who has not become a snowman
Never let Weslie discover
Don’t worry, we’ll keep it secret too
Where has Coco gone?
Cocoa is coming out soon
Are you there Coco?
- Cocoa…
Where are you?
Wow!
Who has built a Wolffy’s snowman here
Shocked me
Isn’t it you? Don’t go there and do it
To find the thread carefully, observe the cat’s footprints
Son, come out soon
cocoa…
Why did you find it there?
no
Find Weslie before he returns
Otherwise it will be irritating
When will Weslie come back?
It must be Weslie Goat coming back
You’ll hide it
good
Hello! What should I do?
Where have they been
Who are they? I don’t know who you are talking about
Yes
These young traps
How could I catch someone
Who said we caught it
oh? So have you seen them?
We don’t know anything
Too obvious
Hurricane Blade!
Found
Weslie I am Tibbie
Tibbie? You are a traitor
You’d better not be too weak
Otherwise it will be no fun
How to do it
Don’t worry, I’ll be gentler
oops!
cocoa!
Escape quickly
There was still a cat not turned into a snowman?
oops! Injured? Need to handle it tightly
Forever, it will be bad if you get infected with bacteria
Come on I have medicine here
Excess cocoa
Otherwise we’ll all be arrested
Cocoa Cocoa…
What to do? If Coco was found by Weslie...
Let’s look for it separately
Yes OK
cocoa!
Alas!
cocoa
Help Cocoa get a chicken leg, and the bread is OK...
cocoa!
Can’t jump
This is the ice lake. If you jump down, you will get ice
fortunately…
Found it or not
no
Where did Coco go?
He’s there
Be careful
It’s really a slim-up. Play with me for a cat
Then let’s have fun
Coco, don’t move me, I’ll save you
I’ll help, too
I’ll help others
Magic Cloud
Don’t be afraid, I’ll save you
Coco, I’ll come right away
Meow…
ah…
Big Wolf, you’re slow, I don’t have a good position yet
It’s fine
Let’s go quickly, don’t let Weslie discover
What to do? I’ve discovered it again
run!
So you want to have a snowball fight?
OK I like snowball fights the most
Everyone came here to me
Magic Cloud
Let me come thunderbolt...
Hahahaha...you are so fun
But...it’s over
I’m here to help
ah…
oops…
You’re so weak
Recover Weslie
Weslie
Weslie Let’s go home together
I made a vegetable soup and I can eat it right away
OK
Do you want to come to the football competition?
We’ve always been a team
This time, we have to fight on our shoulders
And fight on your shoulders...
Have you written your work?
But...No need to write it today. Go and play
Very good…
This feeling...
Very childish
ah…
Tibbie Do you think I will get into the illusion again?
I’m back
Sorry for Weslie
Let’s go quickly
Um
Ha ha ha ha…
It’s so interesting. Let’s have fun with me again