It’s not a way for us to hide all the time
We can’t watch the villagers turn like this
Can’t do anything
We’re going to get the ice fan back
Let everyone recover
But they are many
We didn’t have any calculations for head-on fight
Well…
Then what if…we’re stealing
Stealing?
Do you know where the ice fan is?
Uh… After Weslie comes
Take over the entire game park
I think…it should be there
OK, everyone will listen to me
It’s not like food to attract
Of course not
Come here
Paddi
Use your strange cloud to pretend to be a snowman
This is a good way
Even I admire myself
So isn’t it your plan if you don’t have a nose?
Um?
That husu
Didn’t it be given to us?
You know how to eat
That’s the snowman’s nose
What should I do once I was discovered…
How many of you…
You’re a little suspicious
You are discovered
Then what should I do
you…
sorry
I will never eat my nose next time I go out
Not talking about you
It’s you
What’s going on with your tail?
How can a snowman have a tail?
Tail?
oops! When did the tail be exposed?
It turns out it was you
This…this is…
This is the popular ending of the ball
oh? Is that true?
Show me
ah?
I said let me see your tail
This…this is not very good
Let me see!
Big Wolf, let him see
Otherwise we’ll wear it
ah?
Oh…it feels so good
There is only one soldier or…
Team leader
Team leader, are you doing
I’m playing the latest popular tail
- New
- I want to play, too
I want to do it, too
I want it too, I want it too…
Wow, so soft
Working overtime every day to find someone, it won’t let us live
Meow…
ah
Do you have a tail, too?
oops…
What are you doing
I’m going to pull it out and study it
Pull it out…
This tail is really hard to pull off, just like the real one
Maybe…because…is stuck…
oh? Why is it stuck?
Cat Two Come to help me
- yes
Team leader, don’t pull it off
We still have a job!
It’s better to cut it
Let’s find a way to save Big Wolf
You can just watch it without pulling it
No need for politeness, we will help you to unveil it
Don’t say this with a positive face
Wait… Wait…
It’s Princess Luna
I just saw her running there
The opportunity to make meritorious service is here. Come and chase me
You didn’t say earlier…
There is a shortcut here, let’s go quickly
Um
The game park is ahead
Let’s go to another door
Coco’s father said there are several doors in the game park
That’s great. There’s only one soldier here to guard it.
I’ll go out and lead him out
You take this opportunity to go in
Fulai can still run so quickly!
Run too fast
There are invaders!
Invader?
Go out and have a look
There will be nothing wrong with blessings, right?
It’s okay, go away
This game park is so big
I don’t know where the ice fan is hidden
Only one can find one
Then let’s get the time
It’s so dark here
I think we shouldn’t go forward first
I think it’s too dark, there’s a trap in front of you
No, no… It turns out that the girl’s strength is still smaller
Let’s hand it to us at this time
Let you see what a man is called
That’s right
- Ah…
Ahhhh
Everyone said don’t go
It’s indeed a trap
- Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Very fun
Tibbie, Luna, you are about to get off
There is a large slide here
- Wow…
- Hahaha…
Wow…I want to play too…
yeah!
It’s so fun here
It’s hard to blame Weslie for its own
Yes
What did we do in the beginning?
What’s going on?
Is my park fun?
Weslie
Self-submission network
Oops, run away…
ah…
It’s the ice fan. Get up quickly
Turn into a snowman…
ah…
cocoa?
Thank you for saving us
Run now
Magic Cloud
Don’t want to run away!
Alas! What a steep slope!
stop!
Alas, no choice…
Let’s go
Ahhhhh…
Skiing is so fun
No one can save you this time
Look down on me less
Lightning Strike…
If I have half a word, it will be struck by lightning
oops…
Hehehe…you can’t control the thunderbolt
Wolffy
careful
ah…
Weslie, wake up
We are good friends
We used to play football together…
Leave aside!
Lightning Strike Lightning Strike…
Don’t think that you can cheat me by writing two entries
I only know
You are the prisoner who will be arrested by the Queen tomorrow
Thunder Bird Flash…
Ice fan?
Isn’t that…Ice Fan?
Stop quickly Stop quickly…
The ice fan…broken
what?
That Coco dad and the others…
Go quickly…
Fulai
The soldiers of Weslie should be nearby
Quick…
Don’t run…
Weslie…
He actually fanned the ice
- Broken to me
- I will not let you go
Get me to catch them…