The location here is more biased
Not so easy to find
That’s great, you’re fine
The ice fan is damaged
No need to worry about you becoming a snowman anymore
Sorry, I’m the one who ruined the ice fan
It’s me that I’ve made everyone unable to return to their original appearance
It’s okay, we’re already ill
You should leave here quickly
Staying here is dangerous
no
I want to find out the fragments of the ice fan and repair it
Can it be repaired?
I can try
But now there are soldiers everywhere
We can’t go back at all
There is no Wolffy King in the world
Places that cannot be accessed
You’re waiting for my good news
Alas...
We still led all the soldiers we searched for.
Let Wolffy collect the fragments
Um
Who are you
Come and catch us
There
Huh? ah!
ah…
Then...
There is a situation
ah…
Thank you
Very good I found a piece
Add more robberies
Have you been searching for too long
Something uncomfortable in eyes
ah?
Found again
snort! Do you dare to come back?
Hurricane Blade!
Wait a moment
Let me take it first
goodbye
Want to find the ice fan
That’s... impossible
oops…
Don’t want to run
You’re offending
It’s stupid to have the ability
Then I’ll come too
Thunderbolt
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Failed to hit, gray...
Wolffy
The video...so fuzzy...
The eyes are getting hurting more and more
The light is so bright that I can’t see the way
What’s going on? I can’t see it anymore
Ah...
Are you exhausted?
Good chance to catch you
Let go!
Don’t let it go!
黑风黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑
Don’t think about it!
Let me go
Even if you can’t see it, just catch you
Just hate you?黑风黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑黑
Lightning Strike!
It seems that I heard a bad sound
How did it sink
It depends on the good things you did...
- Ahhhhh…
What happened here?
Ahhhhh…
I heard there was tranquility around the park
Let’s go and have a look
Right, I heard it too
Who is it?
puff!
Get it done
Wow! Big snowball!
Help...
Don’t run
Ah... monster
Don’t come...I will never dare again...
All caught
I don’t know what happened to Wolffy
Let’s go find him now
Um
Oh, I really can’t see anything...
oops
Weslie
Where are you?
I’m under you
Weslie, aren’t you hurt?
My feet...
horn?
Sorry, Weslie, I stepped on your horn
I’ll pack it for you here
Not this corner
My legs were all pressed by stones
Found
Let me help you pry the stone open
Not here, this is my head
Where is that?
Here? Here?
Where are you, Weslie?
Snow blindness?
Now you hear me pointing
Walk towards you at 3 o’clock
Then insert the branches under the stone
12 o’clock 1 o’clock 2 o’clock 3 o’clock
Is that right?
Now my legs are damaged and I can’t move
You can call someone to save us
OK Help...
- ah…
Where to hide? Where to hide?
Right
Jump left
Three circles on the right
Can’t you make a little noise if you call someone?
Then you can clear my eyes
I can take you right up
Hum, I can’t help your eyes clear
It’s not that you use your power
Have my eyes lost sight of anything?
Your eyes are the sun reflected by snow
It’s not visible after a long period of exposure
This is snow blindness
There is no way to recover in a short period of time
Then what should I do now
I...I can’t see it
You can’t leave, you can’t call for help
Then won’t you be able to get out?
How about it...
Still think about what’s the solution
How to do it? I’ve come up with the idea
You are my eyes I am your double digit
Let’s go up together
Is it hard to worry about your strength?
Then try it
Don’t run and hit the stone
Stop and stop…
You stand up first and let me see how to climb
ha! Just go to the right
At that time, I will climb up the vines
Put him here
Go to the right
Listen to my instructions and climb up
There is a stone to tread on the right
There is also a stone on the left
Climbing upwards
Climb to the left a little
Do you... believe me?
We are two brothers on the same boat now
Of course I believe you
- Oh, it hurts so much...
You’re going to hug me
Don’t fall down
I’m here to see Wolffy again
You’re stuck here
Ah, it hurts so much...
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Weslie? oops…
Wolffy, you...
It’s about to fall to the ground...
You’re fine, right?
No...I’m fine
Why did you turn down?
No reason
Don’t care about these
You’ve helped me before
Weslie, aren’t we friends?
Wolffy I’m behind you
I’m not friends with you
We just got on the right time
OK, take a quick ride
Come on, let’s try again
It’s hard to climb on the right, let’s climb from the left
good
- Very good, finally came out
Hahaha…
Weslie
Ahem, you’re just here
Come and carry me back
- yes
So how should this wolf be dealt with?
yes
Wolffy
What’s up
Next
This is...
I’ll give you this favor
Now I’m doing business and hand over the fragments
No, I won’t hand over the fragments to you
yes
Wolffy
Retreat first
yes
Wolffy, you’re fine?
I’m fine
What’s wrong with your eyes
It’s snow blindness, I can’t see anything
What should I do
Don’t worry, this can be cured
Let’s leave here first
Wolffy What’s on this bag
This is…a medicine for treating snow blindness
Who gave it to you?
It’s given by Weslie
what?