Can Wolffy see it?
Here are a few fingers
Five...Not Four
I can see something
Very good
Weslie is still very good to me
May be sure
It will be restored soon
In fact, Weslie is working hard to connect us
So, Weslie is just reuniting my relationship
Wait a minute where are we now
We’re in the ice sculpture
Ice sculpture? What about the scattered ice fan?
Meow
The villagers not only used ice sculptures to cover us up
Also help us find fragments
ah…
Wow! You’re fine, right?
It’s okay, I’ll make it myself
alright
Or we will help you
We found another piece of fragment
Are the others okay?
Weslie brings the villagers who have helped us before
All captured
I don’t know how cool they are suffering
It smells so good
Even at the last moment
We also have to be a little bit...
Have the ability to relax us
Don’t induce us with food
Before the sun goes down
You’re going to carve a hundred ice sculptures
what? How can this be done
- yes
Can’t finish it? That’s the next
Husky soup is so fragrant
We almost couldn’t help it
I don’t like to eat husky
We’ll hand it over to you now
Hahaha... It’s so fun
Ahem...Men...Why are you here
It was Queen Levana who sent me to help you
Since this military officer is here
You have to hear my advice
Hello! You have to listen to me!
snort! They only hear my orders
Watch
hand
I saw that this is the miracle I trained
Wow…
I asked you to give me your hand
Come on hand
Hahaha... So good
Don’t waste time, let’s catch people now
I didn’t ask you to run away first, wait for me
ah…
Stop it for me
Ah... Alas...
Have you got rid of them?
ah…
My nose was eaten
Oh, my nose was eaten, too
Huh?
Alas, it really scared me
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
My husband is not delicious at all...
Oh wow ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah...
Hi
Hi…
ah…
Stop... don’t...
Alas...
I don’t want to secretly let me watch you
Fragments have been found
Wait for the fan to get together
We can change back to what we were like
Sorry, I’ve been slapped
Squeak...
I’ve just been passing by
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Don’t eat my nose
ah…
This...is this an earthquake?
Get rid of the big scoundrel and wait...
Oops! Can’t let it discover Princess Luna
Have to find something to lead it away
I can only sacrifice you my precious nose
ah…
Hello... There is Husky here. Come on
Come…
They actually sent the miracle too
It seems we have to be discovered before
Firmly put into pieces
Yes, just hand it over to me
Princess Luna…
It’s okay, I just didn’t expect to repair the ice fan
It actually consumes so much power
Need to be sanitized
You have some rest first
Let’s wait for the snowman to retrieve the remaining pieces before talking
Um
It’s not until the end of this place can be repaired
It must be the snowman who brought the last piece of debris
No, no, no...not good
Being taken away by a scoundrel
What got knocked out
Is your nose?
Right, my nose was pulled away
Ah...I’m not talking about this
Yes... is the fragments being taken away
Just when I was pulling out the miracle
It should be fine if it leads to such a long distance
Let’s go, I’ll leave the rest to you
Just run away while you’re now
Run...Run...
No! The fragments were broken
ah! That can’t be eaten
So, did the miracle eat the fragments?
No, things are not finished yet
Shocked me
That’s fine
Things aren’t so simple
Have to send the fragments back tightly
It’s over. The fragments are taken away.
What circle do you mean by surprise?
Then let’s go find the little beast
The fragment must be in the Miracle Hand
Let’s go out with all your strength
Um
Curious Bamboo fell asleep. This is a good opportunity
Let me try it with Magic power first
No
Repairing the fan just consumes too much energy
Let this king come out of his own
Wolffy, you have to be careful
Don’t worry, I’ve been experiencing my years of experience in sneaking into the Goat Village
It’s a side dish... a dish...
ah…
You are told to be careful, but you fall down
Just a mistake
Let’s go together
I’ll lift the mouth of the sensation
Quick and easy
It’s so tight
ah…
So tired I can’t run anymore
Big Wolf, think about it quickly
What can I do?
With Thunderbolt
Oh, why did I just chop it against me this time
You want to find a way to solve the problem
It’s not that you want to create a problem
Ah... I’ve fought
- Wolffy
I hug
- Well…
Thunder Bird Flash…
Oops Oops…
- Is this OK?
It seems that Wolffy has defeated the Great Miracle
Wolffy is great
Tibbie, you’re fine, right?
Ah my feet...
No!
And for you
No! The debris are about to fall into the ice lake!
It’s too late to come, I’ll throw you over
But…
quick!
Hi…
Princess Luna, be careful
ah…
Magic Cloud!