Princess Luna…
Pull it hard
Hey!
Alas!
ah…
Be careful not to touch the lake
Oh no, they’re here
So you are here?
What happened?
Your scoundrel has fought with that helper
And that helps people
Another person fell into the ice lake
Thank you for saving us just now
Not good, they’re here
Children, we’re here to save you
It turns out that it is Coco’s father and mother
If you hadn’t come, we might have been arrested
Thank you so much
You’re just for us
This little busy is nothing
Why is it so popular
You, you… your face is melting
what?
Come quickly and let the bright moon warm up a little
You can’t do that
Save…Help…
Snowman dad
sorry
It’s okay. You didn’t mean it
Want to unravel the ice on Princess Luna
You must go to the warm spring on the snow-capped mountains
- Nuannuan Spring?
Yes
The Nuannuan Spring is a spring water that can melt any ice block
Just put it on Princess Luna
Great, Princess Luna is saved
Then let’s go up the mountain with all your might
I’ll take you the way
Huh?
Why did you stand upside down?
You’re too big
Hahaha…
- well…
I really don’t need to show you a way
Last time it was because of helping us
That’s why you were punished by Weslie
We’ll just go by ourselves
A smooth journey
So tired, I can’t walk anymore
Let’s take a break first
Who is it?
Is it a Weslie?
Meow…
It’s cocoa
Coco, why are you here again
Go back soon
Meow… Meow…
It seems he wants to follow us up the mountain
Now I’m sending cocoa back
- Will be missed for a long time
Then bring him on
Meow
We’re going on the road with tight time
Don’t be careless
Beware of Weslie and Goat Flying Hits Hits Hits
Um
It’s your time. Put your right hand on a high point
How do you hear this? Am I dreaming?
Uh… show me your left hand
Ah…I heard it
Right hand Left foot Right foot
head…
Ah, it turns out that’s not
Finally arrived
How did this happen
No spring water
What should Princess Luna do?
Hahaha…
It turned out that Princess Luna fell into the ice lake
It’s hard not to meet you on the road
Have you guessed that we will come up?
But I didn’t guess you’d go so slowly
Oh, I’m almost asleep
snort! Did you do anything about Nuannuanquan?
snort! Who knows?
It seems we can only retreat first
I’m responsible for leading him out, you go quickly
There are also things you can’t guess
ah? Ice fan?
Big Wolf, I won’t show any mercy again this time
Take the call
If you don’t want to be a snowman, just walk away
Stop installing
Isn’t there another piece in Princess Luna’s hand?
What should I do now
You…what do you want to do?
You’re willing to hand over the pieces
I can consider letting you go
Really
You’re such a kid’s cheating
I’m three years old and you go quickly
You asked for it yourself
Ah Help…
ah
Fulai
ah…
Magic Cloud
Coco Where are you going?
Meow
Coco What are you doing
No?
ah!
Tibbie, eat me again
No
Hehehe…it’s a bit interesting
Don’t let him use the food
It depends on whether you have this ability
oops
Let’s fan the ice to him
Not complete anyway
Even if he gave it to him, he would still catch us
So what should I do now
Give me a snail
What are your solutions
I’ll drag him first
You took the opportunity to take Tibbie and Luna and others away
But…
Weslie I’m here
I’m going to help Wolffy
Luna and Fulai will hand it over to you
ah? But…
Weslie!
ah!
If only I could be stronger
What should I do now
Hahaha…
Go back with me and see Queen Levana
I can’t just hide, what should I do
How to do it…
ah?
Spring water is spring water
What’s going on?
Very good
Why did you suddenly feel water?
cocoa
It turned out that the spring mouth was blocked by these ice blocks
But you found these ice blocks
Have you taken them out yet?
aim
Weslie Hello
You need to take care of it
Magic Cloud
Success
This spring is really useful
Wolffy
Tibbie
Weslie, you’ve gotten too much
Don’t think you won’t win if you saved Princess Luna
Magic Cloud
Do you think you can throw me if you are a little older?
I didn’t want to hurt you
Don’t want to trap me
Let’s run quickly
Princess…
Great, you’re fine
Well, what happened?
Put the ice fan together first
Um
Finished
pain…
- He seemed to ask us to follow him
Wolffy
Have a hole? Go in first
Meow
Ahhhhh…
ah? We’ve already fallen on the mountain?
It turns out there is such a secret passage
Meow…
Who are you?
What are you talking about? I’m a Tibbie
Tibbie?