Going here?
I’ll find yours
Wow
Tibbie Please don’t cry
Whenever Weslie heard it, it found us
Weslie?
I don’t want Weslie to see me like this
Snowmen also have the benefits of snowmen
I won’t have to worry about not eating shaved ice in the future
Shaved ice?
Tibbie, let me take a bite
Oh, don’t eat me
Just a spoonful
Wow, I don’t want to turn into shaved ice
We have to fan the ice back
Let everyone recover
Then we are going to find Weslie?
Even if we don’t look for him
He will come back to find us, too
Weslie is here
what!
What should I do if I finish it?
I’ll ask you again
Where did the Yanyang and the others hide?
We don’t know
Then this little cat will suffer
stop!
Finally came out
All turned into snowmen
Ice fan?
ah? fan?
Blessing
snort!
Overestimate one’s ability!
snort! interesting
not good!
It seems that I won
Don’t be proud, even if we become snowmen
Will bring the ice fan back
oh? Yes?
If you want it, just go and pick it up
All turned into snowmen?
Yes Queen
As long as they leave the ice town, they will melt
Humph, good doing
Yes, the ice fan cannot be taken away by them
The queen is relieved. I threw the ice fan into the ice lake.
Throwed it?
Don’t be careless
What should they do when they get it?
No, even if they are cunning
It is impossible to get a fan from the Bing Lake
You should go back and watch them carefully
Don’t have any more accidents
Yes His Highness
How can I get the ice fan?
Let me go down and try
Anyway, I’m a snowman, it should be fine
Pay attention to safety
It seems that it won’t work
Is it hard to get the ice fan?
Ha chi!
Very cold
Paddi!
Haven’t you been hit?
ha? ah
That’s how things are
Great, we still have the chance
What opportunity
Come here, I have a plan
what? Is this feasible?
Now everyone has become a snowman
Only you can do this
Can I really
You can do it, we all believe in you
Everyone
OK, I’ll go and try
The Queen is so attentive
In this case, they can’t leave here at all
Weslie has come. Practical plan
Weslie
It’s just right I’m bored
Give it to me!
ah
Please help us get the ice fan back
Don’t hang on me, I won’t help you
It seems he doesn’t eat this one
Weslie
It’s you again
- Let us give you a massage
Weslie
Can you help us fan the ice...
Don’t want to scold me
I won’t give you ice fan
Weslie
Are you tired after repeated
Want to eat something or not
think
No, you don’t want to
What about the goat
not good!
Why are you still sleeping?
sleep?
Do you want to have a bite of it?
No reaction?
Fake?
What are you playing?
I’ll tell you
The silly goat has already gone to Binghu
Ice Lake?
I’m ready
You must be careful after you go into the water
OK No problem
I have decorated the spring water of the warm spring into the cloud layer
Wear the diving suit on your body again
This will protect me from being frozen
I’ve come out
You must come back safely
Where is the ice fan
It seems you’ve prepared a ridiculous plan
Just take Paddi
Can he save you?
We believe him
Where are you confident
He must be saying now... so tired
I’m so hungry
I’m so cold
Ha ha ha ha
And you may also say the hope of your entire village
It has now become ice in the ice lake!
Why did it suddenly get cold?
ah? Ice Fan!
So cold
Why is the diving suit leaking?
Being broken
I’ll get ice
How to do it
So you should listen obediently
Be here obediently
No one can save you
Paddi
Don’t act
How is it possible?
Paddi
You actually did it?
I can’t leave you alone
It’s a goat
You are so great
It seems that I really underestimate you
Give me the ice fan
ah
Fan the ice quickly!
Not good, goat are in danger
No matter what!
Thunderbolt
I can’t stand Weslie
ah
Weslie