Ice Fan
Everyone, come back
Meow
cocoa
Very good
Great, no one is fine
Weslie
Where are you
Could it be that they are below?
You must be fine
Let’s help everyone
good
It’s all my fault for using thunderbolt
Otherwise they wouldn’t have encountered an avalanche
Wolffy, they will definitely be fine
You see, no one gave up
So let’s dig it out quickly
Must rescue them
good
Weslie Goat Answer me
Answer me quickly
It hurts where am I?
Ah Weslie
Weslie wake up, Weslie
Lots of wounds
Happy goat
ah
Magic Cloud
Weslie, Weslie, wake up
No! I can’t hold it anymore!
This is a lot of snow
I don’t know where I’m buried
And it’s been so long
Weslie and the others will be fine
We won’t give up until the last moment
Let’s keep cheering
good
Weslie
Ha ha
I beg you not to miss it
Weslie: I didn’t encounter any danger before
Will you save me?
You’re getting up now, don’t sleep
I want to sleep again, too
Paddi
Who is it?
Weslie, you’re fine
Sorry, I can’t protect you this time
But you have to be brave
But I’m so cool, I can’t hold on
You can definitely
Believe in yourself, don’t give up?
good
I’ll promise you
Magic Cloud!
Hide
Difficult to tell
The Goat is the Goat
The goat must be below
Meow Meow Meow
You finally arrived
We will rescue you immediately
Rescue first
Weslie!
- Paddi
Save people quickly
Weslie’s hand movement
What happened?
Weslie’s injury should be nothing serious
- Thank you Luna
but
The rest depends on when he wakes up
I’ve tried my best
Cough cough
Princess, let’s take a rest first
- Thanks for your hard work
- Weslie
Weslie...
Let’s go in
It’s been five days, I haven’t woken up yet
Weslie If you don’t wake up again
I will be the protagonist of the green grassland
It won’t
He just fell asleep and didn’t wake up
Weslie, wake up, Weslie
You’ve been lying for almost a week
Don’t sleep anymore
Don’t you
You let Weslie have a good rest
You are a little cold
Weslie will not be a problem
Wasn’t it okay before?
There will be no problem this time
There will be no problem in the future
What are you doing? Stop being done
You said there will be nothing wrong, but Wan will not come when you wake up
I don’t want this
- Don’t do this
If only I could have found you earlier
Tibbie
You don’t have to blame yourself
Actually, it’s all my fault if I hadn’t caused an avalanche
Weslie will not
Don’t be buried in the snow
It’s all my fault, it’s all my fault
No, I didn’t protect him
He suffered a lot and was over
In such a cold place, I’ve been so tired for so long
It’s my bad, it’s my useless
If I could have thought of a way out sooner
Weslie can cure it early
How about you, Weslie, wake up
If you like playing football, can we play football?
I’ll help you with your room every day.
OK
Wake up, wake up
I’ll give you all the snacks
Can you stop sleeping
I know you’re having a hard time
But let it go if it is past
I didn’t expect the result to be like this
You have to cheer up
Heart hurts so much
Hehehe is still feeling worried about your snacks
This is all my snacks
It hurts so much if you think about it
Please leave me a piece
OK OK OK
Hahahahaha
I’ll give you all the snacks
Can you stop sleeping
Really
Then you’ve got all your snacks
Weslie!
You finally wake up
Weslie
You goat, stop crying, I’m fine
I remember that’s not the case when you were avalanche
You are so strong that you protect me
Do you still remember?
Weslie finally recovered
Yes, I remembered it
Everything we’ve ever done
Very good
Sorry, I apologize for the previous injuries
OK You’ve apologized many times
We won’t blame you either
Hahahahaha
Everyone should take good care of themselves
Princess Luna, you must restore the cat country
Meow
See you again, I’ll miss you
See you again
goodbye
Report to the Queen Weslie has become rebellious
And
It’s over, no need to say
You three
Will they betray me like they two?
Of course not
OK Since that’s the case
These three hand rings on my hand are now being paid to you
Thank you Queen
What is this
- Very hard
Disappeared?
The hand ring will automatically retract every time
I’ll give you crystal stones regularly
You better not betray me? Do you understand?
yes