More people and more power
So we have to go to the quicksand town to convince the Sparky
Very hot
So hot
It will be even more popular when you arrive at Quicksand Town
No, they made me very excited
This will make you recover
No matter how hot you are, you can’t let go
Yes, I won’t let go of a single piece
Didn’t you say you didn’t let go?
Too hot
It’s so amazing, it’s still snowing
It’s so hot here
Quicksand Town is very popular all year round
And it’s very water-deficient
Water shortage? Then we
rest assured! look!
I’ve prepared some water
Drink slowly is enough
Um?
ah! You save some drinks
Not afraid, there is
OK OK OK I’ll save some drinks Hee
Yes, finally arrived
Waiting for you for a long time Flame Fist
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Catch them all
yes
Everyone is fine
It’s OK
Who is plotting against us
Been surrounded
How to do Weslie
Since this is the case
It seems that I can only do anything wrong…
We surrendered
surrender
What are you doing with Weslie
As long as we pretend to be caught
You will naturally find the Sparky
Makes sense
Please capture us
It’s so smooth
What was the Sparky  in the past?
He
Fierce and irritating
But he is brave and righteous
But now he
Hip-Hahahaha if he knew he had become like this
Will definitely go crazy
Who is saying my bad words
Please make an appointment for water
There is only one spoonful per person
Why do you have to line up the team?
I’ve been
I heard that it was Sparky  who surrounded the water tank.
ah
Paddi
Ah, there is a pitfall
Go up quickly and don’t disturb my work
Sorry Sorry
What are they digging?
Digging water, Master Sparky needs more water
oh
Look no further. Go away!
It seems that there is really a lack of water here
Wow! So much water!
I’m here to the swimming pool
I’ve already felt the smell of water
Refreshing
Sparky?
Leave nothing to pay
I want to swim, too
Sparky  The residents outside all need water very much
Can you provide some water to the residents?
Don’t I supply them with water every day?
Each person has a spoonful of people. Who can drink it?
You weren’t like this before
Sparky , wake up, you are controlled tomorrow
Stop talking nonsense
Sparky , listen carefully to my explanation
I don’t listen to it. I’ll do whatever I want.
Sparky, what are you like now
I know Sparky, who is very kind-hearted
Happy to help others
Although there is a lot of strength
But this energy is used to help others
Sparky, wake up
I don’t listen I don’t listen
So childish, I can’t even pretend to be able to hear it
Let’s go, don’t want to talk to this person again
stop! Don’t try to sneak away!
Take them all to jail!
What should I do now
Hurricane Blade
Don’t forget that we have great power
Magic Cloud
And me
Sparky , you wake me up
You’ve been chattering together and it’s really funny
Flame Fist
Ahhhhhhhhhhhh
snort! I caught you in one go
Master Sparky Goat is wise and magical
Take them to jail
Not good! My tender skin is sweating!
Let me prepare a new pool water and I want to take a shower
Obey orders
The Sparky  is really too much
It actually closed us
You’ve also been concerned about us
Uh what?
I didn’t remember you at that time
Think about how to get out
Let me try the storm
Hahaha, don’t be exhausted
This is a prisoner to trap you
You just stay here obediently
I don’t believe it can’t be opened
Thunder and birds flash!
Oops! Forgot to take care of
Hahaha I just said it’s useless
Sparky
The ground outside was blown through
what? You dare to break my home?
No, why are your whole body wet?
It’s because the flashing just now penetrated the ground
Water actually emerged from the ground and was then poured on
real? Take him away
His genius may be able to split more water
I’ll go out first and then find a chance to come back and save you
OK, we’ll wait for you
Have you seen it or not? Let me go
Princess Luna
Who are you
Don’t say anything, go out first and say
There are strange people there
Thank you for saving us out
Yes, I don’t know your name yet
My name is Xiaomu
Why did you come to save us?
No, someone has come
Then let’s go quickly
But has Sparky  recovered?
I have not been able to influence the Sparky for a while
Just go to the palace to restore the princess tomorrow
Everything will recover
Um
Yes, we still have to bring Wolffy
Wolffy Can you find a new source of water
Yes Of course
Thunderbolt
Please make an appointment for water
Please use water
Can you please click on it?
This is the wild Qili, I can’t control it well, either
Then continue
well
Sorry
I have to make you mess up first before I can save everyone
Thunderbolt
Can you do it?
Hahaha Impossible
The next hit won’t be missed again
Lightning Strike Lightning Strike Lightning Strike
Thunderbolt
oops
Look, Wolffy is there
Did they escape?
No need to try again, take him back
Wait for a little while and give me another chance
Put your hands open, nothing you say is useless
Come and take him back
Wait a minute.
Let’s go back
How to beat
This is a thorn
Too scary
Hello
How did you escape?
Stop me Flame Fist
ah
Flame Fist
Start Shield
What do you want
I can’t stand it anymore Sparky
What are you doing to me?
I’m going to be black
I won’t let you go