While the Sparky  is not chasing
Let’s take a car to the palace to find Princess Levana
What are you doing with Weslie
You see
What should I do
Just a few soldiers
I used the Lightning Strike to hit the opposite side and led them out
thunder…
No…
oops…
Alas
What are you doing
Wolffy, a thunderbolt hit us here
Uh...it seems to be the same, but I still don’t need it
Now it’s no longer a problem with several soldiers
Then what should I do now
When they exchange
See if there is any chance to mix in
Um
Tibbie
Let me come
Princess Luna…
They’re not sick, they’re lacking water
Have to give them water soon
Where is there water in the desert
ah? What is this
This is...tea pot
That’s the light
Divine light? We’re saved
Why didn’t you react?
That...is not friction
It’s time to knock three times with a cube
Light God Light God
Please help me restore everyone to its original state
I don’t seem to understand what you’re saying
The divine lights here cannot be silly
Only answer questions
What a useless divine light
OK, light god, please tell me where is there water
Every day at 12 noon, someone will give water in the market
Do you have a second question?
That…
I won’t answer some
The light god here can only answer one question
Since that’s the case, I’m pretending to be a resident and go to the team to steer the water
Wolffy, try it
Can you check with residents around you?
Who finds the water first, who will come back to save people first
Princess Luna Fulai
Please find a place to stay calm
Andon they
Um
Sparky
Everyone cooperates with the inspection
All those wearing masks were lifted off for me
How to do it
No one can live without water
I don’t believe you don’t come to get water
The military officer is really tall when he waits for the rabbit
See what they look like
Can’t leave anymore
There will be no water to save Yangyang and the others
What are you doing
All fell off, go ahead
I’ve asked a lot of people
No one has water, what should I do
Sparky  manages here so that it will not leak out
But there must be a miscellaneous secret.
He never thought...
Kid, lend the water gun to the uncle for fun
Um
I didn’t expect it to be so easy to get water
It’s sand again...
Oh, I’m too difficult
Water...water...water...
Why don’t Weslie and Wolffy come back yet
Princess Luna
Wolffy, is there water?
- Wolffy
Now Wolffy has heatstroke
Weslie has never come back
I’ll go find water
You take care of them here
Then you have to be careful
Um
Lift your head
Next
Strange why you didn’t see the goat
Maybe wait and see
Yes
What if they don’t come
You are so wise, they will definitely be
It makes sense, please continue to send water
Um
Alas! ah…
Sorry Sorry...
It doesn’t matter
etc.
Weslie? Catch him!
Water I want water...
What’s going on?
It’s you!
Flame Fist
No more water
Chase me
yes
Go and stare at them
Depend on where you’re running away
stop!
Very good!
Don’t be proud
Everyone went to the back of the street to catch Weslie
quick
Catch him!
Xiaomu?
Don’t go to let it open
Soldier Chief What to do?
Let it open first
not good!
Weslie Xiaomu
A bunch of useless things
Thank you for saving us again
You are welcome
Why do you keep helping us
Because…
stop!
You go quickly and they’re caught up with you right away
- Um
Then you have to be careful too
Um
Just ahead, it’s almost here