The water is coming
Water water…
So cool
It’s great that you’re fine
Brother and sister
Can you give us some water?
But… the water has been finished
Let’s… help them first
Won’t be
This king will never see you who will never be saved from death
But the current guard at the water station
It should be more severe
Where can we find water?
If I don’t remember the wrong thing
There is also a water tank in Sparky’s palace
The water from the water should be transported from there
The palace of Sparky Goat
That must be a lot of danger
That’s not necessarily
Sparky should still be staying at the waters
Then let’s go and have a look
Based on my search
Sparky is not in the palace at present
And there are fewer guardians
Let’s go
Is there anything wrong with it?
There are so many frogs here
frog? Why are there frogs in the desert?
Stop it, let’s go to other places to patrol
Come
It’s really too many Tibbie
It should be here
Wow!
There is so much water hidden here
We packed the water and went back quickly
- good
Let’s go
There are so many frogs lately
give
Thank you Princess Luna
No need for guest
This way we can come out with peace of mind
Weslie will definitely come to get water again
We’re here waiting for sure to catch them
Too hot…
Report to the master, I have been sending the water for a long time
Not only did the princesses and the others come
There are also many fewer residents in the water
what? How did this happen?
How could they not drink water?
How is it possible? This place is so popular
But there is water in the entire quicksand town
Where else can they go?
Could it be…
They did come
Why can’t I see even a water tank well…
But I haven’t seen anyone come
I saw a few frogs
frog? Why do there be frogs in the desert
There is a water tank here, it’s normal to have frogs
That’s right
Neither right or wrong, this must be done by Tibbie
How can I catch them
That’s how it is
I’m talking about military officer
You must think of a solution for me
Don’t you have a desert horn monitor?
What about the images at that time
Hello, go and take the crystal ball over
yes
Have you seen it
Yes, I’ve seen it
Weslie is so despicable. He dares to hold on to me
Not saying this
Don’t look at the surface of everything
I think I already know the reason
snort! They’re finished this time!
So what exactly is the reason?
Why are there so many soldiers
How can we get on the car like this
ah…
Who is there?
Oops…
Go and take a look
Come out tightly, otherwise you will look good
I’m going to be discovered
This is…a hairball…
Meow Meow Meow Meow Meow Meow Meow Meow Meow…
Sorry
My hairball dropped here
- It turns out to be a soldier
Then let’s continue patrolling
Thank you for saving us again
It’s not polite, it’s fine if you’re fine
Xiaomu, you are obviously the one from Sparky
But why do you keep helping us
That’s because…
A long time ago, the water source here gradually dried up
Later, the king sent two princesses to come.
Come and find water sources
Finally we returned to our normal life
Everyone in our quicksand town
Both have received favors from the two princesses
I know that the princess tomorrow has changed now
But there must be some reason
I hope to contribute, too
Let me help you leave
thank you
Come with me, everyone
The fugitive appeared there
Go and catch someone with me
Go catch the fugitive
The soldiers are leaving
Yes, let’s go
what!
Hahahahahahaha…
The military officer said it was right, but it was indeed introverted.
Xiaomu
Sorry, we were calculated
There is no way to go. Get ready for a fight
Stop and stop
ha?
Why do you want to fight? Tired and sweaty
you mean…
Why not… let’s compete
You can leave after you win
Go to jail after you’ve lost it
What’s the point
Or do you want to compete for running?
No, too tired
Tug of war?
No, sweating
That fish?
That’s too hot
Then what do you want to do…
I want to compete in the sand
Scratch sand?
Sand paddling is a dragon boat competition in the desert
The fastest way to the final point is victory
Let’s sign a agreement before the game
I’ll do such a difficult task
Well, the competition is ready to begin
They look so strong
We don’t look bad either
So stupid…you need to work hard
Hit them…
ah…
Be careful, everyone
Let’s go one step ahead
Don’t think about it!
Hurricane Blade!
Stop, stop, you’ve violated the rules
It was you who slaughtered the sand first, but you were the one who violated the law
Written in the agreement, you will be eliminated if you use the sensible power
I didn’t use any weird power
How could you be so traitorous
snort! Written on the agreement
All rights reserved to be Sparkys, Weslies are eliminated
It’s okay, you can do it
The game continues
Sparky , you are playing tricks
ha! I’m looking for success
Chase! Chase quickly!
Great, win!
Sparky , abide by the rules and let us go
Who told you that it’s over? Two matches in three games
You haven’t said it
All rights to explain Sparky
Come on, sir
- come on
Win
Wait, compare another game
Five games and three games
One Hundred Games Three…Four…Five…Fifty-One Games
You’re just playing tricks on us
So what?
The agreement was invalid. Get them for me
Baa Baa Baa Baa…We were hit by Qili
Where is the person?
They haven’t gone far yet. Come catch up
Fortunately, Weslie left footprints in advance
They did run in the direction of the footprint
Where did they go?