Xiaomu What are you planning to do next
Don’t worry, I’ll go back to my hometown
You have to be careful
Neither far or far, the next village is
Let’s go take the car, too
Don’t be discovered
It’s a desert turtle. Hide!
Hunting up!
Where should I hide?
Even if you search through the quicksand town
Find them out too
grown ups
Don’t you really have to ask the Queen to get crystals?
Catch someone first
I have already made arrangements for the crystal matter
yes
These three knives in my hand
Now I’ll pay you
Must catch them
It’s a Jonie!
Desert Eagle should have left, right?
Lord Jonie Please come
It’s a Jonie!
Oops, can’t be discovered
I knew that the last bathroom was so far away
I won’t go
No! The slept with the goat is still hiding inside!
It seems that the 日本語 has not been discovered yet
What to do next
Save the goat!
How did Lord Jonie get to the bathroom
So much heavier
When they step on the beans, they slipped
I took the opportunity to rescue the goat
They are here!
How could this happen?
We want to check!
You actually dare to search our Lord Jonie!
Inside… is the Jonie
terribly sorry
But Master Sparky said that he could not let go anywhere
Jonie
If you have the dignity of being a goat
They must not search
It’s okay, let them search
It’s Weslie
Weslie
Come and chase me
superior!
Weslie!
It turns out that everyone is here
catch!
Go quickly!
You’re fine
Hot Goat
They are prisoners that the Queen will catch tomorrow
Let’s go chase them
No, I have something more important
It hurts so much…
ah…
Report to Lord Jonie is here
Sparky
The Queen asked me to send the crystals over
Great, give it to me
I… seemed to…smash the crystal…
Sparky …
Do not let any criminals go
yes
This is…
Huh? What is this?
It’s like a crystal
…
This big cactus
Will they be hiding in it?
It’s over…
Don’t look for it there
Stop searching for prisoners
I’ll send me the Jonie
On the way
Find a small bag
- yes
What bag are they looking for…
A sac?
Don’t worry about them
Let’s go and fix the car and go away
OK Fixed
Finally, I can leave the quicksand town
They’re back
Can’t find the crystal stone again, Lord Sparky will be in danger
Sparky?
But we searched it all
I can’t find that red pouch
If there is no crystal detox in the sac
Lord Sparky can’t hold back
Something happened to Sparky
Crystal?
Is that what?
Sparky is in danger
We have to go back and save him soon
All of them are cheating us back
There is also this possibility
The crystal was accidentally picked up by the Goat
So Sparky and the others don’t know
And they can tell the characteristics of the sac
I don’t think it’s cheating on us
That…
It’s finally arrived here
Go back
Let’s go I know you’re not going to feel at ease
Um
Princess Luna, you go to the palace first
Let’s save the Sparky first
By then we want to get along with you
You must be careful
We’re here
I found out that the communication was offended
Is Sparky  in danger?
Take us to see him
Sparky
We’re here with a bag, don’t be afraid
Did you take the crystal?
Save him quickly
Sparky, you’re fine
Goat…goat…
We came back to save you
Isn’t it very touching
Have you remembered us
Ah…so dirty…
Soldiers, catch them
Unexpectedly, I was caught when I came back
Sparky  is really cruel
But Sparky  is fine
Yes, I feel relieved when Sparky is fine
As long as he has nothing to do
Sparky, please give me some food
Why are you so cruel…