Look forward to them
No matter what situation can be opened
yes
Open the door and let them out
Two Sparky ?
Wake me up!
This...is this a silhouette lens?
Fortunately, I remember that Tibbie will use the virtual mirror
Come back in time
Stop opening again
yes
Don’t let me down
Yes, I suddenly remembered something
Open the door soon and let me ask them
OK
oops!
I just said something and forgot it again!
It’s so easy to get ahead!
Let me say again. Do I need to open the question?
Why is the brain so ignorant...
Compared to the previous Sparky, he is really more careful
The little one knows
Please calm down your anger, Lord Sparky
The regenerated anaconda comes out
It really makes people feel worried
That’s it
You two go to guard the door
Here is the Desert Germine
OK
and
Give them a bottle of water every day
Just a thunderhead
Can’t be too good to them, do you understand?
- yes
Sparky , please stand me
No need to quit
I won’t let you out, no matter what.
Is it not possible for each person to have two pants?
Weslie What to do now
Why can’t you see anything?
Hello, what are you doing?
This cake is so sweet
This sofa is so soft, this bed is so comfortable
Can’t eat it anymore, it’s so good
I didn’t expect the treatment of this cell to be so good
What the hell is going on?
Huh? There is a hole here
…
Have a hole? What the hell is going on
You open the door and see what happened to the prisoners
You open the door quickly
Don’t go, have you forgotten the teaching?
This must be a illusion
Yes, thank you for reminding me
I’m going to learn to be smart this time
What a fantasy I am a Sparky
Come in and see what they are doing!
- What a fantasy
- I am Sparky
It seems that I can only go by myself
Why are you so good to give prisoners privately
No, Sparky
Then why do they have so much food to eat
There is also a comfortable bed
We just follow the instructions
Each person gives a roe and a bottle of water
Nothing else
Open the door and let me go in and take a look
Wait, this may be a illusion
Have you forgotten your previous teaching?
The innocent goat
Do you think we’ll be there again?
I’ve seen through your tricks
Let it open! I’ll go in by myself!
Hum, as long as we are still standing here
No one can get in
OK, you forced me
Where is the person?
Huh? There is a hole here
…
Is it really a hole that makes them run away?
Where is the hole?
Hiding in the cloud
Escape, everyone
It was locked before entering
Hehe...you think I’m stupid
Take his key!
Shocked me
Hahahahahahahahaha...
You have no way to go out
- You can’t get out by yourself?
- You’re still stupid
You have to keep it! Let me out quickly!
If you want to go out, let the soldiers open the door
I won’t be there
Maybe aside from the key
There are other ways to open this door
What are you going to do...
What are you going to do... Why do you touch my face...
Help, come soon...
It seems that I can’t face it
How about trying finger marks
Maybe it’s the toes
Help Hahahahaha...
Very terrible...
Help Hahahaha...
Come quickly
- Tips for carving
It must be an illusion again. They’re too traitorous.
I can’t help laughing. It’s so fake
Hahaha…
You’ve gotten too far
It seems that he really has no other way out
Get water for me, I want to take a shower
Where is the water?
What you told yourself
Each person has a bottle of water and a puff
All used up
How to take a shower
This is our only food, do you want it?
I don’t eat white horns!
I want to eat apple! I want to drink milk!
Now only those two soldiers are allowed to help us open the door
Or...we collaborate to leave here
I’m definitely not a traitor with you
Then you just stay here all the time
And can’t take a bath
No comfortable bed
And there may be cockroaches here
How? Cooperate?
You bring me in
I’m locked in a prison
Hello…
Her illusion lens is so terrifying
Anyway, we won’t be
Come in and save me!
What’s up?
They’re in
Lord Sparky, why are you here too
Help me open the door quickly
yes
Hahahaha...do you think I’ll be on again?
It seems you’ve really grown
That’s that’s that’s that’s that’s that’s that’s that’s it
Successfully...
No, catch them
I don’t hear fake goods say it!
Catch them all!
Why is this fake Master Sparky?
No matter what, grab it first!
You’re in a illusion. Go and chase them...
snort! We won’t be there!
It’s really useless
Flame Fist
How come this trick looks like Lord Sparky
The prisoner ran away. Go and chase him!
stop! Flame Fist
ah…
I made me sweat so much and let me stop!
Hurricane Blade
Look!
not good! The Sparky  has fallen into the quicksand pit!
Go back soon!
Let your dirty hands open!
ah! Don’t let go...
Magic Cloud
Catched
Catch them
Don’t come
Catch them quickly
yes
Stop and stop…
Almost hit me
Can you take a look at it?
yes
Not for you to aim at me...
Run away, everyone
Don’t chase after
What you’re after
I will be rude to your Sparky
Go quickly!
What a shame! What are you doing
Let me down quickly
How can you let me expose myself under the sun
Give me sun cream and sunscreen
It seems you need food more
I won’t eat
Flame Fist
I’m definitely not tired and tired
Not surprisingly powerful
Eat it
I don’t eat it, don’t stuff it to me again...
Said not to eat...
I don’t eat... I don’t really eat... I really...