There is a divine light there
You can ask a…
Where are the other trains in Quicksand Town?
Markets in East have
Very good
Then let’s go tight
I won’t let you succeed
Flame Fist
Hurricane Blade
Cough cough cough…
Sparky , don’t be slouch
Forget it, they are not easy to deal with if they have too many people
And fighting will make you sweat
I’ll catch you when I see the soldiers
My soldiers have already taken this place seriously
You’re waiting to be arrested
Come
Ummmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm
Hurricane Blade
snort!
Take a break, your feet are almost worn out
- We don’t even say anything
The sun is so sunny
No precautions were taken
How to go
Why don’t we find a place to hide in the sun first
This is really bad for skin
Children’s sunshine sunshine is a replenishment
And in the past you used to be a slim coppery skin
But the most proud
Nonsense
Just take it clean and eat it
The previous Sparky  would not care about these details
How is this possible…
Sparky , please help me
If you don’t have a tent, you’ll sleep in the sand tonight
My hand is broken
Where do you look? Where do you look?
What’s the matter with this little injury
In the past, Sparky  could be treated coldly when injured.
Very strong!
Still hurts…
The opportunity to escape is here
Oh no, I forgot which direction
Great, it’s a divine light
Tell me where is my soldier
In the northwest
Where is the northwest
I only answer one question
There
Sparky where do you want to go again…
I’ll leave first
ah…
Look at you and see…
It’s all you hurt
It makes me unable to eat or sleep well
All are allergic
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Very dirty
snort! It’s all your fault!
If you run away, run away
What are you doing with me, the villain
So dirty…
It’s okay. Commonly used mud mask for red strengths
You’re also confused
Maybe you can beautify and nourish
OK Then I’ll make you a mask
I remember we used to play Mudba like this
I have an impression, too
How is it possible?
How could I have played this with you
A dirty game
Just play
How great is it that I love being clean and refined now
Why do you have to turn me into this
No
We just want to get back the one we used to
The brave and righteous Sparky
It feels like going back to the past now
yes
Sparky  Ah?
You can play with mud by yourself
Go find some water to wash first. It’s too dirty
stop!
Hand over your water
What’s so a little bit?
Recently, the soldiers are looking for Master Sparky
No one sent water
I searched for three days and three nights before I got this
I want it all
ah…
Sparky stop!
So tired…
But why does it feel light and fast
It seems like I have never been here
Stop me!
Very good My people are here
you! Go and fetch me a basin of water!
you! Go and catch me the goat and wolf behind me!
Who is this person? Dirty
Don’t recognize
Go and go…whether one comes from
Flame Fist
It turns out that it is Boiling… Boiling… Lord Sparky
Lord Sparky, we didn’t mean it
not good
There are so many people in them. Run!
Fortunately, I’m able to get it
Xiaomu Why are you here
This is my hometown
To you, your hometown is in the next village
There are many soldiers outside
You should put this on
Disguise yourself as a soldier and find a chance to escape
good
stop
It’s time to change shifts
I’m not sure if I’m going to Lord Sparky’s residence to pay
This is a residential area
Mobile phones will be injured and innocent
Let’s go with the team first
When did you not see it?
Very good I’m becoming glorious again
ah…
How could this be…
What to do…
Don’t worry, it’s okay
Commonly used mud mask for red strength
You’ll be confused, too
Maybe you can beautify and nourish
It’s hard to tell…
What happened to Lord Sparky?
I’m afraid of sweating
How could this be possible
Hearing the Soldiers
What kind of mud pool is Mr. Sparky going to find?
What to do when looking for a quagmire
Who are they?