They’re still hunting us down
Ah, it seems that staying here is safer
Well, let’s hide here first
good
Let it open
Ah…refreshing
Oh, the allergy has improved
Mud is really useful
marvelous
Uh, right
Those backs…
Who are they
Sparky  Sparky
Who
It’s us, come and play
Hahaha…
Uh you…
Wait who are you
Here is…
Ha ha ha ha…
Ah, tell me
Who are you
Ah… it hurts… it hurts…
pain…
Who are they
Forget it, I have to go and get the crystal stone with Queen Levana first
Queen Levana Where is mine?
Sparky
How long has it been since the lamb and the bright moon arrived in your quicksand town
Why didn’t I catch them yet
Sparky  Have you betrayed the Queen?
Nonsense!
Those little lambs made me run for a day
I am not at the same time as them!
OK, let’s trust you
oh…
Thank you Queen
But I can’t catch anyone anymore
I will punish you…
I promise to catch them within a week
You listen to me
They must be caught within a week
yes
It’s so hot I’m going back to the house
You two help me take a shower
- yes
This back…why is it so much like a dream
Wait a minute.
You turn your face over and see it
Is there anything wrong with Sparky ?
It’s OK
You go, go, go, go
Not familiar with it at all
This back…
Hello, you’ve turned over
Is there anything wrong with Sparky ?
Huh? Not familiar
Let’s go
what? Not found?
It’s the seventh day, what are you doing!
Don’t continue to search!
I’m so angry!
you! Take grapes and bring down the fire to me
yes
Um? I said these on your face are…
Back to adults, it’s a natural mole
Not the grape seeds on your face
Uh your mole…
Born
ah!
You are here!
Run quickly
Don’t want to run away!
Sparky  If you run away, you will be sweating all over
What if he doesn’t
This time, no matter what, I will catch you
Their backs…
It looks like my dream
No No no
Stop me
Catch you
ah…
oops
Paddi…
Help, Sparky …
I’m here
Sparky , you’re fine
Hahaha…I have nothing to do. It’s fine
These memories
How could it be in my brain?
- Well
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Below is…
No, here is the cactus forest
Magic Cloud
The Goat Sparky
You…you saved me?
You’re fine…
It’s fine if you’re fine
Well? We’re enemies
Why do you want to save me
What are you saying, don’t you save me often?
I’m here!
Why are these pictures again
We’ve done a lot of things
Playing and laughing, and fighting the wolf tribe together
Laughing together?
Yes, because we are still good friends
good friend…
These pictures…the back of my dream…
It’s all clearer
Let’s play together and laugh together
Take the wolf group together
We want to be a good friend
I…remember it
We want to be friends
Sparky , you’ve remembered it
Ah, Sparky …
You’re fine
It’s OK
I think of everyone
Sparky …
Really, do you think of us?
Yes, I remembered it
You won’t forget to dream
Sparky …
Welcome back Sparky
OK OK Don’t cry
Well…
Sparky!
This is…
Not good, Sparky’s hand ring has been developed
It’s true
Your hand ring has been developed
Mr. Slowy
The Queen has known that you have betrayed her
but
She is willing to give you another chance
As long as you catch them, crystal is yours
Sparky, please respond to him quickly
Get the crystal first and then talk
No! No matter how much I feel, I will not betray my friends!
Sparky …
Since that’s the case, I’ll start
Miscellaneous
Hurricane Blade
Thunderbolt
Magic Cloud
Beware that Wolffy
Um
ah…
The Goat and the Big Wolf…
Also have the heart to care about others
Vague lens
ah
Tibbie
- Sparky
No… hurt them again…
Sparky , you’re fine
Sparky  Your hand…
My hands…
Ah, it turns out that all it bit off was the hand
Just call you nothing
Hehehehehe…
That’s how it is
So that’s how it is
I’m really sorry for letting everyone suffer
and
Water in the reservoir
You can come and get it anytime in the future
Very good
This is…a hand ring?
ah! The scoundrel actually bit the queen’s hand…
Please, please
It is necessary to let Princess Luna return to normal as soon as possible
Don’t worry, we’ll do it
What are you doing
These are of course…
Water
After this time I realized that it wouldn’t work without water
From now on, I can’t leave you for a moment
But the next town is the Aqua Spirit Town
It’s water everywhere
what? Well…
Didn’t you say it earlier…
Hahaha…
We’re leaving
goodbye
Great, we can have fun again
Ha ha ha ha…
Thunderbolt
Magic Cloud
Can’t drag everyone down any more
I must control the thunderbolt
Say, do you want to betray me?
I will never betray the Queen
We will never betray you
We’ll definitely catch them
If the Queen doesn’t believe it
Can I add a few more hands to me
The same goes for me
snort!
- Queen
You want to betray me, no more hand rings will work
and
I hope you can say what you just said so much
The Queen trusts us so much
I swear to be loyal to her forever