The Aqua Spirit town is here
There is only one lake
Strange Where is the Aqua Spirit Town
Everyone should be careful
Wow
This lake is so clear
The air is fresh
But is this the Aqua Spirit Town?
I haven’t come before
- Me too
ah?
Is this… Princess Luna’s?
It’s hard to tell that Princess Luna and the others have not arrived at the palace
But come here too?
Beware that there is something in the water
This is…
I’ll hold him
Welcome Welcome
Lord Jonie has been waiting for you for a long time
The Shuiling Town is just below the bottom of the lake!
Please come with me
What’s going on
I feel sorry
Then do we have to follow us?
Princess Luna may be in their hands
I can only go with them
OK, we’re out
Don’t cats fear water?
Although I am afraid of water, it is protected by an aerobic shield
Did you see that it is the Aqua Spirit Town
We’re here
What a special Aqua Spirit town
You see
It seems this product
It may not be that Princess Luna fell out
Princess Luna and the others
Maybe I’ll be waiting for us in the palace long ago
They’re not here
Should we leave?
What should I do with the Jonie?
Jonie
Thank you, Lord Jonie
Hello
I just thought you were going to attack us
It’s fine if you’re fine
Isn’t the Jonie blackened?
You might think it’s strange if you say it
Don’t know why
It feels very sensible when you see you
Jonie…
I saw you before
I felt very familiar and slowly recovered my memory
Maybe we can wake up the Jonie
Be careful
Jonie
Tell you about us
OK, go to where I live
Wow I haven’t seen such a rich meal in a long time
Can we really eat it?
Of course
No need for guest
Can be added if not
I can’t help it anymore
This Jonie is black
Beware of problems with food
Any questions?
The most painful thing in the world
That’s how many delicious food is in front of me
I can’t eat it
What’s wrong with you? Isn’t it unpleasant?
It seems that there should be no problem
You’re eating too
If you don’t eat it, you won’t be able to eat it
Leave me some…
Chief, do you still remember
Once we went to the mountain to pick apples together
So interesting
Sparky said he could handle it alone
But I can’t pick any apples
Finally, the class leader
Pick the apples to us
It sounds like we were so happy before
I could really pick it up alone that time
Hahahahahahaha…
What’s her harp?
And we used to sing together
You’re so happy to sing
Your favorite song is…
Chief, you’re here
Thank you
Huh? Did your hand slip?
Class leader?
No, class manager
No…
Hello, wake up
You wake up quickly
What is actually a
Big Wolf, you do
You wake up quickly
The Jonie is missing
Are we asleep?
She must have wanted to sleep while we were asleep
What to do to us
Are you awake? That’s just right
Look, what I said is right
I’ve prepared breakfast, let’s have it together
Wow
Eat slowly, there are many more
This is a good thing
Ha ha…
Jonie, let’s go with us
Hot Goat
You plan to help residents with fishing yards today
Sorry, I have no way to accompany you
You can go for a walk first
It’s so good here
Want to stay here forever
Then let’s go out and have a look
Huh?
What are they doing
Maybe it’s fitness
No
You are my friends of Lord Jonie
Um
Because the oxygen at the bottom of the sea is not small
So everyone must take the air in the wheel to provide oxygen
Why do you live under the sea?
It’s like this
Because our water town encountered a big flood
Fortunately, Lord Jonie appeared
Protect the entire water town and move it to the bottom of the water
Keep us safe from natural disasters
The class leader is still so good
I won’t say it, I’ll hand over the shift
Anyway, I have to wait
Or let’s fish
This fishing tool is quite special
Are you going to get on the hook so soon?
- So am I
Me too
It’s a fishbaby
Apple
It’s a torn shoe
Broken Axe…
What about you, Yangyang
The Goat, wake up and get on the hook
We’re here to help
You see
It seems to be a big fish
Shark
Let go
Wow…
- Paddi
- Blade Blade
You’re fine
It’s OK
Wait, it’s not finished yet
This is bad
How did the oxygen mask break
Wow, what’s going on
Water…
The water is coming in…
I’m most afraid of water…
Magic Cloud
I’ll plug the gap
You will take the residents to a safe place first
good
Everyone, get up there
Residents were evacuated to high places
good
Feed the goat
You’re here soon, too
OK Come now
Paddi…
Wow…
What to do? The Paddi were wiped away
You have to block the hole first
It’s all your fault
You’re wearing the oxygen shield
Sorry, we’ll find a way
Want a way? What else can I do if I do this
Alas, my home
My flowers…
My doll…
Nothing left…
The water faded
The adults have already controlled the flood
Brothers, come on
OK, nothing is wrong
Great, fortunately, there is a man named Hunyang
I’m really sorry that my friend didn’t mean it
Please advise them
Since it’s Lord Jonie, please plead
Then forget it
Let’s go
Fortunately, you took action
I’m so sorry I doubted you before
It’s okay
Oh no, look for the goat
Ah, then
Feed Weslie
Paddi
and…
Princess Luna Fulai
What’s going on
When I was just blown away by water
Magic Cloud
Not much help either
A goat?
Huh? How are you here?
She asked someone to close us up
Are we not good friends?
Why do this
Because I am a good friend
I don’t want you to leave
Queen Levana doesn’t want you to leave