What a joke you’re making
You’ve been chasing us from the beginning
You said it was
Jonie, don’t we say we can leave together?
No no no no here is pretty good
Is it also fake to save us?
But Jonie said we were very kind
Not like cheating on us
- Quite?
- You’re too naive
- Lord Jonie has always been rebelling
- A series of words
I won’t play with you anymore I’m going to replenish it
Everyone, please note that Lord Jonie is going to sleep
Start closure of streets
Lord Jonie is going to sleep
Let’s go first
I have something to say
Get off here quickly
Don’t slap the Jonie to sleep
I won’t leave
Get off here quickly
snort! We want to leave ourselves
No matter the Jonie
You’re so weird
What do you want to leave here?
Please ask if there is any solution?
no
Do you know how dangerous it is outside?
There are groups of sharks patrolling the shore
Someone who will spray poison to make the secret of the treasure
There are also overbearing swords
They’re very violent
Look, Lord Jonie also said
There are huge monsters on it
and the volcano that has been spraying
Then the land was divided
The sea water flooded the earth without flooding
Survival environment is bad
Such a danger, are you going up and doing
Before, the flood in our town
If it weren’t for the Lord Jonie
We’re all homeless
You’re all cheated
We came in from outside
Nothing outside
- Sure enough
The soldier said it was right
They say you will definitely find various reasons
The Jonie
We won’t be
It seems that everyone here has been cheated firmly
There is no way to do it
We still want to leave here first
Look there
Bubble
I use a silly mirror
Let the soldiers deliver the bubble tool
Wait a minute they have too many people
We’ll lead one
This I will
Cats like to chase light the most
Watch it
Why? Why didn’t you react
- Because we have all been trained professionally
Vague lens
Catch them!
Let’s go quickly
Hum, they ran away
Always got rid of it
But what should I do next
If we could be like them
Just go for a tour
swim?
Yes, we can swim directly
Swim directly up?
That’s right, I’m a swimmer
There is absolutely no problem when you get ashore
Look at mine
Swimming Master Wake Up
Saved
It’s too far away from the water here
You can’t swim without enough oxygen
Leave it to me
Magic Cloud
If there is danger, you can just rush it
We’ll pull you in
Maybe we should go alone
Help!
- It’s a fish!
well? Miss
It should be wandering
Don’t try it anymore. It’s so dangerous
But we can’t stay here all the time
I’ll try again
This time it will definitely be successful
You’re waiting for my good news
The book was last…
I fell asleep before I even started
Is it boring for me to tell the story?
ah…
Something surprised the monster
Door…door…
Ah… It’s the poisonous seal fish…
- Run quickly
What happened
ah! The oxygen cover is shrinking!
Help…
You’ve come here
Is this the good news you said?
Not this kind of thing
What happened
Has it been damaged?
The oxygen hood seems to be retracting
Hello, come and help
The poison-drafted fish came in
Everyone in the work area is upset
octopus?
It’s hard to tell… it was at that time…
There is no time, everyone is divided into two groups
You go and get oxygen
I’ll find the poisonous seal
I’ll go with you
It’s so tiring to hear
Let’s go out
Look at mine
I’ll come too
It should be around here
That
Come out Poisonous seal fish
Sorry, I’ve been slapped
Very tired
I can’t find it for so long
You won’t be following us secretly
ah…
Zhang Yu is here, Weslie…
Help…
Open goat
Poisonous seal fish
Go back to your original place
Where is it
Weslie
- Success
Always recovered
Very good
But how did Zhangyu come in
It’s them
I saw that they brought Zhang Yu in.
we?
that is!
They also damaged the oxygen hood yesterday
It’s also them who are the ones who are warm and warm.
Yes yes yes…
It’s definitely no good if they are there
Everyone leaves them far away
arrive
What’s going on
Report to Lord Jonie
All the things you arranged are done
Everything is as you wish
Very good, the villagers won’t believe them