Gun Gun...
Have tried all the methods
How do we get ashore
Ask the residents here
Maybe there is any trace
Hello, please...
snort!
Ask something, you still have to rely on cute things
I’m here
Hello, please ask how to get ashore
snort!
Everyone talked about us
It seems that asking passersby won’t work
Wow! There is a person who is very terrible in swimming!
Is swimming very harmful?
He is drowning, save him!
You woke up?
It’s you... it’s you...
Did you save me?
It’s fine you’re fine
Thank you
Uncle, you’re drowning, you’re going out
Must go out
I want to find my jade pendant quickly
- Jade pendant?
A few days ago...
I’m going to sea to catch fish
Unexpectedly dropped the jade pendant from home into the sea
I keep looking for...
What’s the use of these to tell you
You let me open it
No one wants to talk to us
I can’t help it
I’m going to find the Hot Goat
Let her tell us how to go up
Will the Hot Goat tell us?
Let’s go and have a look
Um
Why are there no fish in this dish?
Report The fish cook is on holiday
It’s so dirty here
Sorry, the swatman is on vacation
Where is my doorway?
They just took a vacation
Is anyone else?
Report!
Adults, Weslie and her team come in and want to see you
Let the soldiers at the door hold them
Don’t let them come in
Adults, it’s time to take a vacation
No leave is allowed in the future
Jonie, let’s compete
competition?
Another competition?
Why do I want to compete with you
If we win
You’re going to tell us how to go up
If we get it, please make a request
And why
Come and see off guests
You just serve me when you pass.
OK Deal
The competition is ready to begin
From the left is...Guangyangyang
Ah… Lord Jonie…
On the right is Princess Luna Team
OK The competition begins
No review committee
The audience on the field is the review committee for this competition
All of them are you saying what to do
Uh-huh
OK Who will win first
The competition begins
Ah...so sudden
Can’t blink...
I’m about to blink
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
My eyes are so dry, I want to endure, I want to endure...
Lord Jonie won
Who blinked?
I blinked, sorry
Fulai...blink?
Compare again. If we pass us, we will serve you for five more days
OK
But the next game must be the strength
OK But I’m tired today
Let’s compete again the day after tomorrow
good
Hot Goat is delicious
One person is against so many people
Yes, right... that’s it...
Everyone is calm
Since I have agreed to their competition
I won’t regret it
Even if I’m the only one
Lord Jonie is really a daughter
Lightning Strike...
oops!
well! Practice for so long
Still can’t control the Lightning Strike
The uncle is looking for his jade pendant again
I have to work hard, too
Hoo...
This time is a swimming competition
The first one to arrive on the other side is considered a win
Come on, come on…
Hiccup uh uh uh…
Lord Jonie is so calm
snort! No idea
Let you see my evil
Everyone takes their place
Prepare…
Start
You can’t do sports competitions
Going to win
Aqua Spirit
The winner of this competition is the Lord Jonie
Jonie cheated. She used Qili
The competition rules are not said to be able to use strange power
That’s it...
It’s too late...
That’s not counting, let’s add another day
OK
Sparky ...
Fish competition begins
Haha I’m here
Me too
hey-hey…
Aqua Spirit
I’ve finished it
Lord Jonie won the victory
All this is OK...
Add another day to six wins in eleven games…
Water ballet competition
Sleeping on the water
Water football competition
All of them are the winners of the Hot Goat
I’m not convinced, come another game
Stop it, we haven’t won
No, the Jonie keeps winning
Very dissatisfied...
You’ve been playing tricks
Lord Jonie, please don’t care about them
Since you are so persistent
Let’s compare again
Lord Jonie is actually a great person
snort!
Who gets the prize card on the croaker
Who wins
… shark fish…
Weslie I wish you good luck
Please take your place
The competition... begins
Aqua Spirit
Use Magic power again
Sparky  is tightly caught
Really awesome
- Weslie...
Come on, Weslie...
- Come on, Lord Jonie...
It’s over Jonie is going to get the prize card
Sparky
Huh?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
- Sparky ’s Pill
How could I possibly get it!
The fish wakes up...
Sparky  Run
That’s my ancestral jade pendant
Uncle...
Uncle
Prize cards…
laugh…
Lord Jonie finally got the prize card
Adults shake hands with me
Can you sign me a name?
You...
Wow…
It’s OK…
Finally found you
Although it’s gone, the end is not bad
sorry
If it weren’t for me, you wouldn’t have been to it
Sorry
It’s best if you’re fine
It was impossible for us to win
yes…
Thank you for what you need me to do for you
I’ll definitely do it
- Then please tell us
- How to get out of the Aqua Spirit town
Maybe the floating beads can take you out
Floating beads?
When the first man, the Jonie
It was used to send everyone down with floating beads
Maybe you want to use this one
But I don’t know where the floating beads are
You’ve still lost
Then just follow the agreement and serve me
I don’t agree, we continue to compete
Don’t say it!