Lord Jonie told you to organize this
Very clean
The Jonie is so good to us
You have to sort out all these
Alas, please go to the casino
It’s just not difficult to clean up these
In addition to these
You also need to wash dishes and make meals
Shredding floor, washroom and flower
Change water to fish tank, wash clothes, bed single…
Ahem…you can get these done first
Others will be told to you later
Who proposed the competition!
you
Who answered the competition conditions?
Sorry, I wouldn’t make this appointment if I had known it
It’s okay. You’re also anxious for everyone
sorry
I’ll help you
You said that in the past, the Jonie always helped us
Now we help her in front of her
Is it possible that she remembers us?
Anyway, you have to have sex, so why not try it
What do you want me to see
You see, Jonie
You helped me wash the quilt before
Now I’ll help you
Sorry, I forgot to wash my feet first
Jonie
Do you remember the scene of our sanitation in the past?
Hey! Huh!
Every time I practice like this…
Ah I’m sorry
By the way, I have
Jonie I’ll give you a baked fish and dried
You used to cook it for us
It’s a bit boring
You guys are going to sleep
This method doesn’t work
Or we take this opportunity to look for the floating beads
Floating beads?
When the first man, the Jonie
It’s just to send everyone down with floating beads
Yes, you can take us up if you find it
Um
Not found
That’s all there left
What are you doing
We went in and swept the room of Jonie
No, Lord Jonie is sleeping
Just keep slapping outside
But we’ve finished slapping outside
Is this called sweeping clean?
The hall is guaranteed to be clean
No hair
If you don’t believe it, go and see
I don’t believe it
If you can find a hair, I will give you a bench
- Yes, I can find a hair
- We will also give you a seat on a stool.
Go and go
Don’t let go of any corner
good
Why are they all the same bags?
Here too…
How much does Jonie like bags?
Have found it!
Any discoveries?
I found the snacks hidden under the bed by Jonie.
I searched the entire room
Still no
Haven’t found a place yet…
It’s hard to tell…
Golden Bag…
Retreat first
Don’t quit
I…I just came in and swiped
Then I saw that your quilt fell off…
What to do!
You dare to quarrel with Lord Jonie to sleep
You’re very noisy now, too
Are you not afraid of waking up the Jonie?
You have to care!
Anyway, Lord Jonie is very upset
Don’t want to see you
You go to the kitchen to have sex
I’ve found all the room of Jonie
There is nothing wrong with it
That’s right, is it hard to do with her?
It’s really harder to get what’s on her
I think of another place
Where?
I think it should be…
Jonie’s baby
what…
It’s very likely
You are so smart
But the Jonie is so easy to wake up
How do we get it
Then we will wait until Jonie is not in the room
Go in and get it
Who would have gone better
And he doesn’t show up in front of Jonie
It will not cause suspicion
Yes, who?
whee…
This big brother, dinner is ready
May I feel sorry, please come out for a meal
We’ve prepared for you too
Delicious little fish cubes
Where have you gone?
The boy woke up the adults and went to bed
I’ve already put him in the kitchen to wash dishes
Oh, that’s it
Jonie This is the seaweed cake I made
Jonie
Look, this is my re-baked fish baking
Was it very successful?
Jonie eat this
Eat this Eat this… Jonie
- Jonie Eat this…
And this…
Very cool
Sweet?
Press and press and stop silence
I was just clamored by you so much that I couldn’t sleep well
I’m going to replenish
That’s this…
Don’t leave, eat some more
There are also many delicious…
Something must be here
What to do? The goat is still inside
Do we want to go in and save the goat?
Now going in will expose your purpose
We must believe in the goat
Why is Jonie coming back so soon?
Where have you gone
It’s over… I won’t be discovered
Found
Good
That’s great. I didn’t expect Nuanyang to cooperate like this
Did Jonie treat me as her doll?
The goat in the goat has been there for so long
Will something happen?
Paddi
Too shocked
You are so awesome
Nothing
Check out if there are any floating beads inside
I’ll have to put it back soon
Can’t let the Jonie discover
right
This…this is…
I slept so hard last night
Jonie You’re awake
Come and have breakfast, all of them are ready for you
Yes, I feel very self-righteous
ah? Empty?
well…
Where did she hide the floating beads?