I washed 108 pieces of clothes in these days
I’m more hard
I washed 173 plates
I’ve swept 173 plates
Shredding? Why?
Because the slags break the plate every time
I didn’t mean it
actually
In the past, the class manager took care of us this way every day.
It turns out that she is so hard
Um
How long do we have to stay here?
I really want red and little Huihui
I want to silence the sun
I really want to go back to the green grassland…
You reminded me of the days I used to fight
Although it’s very hard
But I am very happy every day
Right
I used to catch a fish as big as mine
Really? Very terrible
I’ll catch that bigger
There are three fish that are as big as me
Wow…
I also posted the paper at that time
look
My ancient coppery skin was what I got at that time
At that time
People still thought you were a resident of Quicksand Town
What do you know
That’s the standard for bodybuilders
Yes, I understand
I also want to have an ancient coppery skin
But now there is no way
It was pretty good before
well…
Why do I talk to you so much
I’m not familiar with you
Break the oxygen hood
Is it still not enough to release poison-drafting fish?
It’s going to destroy our plants
No, no, I didn’t…
The goat is so weak
How could you blow down a tree?
And how could a tree fall down after sneezing?
Where am I weak? Why is it impossible?
Wait for a moment where do you see
There are also problems with these trees
How did this happen
The Aqua Spirit town sinks under the sea
Lack of light
If this continues, it’s not just plants
Even people can’t stand it
Speaking of which, I haven’t felt very comfortable lately…
This will not work
We must go up there
I don’t believe you
I’m going to ask her Lord Jonie
Nothing is going to be done, just replenish
What a big guy to visit. It’s so precious
Lord Jonie, you are so good
As for other questions you just said
It’s easy to solve, too
This is not a solution to the problem at all
To solve the problem, you must go up
Not good, not good
A water disaster occurred above
The entire land was buried
My bubble was also broken and almost couldn’t come back
It’s too dangerous
Fortunately we are here
he…
Go back
Um
Let’s go back, too
That soldier just had a problem
I’ll go and see
Wait for me, I’ll go too
Princess Luna, you stay here to take care of the villagers
We’ll be back soon
Fortunately, they didn’t find it
I didn’t expect that everything was fake…
Has Lord Jonie been cheating on us?
I want to ask her clearly
Uncle Cat
I’ll protect him. You go and notify the villagers.
Wait a moment
You go first I will go back and get along with you
Hot Goat
The villagers’ sentiment has calmed down
Um
Uncle Cat, etc.
Can’t mess with the palace
You go
Wait a minute.
It’s okay, let them come in
What’s going on?
Lord Jonie, have you cheated us?
The soldier’s injuries were fake
I don’t understand what you’re talking about
You don’t need to install it anymore
We’ve found these props
Alas, Forrest Gump can’t do such a small thing well
Isn’t it true that nothing happened?
We’re going to the villagers now
Expose your true face
Uncle Cat, let’s go
Is it that easy?
careful…
You only keep it for a while if you eat these
Not very useful
How is it possible…
What’s going on
What happened to them?
Their situation is worse
We have found the certificate of the licensing of the Jonie
What’s going on
Princess Luna…
Princess Luna has limited abilities
Can’t help so many people
We obviously ate it, why did we still do this?
These are all cures but not root causes
Everyone has to go up and go to the sun
Only then can you get better
Go up?
But the above is so dangerous
It’s all the Jonie who cheats you
We have found the certificate
Certificate?
Let’s go find the Hot Goat with us
OK, we just trust you once
Everyone will know your true face soon
You won’t know if you close it
stop
Let them go
Wolffy…
Jonie, what do you want to do
What do you want to do to them
Lord Jonie, please tell me
It was their first move…
We found the certificate
She wants to grab us
Don’t believe her
Those are the props she made soldiers feel sick
But aren’t these things available for purchase?
yes
You can’t just stop like this
Lord Jonie cheated us
This…
What should I do? What other evidence do we have?
The certificate is here
Isn’t that the soldier this morning?
He’s the proof
Scar…is fake
Don’t tear it, your hair is real
So the above disasters are all fake
Lord Jonie, is there really nothing above?
Lord Jonie…
If you don’t go up, everyone will get sick
Lord Jonie, please take us up quickly
Lord Jonie begs you…
Jonie…
She is no longer the kind Jonie goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat goat she used to be
What’s the use of her?
No more installed
Alas, catch them in a row
yes!
Ah… Magic Cloud…
You’re always stuck here