We believe in you so much
Why do you want to cheat us
Let us go up
I knew you would be so ill
That’s why I’ve got you stuck here
Hear the Queen will send someone to deal with us tomorrow
snort! I’m not afraid!
You’re fine, right?
I’m fine
That’s good
To put it, you are really simple!
It turns out that you really want to trap us here
We will never surrender.
That’s right
oops…
Didn’t you say you would never surrender?
No
Their bodies are weak
If this continues, everyone will become more and more serious
It must be tightened to let the Aqua Spirit town rise up
Jonie, let everyone go up
I’m going to sleep, grab them
Now many villagers are sick
Have to take them away first
good
You go quickly!
Magic Cloud
Everyone, go quickly
What to do?
Do we really can’t get up in the future?
I don’t want to stay here all the time
Since that’s the case...
Let’s cooperate
There
I misunderstood you before
Too sorry
Too sorry...
No need to apologize No need to apologize
It was true that we were not good before. We were tired.
Let’s think of a way to go up together
But where will that bead be?
Are you talking about floating beads?
Yes, we heard the cat uncle say
It’s the floating beads that make the whole town come down
So I believe that if you find it, you can go up there
Then do you still remember what the floating beads are?
At that time...
The light was too bright at that time, we couldn’t see clearly
Yes, it’s too bright
But...
Since it is called floating beads, it must be round beads
Let’s move separately
Find the floating beads
Um
good
Uncle, the food in the trash can is not eaten
Eat my scent
This may be a floating bead
I searched all over the town, but nothing
There is no area outside, either
Where is it hidden
Only the Jonie knows the answer
You want to...
Um
Do you want to eat?
I’m tired, I want to eat too
Wait for me
The Jonie will come out at any time
Wait for the Jonie to come out
We just came forward with Tibbie
Give her a chance to use the illusion lens
good
That’s now!
Tips for carving and sucking!
Humph...
Hurricane Blade
Can’t be troublesome
Ink fish flying preparation
What’s it?
Launch
Tibbie, what happened to you?
I’m fine, I can hold on
That’s now, the counterattack
What is this time?
Flashing
Ah, so dazzling
Tibbie
My eyes hurt so much
Tibbie...
No, it seems we should retreat first
Tibbie, what’s wrong with your eyes
Let me come
I’ve learned eye exercises
Much better
I didn’t expect that Jonie was ready
The plan below failed
This may not be
report!
He found us
Lord Jonie, do you have anything to do with me?
What did he just say?
…
Actually, we have succeeded
Actually, Tibbie and I discussed it secretly
Flashing
Turn the target into a soldier
Smart!
Soldier
Do you still remember where my floating beads are placed?
Hot Goat
Haven’t you kept hiding the floating beads in the room?
I know, of course I know
Do you know where I put it?
Don’t know
What happened to Lord Jonie?
Uh hahahahaha...
I’m just testing your memory
It seems good, you go down
yes
The room of the Jonie Goat?
But we looked for it last time, no
Something must have been missing
It seems I can only go back and search again
Um
What are you doing?
This may be the floating bead
But which one is there?
Take it all
What are you doing
No, Jonie woke up...
Quick move...
Get the floating beads
Aqua Spirit
Magic Cloud
Hand over the floating beads
Hurricane Blade
Flame Fist
Aqua Spirit
Success
Hahaha... See you again
What’s going on?
Oops! We’ve guessed wrong
The floating bead is its nose
snort!
And me
Get it, everyone, go
Don’t think about it!
Ha ha ha ha…
They... were eaten!