Paddi Jonie
Keep up with that fish
Little lamb, our Jonie
I’ll catch it
This fish is too big
Everyone
We’ll chase
Is Lord Jonie really in the belly of that fish?
It’s not good to cheat you
The head of the class and the slept with the goat are our partners
Well, let’s cooperate first
Where are you
It’s so dark here. You’ll say a word to me
Jonie
Ah monster, let me go, help
Monster Don’t touch the Jonie
I’m not afraid of you
I’ll save you
What? It turns out to be a sea
I used to be the head of the class and you took care of me
Let me take care of you this time
Here is
Swimming so fast
We’ll live there
good
Stop quickly
Our partners are in your belly
Stop now
ah
Can’t delay
If this continues, the goat and Jonie will be very dangerous
Let’s use the power to cut it off
good
Vague lens
ah
The whale is too huge and can’t be controlled
Stop me!
There is water here and there is no fire
Hurricane Blade
Weslie
I’ve practiced so many times before
Thunderbolt
Don’t rush, Big Grey
Falled!
He actually got it!
Ahhh, Kung Fu is not a must
Finally got it
- It has swam here
Thunderbolt
Why didn’t you hit again
You haven’t practiced well at all
Run quickly
Look, there is a cave there
Finally stopped
Where is this?
Hahaha Jonie
It’s you! Aqua Spirit
Aqua Spirit
Aqua Spirit Aqua Spirit
Don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’t come, don’
What’s going on
Hahaha
Today I brought the wind and let’s play together
Very good
- Who is this?
goodbye
Who are you
I’m you
What are you talking about? I’m not you
Come with me and show you something
See
I’m a cat, you’re a goat
We’re not the same
You’ll take a closer look
What’s going on?
Where is the person?
Jonie
We are friends
friend
Let me go, I’m not your friend!
I am I
I’m you
no
We are a friend of mine
Not me
I’m not your Jonie
Then who am I?
Let me open his mouth
The cave is about to collapse
This will hurt him
Rescue the fish first
danger!
Why did it suddenly come in so much water?
Go away quickly
Ah, the Jonie
I will definitely not let you have any trouble
Are you protecting me? Why?
Paddi
Jonie
Aqua Spirit
I’ll save you
Jonie, you finally remembered that I was here
I’m sorry for you about the past
Let’s leave here first
good
It’s going to swim up
Look at them on it
Very good they’re fine
Tibbie
Come and see, the class leader is recovering
Jonie, have you recovered?
Do you remember us?
Remember, remember
Sorry, I was doing this to you before
I’m actually
Nuanyang Goat You finally come back
I’m back
I want to remedy the mistakes I made before
Let’s save the Shuiling Town now
good
Great, you’re fine
More than that, our Jonie is back
Hello Princess Luna, Fulai
You can recover, it’s so great.
Save everyone first
Um
The sun is the sun
Finally floated
Solar Sun Solar Solar Solar Solar Solar Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound Sound
Sorry, I’ve made everyone suffer before
We accept your apology
What you did before was not your intention
Yes, stop Queen Levana as soon as possible
Let the Catland recover
Thank you
goodbye
See you again See you again
Go to the palace