Queen Those lambs are so unreliable
One actually betrays you
That’s true
You had a good relationship before
I’m different from them
I will never betray the Queen
oh?
Trust me I’ve already started training elite soldiers
And I prepared it for them
But the most terrible trap
It’s best if they come quickly
It doesn’t look like a palace here
Here is the final stop
Trains will only park in the Soldiers’ Village
Next we have to hike up to the palace
Soldiers Village?
Yes, a place to train soldiers from the cats
Then let’s go
Wait a minute There are traps nearby
We need to be careful
Very good I will have you again in the future
Come and protect me, this weak boy
Let’s go
Be careful not to attract the attention of soldiers
Otherwise it will be irritating
I’m not afraid
The trap just now has consumed a lot of energy
It’s better to be careful
Too
A soldier has come
Not safe here
Let’s find a safe place to talk about it
They’re leaving
It looks like a house here
You see, there are soldiers here
We can mix in as soldiers as before
But there are only three soldier equipment here.
Then let Fulai and I go out to explore the way
You’re waiting for us here
stop!
Have I caught it
The military officer asked you to gather and you didn’t go
Hiding here and stealing
Come out!
Don’t think I don’t know there is someone else in it
I’ll go
Be careful
Come out and gather soon
Sorry, I’m late
All came with me
Wolffy will not be in danger
Big Wolf is cunning and he will protect himself
Let’s look for any soldier equipment.
Um
Be careful not to be discovered
Mr. Slowy…
It’s just a photo
It seems that this is Mr. Slowy’s residence
I heard that someone was off the motor
Is Princess Luna and the others here?
Feel sorry
It was when I was just guarding
I accidentally touched the machine
You keep staring at me
If you have any feelings, you will come back
yes
All stood up
The military officer is going to talk to us now
Everyone has heard it
The enemy is right in front of you
So what do we do
Work hard to train…
Let’s slip away while we’re here
You have the best soldiers
I’ll promote him to my side
Be my assistant
Work hard to train…
Very good, you let me be confident
Oh!
Military officer, you’re fine, right?
My old waist…
Military officer, hold on, military officer
Hiding
Mr. Slowy…
My old waist…
I’ll give you a massage, sir
Ah…it hurts so much
Will you press it…
will not
Let’s go…
Pour me a glass of water
Tell you to leave, you really leave
Alas…
That’s it
snort! I know to come back
But the techniques have improved
I just want to give you these young people
Just a chance to recognize an error
It’s not that I can’t do it without you…
Go and make me a cup of tea
Go and cook for me
Give me a terrible
A little on the left A little on the top
Right Right
Get off now
Um
Where to go?
Start training soon
You go find your way
Um
Don’t be slow, come here quickly
Yes yes…
The first training: bend and stretch
It’s indeed a cat
Children should not learn this kind of thing
That’s of course
You go quickly
Save me and save me…
This test will test your balance
This is too dangerous
Go out and execute tasks Is there any choice in the environment?
Just to let you sleep anywhere
You just practice more
Wolffy
We found a small path in the back mountain
There were no soldiers there
real? Then we’ll leave tonight
Weslie and the others don’t know where to go
How to inform him
I’ll think about it
Have a rest. Come and gather
Prepare for the next round of training
Also…
The previous ones are just basic training
It’s hard behind it
These confuses
It is used to train your willpower
Want to be an elite soldier…
Failed Failed Failed…
Isn’t it just a wool ball? What’s so confusing?
You boy is a genius, what’s your name
My name is Hui…
Ah Hui
What a genius
Go clean up, I’ll take you to see the military
ah?
marvelous
You know me very well
Especially the massage method is really good
Military officer
I’ll check if the kitchen fire is off
I’ll help him shut up
Let’s collect clothes
Come in
No, is Wolffy caught?
Military officer I discovered a genius
ah?
That’s what’s called Ah Hui
It passed the project with the highest elimination rate in a moment
Willpower is so constrained that it makes people look hairy
Yes, I’ll walk over and let me take a closer look
This…good…
Then I’ll go out first