Yes, you’re Ah Hui
Yes...yes
How do you look a bit like Wolffy?
No!
what! Is this aware?
I…
But the public face of Wolffy
It’s not surprising that there are a few similarities
Thick eyebrows and small eyes
There are scars on the face
Belly like watermelon
A middle-aged man’s oily posture
But you don’t have to be too inferior
How many talented and beautiful like me are
Just have the ability
ah!
Um? What sound is that?
Ahhhhh…
Uh uh uh…
oops
What are you doing! It hurts so much!
There are cats outside
You’re hurt, don’t be upset
Meow…
What I’m hurting is your waist, are you twisting my head?
My whole body massage is very bad
All of them will be given to you
Not bad, it’s really comfortable
Of course I often help red press
Who is red?
Uh... It’s my frog...
Why are frogs called red?
Isn’t the red green green pretty good
Wolnie knows it, the gray wolf is despised
…
Good, it feels very comfortable
OK, I’ll give you a chance to upgrade
What opportunity
Go and find the soldier he will tell you
Let’s go
Alas, I’m almost asleep
Princess Luna is in the back mountain
Found the path to the palace
Wait until late tonight
When soldiers patrol the rules relax
We’ll get together there
good
Didn’t Slowy find out you
He still treats us as soldiers without him
Then we are going back to take care of the village chief now
Then you must be careful
Right...
What did she let me do?
Oh, look for the soldier
Training?
To the military officer, you have performed well
Give you an opportunity to improve
Then...how long will it take to go
Soon, just two days
Two days? How can I get along with everyone at night?
Brother, do you think I can’t go?
OK
Then go to the cell
Anyone who resists the order will be imprisoned in the cell
How long does it take to close the cell?
Two months
Two months...
Brother, there are other ways
Can I stay in the military tonight?
Ahem... there is a way to do it
Or you can take care of the military’s miracle
But…
This is good, I’ll choose this one
Alas...what is going on?
Young people are so brave and have a future
The miracle will be handed over to you
Ah OK No problem
You can hand it to me with confidence
I’ll take care of you today
Guaranteed that you and Baobao will have a great body
After eating these red ingredients
Our previous grievances were curled...
That’s weird
Make you so fierce usually
Can’t eat it, hahaha...
Hahahahahahaha...
Wolffy is not powerful. You think I am Husky
Thunder Bird
If the ability is out of control
It will definitely hurt others
When can I control the Lightning Strikees?
Ah Hui
In addition to feeding the strange beasts, I also need to help the strange beasts take a bath today
Good luck
No...
Alas, I don’t know if Wilie heard about his mother
Take a shower behaved?
I don’t want to take a shower I don’t want to take a shower
I don’t want it, I don’t want it...
Who doesn’t take a bath
Little Bear... Dad is so terrible
You take a shower, dad will teach you how to do it
OK I want so many bubbles
Haha, do you still need to bubble? Xiaoxiao
I...I didn’t mean it
I’m just in a good memory
Oh...I’ll definitely come back...
oops…
Oh, it hurts so much...
Which one does not have the moral integrity to throw garbage...
Wait... Why does this seem to be a red crown?
It’s true, our names are engraved on it
But why did it appear here?
Is it hard to tell what happened?
No, I have to find the red
But where to find red now?
Let me go, I’m innocent
Well, please...what happened to him?
This person sneaked into the Soldiers Village
Very suspicious, I also want to find a prison
Then we will send him into the cell as he wishes
Just sent to the cell?
right
Anyone who enters suspicious privately will be locked in the cell
They all said I’m not a suspicious person
I’m looking for a thatched cottage...
Stop talking, leave quickly
Is it difficult to find Red Red Red also arrested and entered a cell?
I have to go and see...
OK, then we’ll leave first if nothing happens
Wait wait wait wait...
Look
Look at this person’s eyebrows and mouse eyes
There are scars on the face
Belly like watermelon
A middle-aged man’s oily posture
Why do you seem to have heard it?
Forget it... In short, you are the only two, it’s too dangerous
Let me come and help you send him into the cell
Uh...but...
Simply exactly the same...
You’re pretty good
Too dangerous, we can just give it
See you again if you don’t bother
Slow, slow, slow, slow…
Not good, the gathering time is coming
Have to get along with the lambs first
Red...
I must go into the cell to see what happened
The tea has also been soaked by the village chief
I’ll be able to drink it when the village chief gets up
Well...but the painting seems to be a little bit off...
The village chief woke up and saw this beautiful flower
I’ll be in a good mood
We have also cleaned up the house for the village chief
The food and use are also placed by the village chief
Don’t worry about the village chief no one taking care of him
But...will it be a little too grand...
The time is almost done, let’s go and meet
Um
Huh? The village chief was sleeping and wearing eyeglasses
I’ll help him take it off
When did the village chief wake up
It’s finished...
Run...
Hello! You lambs will stop me!
Let’s go to the meeting place now
Come on, let me out quickly
Let me catch you I won’t let you go
Don’t beat me, Weslie...
You’re here
Yes, it was discovered by the village chief
But we trapped him temporarily
Now only Big Wolf is not here yet
No way
Are you missing one person?
You can’t be like this to me...
Not good...
What happened
I just discovered the red crown
what?
How did Wolnie appear here
I don’t know either
You go first
I’m going to check out the cell
Is my red beside it?
You’re too dangerous
Why don’t we go with you
Don’t worry, they all think I’m a soldier
I’m moving alone
It’s safer than with you
Don’t worry
But…
Stop, you fugitives don’t want to run
Bring them up to me quickly
Ah Hui, why are you here?
I...I am...
You can catch us quickly
After entering the cell, we should work outside
Just in time to help you find Wolnie
Just like these few people
Do you think you can catch us?
Hold him
You all stopped me
Otherwise I won’t guarantee her safety
Idiot, you’re going to catch a weak person
Big Wolf, you should say to us
You’re already surrounded by us
Hurry up and surrender
We surrender...
Is it difficult to reveal my baby?
It’s worthy of being Ah Hui
The fugitives caught on the first day of the new arrival
Get them all for me
Come on
Light years, unrestrained future
Give me in
You just stay here obediently
Don’t think about going out forever
Now we can find a way to find Wolnie
Weslie
Weslie...
You finally came to save me
Let’s go out quickly
There is no window here, how can we get out?