How do we know this
Is Wolnie here or not
I’m here
Wolnie...Little Huihui...
Are you here or not...
What arguing? No more arguing
We have to find a way to get out here
Help Wolffy look for Wolffy in the prison guard
I’ll try
Brother Soldier I want to find you if you have something to do
Just now...
Vague lens
What’s going on
I actually wear an eye mask...
I’ll try to use my mind
Take the keys on the soldier
What are these...
Why don’t there be keys
Leave it to us
- Blade Blade
ah…
Ah...I don’t know if they found the red one
They don’t have to worry about it...
Captured Princess Luna and the Goat
Her Majesty the Queen will definitely show me
Go to the palace quickly
Wait, Wolffy hasn’t caught it yet
Wolffy? He has no use, no need to worry about him
What are you talking about?
Wolffy is the king of inventories in the green grassland
Young, handsome, smart, capable
Why is it useless?
Huh? How do you understand this?
I...I heard what other soldiers said
I think we’ll go to the jail time
Please ask the whereabouts of Wolffy
No, I’ve asked the soldiers to look for them
But you are wise and wise, military officer
The lambs will definitely be afraid of you
By then they will tell the whereabouts of Wolffy
Wouldn’t this be twice the result with half the effort?
It makes sense too
The four words you just used are really good
Is it twice the result with half the effort?
Not wise and magical
Let’s go
This monitor is the strongest monitor in the entire cat country
- Whether it is a security facility or a safety facility within the prison
All-in-one
Only through the handprints of my military officer can I open the door
Do you know why this is
Don’t know...
It is because I am deeply trusted by the Queen
That’s why this is the right
When I became a military officer on the first day
I am determined to bow and exhaust myself to Her Majesty the Queen...
Where is the red red...
Red...
Who calls me
Red is so good, I finally found you
Who are you
Red is me, Big Gray Wolf
Wolffy? Are you here to deliver the meal?
Don’t bother me
Why is Wolffy you?
There is no soldier either
So what?
Come on...
Wolffy, is it you?
We’re here
You can wait a moment, I will open the door
Don’t run!
What sound
Oops! I’m going to be discovered!
When I looked for red before
I found that it’s more broken here
No one came
Slowy tell me where the red is
What red
This is the crown of Wolnie
I found it in the Soldiers Village
Where is she
I don’t tell you if I know
If you don’t tell me again, I will eat you!
Wolffy...
Sorry, my job is sick
I’m too anxious
Let me ask
I won’t be in your illusion lens
Depend on what tricks do you have
Let me open me and let me open me...
You’re cold and tranquil, too big wolf
Wolffy, you’re a little cold
We know the village chief he won’t say
Then what if I do? There is no room in the cell...
Don’t give up, I’ll look for it with you
good
Others are responsible for guarding the village chief here
Have to find a way to leave
Before you tell us about the crown
We won’t let you go
Who is the village chief? Come with me for this trick. Hum!
Her Majesty the Queen can’t leave me in everything
She will soon find out that I’ve lost it
You can’t escape by then
We’re looking for this
Actually, I discovered the crown yesterday
I’ve looked for most of the places here
It’s different today
ah?
I have two eyes today
Come on
That’s really a shame... let’s continue to search
Um
It’s dark...
I’ll find you tomorrow
thank you
Impossible
I haven’t appeared for so long
Why doesn’t the Queen send someone to me?
Big Wolf, you’re back
How did you find Wolnie?
no
I still have to think of a way out of the Slowy
I’ll let you let me go quickly
Otherwise, when Her Majesty the Queen arrives
I can’t talk about your love
Wolffy...
Wolffy, you’re a little cold
What do you want to do? Don’t come over...
Help...
Oh…
Master, Is this force suitable?
Ah, increase the amount of force...
Where else is it uncomfortable
My old waist and my old cold legs...
oops!
Military officer, I’m here to save you
Queen tomorrow, you finally come
I knew you would come to save me...
Military officer Have you seen this crown
What...what? I’ll take a look...
Oh, see
I remember falling from the miracle
Why is it in the Miracle
Who knows
Maybe something left?
He always eats something while I’m not paying attention
Yes, what are you asking about this?
You...what do you say...
Red... was eaten by a miracle?
Wolffy...
Village Chief, isn’t this true?
It must be fake, right?
This is what you need to know
No...this is not true. There will be no problem with red
Wolffy Go and be a family
Yes Yes Yes Yes...
Dad, I’m flying...
Wilie is the most harmful
So dirty, go take a shower
you…
What happened to the red
Give me the red...
Don’t think this is fine
Thunderbolt
I’m back...
Why is it hurt again
Come here quickly
Sorry, I won’t meet next time
Next time, you won’t go home
A mother who is fine
Dad was injured
I will use little magic to help my father heal
It really doesn’t hurt anymore Wilie...
I won’t fall until I’m found the red
Give them... to me...
Red...