Let me go, I want to revenge for the red
You’re a little cold
You let it open
How can you calm down when you call me
Both red and Wilie were eaten
I’m going back to claim revenge
Wolffy
What’s the point of going back now
Those miracles are so powerful
You can’t come back if you can’t do anything
Wolnie and Little Gray
Want to see you like this?
I understand how you feel
But now we have to be calm
Maybe Wolnie and Wilie are fine
Weslie said right
No one saw them being eaten
Then will they become miracles?
What do you mean
There are two kinds of miracles in the Cat Country
A wild and naturally existed miracle
The other one is the scoop
What’s the relationship with red
Those who are hit by a spooky ball will become spooky
And you will lose your mind and be controlled
The Slowy use the scoop ball
Those two strange beasts
It’s very likely that it’s Wolnie and Wilie
Wolnie and Wilie turned into miracles?
Yes, very likely
Since that’s the case
Then do you know how to turn them back?
Just play the magic ball
They can change back to their original state
I’ll ask the Slowy
Wait, Wolffy
According to the current personality of Mr. Slowy
I’ll definitely not tell you
This past may also surprise the snake
So what should I do? Red and small gray-gray turned into this
I can’t wait
That’s it
You’re thinking of a way here
The whereabouts of an unexpected ball from Mr. Slowy
Big Wolf and I went into Mr. Slowy’s house and looked for it
good
Then let’s go quickly
Um
Red…
Is Red Red you? I’m Wolffy
She should be controlled now
Let’s go find the magic ball first
But…
Oh…
Wait a minute.
Response?
Do you still remember this crown?
It actually stopped
Weslie, go find the magic ball
I stayed to hold them back
OK, please be safe
Small gray
Dad, come and play ball with you
Oh…
It seems that Luna said it is correct
It’s really them
There may be other methods like this
Let you wake up
Village… chief…
Can you tell me where the ball is going
OK
It’s not impossible to tell you
But…
I’m hungry and want to eat something
Want to eat something?
Have you heard it
I won’t prepare two delicious servings for Mr. Slowy
Why two copies
Because I’m tired too
Mr. Slowy What do you want to eat
Cake 10 lbs
There is a fruit tuck in it that needs to be red.
I want the cream to be domestic
Not too sweet, not too savory
There should be strawberry and mango decorations on it
But Mr. Slowy… these requirements are too high
It seems very difficult
Then I don’t want to say it if I have a stomach suck
Get ready now
Hehe… I finally left
Fortunately, I’ve dug a hole
It feels so good to go home
Sleep first, wake up and eat something delicious
Wolffy?
Don’t come to save me, but I started playing with the enemy
Hey Hey Hey Hey
Slowy, you actually escaped
How can a broken house in the area keep me under control?
That’s just right
Hand over your scoop
Otherwise, I’ll be rude to you
Not polite to me?
It depends on whether you have this ability
Catch him for me
what?
Red Red Little Huihui You are calm
Don’t name my miracle
I haven’t calculated the account with you yet
Why did red and small gray gray turn into strange animals
baffling
Deal with him
Ah…you are sober…
Dare to run into the trap area, hahaha
Isn’t he a self-sponsored website? Hahaha…
It seems that I have nothing to worry about
Red Red Wilie Don’t chase after
I’m Wolffy
Oops Stone Wall
It’s over, there’s no way
What sound
Red Red Little Gray Gray…
Catching…
oops
Oops Not good
Red Red Little Huihui…You will hold on for a while
I’ll save you soon
Don’t want to hurt my family
Thunder Bird Flash…
I will definitely protect you…
Red Red Little Gray Gray…
What kind of trap is this
Wolffy, let’s explode your potential…
It’s safe
What are you doing? Have you been injured
Why are you…remembering me?
It’s so good
We can finally get together
It’s all my fault for not protecting you
Let you become like this
Now that I’m starting, I won’t leave you anymore
Wolffy…
Have you changed back?
Dad, I miss you very much
I thought I wouldn’t come back…
No matter what you become
We are always a family I love you forever
dad…
Wolffy…
Thank you Weslie
Oh, I’m going to do it
That’s great, you’re fine
How terrible I brought you before
I’m really sorry
It doesn’t matter
Why do you come here
This thing starts from after you leave…
That day
I saw that Big Wolf left for so long and never came back
So I went to find him with Wilie
When passing by a waterfall
I discovered our family portrait
Wilie wants to pick it up
I accidentally fell down
I ran over and grabbed him
It was also rolled into the waterfall by the flow
Then I lost my mind
Wake up
I found that we were rescued by villagers from the Cat Country
Then why do you become a miracle?
After talking to the villagers
We’ll find your whereabouts
Looking for it
- I suddenly heard someone shouting to be careful
I didn’t know anything afterwards
I’m sorry, you’re worried
Just know