Not this smell
Haven’t this smell always been there?
Or give me a massage
If it weren’t for this strength, would you?
Military officer, why did you change someone like
Alas, it must have been these two days
It’s so comfortable to be served by the lamb
It really gave the queen and silenced her face
Why don’t you see the scoop
Military officer is not good
Two stunning animals restored their original form
He also left with Princess Luna and the others
The scoop was really stolen
Does the Queen know about this?
Know
Then is she angry?
No anxiety
She also let me bring you this
This is…
This is the secret weapon the Queen prepares for military officers
I hope you make good use of it
Queen Levana is so good to me
I’m not going to be indifferent to her expectations.
Let’s gather the team immediately. We’ll go out
The path to the palace is ahead
Want to see Queen Levana, let me get this first
Village Chief
Everything is for Queen Levana
As long as I have this I can defeat you
That’s… don’t wear it
Village chief…
Ahhhhh…
The military officer’s mighty
What happened to the village chief
That’s a ban on props’ violent head hoop
After putting it on, your ability will become stronger
But you will suffer great pain and lose your mind
Village chief…
Paddi…
Village Chief, please let me go
It hurts so much… I can’t control myself…
Report to the Queen
The military officer put on the head hoop and… it fell out
Yes, please step down
yes…
Is it hurting a companion or being hurt by a companion
I really want to see how you choose
Red Red You can hide with Wilie first
Don’t come out
knew
Come on, Dad
Ahhhhh…
Paddi…
You’re fine
I’m fine
But the village chief…
As long as you take off that hoop, the village chief will recover
Leave it to us
The opportunity is here
Weslie
Weslie…
Village Chief, please bear it
We will…will…save you…
Village chief?
Weslie, you’re fine
I’m fine, but the village chief…
The military officer fell down. Go and help
yes
Let me help the village chief to treat it
The soldiers are coming
It’s okay to remove the head hoop
Let’s go first
But…
Go quickly
You’re fine, military officer
Military officer, you…
go out
Why is the Queen going to give me tomorrow
Such a dangerous prop?
Can I just be a tool?
Didn’t I tell you to go out? Come on
Let’s go!
Haha…It seems that everyone is thinking the same
Since that’s the case, let’s go
good
Where are you going
We’re going back to see the village chief
We’ll be in the palace immediately. Don’t leave
Let’s go and cover them up, too
Princess Luna, please help them
Let’s go and help us, too
Princess Luna, why do you…
The Queen values me not me…
Pay attention to me not pay attention to me…
well…
Do you don’t understand what I said
Are you?
Come on, grab them quickly
Village Chief
- Come quickly
Please listen to our explanation
There seems to be a silence there
Go and take a look
We just…restless
Just wanted to see if you have anything to do
Village Chief
Why not be with us…
You go
Today’s events are just a pen
But tomorrow Princess will do you like this
We… are enemies
Since that’s the case
Then we won’t let you rest
But we won’t give up
It will definitely restore your memory
Um
Then we’ll leave first
Village Chief, remember to finish the food
Eat more food and be as powerful as me
What’s your strength?
What do you know
Village Chief What do you want to eat
Cake 10 lbs
There must be fruit tuck in the red flavor
I want the cream to be domestic
Can’t be too sweet Can’t be too soft
There should be strawberry and mango decorations on it
You…
Very hungry
I’d known to have some food
Wait a moment
If you are hungry, come and eat together
Come here…
I don’t know what happened to the lambs
Go and have a look
I’m not polite
Children cannot pick on food
Only by balanced nutrition can you grow taller
If you don’t eat, don’t eat
- What’s wrong with me if I don’t eat
- If you don’t eat, I’ll eat
Ah, I gave it to me…
Give you
I don’t want to eat this I want to eat skewers…
I’m your savior, you’re so ok
You come and eat this
Wow, it’s so hard to eat
The village chiefs all bully me
Village Chief, I’ll help you with this
Village Chief, let’s help you dress up
Everyone laughs and prepare…
Have you all stood up? 1 2…
Village Chief Sparky always bullies me
Sparky  is for your own good
Village chief…you…you’re like…
We can’t even picky food
Village chief…
You’re finally back
Children, thank you for your hard work during this period
Dad Mom Sister…