The military officer has changed and he will search for me
Let’s go while you’re now
We finally got together
Now it’s separated
OK OK OK Be careful on the way
We will wait for you to come back safely
I’ll be back soon
I know where to hide
You can go with confidence
OK, we can come out
Wait a minute.
This is…
Thank you very much for sending me and Fulai here
I have no answer
This is the unique cat claw flower of our strange cat country
Just be the courageous stamp for you
But now is not the time to answer
We still have to go on the palace
No, it’s time now
What does this mean
Let me go on the next path
Why
It’s really a shame to get you all in
Now you have made a promise
Send me back
Let’s hand it over to me next
Thank you really
But the princess…
Weslie Are We Really Going Back Now
What do you think
I, Big Wolf, have never given up
We followed us secretly
See if you need help
Yes, come out
Quick
I want to catch up with Princess Luna and others
What happened
Help
Be careful, goat
What’s going on
No, everyone, run away
Everyone, hurry up and it will be safe to run up there
ah…
call…
ah
It’s Princess Luna
We’ll go up
The slept with clouds to cover the stone above
Yes, Magic Cloud
OK, everyone climb up
good
Princess Luna…
I’ll save you
no…
Princess, don’t give up
Princess Luna
It’s you…
We’re here to help you right away
Don’t come over…
I’ve fought with you
Thunder Bird Flash…
Wolffy
You can control your own power
Since I saved the red red
I feel like I’m refreshed
Get over now
good
Why it obviously has nothing to do with you
Knowing that there is danger…
Why do you still have to follow
You go quickly, why did you take risks to save me
Because…
We are friends
If you have difficulties, you will face each other together
Thank you…
Hurry, let’s leave here tightly
It seems…stopped?
Look, everyone
It’s the palace
Let’s go in quickly
Do you know how dangerous it is
If you are not careful, you may lose your life
Luna…
Thank you, my friends
Princess Luna…
OK, let’s go to the palace
My sister should now turn on the guardrail
Everyone must be careful, just follow me
ah
what?
Fulai…
The anti-warming switch has been changed?
Ah…Save me quickly
- Paddi
who?
Don’t be hit by the cannon
Will be blocked
This ground…it wants to push us into the trap
careful!
You’re fine
no problem
No…
Look at me smashed the stone
It’s useless?
careful…
ah…
what?
- ah
No…
Sparky  Wolffy…
Tibbie…
Tibbie
This time I’ll protect you
Hurricane Blade
Not good
No
I’ve fought with you
I’m the only one left…
What do I do? How about it…
Hurricane Blade
Great, you’re fine
Put the clouds and I’ll tell you to come
good
Now everyone has fallen
Is there any way to save them?
Find sister
You can know where to save everyone
It’s so dark here
Why is it different here?
What’s up?
The mysterious cat has started
Mysterious cat?
They can offset all the power
We must enter at the fastest speed
I must find my sister
Run quickly…
Magic power really disappeared
The Paddi, and I…
Run quickly…
Magic power is invalid We can’t beat
So what?
But they are just two cats
What’s there to be afraid of
Even if Magic power is invalid…
But don’t forget that we are…
- Goat Village Guardian!
Luna, go first. Leave here to us
I see
Everyone is because of me…can’t give up
If you want to catch Luna, you have to pass us first
Weslie
Hahaha…
drink!
ah…
Paddi…
Paddi
You’re okay, are you?
No! He was poisoned!
I’m fine
I’ll carry you
Luna leaves quickly
But the goat have been poisoned
Don’t worry about me, please leave
Paddi…
Magic Cloud
Success!
We’re going out to find a way to help you detoxify
No, isn’t it finished yet?
- Luna…
Weslie Goat…
don’t want…
ah…
Humph
I haven’t seen my good sister for a long time
elder sister?
elder sister…