"The Secret Road"
Ah...sister...sister...wake up...
you…
Close my mouth
I’m very awake now
Paddi...
You’re fine
My feet... hurt so much...
Sister...Sister
Stop...
It’s time to end
You stay here first
I’ll save Luna
Um
Stop tomorrow
What a guy
It’s so terrible!
No!
Weslie
Magic Cloud
Catch you
Don’t try to escape...
what…
This is...
Fortunately... it’s time
Is it finished
Let’s go now
Um
Be careful
Come, I’ll support you
Don’t want to escape
snort! Do you think you can escape this way?
Come
Go and search them for me
yes
Ahhhhh…
Plain landing perfect
Everyone is fine
It’s OK
I have something to do...
sorry
Don’t be nervous
The most important thing now is how we get out
This is not simple to see mine
Flame Fist
Useless
This cell will offset the kiwi power
Can’t we have no other way?
Don’t give up, let’s look
There will be some way to say
Um
Oh, I’ve been looking for it for so long
Still no discovery
oops…
- What happened Wolffy?
I seemed to be stabbed by something...
This is...
stop! You can’t escape
Search me carefully
yes
Reporting Team Leader No in the room
There is no in the corridor, either
They definitely can’t run away
Follow me to search
yes
ah…
You are okay, 李妻录?
Let’s find a place to hide first
They searched all the rooms here
It should be safe at the moment
Come with me
Here is...
It’s my room
What to do now...
My sister has completely changed her personality
Dad and mom don’t know where to go
Weslie My feet hurt so much
Paddi!
What are you doing
Ah, the toxins have been dissipated
Luna, save the goat
I haven’t detoxified before, I can only try it
Look, I found the key
Hehe... Maybe you can open the door
Wolffy, please stop dreaming
No supervisor would put the key in the cell
That’s it
It’s really opened!
So let’s say
People who are brave enough to try will not be too bad
Then let’s go away
etc.
Don’t just act rashly
There may be ambush outside
If you go out, you will definitely be arrested.
Then what should I do
I’ll go out to explore the road
You’re waiting for my news here
But you will be in danger if you go alone
Don’t worry I used to come here often
Don’t be careless, hide quickly
good
No, I don’t have a rule of law
The toxin must be excreted
I’m here
What are you doing with Weslie
I want to help you suck out the toxins
No, once this toxin is inlet
I’m afraid you’ll get poisoned, too
No, you can’t have something wrong
Then what should I do
I can’t let my eyes look at you poisoned
Don’t you save
You’re a little cold
I think the method of taking out the toxins is still feasible
But you said that toxins will be intoxicated, will I also be poisoned?
Isn’t it okay to not suck with your mouth?
But it may hurt a little
Can’t let the soldiers find that we have to endure it
Really effective
Hold on to the goat
Waiting for the Paddi, wait to return to the green grassland
Let’s have grass cake together
And...and pudding...
Hold on, it’s still a little bit
Take a deep breath
Exhale deeply
Come out immediately, don’t give up
Success
No more pain
Thank you Luna
Princess Luna You...you’re fine
I...I’m fine
I just don’t know what to do next
Should I give up?
Princess Luna, don’t give up
If you give up
There is no hope for it
Even if it is only one percent chance
All have to hold on
Even the Yangyang Goat has been doing this very much
You can definitely
That’s right
ah? What, I don’t care!
Ha ha ha ha…
Let’s work hard together
good
Search this again
yes
Why don’t you come back now?
Is there anything going on
Or let’s go and have a look together
good
Be careful
What is this?
There seems to be something in it
Don’t worry about these, go quickly
There seems to be no soldiers patrol here
Don’t be careless, be careful of organic matter
Wait a moment
Why do we seem to be back
What’s the place?
what?
Really, what’s going on
Not against the robber
Think carefully
Have we ever encountered a fork in the road?
Maybe their cells are the same
Let’s go again
This time we set the mark all the way
good
Sparky  keeps up
How long will we go
Look quickly
These are the arrows we just drew
Back here again, what should I do
It seems that this is a mystery with endless circulation
It’s hard to blame no one to guard it and can’t get out at all
Where has the blessing gone?
We didn’t meet him along the way
Maybe he’s gone out
Since he can go out
Then there must be a solution
Sparky
You try to light up the chicken light
good
Flame Fist
Success
It seems that as long as the lights are not lighted up, it seems
A new path will emerge
The chicken is not bright yet
Flame Fist
Let’s go quickly
It’s a dead end
But the light is already on
Is it really hard to have no way to go?
Well... I won’t be going to get the lights off this time
Aqua Spirit
Success
We’ve gone up
Why did you stop?
ah…
Another trap
What’s the place here
Have we gone out?
It doesn’t seem to be
We fell to another dungeon again
ah?
Who is it?