Who are you…
Queen, come and see
A wolf and three goat fell from it
Really
I can’t tell you are...
The king and queen of the strange cat country?
what?
Haha It looks like my reputation
Has been transmitted to another ethnic group
Well…
We heard you were caught
That’s right I’m the king of the cat country
This is my queen
So you are Luna’s parents?
what? Do you know my daughter?
Well, we came to save you with Princess Luna
Now the whole cat country is going to be a mess tomorrow
Alas... In fact, tomorrow will be affected by dark energy
You are the king
Can’t you stop it?
At that time, I sealed the dark energy
Almost all the Magic power
Our strength is weak now
Even I can’t escape here
What’s more, it’s...
In this case, let us take you out
what…
Wearing...has been worn?
What’s going on
Here is a boundary forbidden us
You can’t touch us
End of boundaries?
We tried it with Qili, and it may be possible to crack it
good
Open the door quickly
This will not last long
You’re here soon
This is...
This secret passage leads to my sister’s room
We used to be unable to sleep in the middle of the night
Just sneaked over this secret passage to find the other party
Let’s go
Fast Goat
Um
They chase me there!
yes
Be careful
Ah Help...
stop
oops…
My Lightning Strike cannot be broken
Look at my...Flame Fist
Success
I can’t break it, either
I didn’t expect that they were powerful
It seems that Luna handed over the magic stone to them
Alas, I still can’t break the boundary with Qili
Is it really impossible to do it?
You...It’s too early to give up now
It’s right to say
Um
oops…
It’s so touching
I want to remember this sentence that makes people full of strength
Right, let me tell you next time
Come on
Flame Fist
Thunderbolt
oh
Come again
ah
Wait a moment
Every time you attack
There is a little glowing in the center of the top of the boundary
It’s hard to tell...that’s the key point of breaking through the boundaries?
I’ll try it
There is really a Sparky...
good
-Flame Fist - Thunderbolt Pin
Success
Thank you, you are such a good boy
Then let’s go quickly
good
Right
I just saw a crystal box in the dungeon
What’s inside
There are people who were about to take away the dark energy that year
He is like you
what?
I remember that year...
Stop Stop…
Stop you can’t escape
What’s going on? Why did he fall suddenly?
Take a look carefully
Keep him in the dungeon
The wolf still hasn’t woken up yet
Maybe he was also attacked by the dark energy
Just in case of
We just kept him in touch
In the crystal box that only our family can open
The most important thing now is the problem of tomorrow’s princess
Let’s talk about the others later
Um
Almost caught
I knew you would escape from the secret passage to this place
elder sister…
No!
Too slow
ah…
elder sister…
Take the blame...
Qi... Magic Cloud...
It can still move?
Only by defeating her will she have the chance to escape
Come together
good
Hurricane Blade
Small tricks of carving
It’s over
Look at my big move
-Ah... -Ah...
what?
Dare to steal me
Ahhh!
Where is the person?
Don’t try to escape from my palm
Finally breathing free air
Levana and Luna
Alas
Blessing
King, Queen, Why are you here
Everyone, hide
Luna
Dad Mom
You finally come back
We miss you so much
Come and let your mother take a good look at you
Hahahaha... It’s really touching
Then you will disappear together
Be careful
This is...
ah…
Tibbie
Thank you for taking goat
Then try this trick again
Let’s go together
Flame Fist
Thunderbolt
Hurricane Blade
Very heavy...
I can’t hold back anymore...
Sister, stop!
Stop tomorrow!
King, you...
Wake up tomorrow
We are a family
Don’t you remember dad?
Levana I’m a mother
Say, say, say, say...
Stop talking...
ah…
If this continues, this belt will be destroyed
Sister, that’s...
ah…
Children...
elder sister…
Wake up soon
Hao... Luna...
ah?
Luna Levana
Levana you will finally wake up
Dad Mom... Here is...
It’s great that you’re fine
Where is the bright moon
Why is she not hurt?
What’s wrong with Luna? You talk
Luna… Luna…
Sorry Sorry...
Don’t be too difficult
Luna
Don’t be too difficult for the princess tomorrow
All blame me, all blame me
How about it...it’s all my fault that I can’t control the violence in my body
Have done a lot of things that hurt everyone
It also hurts Luna... Luna...
It’s my sister, I’m sorry for you
Please wake up
Don’t be responsible
Dark energy is so terrible
That’s why it’s been sealing it
Dad said it’s OK
Dark energy is so dangerous
The place where it is sealed is not strictly secure
Please rest assured
Where to seal it now
- Very safe - Report No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
The king of kings
Bookroom... Bookroom is a little uneven
what?
Let’s go and have a look, too
Let Luna take care of us
Um
But I wish I didn’t have any more trouble...