Why is it so chaotic
There is actually a secret room here
That’s...
Is this the dark energy that will turn tomorrow black?
That’s right
Just put it there?
What if anyone comes to steal
Be careful not to get close
ah…
Squat down
So scary, what’s going on
To prevent anyone from stealing dark energy
I’ve already added a barrier
Then don’t worry about someone stealing it again
But is this really safe?
Can I open it with tools?
This is me and the queen
It took almost no effort to create a barrier
Only people from our family can open it
It is impossible for ordinary people to open it with tools
…What’s up
The King of the Kingdom This is a secret matter
How can I say it out in a casual way
Yes! …
What happened? Fulai?
Dark energy is fine
But... When will Luna wake up
It’s definitely nothing
Um
Let’s go back and see Luna
But why is the room so chaotic
It’s a mouse...
Let’s go
Come
don’t want…
Don’t be afraid, sister, sister is here
Luna woke up
No matter how we call her, we haven’t woken up
I’ll try it
Do you have any way?
Maybe it’s because Luna’s blood is not circulating
Not awake
Patients need appropriate stretching to promote blood circulation
Don’t chase me...
You see, there’s a reaction
But I didn’t wake up
I don’t believe it
oh…
Why…
ah…
I can’t do it, come here...
It seems that I can only rely on me
Do you have any way to go?
Don’t be quarrel
Eat a meal...
Don’t play with the goat
Everyone is worried about Luna
What? This trick is a test of a hundred spirits
This move will only test you a hundred spirits
younger sister…
Luna seems to be doing bad things all the time
Don’t... don’t chase me...ah...
Go open...
ah…
Ahhh...it hurts so much...
Princess Luna
You’re awake
Dad Mom
Luna…
Sister...it’s great, you’re fine
Yes Luna
I’m fine
You’ve sucked out all my dark energy
Thank you
You’re fine, right
Um
I want to write a poem about this situation
Close your mouth!
Although it is difficult
But finally got together
Hahaha…
Sparky , you’re crying
How could I cry
This is emotion, it is emotion...
Hahaha…
- Hahaha…
Oh, it’s finally over
Then can we go back to the Qingqing Grassland?
Right
Let’s pick up Slowy and Red Red.
Then go back together
Levana’s Princess
Is something happening?
Well... It’s okay that...
I never had a chance to apologize to you
I was so sorry to you at that time...
sorry…
It’s okay
You are also affected by dark energy
We believe you won’t hurt everyone again
Yes, and because of this time
We have become more cherishing our friendship
- Um
And after all this
Our Paddi have grown up too
Yes, my appetite has grown
- What? Humph!
By the way, we decided to go back to Qingqing Grassland
So fast
Well, let’s go and find the village chief now
Wait a moment…
Let go, don’t want to catch us
Wilie, don’t be afraid
Village Chief
Everyone…
Red... Little Gray Gray...
dad…
It’s fine if you’re fine
Village Chief
Everyone…
Don’t hurt them
I…
I protect you, you go quickly
Quick
Here I’m holding... Go away
Well…
Village chief...you’ve misunderstood
what?
It turns out that nothing is done
That’s great hahaha...
Just brought the soldiers and they came up
They don’t hear our explanation at all
Sorry, sorry, I thought you were cheating on us
Sorry, it should be me
Sorry, I shouldn’t have hurt you like that before
All over, and that’s not your intention
Now everyone is fine
Thank you... Thank you...
elder sister
I heard that the villagers have recovered their strength
Yes
Dad and mom have already set off this morning
Give everyone the recovered pharmacy
Great, everything has recovered
Thank you for your hard work along the way
Thank you for not giving up me...
What to say
You are mine...Haqiu
The wind is a bit big, sit here obediently
I’ll get you clothes
Obey the order Hehehe...
…This is delicious
Yes, very good
Don’t eat, don’t speak
Village Chief, don’t you tell them?
ah…
…what
What happened to you, Fulai?
Right, good luck
Have you seen Luna and the others?
What happened to them walking in the garden?
We plan to go back to Qingqing Grassland tomorrow
So I wanted to say goodbye to them before leaving
…oh
give
Eat slowly, there are a lot more
careful
My power...what’s going on
careful…
ah…
Levana, aren’t you with Luna?
Yes
I came back to get a coat. What happened?
Oh, we plan to...
ah!
What sound?
What’s going on?
Luna…
Luna
Nothing, just fainted
After absorbing dark energy
Luna shouldn’t recover yet
Then let’s leave first
Let her have a good rest
Um