careful
My power…what’s going on
ah…
How did my strength become so strong
And it’s not under control
It’s hard to tell…
Go open…
Dark energy…has already entered my body?
Princess Luna, are you awake?
We’re here to see you
Why didn’t there reply
There seems to be a sound inside
Is something happening?
Why don’t you hit the door and go in
ah…
You’re fine
It’s okay I’m fine
I just got out and hit the bed
Princess Luna, you’re not
Cough…I feel a little uncomfortable
You go back first I’m afraid it will be infected to you
But…that…
We…we plan to go back to Qingqing Grassland tomorrow
So I want to have a picnic with Princess Levana tonight
Can you come
Are you leaving so soon?
Yes, let’s say goodbye tonight
That’s good…
Very good
I’m going to rest, you go
People of the Cat Country
It’s been a pain for everyone before
To compensate you
Now I’ll give you one for each of you…
True blessings
It’s the king and queen
The Cat Country is peaceful
I’ll decide to reward you…
A poem
Thank you all for your hard work
I’m here to ask everyone now…
have a good rest
Good news Good news
Catland restores peace
I’ll ask…
Stop joking again, let’s talk about the matter
Princess Luna Princess Luna
Weslie and they said you are still a little uncomfortable
I want to see you
I…I need a rest. You go back first
Princess Luna
Is something happening
I’ll find someone
don’t want
What’s going on?
I…maybe I’ve sucked dark energy
what?
You go quickly
If I really sucked dark energy
I might… hurt you
I’m not afraid, we’re friends
And you haven’t hurt me now
I’m afraid I’ll be unable to control myself in the future
I’m going to find my dad and mom right away
Hope they have a way
But the king and the queen are not there
They are out and ready tonight’s smoke-filled celebrating
Then what should I do…
In fact… you may not be hit by the dark energy
Or you try Magic power again
Princess Luna…
Ah…Princess Luna…
Ah…I’m sorry, blessed
I’m fine
No…I’m leaving here
Princess, why don’t we think about other ways
The kings will come back tomorrow
no
Because I don’t know the dark energy now
When will I control me
I can’t harm my family and friends
But…but before leaving…
I want to see my sister and Bai Yangyang again
Great, I can go back to Qingqing Grassland tomorrow
I miss my stool very much
I miss my flowers very much
I really want the potato chips at Sparky’s house
Two bags left last time
Paddi…
Why haven’t Luna and Fulai arrived yet
Sister, everyone…
Princess Luna Fulai
You finally arrived
Princess Luna, you’re not
I’m fine
Princess Luna, why are you crying
I can’t let you go
You can visit the grassland anytime
I’ll ask you to eat potato chips from Sparky’s house
Paddi…
I won’t fall into the dungeon again this time
It’s okay, the connections here are closed
Then let’s arrange it quickly
good
You know how to make such delicious food
Of course
Single! Our Paddi are a little different
Remembering the past…
Hahaha…
Sparky , I’ll grow up too
The appetite is growing
- Hehehehe…
Your relationship is so good
- No
You’ll be fine in the future
Don’t forget us
Don’t forget the precious revelation we have lived together
We’re just leaving for a while
How do you say it’s like it’s always gone
For we’re just going back to the grassland
Will definitely meet again
Um
Wow…
So beautiful…
What a wonderful evening
With everyone…
Thank you
Princess Luna…
What’s up?
Princess Luna, what are you doing
Luna…
Princess Luna…
Don’t come
Sister, what’s wrong
younger sister…
Don’t come over
Don’t come…
you…
Starting from today…
I’m the most darning person in the cat country
Princess Luna What’s going on?
This…is dark energy…
what?
Why does Princess Luna have dark energy on her body?
Aqua Spirit…
We must stop Princess Luna
Look at my Magic Cloud…
Tips for carving and carving
Hurricane Blade
Flame Fist
Thunderbolt
Aqua Spirit
Give it to you
Sister, stop…
Magic Cloud
Let me go… Who dares to touch me…
Why did Princess Luna become like this
younger sister…