Do you think this will trap me?
well
I temporarily sealed the power of the bright moon with my sealing hand ring
Fortunately, King of the Kingdom, you come back in time
Princess Luna What happened to Princess Luna
It’s dark energy
Sure enough, but why
I’m afraid it was at that time...
The dark energy has moved to Luna
How...how can it happen
There is no way to do it
Have you eliminated this dark energy?
Is there any more information about dark energy
Maybe you can find a way to eliminate it
There is indeed a book
There are information about dark energy
Then go and have a look
But I’ve tried the method here and found it
No success
Let’s take a look again. You may find a new line
OK Come with me
You go, I want to stay here to accompany Luna
Me too
Um
It’s all my fault...
Levana this is not your mistake
Is anyone there?
I have a very slim stomach. Can I eat something?
I’m really hungry, please
I’ll prepare now
Quick, I’m very tired
Sister, are you feeling uncomfortable
Are you laughing at me?
How could it be? Haven’t you been hungry
I brought you a bun
Have you eaten, aren’t you hungry?
Dad and the others are thinking of a way
You’ll definitely be fine
Yes
You remember
Did we often eat buns together in the past?
You’ll give it to the little fish
It’s obviously a doll, but it won’t eat it
You insist on giving it to eat
By the way, where did you go to the little fish?
Do you want to eat the little fish?
Sister, do you still remember
Sister, what are you going to do
Do you know what I’m laughing at?
Laughing at you stupid
younger sister…
There are so many books, how to find
Recording the dark energy
It’s a purple book
There are too many purple books
Is this book
ah…
Fortunately, I, Wolffy, are agile
Alas...
Feel sorry
I have to work hard, too
Rizhao Wanli Far, mood over the mountain car
The spring wind blows, the wind is flying high
We are a happy family
On March 3, I will accompany my children to enjoy the poem...
This is my poem, I won the championship
Although I am the only one who participates
strangeness? Why is there a blank book?
That’s the book
There is nothing on the book
Is there any machine button
Because it is important information
So it takes a tone to enter the power of the
This is...
Let me come
Scanned and confirmed as a member of the royal family
What is this? Very darn
The Essence of the Book
We want to know all about dark energy
Dark energy can make people irrational
Become ambitious
If dark energy is absorbed
The ability of the person to absorb will increase greatly
But at the same time, the heart will gradually become uncontrollable
Be ambitious?
It’s hard to blame what the princess will turn into tomorrow
Is it hard to tell if Princess Luna is also unreasonable?
See if there is any solution
It’s a sci-fi
King of the Kingdom What kind of drama is this?
This is...
Not good
Sister...Sister she ran away
what!
It’s all my fault, it’s me that I’m too careless
She probably didn’t run away
You two go search
- yes
We’re here to help, too
Um
Princess Luna Where are you
Princess Luna
Princess Luna?
Princess Luna…
Why is it you
- Stop
- Don’t run...
oops…
It turns out it was you
What are you doing
We chased after Luna when we saw it
There we chase
This hand ring is really a mess!
Hurricane Blade
Princess Luna
Aqua Spirit
Magic Cloud
Princess Luna
We are thinking of a way to help you come back soon
Paddi...
Who is he?
Let’s go
Who are you...
- Let me go
Flame Fist
Fulai?
Why does Fulai do this
Maybe it’s because he and Princess Luna are good friends
Fulai is so stupid. This way, it can’t help Luna.
Can’t let them go
We want to tell the king of the country as soon as possible
Stop them in various towns
Can’t find them
What about the princess tomorrow
She went to the Soldiers’ Village to look for it
Don’t know what happened in other towns
- Report to the King of the Kingdom
Searching all the quicksand towns
No princess or blessings were found
The Princess and Fulai were not found in the Aqua Spirit Town
Got it Continue searching
- yes
This cat country has soldiers guarding it
Where will they escape?
Could it be that...they didn’t escape?
You mean they might be here?
Think about it
There is not another place in the palace that I haven’t found
And there are no soldiers?
It’s a dungeon
Why help me?
Forget it, for you to help me escape
You go
Hahahaha...I’m helping myself
Bless you...
Did you open your eyes?
You are not a blessing, who are you
You don’t have to worry about who I am, hehe...
Is it a crystal that unseals the hand ring?
How it’s in your hands
I stolen from the king of kings
How do we cooperate?
To show my sincerity...
What do I need to help you
Inside is...
Only you can unseal this criticized crystal box
This...this is...