That’s...
Huh? Why am I here?
It’s a blessing, catch him...
Let me tell you where did you bring Princess Luna
Who are you
Stop installing
I didn’t have it
You took Princess Luna away
How about it...what are you talking about
King of the Kingdom will save me quickly. There is an assassin
Tell me where did you take my daughter
I really don’t know where Princess Luna is
What happened
Don’t be stupid for me...
It seems that I can only use torture!
Use...
Ah...No
I really can’t stand it anymore
Humph, I can only continue to torture
Say it
Hahaha…
I really don’t know, hahaha...
Let you not say it, let you not say it...
Sparky , I’m here too
Hahahaha...stop...hahahaha...
Too violent...
No!
What’s up? What happened?
Crystal box...Crystal box is opened
It’s over, the wolf ran away
Dark energy is not safe...
Did the wolf who wanted to steal dark energy at the beginning be here?
But why was it opened
yes
Without the power of our royal family, it cannot be opened.
Will it have anything to do with Princess Luna?
Then let’s go and find Princess Luna
ah?
Who is there?
-Follow up and take a look -Follow up and take a look
Don’t want to run
Sparky ...
Flame Fist
Who are you? Sneaky here
Just let you down, you want to live with me
It’s you? Hurry him
He was the one who ejaculated his dark energy that year
The wolf is kept in here
what?
Hum overestimate one’s ability!
-Princess Luna? -Princess Luna?
Princess, why are you here?
No one is allowed to approach here
Let it open
If the dark energy is revealed
It will cause disaster in the cat country
Please understand Princess Luna
Don’t make it difficult for us
Leave aside!
ah…
Who are you
Since you have caught
Then I’ll tell you
My name is Lone Wolf
Lone Wolf...
This thing
Let me start with my dark energy...
I was a little bit short of
You can successfully obtain dark energy
I didn’t expect to be caught by two princesses
The result was shocked by the king
He sent soldiers to capture me
It was at this time that I just met Fulai...
So you’ve been lucky?
Half right, but I’m not
Instead... occupied his body
what?
So I kept my body here at a moment
Use blessing to escape
Whether it is a body, memory or ability
I can take up all
I don’t blame me for not remembering anything after hitting him
What about later?
Watching his body be sealed
I can only continue to use my blessings
Strange you can occupy the body of the king
This is more convenient to move
Humph, I’ve tried it early
But the king has a strong and powerful bodyguard
I have no way to do it, either
That’s right, our family is so bad
At that time, I still wanted to defect to tomorrow
This makes it more likely to get dark energy
But I didn’t expect that she thought I was Luna’s companion
I won’t let it go
Want to go back to the palace to get dark energy
I am just a long time and I
I didn’t expect you to appear at this time...
Let’s help you
Thank you
After three words, I answered to help us
It’s too simple and pure
hey-hey…
Our goat village is full of simple and lovely goat
People are saying you’re stupid
Don’t get us even if you don’t hear it
Hum, it’s just hidden here
Just this seal...
I didn’t expect it to be so simple
Stop...
Sister, don’t take out dark energy
Then you try to stop me
Take the call
You wake up
Once dark energy is revealed
The whole cat country will suffer
Don’t point fingers at me
ah
Hahaha…
Will you just come and go like a mouse?
Sorry...
Very bad!
Let me go...
I can’t let you release dark energy
not good...
Luna, you’re fine
ah…
You’re still worried about yourself
don’t want…
No one can stop me
I’m not blaming you for always hurriedly saying to leave quickly
It turns out that your purpose is dark energy
It turns out that you have been using us all the time
Hum, for your friendship
I’ve wasted a lot of time
Ice and Snow Town stopped because of the snow
In the quicksand town, to save the Sparky
You actually stayed
Arrive at the Shuiling Town
For those villagers, I went to find the floating beads
After you fight with the Slowy in Soldier Village
I was worried about his injuries and went back...
Sorry...
No, why do I apologize
snort!
continue
You’ve been in the palace so you’ll be familiar with it
So you deliberately dropped the team when the machine is in contact?
Hum, it’s OK
I’ve prepared the keys long ago and I can leave just by opening the door
Unexpectedly...
You actually fell down too
I also made a fuss about my plan
It was an excuse for you to go out to explore the way?
right
I hid the soldiers in the patrol
Arrived in the bookroom smoothly
Finally, we come to the secret room with dark energy
It turns out that the bookstore is so awkward, it is also because of you
Even if you find a secret room
You can’t get dark energy at all
Yes I can’t get it
Later you deliberately went in front of the king
File a security question in the secret room
That’s right. I missed him more
I know only people from their family
Can remove barriers
This is really not a good thing
From the beginning you’re counting all of us
Too much
For the sake of dark energy, use everyone’s feelings
Hum, to me, people are divided into two types
What works for me and what doesn’t work for me
That’s all
There are so many people you hurt along the way
Can’t you feel a little guilty?
ridiculous
As long as my plan succeeds
What’s wrong with me?
What exactly do you want to use dark energy?
Take back our world
What…our world?
Green...grassland?
Why do you tell us so much?
You were caught by us on purpose
Just to delay time for Luna…
Hahaha…
You actually discovered it
Luna should be in the secret room
Hahaha...come
Let me tell you about my plan with Luna again
Let’s go to the secret room to find Luna
Alas
Levana’s Princess
Princess Levana, you’re fine
Quick...Stop her...
Hahahaha…Dark energy is mine!