Luna, please put down the box
Then we have to see if you have this ability
Hurricane Blade
The Goat is well done
My cloud changes are not
not good!
- Flame Fist
ah…
You’re not my opponent at all
Don’t have such a big mouth
Look at my thunderbolt...
Alas...Leifeng
Ah... Alas...
Don’t be idle
Just let you not hold me
Let’s catch up with her
Weslie...
OK I’ll delay them, you go first
Um
Weslie?
Weslie Why don’t you talk
Ah... What’s going on with Weslie...
Whether it is a body, memory or ability
I can use it
Weslie...is it controlled by the lonely wolf...
what?
He is a lonely wolf
- What to do here
Stop playing, leave
snort!
Weslie, you’re fine
Weslie Weslie...
This...what is going on?
You’re just being controlled
I’ve taken action against us
ah…
It’s a lonely wolf!
No! They ran away!
Let’s go back and find the king to help you
What are you going to run? Let me open the box
Didn’t you say that you had taken the dark energy?
Am I the strongest in the entire cat country?
Can you tell me that you are cheating on me?
You just want to be one
Is the strongest in Little Cat Country?
What’s the meaning
I want to help you become...the best in the world
The strongest in the world?
You will know when you leave the cat country
They’re here
You hand over the box
The king has sent all the soldiers to capture you
You can’t escape
Not overestimating one’s ability
report
Luna and the others kept running towards the boundary
The soldiers were also injured a lot
Take it back to our world...
The lonely wolf wants to escape from the strange cat country with dark energy
Yes, notify the soldiers of each village
Start the highest level of boundary seal immediately
Go quickly!
yes
Report All boundaries have been blocked
OK, then they shouldn’t be able to get out
But what about them opening the box?
Is there no way to deal with dark energy?
Book The last time
What about here
That year...
Before the birth of the Cat
A strange beast rages all over the world
Dark energy will be emitted from this anomaly
The infected villagers will face each other with swords
And very ambitious
Finally in this dangerous period
A warrior stood up
He used his powerful power
Fighting against the alien for ten days
Finally killed the anomaly
Just when the villagers were excited
The Warriors seem to be a little worried
Because after the anomaly dies, the dark energy still cannot be eliminated
Later, the Warriors decided to seal the dark energy
And established a cat country
Generations of towns are pressing on dark energy
But then
Another person with some intentions has taken dark energy
And let it go
Warriors who have become kings of the nation
Fighting against dark energy for several days and nights
In the end, the king of kings used a sword
This eliminates the dark energy of the ejaculation
But after the war, the Guangshe landed into the cliff
No one has seen it again
That’s it
It turns out that there is also a handful of light sculpting energy to eliminate dark energy
That’s what
We found that silhouette
Can you solve the dark energy?
Huh?
Every king of ours
They have sent people to the bottom of the cliff to find them
There are gold dramas, wooden dramas, stone dramas,
Plastic Strip Strip
There is also a carving boat to ask for a sword...
Alas, but it’s not that silhouette
This statement won’t be fake
It’s true
The book of the Cat Country will not cheat people
One fake one pays ten real
I haven’t found it
Because I haven’t had any trouble for many years
I didn’t send anyone to find it
I didn’t expect that now...
It’s not your own responsibility now
Since no one found that piece
It’s clear that the sword must be there
Now only this method can stop them
Where is that cliff
Let me lead you
Um
tomorrow
You just stay to protect others
Now Luna and the others can’t get out of the strange cat country
Maybe I’ll go back to the palace for trouble
Um
No, the boundaries are all covered
We can’t get out
They actually blocked the entire cat country
Turn on the dark energy
What are you waiting for
Not the time now
Arrived
It’s time to arrive at the cliff in front
It’s Weslie and the others
未分类
Let’s see what plans they have
We went to that cliff
We can definitely find the light slab
Disinfect all dark energy
I’ll send you here
Wish you success
Is there a way to eliminate dark energy by using light sculpting?
The drama that dispels dark energy in the story
But no one has found it
If they found that light drama
Then I’ll be able to do it
Let’s stop them
no
It will be terrible when we are caught together
Dark energy cannot return to their hands
So what plan do you have
Since we two can’t get out
That’s all I can do
We’re...
Take this one and go back to capture the palace
Don’t turn on this threat before clearing it
What about you?
I’ll be before they find that saurus
Take one step ahead and destroy it!
The light drama is below
Magic Cloud
Snake
Let’s go down
Um
Where will the sculpt fall?
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
There is a treasure box here
Is the Daoguang Sword right inside?
ah…
You’re fine
After searching for so long, I still haven’t found anything
They searched for it for so many years but haven’t found that piece of cake
How can we find it so easy?
That’s it
It also caused my ass to be bitten by a snake
Cough cough cough...
Look!
There is a sword there!