This is hard to say that this is the light drama of that year
Very likely
The strange king has never been found
It turns out that the light sculpt was inserted into the stone statue
But this sword is inserted into the stone
It seems difficult to get
Hehehe… I’ll give it to me when this is the case
After so many years of training, it was finally put on the stage
come on
ah…
Sparky , you’re fine
How can I not even have the most powerful Sparky?
Will it be the only selected warrior
Can you pull it out
Just like the stone in the morning of that year
- Stone Spot…
ah…
It makes sense. Go and try it
Then I’ll try it
Huh…ah…
Successful uh…
I got the silhouette
ah?
How did this happen
I’ll break it with kiwi
It depends on the time machine to remove the sword
Just now
Did it succeed?
Where is the light drama?
What should I do
Come quickly everyone
What’s wrong? Tibbie
Look quickly
It’s a shoe print
Hehe…it’s successful
Lone Wolf stands
Don’t want to run
Look quickly
The stone shattered
Let me test its power
No!
Even the cloud shields are cut
This is a drama of light
Your bad egg cannot expose its true power
What do you mean…
Thunderbolt
Get the scimitar
yeah!
You don’t have to worry about it
I believe they will find Weslie
ah? Um
Who is coming
Who are you…
Be careful
ah…
Will something happen to Luna?
Mom Where is Dad?
Dad is back soon
Luna Where are you
Luna
Luna, you’re back
Luna You finally come back
Luna
Luna…
Luna, are you doing
I will call me…Luna
Hahahahaha
He seems to have passed
Then how to deal with him
The most important thing now is to bring the sword back
Take Lone Wolf back together
Yes, I’ll carry him
OK Let’s go
I’ll get it
What’s up
This important thing
Of course I have to hand it over to me, the most powerful person, to keep it
But we are except you
It’s hard to carry Lone Wolf
Are you looking for excuses to steal?
Uh I…
It’s okay, I’ll come and recite it
It’s so strange
Isn’t it that Sparky  takes the initiative to carry Lone Wolf?
Wait a minute I’ll get it
You…you are not a Sparky
what!
Flame Fist
Wolffy…
My doubts are correct
The Sparky  is controlled by Lone Wolf
goodbye
Don’t let him run away.
Wait a moment
This will hurt Sparky’s body
Innocent
See
Just want to defeat me, you want to defeat me
And we
Oh wow…
Have to find a way to leave
It’s time to be old this time
Lone Wolf
Give me a quick leave of the Sparky ’s body
Otherwise…
But don’t blame us for being rude
The opportunity is here
Sparky
What happened
How did I hold me
You don’t remember it?
You were just controlled by Lone Wolf
The light drama was also taken away
Successful, and the light drama is here with me
- Only the one who can handle this help
Hunting Yangyang, please help me untie the skeleton
good
Don’t believe him
Lone Wolf hasn’t woken up yet
So he must be still controlling the Sparky
Almost cheated by you
I’m…really
I want to make a mistake
No I don’t
See you again, lamb
careful…
Weslie
Weslie, you’re fine
What happened?
Ha ha ha ha…
Wake up Luna
You are controlled by dark energy
I’m very awake
Then you still remember…your family
Are you with my sister?
How kind you are
Take care of me when I’m sick
Love every inch of flowers and plants
Rescue me from the darkness
Have you finished speaking
- Levana
You just want to stop me?
It’s over!
Don’t beat it again
Everyone hears the bright moon
Hahahahahahahahaha…
Now I’m the strongest
I’ll catch up first
Give us Lone Wolf
He caught up so quickly
Have it!
OK, go and take it yourself
Just go down and get the sword and don’t want to come up alive
Really desperate
Weslie
Magic Cloud
Everyone, hurry up
you…
Can’t let Weslie goat have something to do
He actually did this in front of the enemy
Do you look down on me?
Lone Wolf, please take it
Don’t hurt them
Weslie…
Hahaha…
Weslie You actually believe in your so-called friends
They just pretended to be false
They’ll be able to relax soon
Stop Lone Wolf
It’s too deep, Hurricane Blade cannot be used
ah…
Very strong, then continue
Why don’t you let go
Because…
We won’t give up our partners
Then let me cut this faint mask
Can’t give up
Everyone pull it hard
Hurricane Blade
Escaped?
Sorry, I’m tired of everyone
What are you talking about
Isn’t this what a good friend should do?
Haha…The light drama is back in our hands
good friend? It’s so ridiculous
Have to go back and think about the solution