Hahaha…
From now on
I’m the strongest person in the entire cat country
Hahaha…
Take them all to the dungeon
I understand, just do what Luna said
Take us to the dungeon
I won’t blame you
But…but…
How did you get the sword?
The lambs have already obtained the sword
They should be on the way to
Why don’t we hide first
Hahaha…
- Luna…
But it’s a story
What are you so afraid of doing
I’m the strongest in the entire cat country now
I won’t leave
The power I have now
Whether it is the storied drama, it’s good
The lamb is also done
As long as you dare to resist me
Just eliminate it
If that statement is true
Your power will no longer exist
Have come to this point
We can’t take risks anymore
Plans cannot be lost
You have to remember
Your goal is not only to be the strongest person in the country
But the whole world
Let’s go
snort!
They’re here
Wolffy…
Disappear Dark Energy
Hi…
Don’t look at his eyes
Use up the slab
Uh, why didn’t you react
I said, is it wrong to have a posture
Makes sense Come again
Disappear Dark Energy
Quantity…quantity…quantity…
It’s hard to tell…
It’s hard not to open the pill yet
Wait for me to polish
You didn’t hit them
look
Wow…
Oops
It turns out that there is nothing to be afraid of about this thing
You’re too careless
Can’t let the light snare fall on their hands
We’re here to help you
Don’t worry, open it for me quickly
You’re fine
Take care of yourself first
Oh…
not good
Thanks
No need to be a guest
Don’t be too excited
Sparky
Paddi
I won’t miss this time
A group of people who are in charge of things
I’ll just scavenge you first
Dad, I want to go back to stop Luna
But… your body…
I’m not afraid
Even if I want to sacrifice my life
I want to save Luna, too
Save the cat country back
This is our home
As long as I have the last breath
You can’t just watch others destroy it
Do nothing
Want… want to do… what do you want to do…
you…
We also want to make some effort to the cat country
I am worthy of being the soldier I teach
Ha ha ha ha…
tomorrow…
Dad, everyone will ask you
But…
I understand I’ll take good care of them
- Thunderbolt
Aqua Spirit
Good opportunity
Gossip
Vague lens
What’s going on? It’s so dark around
Paddi
You’re fine
Almost controlled by Lone Wolf
Fortunately, there are Tibbie and goat
I made him unable to see what was around me for a while
Luna
Give us dark energy
We’ll help you restore it
Don’t think about it!
You can’t beat so many of us
That may not be
ah…
Come together
No, too many
Magic Cloud
Stop, goat
Ha ha ha ha…
Think of a way, Weslie
Can only…stop it first
Everyone… hold on
Depend on how long you can still bear
Why did you stop?
It’s tomorrow
Have you found the sculpture?
While now
Dark energy
Try again
Um
Not good, stop
Hiding here shouldn’t be discovered
I don’t know if they found Weslie
Surely found
Unfortunately, we don’t have any ability
Can’t help at all
There must be hope for life
We need to be happy
What’s there to be happy about
There are endless foods here
There are so many toys
You can also chant and make confrontations
It really should be as good as possible…
Mom, I want to go to the bathroom
Sorry, there is no toilet here
I’m a little anxious, too
It’s time and I’m still joking
Alas I just don’t want everyone to be too depressed
I’m very guilty
I am the king of the country at this time
I don’t have the ability to fight with everyone
The only thing I can do is protect you
Don’t distract them
So everyone must cheer up
Don’t hang your head
We have to trust them
Um
ah…
What are you doing so hard…
I…I don’t know
I’m not afraid, I’ll repair it
Magic Cloud
It’s even more harmful…
Let me come
Will it be necessary to use fire to repair it
How did this happen
What kind of protective cover is installed in this box?
Hahaha…
- Hahaha…
I’d believe this sword is useful
No one can stop us now
Box
tomorrow…
No…don’t…
Oops
Hahahahahahaha…
tomorrow…
Hahaha…ah…
ah…