Be careful, everyone
Don’t inhale dark energy
The dark energy has dissipated
The cat country is about to suffer
Luna takes the next step
Oops
Luna absorbed a lot of dark energy again
If this continues, we can’t stop her
Enjoy the final friendship slowly
Their plans will definitely be bad for the cat country
We must stop them
Um
What’s the matter
Help…
Let’s try who is stronger
Put on the pad again
Hello, you’re fine
Why…you can catch fish
What’s going on
I’ve contracted this fish pond
be mine
mine
This location is mine
Don’t you have eyes? It’s clearly mine?
I’ve said the final word here
Come on, who are you afraid of
Don’t touch my fire pot, it’s mine
be mine
It’s mine
Don’t think about it
Get the water supply
Hand over the water tank
Don’t steal it
- I want to be a soldier
Hand over the position
- Hand over
Why is it so noisy outside
I’ll go out and have a look
What’s wrong with him
It’s hard to say that the dark energy has been dissipated
What do you want
Decide
- Come on
Your opponent is me
The king of the king…
Decide
Mom, I’m afraid…
Are you worried?
It’s me this time
I won’t let you hurt them
Can’t stand it anymore…
Why do they’re almost out of the way
I won’t let you stand up again this time
What to do
You are fine, king
I’m fine
Something must have happened
I’ll go out and have a look
What’s going on
Stop it quickly
careful
It’s Luna
stop
Decide
Thunderbolt
You’re fine
dad
Son
Dad Mom
It’s too dangerous here
You can take everyone to the palace to avoid difficulties
But…
No problem, hand it to us dad
They are all reliable partners
We will definitely restore the cat country to its former state
OK, Dad ordered you
Must be safe
yes
King of the Kingdom, please protect everyone
Um
Come with me
Big Wolf I’ll wait for you to come back
Come on, Dad
Um
Bring the box off
Magic Cloud
Oops
Let me play with you
ah
Paddi
You’re fine
Um
Why did the earthquake suddenly
Earth…Is the earthquake?
What’s up
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Run quickly…
What happened to this earthquake
No…not just an earthquake
You see
Lianyunduo’s movement speed has increased
Can’t we go back in time?
It’s not that Yunduo’s movement speed has become faster
But…
It’s Luna in the mobile cat country
- what?
What exactly does she want to do
Lone Wolf said before
Their purpose is to bring out the dark energy
It’s hard to tell…
She wants to use the cat country to break the boundary
Let the entire cat country move to the green grassland?
This is not a way to go on
We’re going to take the initiative to hit
Um
Everyone…be ready to try it out
good
Be careful not to touch dark energy
What’s going on?
Feeling full of strength
And it keeps coming from the body
Um? My arms turned into rocks
It’s hard to say…
This feels… amazing
Be careful not to touch dark energy
Paddi
Magic Cloud
Everyone comes
A group of guys who are overestimating their abilities
Hurricane Blade
Thunderbolt
You’re too slow
- Flame Fist
You can use any moves
Luna, sister will save you
Let me go…
It’s the dark energy that controls you
Sober up
ah…
Levana’s Princess…
My plan cannot be broken
Flame Fist
ah…
Sparky
Hurricane Blade
Thunderbolt
Magic Cloud
Aqua Spirit
What’s going on, our attacks have been taken down
In the past, I could only control people with my eyes
With dark energy
I can absorb everything with my eyes
The ability to obtain all things
I’m all things I’m the world
ah? Did he absorb dark energy?
ah…
He’s become so strong…
Hao…yue…
I won
The world will fall into darkness
Why…you are hit by dark energy
Isn’t it controlled by dark energy?
control?
Hohoho…
My heart has long been numb
Even dark energy can’t move me
Hahaha…
No matter what, we must stop you
Humph, it’s too annoying
Luna…
What’s going on
Our plan…has been successful
Dad, look…