You go first
I’m walking slower, please pass first
Don’t worry, don’t worry, you go first
You’ll be the first
Friends walk together for life
There have been
We are… the three brothers in the grassland
Why is he so slow? The tea is almost over
Who knows
Huh? Why is it getting dark?
Ah…ah…
You let me come first
If you walk slowly, let others leave first
I’m the boss, you have to hear me
I’m the boss
I’m
I’m the strongest
Yangguoguo What’s wrong with you
It’s all your fault. You’re really sorry…
This is…what happened
Hello Run
What’s going on
not good
The dark energy has dissipated
ah
ah…
Ah, sister…
Ah, no!
If this continues, Yang Village will be terrible
ah
More people will be affected if that is the case
What should I do now
Great, the mission was finally completed
It turns out your purpose
It disperses dark energy into the green grassland
snort! This is just the first step in the plan
Big Wolf, don’t you think anything happened to me…
Is there any way to do it
Let Levana and Luna hurt each other again
Children…
Princess Luna…
I won’t play with you anymore
Let me take a good look at the world
Sister, wake up
Am I the strongest person on this land now?
Before this land was destroyed
You should be the strongest
You…what do you mean
Catch him for me
Good, give you a crown
You are the strongest
You just want to use me to move the cat country out
Um? Guessed correctly
It doesn’t seem too stupid
younger sister…
I don’t have time to spend with you
Can’t let Lone Wolf leave this
Don’t want to run
Don’t chase after you
There are so many things to do
I’m the strongest
stop
Luna, look
Do you still remember this
Good luck never come
danger…
This is a kid
Your sister risked the danger to help you find the doll you came back
Remember it soon
We were still young at that time…
Fish wandering
Luna, wait for me
ah…
Luna What’s wrong with you
Who bullies you, I’ll help you
Why are there so many wild grasses…
I woke them up accidentally
The doll was taken away by them
Don’t be afraid, I’ll help you get it back
Sister, it’s too dangerous
I don’t want it anymore
If only my body is better
The moon gives you
This is the seven-color flower
Just let it open seven colored petals
You can realize your wish
Really
Yes, let’s try it
Levana’s Princess
The princess wants to get the fish doll herself
Princess…
Fulai, you go first with the fish doll
I can’t let you go
This is my order. Go quickly
Fulai… Fulai
Why are you still here?
I can’t just leave the princess alone
Thank you for your blessing
Finally took the doll back
Why did you come by yourself
You are not saying that you have produced seven-color flowers
Can Luna recover the fish doll?
That’s what I wrote blindly
I’m afraid that Luna will worry
Please, please keep this secret
After the bright moon emerges from the seven-colored flowers
We can… help her realize her desire
Wow, fish doll
Sister, please see
It’s a risk tomorrow
Go and help you find the fish doll
Instead of the Seven Color Flowers help you find it
Fish wandering
Sister, wait for me
Hahaha…
Fish dolls…
Ah… sister…
younger sister
You… have you been awake
Luna What’s wrong with you
Luna
Don’t be afraid, sister helps you
But tomorrow, Princess, you’ll be injured, too
It’s okay…I can
Luna will definitely wake up
younger sister…
Lone Wolf, don’t run away
Be careful
Don’t let me go
That’s to ask me to take action
Vague lens
District fantasy
what…
Hurricane Blade
Flame Fist
Magic Cloud
Thunderbolt
Aqua Spirit
You can’t win me
Be careful he can absorb our power
And… for you…
Help…
Hunting Goat, catch me…
Catch tight…
ah…
Hold me
Wolffy…
careful!
Paddi…