This place has been our goat clan since ancient times
Nonsense
It’s from our wolf clan
My newly invented multi-functional gun is really easy to use
Hahaha…
Ah…Magic Cloud
A goat?
I finally returned to the green grassland
Paddi
Master, that’s great. I see you…
Functional switching
Look at my invincible ice pot
Master, what happened to you
Master, I’m a slept with goat
You dare to suppress me
ah…
Depend on where you run
How come it is you
Come with me
I’ve fought with you…
Return the Paddi back…
To save the goat…
Aqua Spirit
Flame Fist
Thunderbolt
Don’t worry about him first
Go back to Qingqing Grassland to find the Paddis to be tight
I wanted to leave after the fight, it wasn’t that easy
not good…
A group of guys who are overestimating their abilities
See you again
Levana’s Princess…
Then let’s clean up you first
ah…
younger sister…
Don’t hurt her
You still have the strength to resist the invasion of dark energy
But everything is over
Strange, why didn’t you see anyone
You…
Duojiu goat saved us
It’s too dangerous outside
Unexpectedly, the green grassland became like this
That time the sky appeared…
Many strange stones
Everyone was hit
Afterwards, they seemed to be poisoned
Becoming irritable
Fortunately, I escaped
I saw them being chased later
I’ll save them all
We hid and were not poisoned
It’s dark energy
Dark energy?
It makes everyone very ambitious
Right
Why didn’t you see Weslie and the others with you
Weslie and the others are still in the Catland
I must go back to find them
Although I don’t know what happened
But I will definitely help you
It was just to save me…
Just a little bit of a bad accident
I know where there is medicine, I’ll get it
What does he want to do?
He is absorbing the power of the shadow
It’s not bad, Weslie
I didn’t expect that I could still absorb shadows
Hey…
You are so important to you
Let’s be together forever
Hahaha…
ah…
younger sister…
Don’t come
Isn’t Princess Luna okay?
My sister really wants to take control
But there was always dark energy in her body
Sister, don’t come
I’ll hurt you
I’ll go find my sister
See if you can break the black cover
younger sister
It’s okay to have a goat…
It’s definitely nothing
We must go out quickly
Only then can you find the goat
Flame Fist
Hurricane Blade
Aqua Spirit
Thunderbolt
Open it for me…
Let me… open…
dad
Wolffy
- dad
Red and small gray
Dad, I’m scared
Don’t be afraid of Wilie
As long as there is a dad here
I’ll always protect you and your mother
Mr. Slowy…
Mr. Slowy, Yuyangyang…
We didn’t protect the goat
We shouldn’t give up like that
The Paddi have great protection
Maybe it’s okay
Yes, don’t give up
Um
The pharmacy is here
I’ll definitely go up and find yours
I didn’t see it wrong. It’s really you
Magic Cloud
You have invented it too
Then let’s see who’s more powerful
Let’s take a look at my burning splash this time
Burning bullet?
Ah… Master, don’t…
This time it depends on where you run
ah…
Magic Cloud
Or is my invention more harmful
Paddi…
Oh…my cake…
What can you do if you don’t have us in the future
No, I must go back to find everyone
Hehehehehe…
pity…
You can’t even get out of this door today
Yes
My baby will be stolen
Magic Cloud
Wow…
I’ll definitely go up and find yours