Weslie
I’m here to save you...
ah…
What are you doing
I...I want to go up to the cat country to save people
Um…
Paddi
Let me come and give you a ride now
The sword goat in front of the goat...
Come quickly
ah…
Go, goat
It depends on you next
Alas, I must save them
ah
ha
ah…
Huh... Fortunately, there is a curious help
OK, you must wait for me
Very tired
Um? Finally came up
Um? Something is moving under the butt...
What a coincidence, it’s you again
Have you eaten?
Don’t hold the tail
Looks like you’re so tired
I’ll cook noodles for you
Ah...Help...
This is another move
Do you have any new ideas?
Have it
Magic Cloudd...
Look at mine
Ah...Oh
Ah...Help...
Um?
It turns out that the strange beasts are also eaten
There is less oxygen
You save some physical strength
Red and small gray
Village chief…
Delayed oxygen
Everyone will be in danger
Don’t be afraid, there will be a way out.
What should I do
Why don’t we try to concentrate on attacking one point
Maybe this will break it
Try it quickly
good
Oxygen consumption is getting faster and faster
Everyone hold on
I’ll help, too
Levana’s Princess...
Don’t give up, everyone
good
Fortunately I didn’t catch up
You let it open
I must have caught the enemy first
I’m even more harmful
Huh? Why did they fight by themselves
- You’ll stand me
Let it open
careful!
Old grandma, you’re fine
I’ll help you go
Thank you little boy
This is what I should do
Oh, I’m about to die at work
Then grandma, go to work quickly
I’m leaving, too
Hehe...Goat goat
Have you caught it by me
The lone wolf man
I’ve caught someone
You’re a soldier
Oops
He is mine
Don’t run
stop
You let me open it
snort! You can’t escape
Oh
He flew there
Where is this?
I was actually shot to the station
I’ll definitely defeat the lonely wolf
Rescue you
Ah hahahahaha...
Oh, don’t follow me
I first discovered that he was running in this direction
After chasing...
Why didn’t it go wrong?
I saw a figure running over
I think you’re dazzled
How dare you kill me
It must be nearby
He couldn’t go anywhere even after the train was stopped
Difficult to be in the car?
In the car?
The train... is stopped...
How to do it...
Have it
He’s there
Found
Excuse me
Let me catch him
You are mine
stop
It’s all your fault that he lets him run away again
It’s obviously your mistake
snort! Everyone finds their own, don’t disturb me
Back to the original starting point
Train stops How should I get on?
There is a way
Weslie I’m here to save you
Left left
Right right
Rush...
I’m going to bump into it
ah…
Be careful...
You... are going to wait for me... to save you out...
The class leader…
Sorry I’m a little bit...
Sparky ...
I... can’t hold on...
Why can’t you break after so long
Everyone is working hard
Keep going like this...
tomorrow…
Wolffy...
You wake up and can’t sleep
Everyone…
Hahaha…
We... will definitely... be fine...