I’m sorry, let’s make it...
Good, continue to fight
Sorry, let it go
Paddi...
Lone Wolf...
He didn’t catch up?
No matter what, Weslie
I’m here...
Hum, what can I do when I come back
Those people in the black cover...
It should be almost finished
ah…
I’m back with the goat
Don’t eat me
What’s going on?
What’s this black?
Palace? Where are you?
Weslie, Sparky , are you there
King of the Kingdom Levana you have heard...
Let me smash it open
Why can’t you break it...
What’s there in the flash...
Weslie
This is...
Everyone, there is a light here...
Everyone’s power was almost sucked by the black cover
Speaking of what is this spot?
Hurricane Blade
There is a reaction
Everyone…
After the return of the goat
I always have a bad feeling
Go and have a look
Become stronger
Weslie...
Sparky ...
Is it you? The Goat...
Weslie...
I can’t see you, but I feel it
I can also feel it. Everyone wake up...
Paddi...
Goat...goat...
Weslie, it must be Weslie
But why is there no light?
Weslie, you’re fine
Lone Wolf
Paddi
It’s you. You made this dark thing
Do I need to answer you?
I knew it was opened quickly
I want to save my friend
Ridiculous friends do you think they will be grateful to you?
Don’t waste it
Your companions are almost out of reach
Nonsense, they just responded to me
Hahahaha…response?
Weslie...
Useless, you’re the only one left
But you ask me for your words
I can consider letting you go
Me and my friends
You won’t be easily beaten
Friends... Friends do not exist
Weslie Weslie...
Paddi...
Everyone... Get up quickly... The goat are waiting for us...
No...no more...
Paddi...
You’re too weak
It’s impossible to win me
Happy... Weslie...
Paddi...
I believe you are here and respond to me
We are all here...
Weslie I’m here...
What’s going on
Paddi
Weslie Weslie
Goat
This...what is going on
What happened? How could there be such a reaction
I’ll come if I have something to do
Don’t hurt the goat
He is fighting Lone Wolf himself
We just lay here...
Move, Big Grey Wolf...
The goat...need us...
I’ve said it
How could it be...
My friends and you can’t easily defeat me
I...I’m very concerned about your current expression
Everyone is still waiting for me
What are you and what friends
All are not true, so wake up
Why are you so resistant to friends
You can’t tell
Don’t have a friend who can trust each other?
Close mouth Close mouth…
You’ve always believed in friendship
That’s because you’re still living in dreams
Dream...is the right
You’re wrong
Paddi...
Well…
He is there...
How can we lie down
He will be fine if he is in trouble
From the Qihua Town to this place
He is no longer the same as before.
He’ll be fine
Because he must be waiting for us
Of course
Wake up
Ah...I’m dead
Why am I still dead
Another trouble
Miscellaneous Are you here to help me?
Did you help me
Strange
Everyone…
Don’t run
Little mouse, don’t worry
Don’t mess with the beast in the future
It’s too difficult
Come back to me
Oops it hurts...
Miracle After the matter is over
I will definitely give you a bunch of husky
Don’t bother me
Everyone…
Wolffy
The goat...and...and waiting for us...
Everyone...I’m here
Feeling it
Weslie, Tibbie, Sparky
This time I can see you
Paddi...
The black cover... disappeared
You’re fine
It’s OK
This time I have been using the Paddi
Hehehehe...
It must be the power of our friendship that made the black shield disappear
Friendship…
You’re really too annoying...