Let’s go quickly. Many people in the Qingqing Grassland have been turned into evil
Even the master was turned evil
what…
A vulnerable guy
It’s you
All disappear
I’m the most darning person to deceive me
Is this only level?
Shock!
ah…
younger sister
Luna…
Since you keep the dark energy, it’s useless
Why not give it to me all
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
whee…
Let my sister go
Sister, wake up
You wake up
Wake up quickly...
Hahahahahahahahaha...
Now...you can’t stop me
stop
I’m...no one can win now
You are like my sister
I won’t let you go
Do you have only this ability?
Can he actually use my power?
No!
Disappear
Magic Cloud
ah…
tomorrow
tomorrow…
No, he uses dark energy
Absorb all the power of the world
Don’t want to hurt them again
Give me aside, you can’t stop me
We... don’t give up...
Then let’s play something more interesting
Paddi...
Come and hurt each other
No, Lone Wolf controls the goat
Spread quickly
You’re fine
Let’s have fun together
not good
Don’t try to escape
It won’t let you escape
Careless
not good
Must find the body of Lone Wolf
Only then can the goat wake up
But how can we catch up with the miracle
Use a blanket
Desert horns will help you find the direction of the strange beasts
We’re out first
- You must come back safely
It’s there
Let me open my body
Magic Cloud
Stop it
This will scare it
It didn’t run away...but it was...
ah…
Stop and don’t run
Don’t run away, right?
So...we are more harmful than seeing who Qili
ah…
Stop shouting, no one will come to save you
Hurricane Blade
Hello... are you... here to stop me from fighting?
It’s amazing to have too many people
I’m not afraid of you
You give me a look
Thank you for saving me
OK Now it’s safe
You go home with all your might
Now there are all blackened villagers
I’m nowhere to go
How about it...
Don’t cry... Don’t cry Weslie...
Yes, we’ll send you to a safe place
Desert Grim, go find the magical beast first
This is not easy to be discovered
Yes, thank you so much, you should be careful too
But before the cat country resumes
You still have to be careful not to be discovered
snort! I’m so frustrated and still love so much
- what
-Aren’t these all good things you did?
There is this space
It’s better to get my body back
You have made the world like this
Still thinking about myself
You are indeed a cold-blooded guy with no feelings
emotion?
Ha ha ha ha…
Feelings are the most fortunate thing in the world
Lone Wolf...
You don’t have to say this in the way of a goat
Friendship
Or...I haven’t changed back now
Give up the goat and save the whole world
what
Come on... choose... to save the goat
Or save the world
Choose quickly
What a joke
We will save both the goat and the world
That’s right, none of us will give up
A bunch of innocent guys...
Let’s stop talking to him. Go and look for it
Um
Mom...
When will Sister Luna wake up?
Wilie, this mother doesn’t know either
It should be Weslie and they are back
You are...
I want to compare with the king of the country. See who is more harmful
A stingy gangster
Fulai Cold and quiet
Can’t let them fight until tomorrow
Can you try to compete with me
But there are very strict conditions
Guardians
What are the conditions you tell them
Guardian military officer? I?
Conditions for competing with the king of kings
True or fake?
That’s right. Only the most outstanding cats of the strange cats
Only by competing with the king of kings
Isn’t this me?
What is you
I can, too
Do it
Compare with whom
I’ve been snatched
I’ve been beaten, hahaha...
Hand over the crown
Hehehehehe...
Do beautifully Slowy
The king has won the prize
Hahahahahahaha...
Desert Eagle found the miracle
Is it there?
That’s not... the direction of the Thunder Valley?
Must change back to your body first
Let’s go quickly...
Why don’t you see Lone Wolf?
Not good if Lone Wolf is regained
The goat will be in danger
Chase quickly
Finally found
Magic Cloud
Oh...
Strange where did my body go
It turns out there
Lone Wolf, don’t try to escape
Only shoes...whether of my body?