My shoes are found here
That should be nearby
Nearby…It’s hard to find the Thunder Valley
Thunder Valley is too dangerous
But there are no other traces now
We can only go in and look for it
But…
It’s okay I’m familiar with the valley
My Lightning Strikees were obtained from this thunderbolt valley
I’m the most familiar here, let me find it
How could you go alone
Don’t worry
Wolffy
What do you want to do me
It won’t let you in
You’re always rude
What should I do if I hurt my body?
Ha ha ha ha…
Don’t want to go in. The lonely wolf
Can’t find it anywhere. What should I do
Can’t beat
Hey
ha
hey-hey
Perfect
Come on, this time it’s...
Left
Right
Ah What...
Oops...
Just worry you want to trap me
Hurricane Blade
ah…
Tibbie, you’re fine
I’m fine
Huh...it’s going to be something now
Magic Cloud
This...what is going on
Sure enough, it’s still the body of the goat
It seems that it was just a lot of attacks
Too much energy consumed
Magic power has also become weak
I’ll save you some energy
You... don’t underestimate me...
Take the call
Oops, the lone wolf ran in
Let’s chase
call…
If you run here, you shouldn’t be able to catch up
But why can’t I resist fatigue with such a broken body?
I can’t use the power of the genius for a while, but I can’t run away.
It’s hard to call the goat
ah
The lone wolf
You...you’re fine
Don’t run away again
The current goat must be hungry and suckling
If this continues
You can’t stand it
This body is useless
what! You dare to say it’s useless to take goat
But you usually say this
Uh-huh
I’m different, I’m so picky
Do you want to eat a bun?
No matter how you say your body is also a goat
We won’t let him get hungry
The lone wolf
Since I took our buns
You promised us not to run away again
Let us find your body with you
I want to find it myself
Don’t run
Levana is coming!
Levana, you’re fine
Levana, I will send you great power to Luna
It should be very weak now
I...I can...
I must wake up my sister...
elder sister…
Sister...you stop
Luna woke up
Where is this
Wilie, you step back a little
She will attack us
oops
Small gray
careful
Thank you Sister Luna
Luna I can’t tell you’ve regained your understanding
So how do you feel now
I…
Grudge...
I feel a little bit intensive
The dark energy disappeared
How did this happen
It’s hard to say...
It must have been sucked out at that time
That’s Luna...
It’s nothing
Don’t run
Wolffy
Hahaha…
Very tired
This body quality is too poor
Don’t run away
Big Wolf, you’re fine
Your legs...
It’s nothing, it’s just being pressed...
Hum, I didn’t find my body
you…
Don’t mind him
Sorry, I was too confident before
Let’s find it together
Lonely...heart...wolf...
None here
None here either
This place is so big when should I find it
Lonely...heart...wolf...
Come out for me...
I’ll look for it there again
I’ll accompany you
Don’t have any trouble
Hum, this stupid trust
You will regret it after helping me get my body back
Come again...
Everyone should be careful of the rocks that are rolling down
Well...yes
Haven’t you found the mountain top?
Weslie, be careful of flashing
Have you found Weslie?
I’ll go up and take a look
No, your legs are injured, I’ll go
Hello…
I found...
In the nest of the miracle
Fortunately, there is no miracle guarding
My body...
Hahaha…
Ha ha ha ha…
Ah hahahahaha...
I feel so disgusting
Use Magic Cloud to help them come down
Paddi...
Where is this
Why are you looking at me like this
What do you want to do
Great, you finally came back
Who can tell me what happened
And the back of the brain hurts so much
That’s it...
Is the group fun
Thunder Valley...then...
Let’s play with thunder
Ha ha ha ha…
The group gets very happy, kids
We’re here
Too late
ah…
Wolffy
Everyone pulls up
OK let me see how long you can last
Wow...
Does it hurt
Just let go
All friendships are fake
No...let go...
we…
How...
possible…
Let go...abandon... companion...
Death piercing
What is this
Haha No matter what that is
You’re going to disappear today
What’s the matter
It’s because of this...
It’s because of you
Care about this ridiculous companion and friendship
It will be defeated for me
Disappear
Wow...