Not overestimating one’s ability
No matter what you say
No fight to the end
We won’t give up
So, let’s start to eliminate it from you
Weslie
Weslie Are you OK
Yes, thank you
Be careful above
Go quickly
We will be friends in the future. I’ll send it to you
Weslie Your hand…
It’s nothing, it’s just a minor injury
Why…you want to save him
Wouldn’t it be fine if he escaped by himself?
Of course I’m going to save
Between friends
It was originally just support and rely on each other
Support and rely on
Do you still need these with strength?
That’s you don’t understand
Hum, let me tell you a story…
How can I spend the winter with so little food
Alas, tighten your waistband, let’s live
What are we here to do
Let’s have a meal today
Wait, where is the key
I took it secretly
Wow…
Xiaohao, come and eat, too
This is not good. This is everyone’s food…
So what if we eat a little
I heard the thunder sound
Look, it’s a fish can
We have meat to eat
Help me take the keys and I go up and get it
Be careful
ah…
Oops, what about Xiao Chao
Xiao Chao…I’ll save you here
Can’t pull it out…
What’s going on? Such a silence
Little… Xiaohao…
Xiaohao…ah…
-Oh, too selfish
- It’s really him doing
- So selfish…
What…what…
No…not me
When we came, you were the only one.
The key is in your hands too
Duo Ni Xiaohao told us you are there
Yes, let’s catch you right
Not me, you know
You explain it to everyone
I…
I…I don’t know
Thieves, I don’t want to hear you cunning anymore
You hurt us all
Mom, are we going to have a stomachache?
It won’t be, my mother will find you something to eat
Traitor of the Wolf Clan
traitor
- Traitor
traitor…
Insult
The Wolf Clan’s Incest
Why is this for me… Xiaohao…
There’s even a face coming out
snort…
We didn’t have food to steal it for him
Such a bad wolf should have left the village
Leave here we can’t afford to eat wolves
Leave here
- Leave
Xiao Chao
You heard me explain…
actually…
Wait a minute…
Don’t touch me
So the friendship you talk about is the same
It’s just something that’s dirty
When facing the hope, I can give up at any time
The story is that…
This is different
We won’t give up our friends
oh? Yes?
Then let’s take a look…
Your friends
Can you rely on it until the last moment
ah…
Not finished yet
Tibbie
Where to look
Be careful, Weslie
And I’ll give you…
That’s right
Jonie…
Worry about yourself
Lone Wolf
All will disappear to me
In fact
Your strength is only at this level
This strange flow…
It turns out to be like this…
Small tricks of carving
Tibbie
Just want to trap me even if I miss this illusion
This is…
Not bad, a little bit different…
Hahahaha… Interesting
If you think this level can defeat me
Then let’s try it
He’s here, everyone be careful
Delay a little longer, please feel free to everyone
Leave it to us
Aqua Spirit
Don’t understand yet
Your friendships are in the absolute power of
It’s nothing at all
Just take down others and run away
Don’t you still have a chance to survive?
Thunderbolt…
Indecent slap
It’s because we’re weak
I need help from friends
Just hold your friend’s hands tightly
Even if you fall, you can stand up countless times
Stupid
Just now
That’s right…
Support each other…
Unconditional trust…
This…is…
Our friends…
Our strength…
ah…
We…have we succeeded?
Magic Cloud
I…we fell back to the green grassland
Yes, I’ll beat Lone Wolf
Everyone who turned evil must have recovered
careful
It’s red
You see
What you mean is that my bread is not delicious
Can be a baseball bat, what do you think
I’ll fight you
I am the king of the grassland…
What are the villagers on the grassland
Haven’t recovered yet
It’s hard to tell…
Hahahahahahahahaha…
I really think you’re experiencing that little power
You can knock me down
Lone…Wolf…
Since I’ve had such fun
Then don’t let it stop
What…what…
The villagers here heard it to me
Who catches this goat first
I’ll divide the dark energy to him
Give him no power
what
Is there no power?
I’m here
That’s mine
That’s the problem…
ah
Can you protect him as exhausted?
How to do it
Our Magic power has not recovered yet
Don’t be afraid, there are brothers and sisters here
Run into the forest
Hide, don’t come out
Even if you have the last breath
I can’t let them pass
I won’t let you pass
Everyone, be a little sober
Can drag for one second, one second
Hahahaha… I can’t hold it back
It won’t take long for the blackened villagers to
You can catch up with that lamb
You can’t save a lamb
What is the power of friendship?
It’s really a bit unhappy
But it’s gone too…
Um?
It’s you… Lone Wolf
Who is it?
Cough cough cough…
It’s been a long time since I saw it, lambs…
oh? Rare guest…
What wind blows you up
This sound is…
The wolf will fight!