"The Guardian of Goat Village Three"
"Saving the Great World"
"The Fall of the Island"
Wolf will fight you too much
Let’s work together to stop him
Um
By the way, do you know him, Wolf,
He finally...
I have sent the lamb back to the goat village just now
You go and evacuate the villagers here
He’ll give it to me
Just hate you
Humph, you’re quite polite
We’re here to help...
Go quickly
But...but...
Go...Goat Village Guardian
Now is the time when villagers need you the most
OK I understand
Let’s go
Um
Thank you, Wolf Corps...
That’s how I want to protect them
Are you helping him?
Hum, I’m in vain, traitor
It’s just right. Let me take you back and thank you for your sins
Stop the lonely wolf
Stop doing wrong things for that person
Hey Hey Hey Hey
Will I start teaching mode if I can’t win?
I was like you, too
Blinded by hatred
I believe that all trust and friends are false
Because of this
We’ll be used
You’re talking...too much
It seems that you have already walked too far on this road
Final chip, second-stage change
Open
Hum, what can I do if I change a color...
Be awake
I’m very awake
Humph
Don’t even stop me
The lone wolf...
You don’t know anything at all
Hum, that’s the end
Why…
Why don’t you just fall down...
Because...I want to protect this
Why do you have to show mercy
I think you can let it go
Start over
Start over?
Ha ha ha ha…
Regret for your kindness
This is...
What happened
This feeling of weightlessness…
Qi... Qicao Country... is going down
what
ah…
Alas...
Ahhhh…
- ah…
Everyone, run to empty places quickly!
Ahhhhh…
It...it...
It’s coming down...
Run!
Protect everyone quickly
ah…
Magic Cloud
It’s okay
Um
Ahhhhh…
Everyone, please leave here
Hahahahahahaha...
I’m going to wipe out all these foolish people
You just run away as much as possible
Hahahahahahaha...
ah…
This is not a way to go on
We can’t just defend
I need to try to stop the cat from colliding.
You see
The Wolf Corps...
Just want to live in the entire cat country alone
Hahahahahahaha...
The Wolf Corps...we also need to help
I also remember we were in the Thunder Valley
Is the magical power that is stimulated together?
It may not be possible
Then let’s start now
But the villagers...
Leave it to me
Strange... cloud... change...
Well…
Paddi...
Everyone is in a hurry
Um
Ha, do you think this will stop me?
Success
ah…
This is...
Worked
Not enough yet
Paddi
You’re fine
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Two-man guy
All will disappear to me
The Wolf Corps...
No, no Magic power is enough
For...why...
Because...I believe you...
The Wolf Corps...
Hahahaha...see
This is the one you want to protect
Said such a beautiful word
Come to the head...
Your desperate efforts only touched yourself
Hahahahahahaha...
Let me open quickly... let me open
I’m going to go down and help
Cold and quiet
We’ll only get into trouble now
But this is what happens again
Everyone will be destroyed
Let’s go
Slowy said it right
We can’t do nothing here
but…
You two...
Dad, I know you’re worried about us
Go
But you have to answer me...
Must come back safely
Um
No...
The Cat Country is getting closer and closer...
Is it time to stop in Yang Village?
Can’t give up
The lone wolf
Let us... let you see...
The power of trust