It seems that the wall is getting slower
Come and see everyone
Children
Wolffy
This is...
Slow down...
Everyone hold on
We can stop him
good
The light column...is being invaded by dark energy
I’m almost out of reach...
Oops, the light has become weak
Hahaha…
Just a few of you want to stop me
It’s just a waste of energy
Big bad egg
You may not hurt your brothers and sisters
He is...the lamb who was rescued by the wolf just now...
Why do you want to come back
Are you not afraid of me?
You are not allowed to destroy the green grassland
Just because you are a little bit too want to disturb me
No!
It’s tomorrow, Luna
You’re so childish
Why do you have to go back and forth
Do this kind of thing that lets you down
Do you think this is amazing?
You’re fine
Um
Not naive
Not because it’s so great
But because we all want to protect this
I want to protect this too
Hahaha…
You don’t have this little devil
What can you do
We won’t lose
Does this lamb have Qili?
This...this is...
This is hard to tell everyone’s heart
Is there any power of light?
There are only three more people
This is how proud
It’s over... The end of the green grassland has arrived...
Is there no hope?
It’s not the time to give up now
This is the voice of the king of the king
Everyone hears me
There are nine warriors on the grassland now
Working hard for everyone
They are brave and kind, not afraid of darkness
I hope everyone can do their best to do their part.
Although we all have very little power
But with thousands of meager power
When gathering together
Can fight against the dark
Everyone...please hold your hands
Borrow your power of light to the Warriors
This time we came to protect them
yes
This...this is our power of light
This is... everyone’s power
What a warm power
What’s going on
Why is there so much power
What a huge drama...
The dark energy surrounding the Catland...eliminates...
Sure enough, it’s OK
Real light drama
It requires everyone’s strength to summon it
The king of that year
It must be to report the people who have helped them
So seal the dark energy in the cat country
It’s just not to let dark energy
Influenced elsewhere
It’s obviously a group of people
Why can this be done
Dark energy can no longer stop us
Stop it
I can’t look back
It turned myself into
Complete dark energy
Quickly use optical drama
- Just hand it over to us to end all this
come on!
Hold on!
It can be done!
We will definitely fight for the darkness!
This is the power of trust!
Is this the power of trust?
There is a little difference from the world I have always known
So warm...
Isn’t this Lone Wolf’s sacred story
Let me see
Can’t open...
Please let me represent all residents of Cat Country
Zheng Zhong said thank you to you
Thank you for saving us and our home
That’s right
Fortunately, you started
Just be willing to believe me and help me
Only the strange cat country can get out of the darkness
There is power for everyone
Only then can we fight this difficulty
I will never forget everyone
Wait until the cat country recovers
Welcome to come and play
OK
Hello, let me go
A Xin, don’t get hurt again
It’s been a year...
Have a little bit of it...
Open it for me quickly. Alas...
That’s it
Finally, with the joint efforts of all residents of the Cat Country
The Cat Country also returned to its original place with them
- See you again
- Everyone should take care of themselves
Everyone is looking forward to the light and trust each other
We have protected this world together
This adventure finally welcomed the final chapter
The sunlight here is so good
I hope Lone Wolf will like this
Ah, finally came up...
Why are there wolves there...
Hello
Hello, my name is Weslie
Please ask you are...
My name is Ahao
It’s Xiaochao...a friend of once
Xiao Chao? Does it mean Lone Wolf?
Thank you very much
Find a beautiful place for him
The villagers must be very opposed
ah? Then you are that one
Is the little hero who caused Lone Wolf to be misled by the clan members?
Will you say anything, 李六国
That’s right. I...I’m that evil wolf...
We used to be...
Happy birthday to Xiaochao
Wow! Watch! So beautiful!
This is what I did by hand
It needs to be opened in a special way
Turn left and right
Wow...
Huh? Why don’t the fingers move?
Hey... this... I won’t do it...
thank you!
This is the best gift I received!
When things happened...
I want to go out to find the villagers and help me rescue Xiaochao
But I didn’t expect
The villagers burst into thunder when they see a group of trash in the village
Scratched
And I chose to escape because I was afraid
I want to explain it to Xiaochao, but...
It’s already too bad
In order to get his original meaning
I embarked on a journey to find him alone
But how many years have passed
He can’t find his image
Until everyone is in
A foul wolf carrying a belt was wiped out
I just found this
He must hate me very much
I think he will instruct you
Just like Lone Wolf said
Everyone has shortcomings
But as long as we find it
Face it Change it
Then won’t we be better?
And you already know you’re wrong
Confess the truth
The reason why he represents your friendship is the symbol of
Keep it on your body
I must also hope you can let go
Start over
Let go of the past and start again...
Is this really the case? Xiao Chao...
Uncle Hao, let’s go back first
Is it really okay for us to leave like this?
Just let him stay for a while
This is for you
Wow! It’s a watch! So beautiful!
Haha, this is something I did by hand
It needs to be opened in a special way
Turn left and right
Why don’t the fingers move?
Hey... this... I won’t do it...
thank you!
This is the best gift I received!
Xiao Chao…
sorry…