A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Nice to Meet You
Let’s play a game, okay?
Okay!
You must go to Green Green Grassland and find your big brother,
giving this Cube to him.
We couldn’t complete it.
It’s up to you now.
Are you ready?
I know we came prepared,
but I never thought it’d be this messy.
I mean, it’s better than my room is.
Anyone comparable to you in that area is no typical goat.
I stayed up too late doing homework,
and I ended up falling asleep.
But today is the day that my parents are coming home,
so I was hoping you guys could help me tidy up.
No problem.
We’ll be sure to leave the place spotless.
Here we go, then!
Yeah!
Done!
Mom, Dad,
we’re going to meet again very soon.
Let’s go pick them up once I put the books away.
Couldn’t they do a smoother landing?
Now, we have to tidy up again!
Let’s go pick them up.
Mom! Dad!
Dad—
Who… Who are—
Found you!
Weslie!
My big brother!
“Big brother”?
It’s frog for dinner tonight!
Where’s the frog?
There it is!
Come here!
I haven’t had meat in a while.
Time to cook!
Big brother?
Little girl, I’m not your brother.
I’m a girl.
Such a cute lamb!
What’s your name?
My name is BB Goat.
What’s your brother’s name, then?
My brother’s name is “Brother”.
What are your parents’ names?
Daddy is “Daddy”, and Mommy is “Mommy”.
Since she seems to be one of us,
let’s take her back to Goats’ Village and find out whose child she is.
We can ask Mr. Slowy.
Where’s BB Goat?
Over there!
Time to find my brother!
Stop!
Wait for us, BB Goat!
This is perfect!
That’s odd,
I swear I heard BB Goat’s voice just now.
Let’s search that way.
Don’t want to get hurt? Then undo the seal for me.
Otherwise, you’ll be sorry!
Stop!
What are you doing, Wolffy?
I can’t believe you’re bullying a little girl.
Are you okay, BB Goat?
Yeah!
It’s very dangerous for a little girl to run off alone.
Come on, let’s go home.
You’re not going anywhere.
Wolffy?
You may leave,
but that little one may not.
What’s wrong with you, Wolffy?
Stop it.
Let go of me.
Weslie!
Are you okay, Weslie?
What are you doing, Wolffy?
Get off of me!
What in the world is wrong with Wolffy?
Get off!
BB Goat!
Are you okay, BB Goat?
That was fun!
How could you treat a child like that, Wolffy?
You’re a father, you know!
What in the world is wrong with you today?
Such nuisances!
Invention time!
Go away!
Weslie!
Wolffy, you—
What a strong weapon.
Stay away from Wolffy, guys!
Something’s wrong with him!
Are you okay, BB Goat?
Wolffy?
I’m Weslie.
Aren’t… Aren’t we friends?
What… What the—
Nuisances
must be dealt with.
Weslie!
He’s completely gone!
This is a joke, right?
Here’s over there!
How exactly did he dodge that shot?
What’s going on?
I feel like I can’t control my own speed anymore.
My shoes
look different.
Could it be…?
Did he just use the Super Cube’s powers?
Be annihilated along with the Cube, then!
I’m faster now!
Oh no,
I think I’m getting double vision.
Me, too.
Your attacks do nothing against me.
Just give it up, Wolffy!
Over there!
Full power!
Are you guys okay?
What are you guys doing here?
Did…
Did I knock out your memory with that hit or something?
You were chasing and attacking us with a super big weapon just now!
You can’t not remember even a single thing that happened, right?
What are you talking about?
Why would I chase or attack you?
I was just hunting a frog, is all.
I’m starving! What’s taking you so long?
I’ll be right there!
I need to go home to cook.
Let’s chat next time!
BB Goat!
Take her to Goats’ Village for medical attention!
“BB Goat”?
We don’t have her in our records.
So, does that mean she’s from a different village?
That’s possible.
We’ll just have to take care of BB Goat for the time being,
until we find her parents, that is.
Also,
when I touched this weird box,
I remember some kind of energy
coursing through my body.
But after it ended,
nothing’s been happening if I touch the box again.
Daddy told me that this is called the “Super Cube”.
It belongs to BB Goat’s dad, I see.
Give it to me to analyze,
and I’ll see if I can find any clues.
I’ll leave the search for BB Goat’s parents up to you guys.
Great!
By the way,
your parents still haven’t come back yet, Weslie.
They’re probably still busy
and don’t have time to return.
I wonder what BB Goat’s parents
are doing right now.
One day ago
I wonder if Weslie will accept her as his little sister.
I hope he will.
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy