A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
I'm Looking for My Brother
One day ago
I wonder if Weslie will accept her as his little sister.
I hope he will,
but—
Don’t worry,
we’ve gotten King Bacteria under control.
Once we send him to some other galaxy,
we’ll be able to go home and see Weslie.
The refrigeration process is almost finished.
What’s this, Daddy?
Mommy, Daddy, let’s play hide-and-seek!
Turn around and start counting!
Don’t run around. Some places are dangerous!
King Bacteria has entered hibernation.
Let’s head for the Sealing Lseal away the lobby.
They’ll never find me in here!
Let’s begin.
I’ll leave this part to you.
Opening the cell.
Ready for fingerprint enrollment/registering.
Quick, cClose the cell!
Closing it now. Get out of there!
I didn’t realize you would feign sleep.
How naïve of you to think I’d hibernate
when it’s hardly cold in here!
I’ve been waiting for you to come in ide awake this whole time!
Huh?
BB Goat?
What…
Undo it right now!
What’s that, Daddy?
He’s so cute!
Oh no,
the seal has captured BB Goat’s fingerprint!
What?
Come out of there first.
Okay.
Where’d he go?
King Bacteria escaped.
I can’t believe you guys sealed away my powers!
I won’t let this slide!
Follow us, okay?
Where do you think you’re going?
She must have been the one who sealed away my powers, right?
If you hHand that little one over,!
If you and undo the seal for me, I’ll let you go.
Take BB Goat to the escape hatch.
I’m going to get the Super Cube.
Just you?
There’s no time. Trust me.
What are you doing?
Behave yourself!
At this point, I can’t even use the Super Cube anymore.
But even then, he must be stopped.
Senseless/Pointless resistanceJust give up already!
Mommy, where’s Daddy?
BB Goat, sweetie,
I’m going to find Daddy right now.
Later, we’ll all play games together.
Stay here and don’t leave,
okay?
I’ll stay put!
Don’t be too long.
I need to hurry up.
Run!
You have nowhere to run!
Look out!
Lily!
I’m fine.
We’ve been frozen. I guess we’re not escaping.
BB Goat and the Cube are our last hope.
We’re back.
Mommy, Daddy,
why aren’t you getting in?
Listen closely.
Let’s play a new game.
Okay!
Keep this Cube safe, BB Goat.
Go to Green Green Grassland and give it to your big brother.
Got it?
Got it!
Come out!
Green Green Grassland is our hometown.
Destination: Green Green Grassland.
Head there and find your brother.
His name is Weslie.
Huh?
What?
We trust you, Weslie.
BB Goat is all yours now.
I can’t believe she got away!
Present
Mom, Dad, when are you coming home?
Brother Weslie,
when are you taking me to find my brother?
Right now, I’ll—
The inventor of these two things is really talented.
Have you found some clues, Mr. Slowy?
I don’t understand the science behind this at all.
No,
how could the grassland’s greatest inventor concede?
I’ll be sure to solve the riddle behind these two things!
Come help me move them, guys.
Just wait for a bit.
I’ll take you later,
BB Goat.
All done.
Where’s BB Goat?
That’s how powerful my Super Stink Spray is!
Who’s there?
Look out!
Freshener!
Good thing I added the Freshener, too.
It’s you again, mister!
Have we met before?
You played tag with me last time.
How could that be?
I’ve been hunting frogs lately.
When did I—
What are you guys doing here?
Did I knock out your memory with that hit or something?
Am I already having memory problems
at such a young age?
Do you know where my brother is, mister?
I can’t find him.
What’s your brother’s name?
What does he look like?
Just tell me,
and I’m sure I can find him
with my years of goat-hunting experience!
Yay!
I don’t know what my brother’s name is,
but I think he has two eyes,
one mouth,
and two ears.
Who doesn’t look like that?
Is he my brother?
You’re a goat,
so your brother can’t possibly be a monkey,
okay?
Why don’t I just take her to Goats’ Village?
Sweetie, finding your brother is going to be difficult
if you don’t have any information.
Stop right there!
Who are you?
It’s you again, little one!
You’re the little one!
I’m the big, scary, Bacteria
King—
I’m the King around here,
you impostor.
How dare you insult me!
Take this!
My only remaining power after the sealing
is possession invision!
I can enter a dirty body,
and disease-prone bodiesgiving it a sickness,
and thus
possessing them!
Possession complete.
Got you at last!
This “Wolffy” guy is a bit too dirty, isn’t he?
How long has it been since he showered?
I’m a bacterium who likes to be hygienic, you know!
If it weren’t for the fact that I can only possess dirty bodies,
I would never choose someone as dirty as this!
Wolffy?
Over there!
It’s them again!
I can’t let them get close!
When I possess someone,
I can enhance all of their original abilities!
Watch this super invention!
Wolffy’s gone mad again!
Gross!
Watch out, guys!
Still one more standing, huh?
Get it together, Wolffy!
Go be with your friends!
Let’s see just how much you can take!
I can’t take it anymore. What should I do?
Finally, no more goats getting in my way!
I’m defeating bad guys
and protecting Mommy and Daddy!
If you ever have a little brother or sister one day,
will you protect them
like you protect us?
Of course I will!
You’re not going anywhere!
Just you wait!
One of these days, I’ll get that little one
and unseal my powers!
When that happens, you’ll all be meeting your doom!
He was going after BB Goat to unseal his powers, I see.
What “powers”?
I don’t know,
but either way, we can’t let him succeed.
Brother Weslie!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I’m okay. I shouldn’t have ran off.
Promise me that you won’t run off,
and I’ll help you find your brother.
Okay!
Here,
let’s pinky-promise.
Okay!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy