A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
A New Family Member
What an impressive invention.
I must be careful with it.
Grandpa Slowy!
BB Goat!
Come get me!
Grandpa Slowy!
Enough, BB Goat.
No.
I want a hug, Grandpa Slowy!
Hug!
What is it?
BB Goat has been doing nothing but playing for these past few days.
She hasn’t slept at all.
To get a little kid to sleep, you’ll have to lead them into it.
There, there, sweetie. Go to sleep!
Go to sleep, sweetie!
Amazing, Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy hasn’t rested for quite some time
because of the Super Cube.
Why are you sleeping?
Let’s think of our own way to get BB Goat to sleep, then.
Let’s not disturb Mr. Slowy.
Yes!
I’ll wipe the windows, too.
Thank goodness.
What a familiar feeling.
How is he even dirtier than last time?
How is it that I can only possess such unhygienic people
despite being such a hygienic person myself?
I’ll suck it up for the sake of getting my powers back!
I used this workout bar
to get my physique to where it is now!
Here, try it!
Don’t be ashamed.
Give it a try.
I’m not strong enough. I can’t bend it.
Here I come, BB Goat!
Wolffy?
Where are you going?
Weren’t you cleaning Wolf Fortess?
I’m a King, you know!
I can’t believe you want me to do cleaning!
What?
Say that one more time!
You want me to clean?
No way.
I think I’m trembling.
I guess Wolffy really fears this she-wolf.
Never… Never mind.
I don’t want to live in such a dirty place, anyway.
What are you looking at?
Hurry up!
Yes, ma’am!
The way I see it, just let her play until she’s tired,
and she’ll fall asleep naturally.
Let’s play a game, BB Goat!
Okay!
Come and get me!
Don’t run!
I can’t take it anymore.
More!
The way I see it,
just let BB Goat eat until she’s full,
and she’ll fall asleep naturally.
Where’s BB Goat?
Brother Paddi,
is there more?
Leave some for me, won’t you?
That didn’t work either.
She’s still so awake.
Let me hold her for a bit.
Do you like stories, BB Goat?
Yes.
Once upon a time,
there was a very big tree.
On the tree…
BB Goat is getting sleepy!
Then, they—
This story is so boring.
I want to hear “The Black Snow Prince”!
Wolffy, are you done cleaning?
Come on.
See just how much I can do.
Now, take a look at how well I wiped the table.
Very good.
I’m very hygienic, you know!
Are you satisfied now?
Now, I can—
Go clean some other places.
Clean it thoroughly, okay?
Am I the kind of person who does this sort of job?
Once I get my powers back,
I’ll teach you a lesson!
Did you call me?
No…
No, I didn’t.
I’ll start cleaning right away.
Wolf Fortress is huge.
This is going to take forever!
At this rate,
I’ll never get my powers back!
Aha!
All done.
Here we go!
Time to capture BB Goat!
How’s the cleaning going?
Wolffy!
We’re leaving it to you.
BB Goat, just go to sleep.
I don’t want to sleep! I want to play!
I’m not sleepy!
I want to play!
It’s time for bed, Weslie.
No, I’m not sleeping.
I want to play!
Is he acting up again? I’ll handle it.
Daddy!
If you don’t go to bed now,
the little bug is going to bite you!
Here comes the bug!
I…
I caught the bug!
I caught the bug.
She’s asleep.
Finally!
Quiet!
Run!
Wolffy’s been possessed again!
There she is! Hand BB Goat over right now!
Hand BB Goat over!
Take care of BB Goat.
I’ll go knock some sense back into Wolffy.
BB Goat?
Take BB Goat and run, guys!
We’ll slow him down!
That can’t stop me!
No more fooling around!
Wake up, Wolffy!
I’m wide awake!
BB Goat!
I’ll be sure to protect you.
Out of the way!
We’re losing it!
Do
not
give
up!
Get over here! Over here!
Over here!
What the heck?
Move—
I’ll be back!
What am I saying that for?
We’re safe.
Wasn’t I cleaning?
How did I get to laying on the ground outside?
Where am I?
You were possessed by a self-proclaimed “king” just now.
Did I really get possessed?
Luckily, I’m not injured this time.
Wolnie,
I’m back—
The place is spotless,
but why is all of our furniture gone?
Wolnie, where are you?
Where are you?
Wolnie,
are you okay?
I’m okay.
However,
you won’t be!
What… What’s wrong?
I told you to clean the house,
but you threw out absolutely everything!
Wolnie, let me explain!
What a difficult wolf.
I love Mommy, Daddy,
and my brother, Brother Weslie.
I’ll make sure to find your family.
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy