A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Amnesia Crisis
Take the medicine, and you’ll be okay.
Thank you, Doctor.
Next!
Doctor,
help me!
Calm down!
Tell me.
Doctor,
have I developed dementia or something?
Dementia?
Yes.
Lately, I keep forgetting stuff I’ve done.
Good morning, Wolnie!
Wolffy!
What’s wrong, Wolnie?
Look at what you’ve done!
I didn’t do anything.
Why do all of these have your footprints, then?
Bad Daddy!
What’s wrong, Wilie?
You ate my lollipops!
How could that be? I don’t even like them.
Wolffy!
…That’s what’s going on, Doctor.
Alright, alright.
Just calm down. I’ll examine you.
Nothing’s wrong
except for a bit of bacterial infection.
I’ll just prescribe you some antibiotics.
Are you okay, Doctor?
Yeah, yeah.
Alright,
here’s your medicine.
Doctor, I’m over here.
Sorry, I’m nearsighted.
Take the medicine as prescribed.
Thanks.
Where are my glasses?
Recently, there’s been an alien wreaking havoc on the grassland,
known as “King Bacteria”.
A villain with the same name exists in the cosmos.
The King Bacteria of the cosmos possesses extraordinary powers,
causing mass destruction and committing any crime imaginable.
Whether or not it’s the same guy, we need to stay alert.
BB Goat seems to be his target.
Yeah,
and he said something about using her to unseal “powers”.
Unseal powers?
No matter what he’s trying to do,
we must protect BB Goat.
Yes, sir!
Great,
but finding her brother will take some time.
Decide on whose house she’s going to stay at.
I’m going to study the Cube now.
Take care, Mr. Slowy!
The kids are growing up.
They can handle anything.
Stay at my house, BB Goat.
We can exercise together!
You should come to mine instead.
I’ll plant flowers with you!
Come to mine. I’ll study with you!
Come to mine! I have a lot of snacks!
How is she supposed to choose?
You’re right.
I know!
We can build her a secret clubhouse.
That way, we can move in with her and live together!
Yeah!
That way, we can all be with BB Goat!
What a great idea!
Secret clubhouse!
How am I supposed to take this?
The doctor must have given me the wrong thing.
That being said, is it really as simple as me just being infected?
Aha!
Eating the lollipops: complete.
Destroy Wolf Fortress: complete.
It’s actually not too bad, setting aside the thing with BB Goat
to have some of my own fun every now and then.
Isn’t that the grimy, grubby Wolffy?
Perfect,
I can have some fun again!
All done!
Here I go!
All done.
Do mine!
A secret clubhouse should have lots of workout equipment
for health!
It should have lots of plants for freshness!
It should have lots of snacks for a full belly!
It should have lots of books for knowledge!
Do mine!
Are you okay?
That was fun!
I want to do it again!
Again?
That’s too dangerous, though.
Aha!
It’s much safer for you with this slide.
Brother Weslie,
you’re awesome!
Thanks!
Help!
What’s wrong?
Come on, play with me!
Mmm!
Come here!
It’s you?
Where am I?
You were possessed by a self-proclaimed “king” just now.
So…
So I was being possessed!
Darn it, I’ve been caught!
You’re coming with me.
My shift is over at last.
Possession!
Who’s coming with who now?
All done!
BB Goat can live here now!
Do you like it?
Help!
It’s King Bacteria!
Let’s get him!
They’re so reliable!
Tell us what exactly you’re after!
It’s not me!
Behind you!
Why didn’t he possess Wolffy this time?
BB Goat is here, too?
Hand her over, then!
Take BB Goat and run.
I’ll slow him down!
You want to run?
I don’t think so!
Oh no,
the clubhouse!
Get out of here, guys!
Run!
Wolffy!
Hang in there!
Stop!
Stop right there!
Look out!
Doctor, I’m over here.
Sorry, I’m nearsighted.
Oh, yeah!
Weslie, take off his glasses!
Huh?
Dr. Boar
is nearsighted.
Got it!
Hold on tight, Wolffy!
Just you wait!
Come back here!
Wolffy!
Weslie,
we’ve come to help!
Where’s King Bacteria?
Everything’s okay now.
We chased him away.
Let’s get Mr. Boar back up here.
The clubhouse we worked so hard to build is destroyed.
I guess BB Goat will just have to live in my house.
I want to live in Brother Weslie’s house.
Don’t you want to live with me, though?
We can plant flowers together.
No.
I want to live with Brother Weslie.
Why does BB Goat only want to live with Weslie?
Because you guys thought only of yourselves.
Mr. Slowy?
Although you guys built a clubhouse for BB Goat,
you only put in the things that you wanted
and only thought of the things that you liked.
Weslie was the only one who thought about what BB Goat needed,
so of course, she prefers Weslie.
We’re sorry, BB Goat.
We thought only of ourselves,
and we never asked you what you liked.
Can you forgive us?
Let’s go back to Goats’ Village, guys.
You still need to show me how to play with all of those things!
Then let’s have a race to see who gets to Goats’ Village first!
Yeah!
I can’t believe he got away.
What… What in the world happened?
Could it be—
There’s no way.
I wasn’t possessed!
There you are!
Wolnie, let me explain!
I swear I didn’t do any of this, Wolnie!
Wolnie!
How dare you mess with my makeup products!
I won’t let this slide!
So it wasn’t me.
I thought I’d gotten possessed again.
Come help, Wolffy!
Yes, Wolnie!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy