A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
A Helping Heart
It’s so warm out.
I’m so thirsty. I need a drink!
I’ll get you some, Mr. Slowy!
Here, Mr. Slowy.
Your drink.
Rest for a bit, Mr. Slowy.
Thank you, Weslie.
It’s nothing.
Weslie’s incredible.
There, there, I’ll help you—
Here’s your kite.
Someone help me!
What a huge log!
Leave it to—
Thank you, Weslie!
Coming!
Wow,
Weslie is able to help so many people.
If only I had gadgets, too.
Gadgets?
All done!
There’s no way Wolffy will find out
that I’m living above his ceiling.
With such a clean environment,
I’ll surely come up with a way to capture BB Goat.
Oh, come on!
Let me see what Wolffy is up to.
Why is this refrigerator so complicated?
I’m an inventor, yet even I can’t get it fixed.
Why call yourself an “inventor”
when you can’t even fix a refrigerator?
Let’s try using this!
How clumsy. I’ll have to take matters into my own hands.
Fixing a refrigerator isn’t that complicated.
This will do.
All done.
The refrigeration capacity of this thing is awful, though.
It couldn’t even keep my ice cream cold last time.
Come on!
All done!
But the chocolate I stored last time only lasted me two days.
I’ll increase its volume, too.
There we go!
Let me test it out.
I may have overdone it.
Wait,
I could this to capture BB Goat.
No one’s here.
If I get the Super Cube,
I might just get to Weslie’s level!
What are you doing here?
Mr. Slowy?
Oh no, have I been caught?
I…
I was worried that the Super Cube might get stolen,
so I came to check on it.
With this top-tier security system that I invented,
no one will dare to take the Cube under my watch!
I nearly set it off.
Well, I need to go out for some materials now.
It’s been stolen!
Mr. Slowy,
the Super Cube—
Stop worrying about the Cube, okay?
Let’s go, Sparky.
BB Goat, this Cube is very important.
Don’t mess around with it.
What if I “accidentally” get a gadget
when returning the Super Cube to Mr. Slowy?
Awesome!
BB Goat,
give the Super Cube to me, okay?
I’ll help you return it to Mr. Slowy.
If you play with me, I’ll give it to you.
Okay, I’ll play with you!
I can’t take it anymore.
Watch it for me. I’m catching a butterfly!
My hard work paid off!
How am I supposed to get gadgets, though?
I remember that when Weslie got his,
he held a very particular posture.
Perhaps…?
Come on out, my gadgets!
Was…
Was my posture not right?
I’ll try a few more and see.
Come on out, my gadgets!
Come out! Come out!
Nothing’s happening.
Mr. Slowy says to read a lot of books when running into problems.
The answer must be in here somewhere!
I don’t understand it at all.
It’s Paddi’s voice!
Paddi,
don’t worry! I’m coming!
Come on,
do you really need to cry out so loudly when you fall?
Right, Weslie’s here, too.
I guess there’s nothing I can do.
I was picking apples,
but all of a sudden, ice formed right here,
and I slipped.
Ice?
How did a patch of ice form here?
That was me!
Look out!
What… What the…?
Has Wolffy gotten possessed by bacteria again?
Hand over BB Goat right now!
Run! Run!
What a big refrigerator!
There you are!
BB Goat!
Take BB Goat and run.
I’ll slow him down.
No way!
There’s more!
What now?
Just give up already!
Hand over BB Goat!
You’ll have to get past me first!
Bring it on!
Where’d he go?
Now!
I knew it!
See how powerful I am now?
Weslie!
I’m fine.
It’s so cold!
Nope, I’m catching a cold.
He’s stalling!
I’m King Bacteria, you know!
You’ve been fooled once again!
Weslie!
So what if you’re fast?
It’s not like there’s nothing I can do about it!
Look out, guys!
Paddi!
It’s so icy and cool.
Worry about yourself first!
You have nowhere to run!
Sparky!
Brother Sparky!
No one can stop me now!
You’re coming with me!
Brother Sparky!
Why is it
that I can only stand and watch when my friends are hurt?
If only I were more powerful.
If only I were stronger.
I want to protect my friends, too!
What’s happening?
What the…?
Stop!
There’s more!
Are these my gadgets?
I feel warm all over.
Perhaps…?
Why?
It looks like my gadgets can control heat!
Let’s take him down together, Sparky!
Don’t get cocky just yet!
What a nuisance, jumping here and there!
Don’t forget about me!
It’s so hot! I’m burning!
I hate heat!
I’ll be back!
Great job, Sparky!
Where am I?
I feel sore all over after that nap.
Wolffy, you were possessed by bacteria again.
What?
If you were as hygienic as I am,
you’d stop getting possessed.
I guess the security system still needs some work.
Sparky?
Yes, sir!
You may also have gadgets now,
but with bigger powers come bigger responsibilities.
What are your thoughts on this?
I may have my own gadgets now,
but the most important thing
is to have a desire to help others,
no matter how big or small your powers are.
Good.
Sparky, come help!
Coming!
Heat water for me!
Heat my towel!
Heat my food!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy