A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
I Just Want to Play With You
Sparky? Sparky!
Coming, coming.
Sparky!
What’s the hurry?
Hide this.
What the…?
So many toys!
Why do you need them hidden?
It’s a long story.
Just one more piece.
My puzzle!
I’m sorry, Brother Weslie.
I didn’t mean to do it.
She’s still young. I should be the bigger person.
It’s okay.
Go on.
Brother Weslie,
watch me skateboard!
Don’t!
That’s dangerous! Stop it!
That’s not how you play with this toy.
My remote-control car!
That’s not how you play with a ball!
These are my last few toys.
I don’t want her to ruin them.
Don’t worry.
I will guard these treasures of yours!
Thank you!
No,
I must use the most scientific method
to figure out why I failed!
Omnipotent genie of the empty bottle,
please give me your answer!
What does this mean?
Could it be
Wolffy?
Perhaps Wolffy’s new invention
can help me succeed!
With this,
my son won’t strain his eyes anymore while studying!
Next up, I’ll test out the main weapon against King Bacteria,
the omnipotent glue!
Omnipotent glue?
If the bacteria step on this glue,
they won’t be able to move a muscle!
Oops.
I guess I’ll rework it a little more.
It turns out that Wolffy is the reason for my failure.
I must find a stronger body!
Let’s push chairs, Brother Weslie!
Play by yourself.
Let’s draw together.
Draw by yourself.
Let’s clean together!
Clean by yourself.
I’m doing homework, and I’m very busy.
Is that—
That’s my bell!
You can’t play with that!
Let’s play hide-and-seek!
I’m going to get you!
Come get me!
This is so much fun!
Can’t hide now, can you?
This bell is very important.
You can’t play with it.
I want it!
Who should I find?
Such strong claws!
You’re the one!
That was close.
What a strong horn!
He must have great charging power!
Let’s see
just how destructive a rhino’s horn is!
I’m stuck.
Nope,
this one won’t do.
I need to search for more.
Such sharp spines!
Here I come!
Ouch!
It looks like Wolffy wasn’t so bad after all.
Here comes my newly revised omnipotent jelly!
Jelly,
shapeshift!
Cage!
Wall!
Beautiful!
I guess Wolffy might just do.
Mom, Dad,
I’m sorry.
I broke the bell that you guys left me.
Brother Weslie,
I…
I’m sorry.
I don’t need your apology.
No matter if they were toys or a bell,
you ruined them all!
What’s the use in apologizing now?
I just
wanted to play with you.
Wanted to play with me?
Was I a little too much just now?
BB Goat!
I can undo the seal at last!
I’ll get my powers back very soon!
Let her go!
Also, stop possessing Wolffy!
No way!
I’ll need to get the remote control first.
Just give up!
There’s no way you can get close to me.
Stay where you are and wait for me to get my powers back!
I won’t let you get away with this!
No one can stop me now!
Brother Weslie?
You big bad guy,
let go of Brother Weslie!
BB Goat!
Let him go!
Stop it,
or you’ll be sorry!
No!
I won’t let you hurt BB Goat!
My remote control!
You have no remote control.
I’ll be back!
Brother Weslie,
here’s your bell.
I’m sorry,
I shouldn’t have ruined your bell or toys.
I’m sorry, too. I shouldn’t have yelled at you.
Let’s make up, okay?
Are you going to play with me, then?
Yes,
but make sure to take care of toys.
Pinky promise?
I know how to fix the bell!
Brother Weslie, come help me!
Done!
It’s just like new!
Thanks.
Yay!
That’s odd.
What am I doing here?
Sparky? Sparky!
Weslie?
What brings you here?
I’m here to take back my toys.
These are your most precious babies, you know.
Aren’t you afraid that she’ll ruin them?
I promised Brother Weslie that I won’t ruin them.
What’s important is that we play together.
Just wait.
Here you go.
My babies!
Sparky,
you promised me that you’d take good care of them!
I’m sorry,
I didn’t mean to ruin them!
Go, Brother Weslie!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy