A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
The Insect Princess
We still haven’t found any leads on BB Goat’s brother.
Is that Mr. Slowy?
Mr. Slowy,
I thought you were in the laboratory
looking for leads of BB Goat’s brother?
I wanted to bring some everyday items to the laboratory
so I wouldn’t need to run back and forth.
Oh, my back!
It’s fine. I’ll be okay.
We’ll do it, Mr. Slowy.
I’m really sorry. Thank you, though.
Could you guys also move all of this stuff over there, too?
All of that?
Leave such heavy tasks to us boys!
Thank you, Sparky.
Don’t run off, BB Goat.
Let me help, too.
Leave the carrying to us, Tibbie.
You can watch over BB Goat.
Okay!
Where’s BB Goat?
Come back, BB Goat!
Come here, buggy!
You’re the one who needs to come here!
I failed because I was too high-profile before.
This time, I must possess someone who doesn’t stand out.
Swimming and fitness!
Try it out, ma’am!
Swimming and fitness,
yoga class!
Try it for free!
We’ve got a children’s fitness class, too!
He’s doing so much, yet everyone’s ignoring him.
He’s all sweaty, too.
You’re the one!
This body is so strong!
He stinks, though!
I’m a hygienic bacterium, you know.
Whatever!
No one will suspect me this time!
Wait for me!
BB Goat, wait for me!
Sister Tibbie,
look!
Don’t do that!
You’ll suffocate it!
It won’t suffocate
if I hold it like this!
It flew away, too.
Holding it like that will hurt it, BB Goat.
It’s a bug!
If you don’t stop running off, I’ll get mad!
Look, Tibbie! It’s a bug!
Look! Look!
BB Goat!
Don’t move! I’ll pull you up!
I’m so tired.
If I can get this guy,
I’ll be able to force him to tell me where BB Goat is!
It’s so heavy.
I’ll warm up a bit first.
Am I some sick cat to you or what?
Got you.
Got who?
Well, of course it’s—
Are you helping me carry the chair, Tyger?
Carrying chairs?
Tyger?
Doesn’t this guy not stand out?
Why do the goats all know him?
Let me help you guys out with this.
Thank you, Tyger.
You’re so kind, Tyger!
Sorry that there’s so much stuff.
Are you actually sorry?
It’s fine.
I’ll just finish this first.
All done!
I’m so tired.
We only finished so quickly because of Tyger!
Thank you, Tyger!
You’re welcome.
Mr. Slowy!
There’s less room than I thought.
I’ll just keep this.
Could you guys move the rest of this back for me?
I’m really sorry.
What?
BB Goat, are you okay?
This place is so scary.
Don’t worry,
we’re just in a cave.
I’ll protect you.
What’s that?
So many stars!
These aren’t stars.
They’re called fireflies, and they glow in the dark.
Why did it land on your hand?
If you treat them kindly,
they’ll gladly be friends with you.
So pretty!
Is it leaving, too?
I think it’s trying to lead us to the way out.
Let’s follow it!
There are so many insects here!
I want to be friends with the bugs!
Bugs are so cool!
Yes,
but at the same time, they’re very fragile.
We have to make sure not to hurt them.
Tyger’s done a lot for us today.
By the way, what have you come to Goats’ Village for?
I heard that there’s a new kid in the village,
so I wanted to see if she’d be interested in joining
my children’s fitness class.
That’s too bad, then. She and Tibbie aren’t here.
What?
Why didn’t you guys say so?
You made me do so much work for so long!
Paddi!
What’s wrong with you, Tyger?
Has he been possessed by King Bacteria?
Since you’ve found out, I’ll destroy you all!
Let’s go!
Bring it on, Bacteria King!
Weslie and Sparky are still better than you!
What?
Tyger is really strong.
Good thing BB Goat isn’t here.
We’re back!
Tibbie!
Are you guys done?
Behind you!
Tibbie!
BB Goat!
I’ve caught you at last!
Where in the world has King Bacteria taken BB Goat?
It’s all my fault for not protecting BB Goat.
No, Tibbie!
This isn’t your fault!
It’s all because of that—
Where in the world has she gone?
Can anyone tell me?
Look, guys! This butterfly is glowing!
What the…?
It’s not just that butterfly.
All of the insects in this forest are glowing.
It’s that light again!
What the…?
Follow me. BB Goat is this way.
Follow me, guys! BB Goat is this way!
Tibbie,
how did you know where BB Goat is?
The butterfly told me.
I’m not lying!
Let’s cut to the chase.
Hurry up and undo the seal for me!
Stop it!
Let BB Goat go right now!
You really think you can stop
these speedy, strong muscles of mine?
Tyger is, in fact, very strong.
That was just a one-time thing.
We won’t lose this time!
Let’s go!
No matter how many times you try, it all ends the same.
Is that all you’ve got?
You’re powerless,
so stop causing more trouble for Weslie.
You think dodging will be enough, huh?
How naïve.
Weslie!
I’ve had enough.
It’s time for the end.
What…
What are these?
Get out of my way!
All the bugs are here!
Thanks, guys.
Can you hold him off for just a little longer?
Is communicating with insects
Tibbie’s new ability?
Go!
Good thing we’ve got Tibbie.
What the…?
Weslie, since he’s a bacterium,
he surely can’t stand cleanliness!
Got it!
Again?
If this guy gets cleaned,
I won’t be able to possess him anymore!
Sparky!
Here comes some warm water!
Oh,
how
lovely!
Bathing feels so good.
Just you wait, guys!
I’ll be back for sure!
Come play again soon!
You have a gadget now, too, Tibbie!
Tibbie saved us!
They are the ones who saved us.
Thanks, guys!
Have some cake, guys. You’ve worked hard.
Yay,
cake!
How dare it steal my cake!
Get rid of it!
Sister Tibbie said that we can’t hurt bugs.
Flies are bad bugs. We must get rid of them!
No,
you
can’t!
Get rid of the bug!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy