A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Paddi’s Great Cleaning
Go ahead and search for BB Goat’s big brother.
I’ll take care of her!
A stamp?
I’ve gotten quite a few lately.
When I get ten, I can trade it for that big cake!
I’ll look around.
Paddi,
would you like to test out my newly invented cleaning kit?
No.
Oh, come on.
Look,
a soap dispenser with eight nozzles.
One push allows eight people to wash their hands at the same time.
I don’t have eight people in my house, though.
How about this extra-long broom, then?
A push of a button, and it extends.
You’ll be able to sweep up to ten meters away from you.
My house isn’t that big, though.
That’s alright.
I also have this gentle feather duster.
Using it with too much force will cause it to fall apart,
so it forces you to carefully dust your entire house.
Alright, alright. I’ll take them.
Remember to leave a positive review if you like them!
Sure.
It’s very important for me!
Remember to leave a positive review!
The easy-to-deal-with Paddi is all alone.
Here I come, BB Goat!
Stamps… Stamps…
I’m about to get—
I’m about to get the handprint!
This house is so dirty.
It doesn’t suit a hygienic bacterium like me one bit.
Disgusting!
It’s you again, little one!
Let’s play together!
Little kids are so loud.
Eww!
I’m a hygienic bacterium, you know!
I’ll come back to deal with you once I’ve gotten clean!
Come back!
Too loud! Be quiet, BB Goat!
You can’t run off, BB Goat.
Brother Paddi!
Eww!
Go wash your hands!
Go… Go wash your hands!
Washing hands!
I’m washing my hands!
Don’t use this soap!
What a nuisance.
Look, Paddi!
So many snowflakes!
Snowflakes!
This isn’t a toy!
How am I supposed to clean up all these feathers?
Let’s clean, Paddi!
Stop sweeping!
How did it get longer?
BB Goat,
go take a bath.
I’m back!
How did it get even dirtier?
I need to get out of here as soon as I get the handprint.
Dry yourself off before leaving!
Come back!
I didn’t realize how dirty it was.
I guess I’ll have to do a deep clean!
It’s a stamp!
I found a stamp!
A flower?
Yeah, let’s keep looking for these flowers.
Flowers! Flowers!
A flower!
Found another one!
Let’s make the bed!
…eight, nine.
We just need one more,
and we’ll get to trade it for that big cake!
I collected the stamps,
and I also got my house super clean.
What a wonderful day.
Cleaning for so long was a lot of hard work, too.
Let’s have a good rest.
Remember to leave a positive review if you like the cleaning kit!
Wolffy, your cleaning kit—
My cleaning kit is very useful
and very clean!
Shut up!
I’m returning your cleaning kit to you!
Oh…
I’m returning
your stuff!
Have my inventions caused other people trouble?
I’m so full.
What happened?
I’ll get the handprint for sure this time!
Dumplings…
This is my mouth, not a dumpling!
A flower!
What was that?
You made another mess?
No, I didn’t.
Enough excuses!
Why do I always fail?
Spider!
BB Goat,
you have nowhere to run!
Paddi—
I have to clean again.
Paddi!
What now?
BB Goat!
Let go of BB Goat!
Are my inventions actually completely useless?
Out of my way!
Huh?
It’s you again!
BB Goat’s been captured!
BB Goat!
Let go of BB Goat!
Are you okay, BB Goat?
What’s going on?
The flower!
BB Goat,
get back here!
I’ll help!
Use the soap to scrub the spider clean
so King Bacteria can’t possess it anymore!
Okay!
I can’t get hit again!
Watch this!
Goodbye!
Can you think of anything else?
Aha!
I’ll use the broom to get you to the spider!
Go, Paddi!
You said you’d use the broom, not make me fly!
Another one?
BB Goat, why aren’t you letting go of the spider?
Let go!
Got it!
BB Goat!
Will I…
Will I be stuck like this forever?
I have a gadget now, too?
BB Goat!
Are you okay?
My power is suction?
Hand that little one over!
I’ll be back!
Brother Paddi,
the flower!
Silly,
did you not let go of King Bacteria just to help me get a stamp?
It’s your flower!
Thanks.
I’ve come to rescue you, Paddi!
So this is the cake that you traded your stamps for?
No, it’s not.
Those stamps have memories attached,
so there’s no way I’m trading them.
Just eat what I’ve made.
By the way,
thank you, Wolffy.
Your cleaning kit really did help in saving BB Goat.
My cleaning kit is very useful, isn’t it?
Don’t get stuck in your head, okay?
Just you wait.
Next time, I’ll invent something even more useful.
I look forward to it.
We’re back.
Weslie, have you guys found BB Goat’s brother?
No.
Let’s keep searching tomorrow, then!
What are those on your arms, Paddi?
They’re my new gadgets!
New gadgets?
What happened?
Tell us!
On a windy, dark morning…
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy