A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Doppelgänger Rescue
Class is over!
School ended early today,
so I’ll go buy a cake while the bakery is still open.
Jonie,
I’m on day duty today.
Could you watch BB Goat for me?
Hi, Sister Jonie!
Sure.
Thanks, Jonie.
Watch BB Goat.
Jonie,
I need to go shopping.
Could you water the plants for me?
Of course.
Thanks, Jonie!
Jonie!
Sparky?
I’ve got a basketball game coming up.
Could you help me mail a letter?
A basketball game?
Sure.
See you later, then!
He’s so fast.
The list isn’t too long, though.
I can go buy the cake when done.
Jonie, could you help me mail a package?
Jonie!
Thanks, Jonie!
Help Planie turn in his homework.
Work out with Tyger.
Help Auntie Cow with housekeeping.
Help Mr. Monkey move.
Up next…
Why do I have so much to do?
Whatever. I’ll just do them one at a time.
Let’s play, BB Goat!
Okay!
How did they defeat me every single time?
No,
I need to hurry up and think of a way to defeat those goats for good!
Wolffy,
clean the kitchen when you’re done with the living room.
Got it, Wolnie.
Cleaning up all of this is going to take forever, though.
If only I could clean it all up in one go.
It’s you!
Stop right there!
You have nowhere to run!
Help!
There’s no way you can escape from my eight arms!
Eight arms?
Aha!
If I had eight arms,
the goats would be no match for me!
I’d be able to clean the place super quickly!
What a wonderful plan!
I’m not your friend!
I guess I’ll have to just use your dirty body one more time!
What did you say?
Not again!
Just you wait, little goats!
Look, Sister Jonie!
Wow, BB Goat!
One down.
You can do it, Jonie!
BB Goat,
stay right here and wait for me a bit, okay?
Okay!
Done at last.
I’ll go find BB Goat.
BB Goat?
BB Goat’s gone!
Weslie,
aren’t you with BB Goat today?
I’m on day duty today,
so I asked Jonie to watch BB Goat for today.
I asked Jonie to help me send a letter, too.
Then, in a bit, let’s go thank her together.
Sure!
Why are there so many people here?
Paddi and the others are here, too.
Paddi, Tibbie,
what are you guys doing here?
We asked Jonie to help us, so we wanted to thank her,
but she’s not here.
What?
Did all of you guys ask her for help?
Yes.
We… We did, too.
Jonie had so many things on her plate at once.
She’s probably still busy.
Why don’t we go help her out?
It’d be such a waste
to use such a wonderful gadget for housekeeping.
It’d be better used for capturing BB Goat!
What a coincidence! I was looking for you just now.
It’s you, Mister!
Do you want to play with me?
Sure,
I’ll have some real fun with you!
BB Goat!
There you are!
You were with Wolffy, huh?
Sister Jonie!
You want to leave?
Wolffy, what are you doing?
Let go!
Let go of her!
Wolffy, you—
It’s not “Wolffy”.
It’s “King Bacteria”!
It looks like Wolffy’s been possessed again.
Let BB Goat go!
Bring it on, then!
Are you too weak,
or am I too strong?
You really think you can fight me alone?
Even if I’m alone,
I won’t let you
harm BB Goat!
Huh?
Do I have a gadget now, too?
How am I supposed to use it, though?
What?
So many!
I mean,
they’re really small.
What did you say?
Who are you calling “small”?
What happened?
It must be from the Super Cube!
Yay! I’ve got a gadget now, too!
Yeah! This is awesome!
This is awesome!
Yeah!
Why don’t we rescue BB Goat first?
Here I come!
Who are you kidding, huh?
Look out!
Why did we all bump into each other?
You didn’t say which way to run.
I’ll tell you.
I’m done playing with you guys!
Wolffy?
What are you guys doing?
It’s you again!
It looks like I’ll just have to do this the hard way!
Paddi!
Let me go!
I think Wolffy’s been possessed again!
Look out!
It’s no use.
My invention is specially designed to withstand your powers!
Come back here!
Now!
Do you see just how powerful an eight-armed me is?
Let me go!
Can’t move, huh?
None of you can stop me now!
Stop!
It’s Jonie!
Am I seeing things,
or has Jonie shrunk?
You again?
Haven’t you learned your lesson?
Now!
Wh… What?
Where did those two Jonies come from?
There’s another one over here!
I’ll explain later.
Apparently, my strength is still the same even after splitting.
Paddi has been rescued!
Got it!
Such a nuisance!
Since my gadgets do nothing against you,
I’ll use my own strength to stop you!
How did he escape?
Sparky has been rescued!
It was you!
You bastard!
Get out of Wolffy’s body!
All rescues complete!
Roger!
You have nowhere to run,
King Bacteria!
I’m done!
BB Goat!
Darn it, he’s gotten away!
Don’t forget about me!
Just you wait!
Are you okay?
Thank you, Sister Jonie!
I see. Does that mean
that Jonie has her own gadget now, just like we do?
Yeah,
I’ll be able to use my doppelgängers to help even more people.
Jonie,
we were wrong
to ask to do so many things for us.
We’re sorry.
We won’t do that again.
It’s nothing.
I’m very happy to be able to help you guys, too.
Jonie,
you’re so kind!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy