A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
The Troubles of Mosquito-Keeping
Come play with me, Sister Tibbie!
Wow, Sister Tibbie!
It’s a mosquito!
Mosquito,
I want to play with you.
You can’t play with mosquitoes, BB Goat.
Mosquitoes are pests.
No, the mosquito wants to play with me.
She’s still too young.
She has absolutely no sense of fear.
The way I see it, the mosquito is probably more scared.
How about I call you “Whizzy”?
If you’ve got unique anti-mosquito inventions,
I need you to join the anti-mosquito competition in three days!
If I participate…
Poor you. Your face is all swollen from the bite.
It’s swollen because you hit me!
Oh, yeah,
I can create an anti-mosquito invention!
Those “mosquito” creatures
seem to really annoy them, huh?
I might be able to use them!
What’s that?
How dare you bite King Bacteria!
What are you doing?
No need to fear me.
I just want to collaborate with you, is all.
You can understand what I say?
Of course I can! I’m King Bacteria, you know.
I’ll need more than just one of you.
Are you hungry, Whizzy?
I’ll get some food for you.
Don’t you want some ice cream, Whizzy?
I’ll eat it, then.
For how much longer is BB Goat going to keep that mosquito?
We can’t take it anymore!
We’ll have to think of a way to get rid of it.
BB Goat’s so protective of the mosquito, though.
We can’t even get close to it.
How should we separate the two?
My hands are dirty.
I need to use the bathroom.
I’ll take you to wash your hands.
What are you guys doing?
Why did you guys scare away Whizzy?
BB Goat, we were just—
The people of the grassland are awful,
always using various methods against us!
My brother was a victim of their insect repellent.
My nephews were crushed by them.
My uncle was killed by one of their slippers, too.
I think I’ve gone to the wrong meeting.
Sorry.
That’s why we must stand together
and show them who’s boss!
I’m strong. I should be the captain!
I fly the fastest. I should be the captain!
I’m the captain!
I am!
What a chubby mosquito!
Look at how round his stomach is! How much does he eat?
I’m so jealous!
I’m the captain! Any questions?
No, sir!
Let’s go, then!
Our first target will be that group of goats!
Hold on.
I think Wolffy is working on some kind of anti-mosquito invention.
Wolffy’s stupid inventions
could never be a match for all of these mosquitoes!
Here we go!
I hate you, Brother Weslie!
We did this for your own good.
Give Whizzy back to me!
Whizzy’s long gone, though.
Look, guys! Whizzy’s back!
Whizzy!
Why are there so many mosquitoes?
Get out of my way, Brother Weslie!
Hang on. Something isn’t right.
Team Two, go!
Leave it to me!
I hate mosquitoes!
Team One,
capture their leader for me!
Whizzy!
I want to play with Whizzy!
If those mosquitoes get any closer, they’ll hurt you!
But Whizzy is my friend!
What’s going on?
I come back from the bathroom, and I find all of these mosquitoes?
Help!
Don’t worry!
This is my invention.
We don’t have tongues as long as yours, though.
Next.
My solution is to move the mosquitoes with music.
Ouch!
Isn’t there at least one practical invention?
I have one.
Time for a demonstration!
How is this different from using our own hands?
Your hands are too small,
so you can only get one at a time.
My invention changes that, though.
Guys—
Don’t interrupt the competition.
My robotic hands can get this many at a time.
Uh…
Over there!
Wow!
Don’t blame me!
I’m going to use every drop of power that this mosquito has!
Whizzy has gotten bigger!
So this was King Bacteria’s doing!
Run, guys!
Are you okay, Brother Weslie?
Yes.
Mosquitoes are pests that suck our blood.
Soon, the site of the bite is going to itch a lot.
We just didn’t want the mosquitoes to hurt you.
Worrying about others, still?
Whizzy,
why did you hurt Brother Weslie?
Because I can!
My invention is specialized for killing mosquitoes!
It looks like your inventions are still useless, as always.
I still have more up my sleeve.
Insect repellent incense, fire!
Bug spray, fire!
He’s flying too fast for me to hit him!
Wolffy, get me behind him!
No problem.
Nice shot, huh?
Watch this!
Don’t you know?
Mosquitoes are very agile!
You’re no match for me!
Why are you smiling?
Here I come!
Extra-strong bug spray!
Thanks, Wolffy!
You’re welcome.
It itches!
I’ll put some ointment on it when we get home.
Do you still want to keep mosquitoes?
I’m sorry, I’ll never play with mosquitoes again.
They’re evil!
What’s your name?
I want to play with you!
Are you kidding me?
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy