A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Here Come the Seven Evil Wolves
Wolnie and Wilie are at Wolnie’s parents’ house,
so I can do some experimenting!
The evil queen is gone now,
so hand over your body,
Wolffy!
Here I come, Wolffy!
Trying to possess me again?
It would be your honor.
I’m… I’m so dirty!
You’re the dirtiest person ever, Wolffy!
Go wash your hands right this instant!
You’re the most annoying one ever!
Get out of my sight right this instant!
Who is it?
Hi, Wolffy!
Where did all those wolves come from?
I can’t let them see me.
What are you guys doing here?
Wolnie asked us to come.
She says that you’ve been talking to walls lately
and angry for no apparent reason.
She worried that you weren’t doing well, so she asked us to stay with you.
Wolnie must have seen our arguments.
No need to welcome us.
We can help ourselves.
This isn’t your own house, you know!
Wolffy, where’s the telephone?
Wolffy, where are you?
Leave me alone! Just do your own thing!
What a nuisance.
Can’t I just experiment in peace?
Disturbing my experiments
is the last straw for me!
Why don’t you be quiet, huh?
Are you trying to destroy my house or what?
This is outrageous!
I can’t believe this! Bring it on!
There’s no way to get through to them.
I’ll just keep experimenting.
What exactly are you doing?
Would you like to buy a face mask?
[Translation missing]
No.
I have smiley face masks
that really suit you!
No thanks.
Would you like to see any others
like this?
We have bubble tea masks,
rainbow masks,
and clown masks!
I’m sure we’ll have one that suits you!
Buy two, get one free!
Where’s Wolffy?
I’ve had enough.
I need to call Wolnie and have her make them leave.
Is this A Gan?
Have you finished watching Rescue Across Time?
There’s sixty episodes in total,
and last time, we chatted up to the fifth.
It’s okay,
we can talk all you want.
No,
you’ve already seen him.
He was quite handsome, right?
He looked amazing!
Yeah, you go on watching.
Goodbye!
He’s finally done.
Is this A Qiang?
King Bacteria is much quieter in comparison.
Wolffy, today is your day, isn’t it?
I’m so hungry.
I’ll get something to eat from the kitchen and then continue watching.
There are so many wolves.
I wonder which one I should possess for capturing BB Goat.
Who was that?
How dare you!
What’s going on?
Why is this guy painting in here?
He’s made a mess all over, too,
and the refrigerator is all the way over there.
I guess I’ll just have to charge through.
You really think you can get me with just that?
Here I come!
What now?
Since it’s so loud outside,
it’s best that I make mud figures inside.
That’s right.
Besides, you can get a lot of inspiration here.
Artists, huh?
This isn’t even a kitchen anymore!
My destination is right up ahead!
I can’t turn back now!
I’ll practice right here.
Wolffy is much cleaner
in comparison.
These wolves are so dirty and grimy,
so I’ll just possess them and send them home.
I’ll start with the least hygienic.
He moved!
Never mind, I’ll possess him instead.
There’s a bug!
Eww!
I can’t fail this time!
Help!
What are these?
This washing machine is quite nice,
so I’ll take it with me as a gift.
The quality of this telephone is quite nice, so I’ll take it.
I can’t believe both of you.
Listen to me!
By the way, Wolffy…
We…
We can talk about this.
We had so much fun here
that we almost forgot to give these to you!
These are from our house!
And this mud statue, too.
Looks just like you, doesn’t it?
I spent three whole days making it.
I painted you a wall portrait!
Guys…
By the way, what were you saying earlier?
It’s nothing.
You alone
won’t be able to eat all of this,
so we’ll eat some of it for you!
Trying to get rid of them is impossible.
That is, unless there’s a way to make them leave on their own.
Leave on their own?
I’ve got an idea,
but it’ll need two people.
It’s a deal.
Who’s screaming?
He woke me up!
I’m teaching him a lesson!
A monster has entered Wolf Fortress!
Hurry,
come this way!
You’ve gone mad, haven’t you?
No…
No, I’m serious!
Look, guys, there’s fog!
I feel a strange breeze, too.
I’ve read in storybooks
that this is usually when the monster appears.
What are you doing?
You scared me!
Can’t you just turn on the lights?
You guys are such an embarrassment to the Wolf Clan.
Look at how brave I am!
What’s that noise?
The claw marks are so deep!
There’s a huge footprint, too!
What monster is it, anyway?
What’s there to be afraid of? I can do that, too.
It’s Wolffy!
Let’s rescue him!
Wolffy!
Didn’t you guys come to rescue me?
This should have scared them off for good this time.
We’re back!
Stop!
What?
I’m…
I’m the youngest,
so I’ll go first and see what’s up with that monster.
Wolffy,
how would we just let you be the cannon fodder?
Be careful, okay?
Here I come, monster!
I’m coming to help you, Wolffy!
—No!　—Stop it! Calm down!
It’s terrifying!
Run!
They’re finally gone.
We forgot about Wolffy!
How could we ever leave you behind?
Uncle Wonky,
I didn’t realize you cared so much about me.
This isn’t good. Your face has turned yellow from the terror!
With how rough that guy looks,
I’m surprised to see that he has some sense of affection.
I’ll let you go this time.
Our collaboration worked out quite well.
It was all thanks to the “monster” puppet show I put on.
What?
I was the one who did all that acting in front of them!
[Translation missing]
Wolffy, are you okay?
We didn’t realize that we took the statue until we’d gotten home.
Are… Are you mad at us?
No,
I’m just glad that you guys are home safe.
Goodbye, then.
Who did that?
I can’t stand the mess in here.
Clean it up for me right now!
I can’t clean it up alone.
But it’s too dirty!
Well,
someone could give me a hand.
I can’t believe you’re making me clean!
I won’t forgive you!
I almost forgot to wash Wolnie’s dress.
I already took care of that for you.
You mean you already washed it?
I already threw it out. It was too dirty.
Threw it out?
Why did you throw out Wolnie’s red dress?
Well, it was just too dirty.
That’s her favorite dress, you know!
Where did you throw the dress out?
Get it back!
I don’t know. The garbage can?
Go find it!
How dare you get me dirty!
I can’t stand you!
Get out of my castle!
Watch this!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy