A little goat has come to the grassland
Bringing joy and hope to everyone
A family in the Goats’ Village
Care for her and make her grow up happily
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
For the peace of the grassland
For the little goat’s wish
We fight bravely and reserve hope forever
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Many goats on the Green Green Grassland
Strive to create warmth and sunshine
For my little sister’s wish
Nothing matters even if I’m hurt
We fight alien forces together
Protecting our family from danger
Attaining the power of justice
We will eventually greet peaceful time
Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
A Clash of Interests
The next step is to rewire the cables.
I can’t mess it up.
This is outrageous!
Don’t watch television that close up!
Hold on, what are you doing here?
Weren’t you playing with the others?
I don’t know how to play anything that they’re playing.
Oh, yeah. You’re from outer space,
so you’re not familiar with our grassland.
I have an idea!
Your task today
is to cultivate the grassland’s interest into BB Goat.
Cultivate interest?
Soccer is certainly the best!
No way. Gardening is better.
I think working out is the best.
At last, I can focus fully
on my experiment.
How should I capture BB Goat this time?
Done!
With this shapeshifting potion,
I can transform into anything I touch!
I can transform back whenever I want to, too.
I can also use it to—
Son, how about I play with you?
Yeah!
Here we go!
Wow, Daddy!
Daddy, I want to fly kites!
Got it.
Daddy, I want to play with a teddy bear!
Let’s play, Daddy.
I never thought Wolffy would have an actually useful invention.
Once I drink this potion, it’s game over for all of you.
Outrageous!
How dare you—
Where did the ball go?
So this is soccer, BB Goat.
Is it fun?
Yeah!
I’m so dizzy…
Now’s my chance!
Overhead kick!
That’s odd. How did it get over here?
At least let BB Goat touch the ball, Weslie.
Sorry, I got lost in the moment there.
BB Goat,
here you go.
I got kicked around for so long,
and now you pick up the ball?
I’m not kicking the ball. It’ll hurt the ball.
I guess BB Goat doesn’t like playing soccer.
Let’s try something else.
Okay.
Let’s see if you can kick me around now!
This is how to use punching bags, BB Goat.
Watch this!
No, that’s too much force!
Don’t you have something normal to show her?
I do.
BB Goat will for sure like the things that I do all the time.
What is it?
Sleeping neither harms the body nor consumes energy.
It’s perfect for goats who don’t like moving, such as BB Goat and myself.
This doesn’t even count as exercise.
Then, I’ll give you guys a taste
of my ultimate move!
I guess BB Goat doesn’t like what you guys have to offer.
We’ll take it from here.
I’m sure that I’ll succeed
if I try just a little harder!
Those goats are way too dangerous.
I’d better just hide and wait for a chance to act.
Your house is so organized, Tibbie.
A chance has come faster than I expected.
BB Goat,
why don’t I teach you how to water plants?
Watering plants? That’s all?
There’s no skill in that.
Watering plants requires a lot of precision, you know.
You can’t give too much or too little water.
You can’t be too rough with your movements.
Wow!
Stop it!
The flower is dying!
Stop right now, Sister Tibbie!
I’ve never seen such a condition before.
I almost exploded.
You might have messed up just a little bit,
but you’ve done a great job!
Well, it’s my turn next.
I’m going to get in trouble sooner or later.
Since I’m this small, I won’t be—
If we run out of yarn,
we can tie multiple strands together.
Amazing!
Can I try it on?
Well,
I haven’t washed my feet in some days.
You don’t mind, right?
This sock isn’t quite breathable enough.
Which one do you like, BB Goat?
Wow, the sock can move!
Even the sock is moving.
Exactly how long have you not washed your feet for?
Ours is better!
BB Goat should take after us!
She should take after us!
Us!
Let’s ask BB Goat, then.
BB Goat, who do you pick?
How do I play with this?
My time has come!
BB Goat!
Look! BB Goat is on the bridge!
Skateboarding is fun!
This is exhausting!
The skateboard walks and talks?
No, that’s King Bacteria’s voice!
Stay away!
If you don’t, I’ll jump!
Despicable!
Let BB Goat go!
Have you ever met a king that just lets go when you ask him to?
No one shall stop me today!
Good job minding your own business.
Once I recover my powers,
I’ll take over the whole universe!
In your dreams!
Recall the strongest sleeping position that I taught you.
Go, Sparky!
My super strike,
Thermofist!
Hot!
I knew it! Wolffy’s inventions are awful!
Knitters are very good at making knots, you know.
This is fun!
Don’t spill when watering plants.
Keep it precise and elegant.
Overhead kick!
So, you guys argued over this for a whole day?
Well, BB Goat?
What do you think?
I like to play with everyone.
Apparently, what BB Goat wanted is to just play with us.
Actually, I think that all of our interests are really cool.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah!
End
Don’t think of me as just a goat
Because of me, the green grass is more fragrant
Because of me, the sky is bluer
The clouds are even fluffier
In the face of any problems, I won’t be heartbroken
In the face of any dangers, I won’t panic
Even if a pack of wolves is chasing me, I treat it as a game
I’ll be happy all the time with my smile soaring
I’d rather stand up than be upset even if I fall down
I’m able to bring laughter, no matter the weather
Although I’m just a goat
Weslie, Tibbie, Paddi, Sparky, Slowy, Mandy, Wolnie, Wolffy