Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Safety Buddy
Careful!
Don’t run!
Can’t you just chill for a bit, BB Goat ?
Don’t eat food from the ground.
Don’t lay on the ground, either.
This is exhausting.
BB Goat ,
please have mercy on me!
Just let me take a nap!
Fine.
I’m playing outside, then!
Come back, BB Goat !
It’s dangerous out there!
You guys worry too much.
It’s normal for a little kid to have a lot of energy.
Oh no!
Are you hurt?
An infected wound would be bad.
You’re the one who worries too much, Mr. Slowy.
Mr. Slowy,
what’s this?
I came because I’ve designed a robot
that will protect BB Goat ,
the Safety Buddy!
Safety Buddy?
Come down!
Stupid King Bacteria,
hiding in my house all day!
Show yourself!
You think I can’t find you if you hide, huh?
Uh-huh.
You’re never finding me.
Sterilizing Tracking Missiles!
Target confirmed!
Fire!
You have nowhere to run!
It seems that this thing isn’t too bad after all.
Since you’ve passed out,
I’ll help myself!
Come get me!
Is this thing really going to work?
Rest assured.
I put my entire heart and soul into him.
He even has a self-upgrading system,
so his protective abilities get even better.
Will this thing do the job?
Come get me!
Watch out!
Hazard cleared.
Wow!
Danger.
Safety hazard. Hazard clearing.
See what my inventions can do?
Yeah, they’re amazing!
Analyzing hazardous materials…
Fruits and fruit peels: Dangerous.
Let’s play outside, Safety Buddy!
If the goats are here, things will prove difficult.
I must be on high alert.
Come get me! Come get me!
BB Goat ?
You got me!
That was easier than I thought it would be!
Release BB Goat .
Warning:
Release BB Goat  now, or attacks will begin.
Attack me, King Bacteria?
You don’t stand a chance, stupid robot.
Wolves: Dangerous.
I’m not giving up!
Goats: Dangerous.
Lollipops and dirt pits: Dangerous.
Dangerous.
That robot foiled my plans again.
I’m…
I’m so done!
What now?
Aha!
All done!
You’ve got nowhere to run, robot!
I’ll be using extraterrestrially-modified missiles to blow you up!
Dinner time!
I’m coming!
BB Goat ,
have some green grass balls.
Danger.
What’s going on?
Hazards cleared.
BB Goat  is in danger.
Deactivating elimination mode.
Activating rescue mode.
Jam bombs.
We can’t let him destroy Goats’ Village!
I’ll take BB Goat !
Brother Weslie caught me!
Danger.
Piece of cake!
You’ve got us, too!
Let’s play “red light, green light”.
If you move, you lose.
Okay!
Don’t forget about me!
Oh no, not another one!
You have nowhere to run!
I’ve come for revenge, robot!
What… What’s going on?
BB Goat !
Oh no,
the missile is out of control!
Run!
I’m not moving.
If I move, I lose.
Hazard
cleared.
See what I can do now?
I’m out of missiles.
You guys can have BB Goat  back.
I’ll be on my way.
I’ll capture BB Goat  someday!
To be honest,
the Safety Buddy wasn’t that bad.
BB Goat  only avoided injury
because of his protection.
BB Goat !
Does it hurt?
Yes.
Don’t run off anymore, okay?
Okay.
Don’t eat anything off of the ground, either.
If you eat them, you’ll get a stomachache.
See? I told you guys that you worried too much.
As kids are growing, we shouldn’t overprotect them.
I guess I’m the one who worried too much.
End