Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
The Bacterium Gets Sick
Squeaky clean, no disease.
What’s going on?
Is the world ending?
Wolnie and Wilie are out,
and I’m sick.
How long have you not cleaned for the place to get this messy?
Can you help me out?
You want me, the high-ruling King Bacteria, to help you clean?
No way!
You penny-pincher!
I’m going to catch goats now.
I can’t take it anymore!
I need to possess him and make him shower!
I’ll fix his nails, too.
Dry skin calls for a face mask.
Good hygiene is always a confidence boost.
Darn it, I made him too clean!
I’ve lost control!
How dare you kick me out!
How dare you!
Sorry.
I think my nose is cleared up
and my fever has gone down.
I’m sorry, okay? Calm down!
Why have you gone pale?
What…
What in the world is happening?
All done.
With this scanner,
we can scan bodies for their cleanliness level.
Being below a certain threshold means they may be possessed by King Bacteria.
When the machine detects that someone is currently possessed,
it’ll immediately spray water onto the person.
Will it really work?
I’ll demonstrate with a test.
People like me, who aren’t possessed, can walk past just fine.
Those who are—
Oh no,
Mr. Slowy has been possessed!
Calm down.
The system just made a mistake, is all.
I’ll just fix it up.
All fixed!
Yay!
You’ve got mail—
It’s King Bacteria!
What’s going on?
I’m just here to deliver a letter!
But Mr. Slowy’s scanner
detected that your body’s cleanliness level is below ten percent.
I’ve just been really busy lately
and haven’t showered for a long while!
I’m really sorry, Mr. Rabbit.
It looks like the scanner has some flaws.
I’ll fix it.
What…
What exactly do you want, huh?
My hero,
thank you for your hospitality.
My hospitality?
You’ve given me a place to stay,
brought me food, and kept me company.
See? You’ve helped me once again!
I’m returning the favor!
Is there anything else you need help with?
The windows need cleaning.
Is there anything else?
The bathroom needs cleaning.
The floor needs sweeping!
Is there anything else?
Uh… No, that’s all.
No,
I feel awful if I’m not helping others out!
I’m going outside to see if there’s anything else I can help with!
What in the world is going on?
The road is blocked. What should I do?
Stand still!
Oh, you’re helping me?
Thanks.
What in the world is going on?
Help!
Are you okay?
Do you need me to help you with anything?
I’m… I’m fine.
Thank you! Thank you so much!
Breaking news!
A mysterious person on the grassland
has been selflessly helping those in need.
He’s now everyone’s favorite.
Who exactly is this helper?
Come here, guys!
I’ve redone the whole thing.
This time, it’s sure to only target King Bacteria
and not innocent people.
Do you need help with anything?
Mr. Slowy,
why didn’t the scanner catch anything?
I must fix it no matter what!
Now’s not the time to worry about that, Mr. Slowy.
We have to protect BB Goat !
Where’d BB Goat  go?
I’ll help!
Good thing I made it on time.
It’s you again!
Stay away from BB Goat !
Okay.
Why is he so pale?
He must be up to something.
Let’s not fight.
He’s not a bad guy anymore.
Guys,
he’s the person who’s been helping around the grassland lately.
Kind sir, can I get an autograph?
Please take these gifts!
Kind sir!
What in the world is going on?
I don’t know, either.
He helped me take a shower, and he’s been like this ever since.
Goodbye, everyone.
I’m going to the cosmos to help even more people.
Goodbye!
Is he really leaving?
I thought he was a bad guy,
but it seems he’s actually nice.
I’ve taken my rocket out!
Thank you, my hero!
Thanks, everyone.
I will remember your kindness and continue to help more people.
This is my gift for you.
I wish you safe travels.
I won’t forget you guys.
Goodbye.
Goodbye!
Where’s Mr. Slowy?
Mr. Slowy has been working on his scanner since yesterday.
I don’t want to disturb him.
It was nice knowing you
and being your friend.
Although I’m sad to see you go,
I know that you have dreams to go after,
so I’ll cheer you on as a friend from far away.
This rocket was once a goat-hunting invention of mine a long time ago.
I hope that with it, I’ll be with you
through every corner of the cosmos.
By the way, I noticed that you’ve caught a cold,
so I’ve prepared you a tea for it.
Don’t forget to drink it.
Wolffy is so kind.
Finally, we don’t have to worry about BB Goat ’s safety anymore.
Look, the rocket is back!
The kind sir is back!
He’s coming back to help us!
You bastards!
You want me, King Bacteria, to help you?
He’s changed!
Run!
Why has he changed again?
What kind of gifts did you guys give him
to make him change?
Wolffy,
your tea for colds had some perfect timing.
It cured my cold,
fixing my loss of control!
So it was me, huh?
Apparently, when he catches a cold, he turns into a good guy.
Let BB Goat  go!
I’m flying!
I can’t fly no matter how fast I run!
What the heck?
What?
As I said, my inventions aren’t useless.
Not only have I improved the detection system,
but I’ve improved the water spraying.
It won’t let go even a bacterium in the sky!
Have a taste of the rocket feast I’ve prepared for you!
I can’t believe they’d do that to me.
I’ll teach them a lesson!
Wolffy, what are you doing?
Why haven’t you caught my cold yet?
For the cosmos and the grassland,
I took a lot of cold showers to get myself sick, you know!
The probability of me getting sick is one in ten thousand!
I suggest that you give up!
One in ten thousand?
I made myself catch a cold for nothing, then?
End