Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Sister Snail
Wolffy’s favorite drink
has flavor and color for ten li.
I’ll give it a try.
What are you doing?
You must have attracted all these flies here!
Go away!
For goodness’ sake,
are you really trying to interrupt my tasting of this wonderful drink?
What the…?
It’s disinfectant!
You can just clean like a normal person, you know!
What’s with the disinfectant?
How inconsiderate!
Exactly!
Fine, I’m leaving!
I’m leaving!
I won’t come back even if you beg me to!
Bactie,
I’m begging you.
You miss me already, huh?
No!
I’m begging you to never, ever come back!
To slow the spread of mosquito plague,
everyone must head home right now and clean.
I’ll inspect them all later.
Okay!
I hate cleaning.
I’ll just take a nap to rest my body.
A snail?
Do you want to be with your friends up there?
I’ll give you a hand.
Alright, time to sleep.
This looks much more comfortable than Wolf Fortress’ attic does.
This is it!
Disinfectant!
If I hadn’t lost my powers,
all that disinfectant would have no effect on me.
I just want somewhere to live, okay?
What’s so hard about that?
No one’s home.
This is it!
Why is it so dirty?
Thank you for helping me up the tree.
Please take this gift.
Thank you!
Paddi.
Paddi!
Are you finished cleaning?
Pretty much.
Good.
I’m doing inspections right now.
If you didn’t clean thoroughly,
you will not
be eating dinner tonight.
Huh?
Wait, Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy,
why don’t you go inspect the other houses?
I’ve already inspected all of them.
You’re the last one.
Paddi!
No, my dinner is gone!
It’s spotless!
Job well done.
You meet the hygiene standards!
How is it so clean?
Good job.
Keep it up.
Who cleaned the place for me?
Never mind.
Let me eat first.
I have to go all that way just to dump some garbage.
Goats’ Village is so inconvenient.
Finally, I can rest for a bit.
I literally just cleaned everything up,
so why is there more garbage?
How is the place all clean again?
All the garbage on the floor is gone, too.
Who exactly is helping me?
Could it be
I’ve been caught!
you,
Sister Snail?
You must be here to return the favor after I helped you.
I’ll have everyone come over and see!
Everyone’s coming to see Sister Snail,
and if BB Goat  comes along,
then I could capture her right then and there, right?
Actually,
wait a minute.
Wasn’t he going to have everyone over to see Sister Snail?
I’m all out of fruits,
so I’m going to wait for Sister Snail to go buy some
before I can make everyone welcome here.
Huh?
Fruits? Check.
What if they want to watch television, though?
My television is broken.
I’ll just leave it to Sister Snail.
…recent breaking news.
Nice.
I’m not done with my homework, though,
so I guess I won’t go out yet.
I have to do your homework, too?
Sister Snail is real!
You’ve done your homework all wrong.
I guess Sister Snail isn’t very literate.
Is Sister Snail here?
I want to find her, too.
Me too!
Paddi, I want to meet Sister Snail!
Okay.
Now’s my chance!
When we go to sleep,
Sister Snail will be here to help us out with chores.
Yay!
Is Sister Snail here yet?
Why isn’t she here yet?
Keep quiet. She’ll be here soon.
Paddi—
Keep quiet.
You’ll scare her off.
Where’s BB Goat ?
BB Goat !
What’s wrong?
BB Goat ’s gone!
What?
But I was standing by the door just now,
and I didn’t see anyone come out.
Over there!
Where are you going, Sister Snail?
That’s no “Sister Snail”!
That’s obviously a snail who’s been possessed by King Bacteria!
Leave it to me.
Hi there.
You think you can stop me?
No way!
Ants, don’t let him get away!
Beautiful!
The fun is only just starting.
Speeding up!
What happened?
Goodbye, goats!
He’s getting away!
Weslie, think of something!
Aha!
What is it?
All yours, Sparky!
This isn’t going to lure me out.
Give BB Goat  back to me!
How dare you trick me!
You’ll pay for this!
I’ve failed again!
I’m sorry.
I almost made you get caught by King Bacteria.
Thank you for letting me see Sister Snail, Brother Paddi!
I’ll savor the taste of this drink.
Who’s there?
Please, let me explain.
What?
I’m back!
Outrageous! Didn’t you say you weren’t coming back?
Give me back my drink!
This place suits me better.
I really wish that Sister Snail were real so she could help me.
It’s Sister Snail!
BB Goat ?
My cake!
End