Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
A New Helper
Look what you’ve done to my house!
Your house was no good to begin with!
I’ll kill you!
My choice to live in such an awful house should be taken as a compliment.
Possession time!
I’m so done with you!
Here we go!
Capture that little one!
Why didn’t it work?
I’ve taken eight hundred showers.
I’m absolutely spotless all over.
There’s no way you’ll be using me for evil anymore!
You think stopping just myself will do?
I’ve told my good friends to come,
and once they’re here,
we’ll be destroying every inch of Green Green Grassland!
You have friends?
Of course I do.
They’re my best friends,
especially my Goldy.
We’ve known each other since childhood.
Back then,
if he had any good stuff, he’d let me have it first.
I won?
I got another!
Goldy is the best!
Once, during a very important bicycle race,
he lended me his most prized bike.
Because of that, I was the champion!
To protect me,
Go, guys!
Go!
he’d even risk his own life.
Goldy, my best buddy!
What are you doing?
Put me down!
I have absolutely no interest in your story.
Hello, Weslie?
Oh, yeah!
Today’s our picnic!
But
that big bad guy ate all of the food I prepared.
I’ll get some more right now.
Just wait for a bit, okay?
It’s all that King Bacteria’s fault.
I’ve never seen someone as thick-skinned as he.
I have to think of a way to make him leave.
Who?
Piece of cake!
Earthlings
don’t stand a chance.
It seems that I can take over this whole place very quickly
once I team up with King Bacteria!
Are you that “good friend” of King Bacteria?
Yes,
I’m His Majesty’s best—
What are you doing?
Stop… Stop it!
Do you know just how much trouble
your “King Bacteria” has brought me?
I’m getting rid of all of you!
I’m not actually here to help King Bacteria!
Haven’t you two been friends for years?
Any time something good happens, he takes it from me.
My candy!
It fell on the ground,
but let’s not waste it.
I won!
This time, I’ve gotten myself a great bike.
The title is all mine!
The brakes are broken!
Your Majesty, here’s a better one.
Go!
Go! Go!
If I get rid of him, I’ll be the chief!
Watch this!
Headbutt!
I hate this!
I hate that he steals every good thing that happens to me.
Sooner or later, I’m going to take his position as chief!
That’s why I usually bring this stuffed toy with me
to remind myself not to forget this enemy!
A radish!
I’m not food!
He’s King Bacteria’s new helper,
Proteus.
What?
Protect BB Goat !
I surrender!
There’s no way I’m here to help him.
He and I are archenemies!
He seems to really hate King Bacteria,
so we might as well have him on our side.
Yeah, I’m very strong.
Well, what can you do?
Yeah,
King Bacteria complimented you so much just now,
but you seem weak to me.
Don’t underestimate me.
I can do a lot!
If I see it,
I can transform into it.
Earth’s things are quite simple, huh?
Transform!
A trampoline!
Turn into a toy!
A robot!
An airplane!
I guess this “Proteus” isn’t much of a threat after all.
Wolffy,
would you like to eat something?
Of course I would!
Turn into a balloon!
[Translation missing]
A spaceship! A bicycle! A toy!
No more!
Good thing I escaped,
or otherwise, I’d be dead.
There you are.
Stay away!
No more!
Goldy?
Chief?
It’s really you!
Chief!
We’ve finally met again.
Have you been well lately?
No,
I was bullied by a bunch of goats and a wolf just now.
You ran into them, too?
If my powers weren’t sealed,
I wouldn’t be so unfortunate
to be bullied by those animals.
Sealed?
Now that you mention it, you do look quite different.
It’s a long story. Here’s what happened…
…And so, BB Goat  accidentally sealed my powers.
I see.
It looks like this is the perfect time for revenge!
However, now that I have your help,
every problem is a piece of cake to solve!
My help?
Back then, when we teamed up,
we fought against countless enemies.
Just when it seemed like all hope was lost,
your powers always opened up a new door for us.
I was
that important?
Now, I just need to undo the seal,
and the entire universe will be ours!
Yes,
you’re right.
It will all be ours!
If that’s the case,
I’ll just wait for this to be over to steal it from you.
Come on, then. Let’s get our revenge.
You seem to have dropped something, Goldy.
Huh?
No, I didn’t.
Then
what’s this?
Let me explain!
No need for that!
I never thought
you’d honor me so much!
You kept my doll by your side all this time.
It’s so tattered now, yet you still won’t throw it away.
My good friend!
Exactly.
I’ve always honored you, sir.
Let’s go.
Let’s get our revenge!
Did you find Proteus?
No.
We’re back!
Hand over the—
Proteus!
Where did you go?
We were looking for you.
Turn into a slide!
What in the world is going on?
We’ve come to teach you a lesson, you know!
Didn’t you say you were here to get revenge on King Bacteria?
Don’t listen to him, sir!
How dare you…
No, let me explain!
How dare you lie about my friend to my face!
I’ll show you our true colors!
Goldy!
Yes, sir!
Fire!
Weslie!
Guys,
please help us out!
You’ve still got me!
It’s heat-resistant?
Gloves, huh?
Try mine!
Sparky!
Did you actually think I’m heat-resistant?
You’re right. I’m sorry.
I never thought they’d be so powerful together.
Alright, no more fooling around.
Give it to them good!
Okay!
Accept your defeat!
I did too much transforming.
I need to catch my breath.
What do you want?
You think all that shapeshifting makes you powerful?
I’ll be back!
Stop copying me!
It’s time to go home for dinner.
Until next time, then.
Wolnie, I’m home!
Not you again!
Unless the seal is undone,
we’re staying right here.
Who gave you permission, huh?
Get out right now!
Someone help me get rid of them!
End