Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Team Treasure Hunt
Once upon a time,
a brave adventurer used a treasure map
to get to a mysterious cave.
He passed through collapsed rocks
as well as traps made of man-eating plants and big boulders.
Finally,
he found the rare treasure.
Treasure!
I want it, too!
That’s just a story.
It doesn’t actually exist.
Maybe there’s no treasure,
but I have a treasure map.
That doesn’t look anything like a treasure map.
Where did you find that?
I found it under Brother Weslie’s bed.
Under my bed?
Look,
this is where to go next!
Those are my straps.
Wait!
There’s no “treasure” at my house.
I found it!
Huh?
I never thought you were this childish.
The new map piece says that the next clue is at Brother Paddi’s house.
Mine, too?
Found it!
There’s one at Sister Tibbie’s house!
What in the world?
Done!
It’s complete now?
Could the treasure actually be real?
But
why wasn’t there one at Sister Jonie’s house?
I don’t know.
Well,
we might as well go for a search.
Yay! We’re going treasure hunting!
Treasure hunting!
BB Goat ,
be careful. Don’t go too fast.
The cave must be right up ahead.
Hey, wait!
It looks like they’re going to a cave to treasure hunt.
Back in our day,
we had those kinds of happy moments, too.
“Happy”?
It’s very dangerous up ahead, Goldy!
Don’t worry, though.
I’m here to protect you!
Your Majesty…
Watch out!
Are you okay, Goldy?
Thank you for saving me, Your Majesty!
You’re safe with me.
Goldy!
It’s okay, Goldy! I’ll take it down!
What should we do, Your Majesty?
This way!
We had so much fun on our adventures back then.
Only you did!
I was the one who kept getting hurt!
Oh, yeah.
If we set up some traps along their path,
catching all of them will be as easy as pie.
Good idea!
Let’s get going!
We’ll be encountering monsters soon.
BB Goat  will protect you!
We know this place.
There aren’t any “monsters”.
Just let a little girl have her fun, won’t you?
Guys,
there’s a monster nearby!
BB Goat  will protect you!
That sound… Could it be…?
I knew it.
Wake up, Brother Paddi!
It’s very dangerous here.
There’s not a single thing here, BB Goat .
We should just go home and sleep.
Look,
it’s a cave!
The story says that the treasure
is deep inside the cave!
Wait, what?
Come on, guys!
Slow down, BB Goat .
BB Goat !
Are you guys okay?
We’re fine. Be careful, guys.
—Your Majesty!　—What’s going on here?
It’s probably just too run-down.
I’ve got a Plan B.
I snuck some extraterrestrial man-eating plants
onto their path up ahead.
BB Goat !
Watch this!
It’s a man-eating plant! Just like the story says!
Now’s not the time to be happy, is it?
This adventure is getting more and more interesting.
Come on, we’re close to finding the treasure!
They got away again!
Be careful.
There’s going to be a big boulder up ahead.
How do you know that?
The story says so.
We’re not giving up just like that!
What’s going on?
Look, here comes the boulder!
Run!
I’ll block it!
The boulders are real!
We’re losing it!
There we go!
It’s too heavy!
Tell us how to escape it!
This way!
Follow me, guys!
Thanks.
They got away again!
Well, at least we didn’t get injured this time.
How exactly are we supposed to capture BB Goat ?
If what they’re doing is treasure hunting,
then their goal is to find a treasure chest.
I’ll transform into a treasure chest, wait for BB Goat  to come,
and then…
Good idea!
If only the treasure were real.
Treasure is just a thing for little kids.
I don’t care about it.
Look,
there is a treasure!
It’s real!
I’m still just a kid, okay?
Go ahead.
I’ll be capturing all of you very soon!
Is it safe?
Let’s go take a look!
This isn’t the place.
How do you know that?
See?
The treasure on the map is under a tree.
The treasure map must be wrong.
It’s a trap!
What now?
It’s you!
Were you the one behind all those traps earlier?
You should have known. It’s too late now!
Run, BB Goat !
Don’t let him get to you!
You want to run?
BB Goat !
It’s you, Mr. Banana.
Well done, Goldy.
Keep an eye on them.
I’m undoing the seal right now!
My treasure map!
Yes, Your Majesty!
BB Goat …
A treasure map?
They’ve tricked us again!
I can’t believe it!
Why don’t I find the treasure first?
I’m stuck.
Where are the goats?
Right here.
You’re on your own.
Wait!
Help me!
Be quiet. We’ll be done soon.
Let BB Goat  go!
How did you guys get here?
Where’s Goldy?
I’ve failed, Your Majesty.
How stupid are you?
Can’t you just transform into something small to escape?
Oh, yeah.
Watch this!
I’m even more stuck now!
I’m sick of you!
Maybe I’ll try again next time.
Just you wait!
If we know that King Bacteria was lying to us,
why are we still digging for treasure?
Just let BB Goat  have some fun.
I found the treasure!
What the…?
Paddi, your drawing of me is awful!
Your drawing of me isn’t much better!
Start over!
No way!
Come here!
Come back here!
How about we hide the drawing
and leave it for when we grow up?
This is our treasure map.
Keep it safe, okay?
Okay.
So, the treasure map was real?
This was our treasure.
Brother Weslie,
why isn’t Sister Jonie on there?
That’s because I wasn’t living here at that time.
Let’s make a new one with our memories, then.
I want to draw!
Let’s draw together!
All done!
This is our most valuable treasure!
End