Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
Meeting a New Friend
Paddi,
I told you not to bring all of those nuts!
Hurry up!
Don’t get lost!
Don’t worry.
Even if I were to get lost,
I’d just meet you guys at the big tree on the mountain.
What are we going up there for?
There’s a meteor shower tonight.
We’re going up there to watch the shooting stars.
But “Shooting stars” are just rock.
I’ve already seen those before.
A meteor shower won’t be the only thing, though.
There’s a new friend waiting for you up there, too.
A new friend?
Let’s hurry!
My nuts!
Oh, for goodness’ sake.
You’re always giving us trouble!
Hey!
It’s gone.
Where are Brother Weslie and the others?
Mommy! Daddy!
Where are you?
I told you not to bring so many, but you just wouldn’t listen.
Where’s BB Goat ?
Wilie!
BB Goat ?
—Have you seen BB Goat ?　—Have you seen Wilie?
Wilie’s missing, too?
Well, you see…
Wolnie,
why must we bring so many things
just to watch
a meteor shower?
The mountaintop is totally empty.
What if we need something?
Mommy, Daddy, come on!
I want to
meet my new friend right now!
I haven’t seen him this happy in quite some time.
Exactly.
Slow down, Wilie.
Where’s Wilie?
We turned around to search, too,
but we didn’t find him.
BB Goat ’s missing, too.
Let’s go search together.
Mommy, Daddy, where are you?
Who are you?
Why are you crying over here?
My name is Wilie.
My name is BB Goat .
I was going with my parents up the mountain to watch the meteor shower,
but I got lost.
Me, too.
My friends got lost, too.
You’re the one who got lost.
What should we do, though?
Don’t worry. Even if I were to get lost,
I’d just meet you guys at the big tree on the mountain.
Let’s go find them together.
No.
My dad says that when I get lost, I should stay in one spot.
Let’s go!
It’s dangerous to run around!
Let’s just stay put, okay, BB Goat ?
There could be monsters around.
Look!
What’s this?
These are dandelions.
Just blow on them,
and they’ll fly.
They’re flying!
It’s so pretty.
It’s a bird!
Wait for me, BB Goat !
Luckily, I overheard Wolffy saying
that he has plans to watch the meteor shower with Weslie and the others.
What’s so interesting about some random cosmic rocks?
I wouldn’t be going
if it weren’t for the sake of capturing BB Goat .
This place is huge, though.
How are we supposed to find her?
It’s BB Goat !
What is she doing here?
It is BB Goat !
Plus, Weslie and the others aren’t here.
It seems to me that they’re lost.
Transform into a cannon.
I’ll go after her.
They’re just two little ones.
We don’t need to do that much, do we?
If we make too much noise, we risk luring other people over here.
That’s true.
What are you doing, Brother Wilie?
I’m making a sign for my parents.
If they see it, they’ll be able to follow it and find us.
Okay!
All done.
Look,
this is me, and this is you.
If I’m the first to capture that little goat,
I can demote His Majesty and become the king.
What are you smiling about?
Watch this, Your Majesty.
Goldy can’t do anything.
I just knew it.
I’ll take matters into my own hands.
Get up!
They’re getting away!
I’ll teach you how to pick them.
Take the bait, my fishes.
I think I hit something.
That’s fun!
I want to try, too!
Oh no,
you hit a beehive!
Run!
What’s going on?
Where’s that goat?
I can’t take this anymore.
I’m going to capture you right this instant!
Mud monsters!
Wilie made this sign.
BB Goat  must have drawn this.
Are they in danger?
If only my dad were here.
It’s a shooting star!
My dad says they make wishes come true!
I wish my dad would fly over here to protect us.
Those are just rocks.
You’re too young to understand.
My dad is amazing!
I know he’ll fly over here to protect us.
My dad is amazing, too.
He can also fly.
My dad invents things!
My dad captures bad guys!
My dad makes traps!
My dad can do everything that your dad can do!
Aha!
I can use the traps that my dad taught me to face the monsters.
What are “traps”?
Here, I’ll show you.
Okay.
There you are!
I’m getting you for good this time!
Someone’s that way!
These are Wilie’s traps.
This way!
They’re on the other side!
How do we get across?
Aha!
Be careful, Wolffy!
It’s my dad!
BB Goat ,
my wish came true!
My dad really did fly over here to rescue us!
We’re here, too.
Transform!
Hot!
I need to possess someone.
Wolffy!
Not the bees again!
Not again!
Are you okay, BB Goat ?
Don’t run off anymore, okay?
Okay,
I won’t.
You too, Wilie.
Don’t run off anymore, okay?
Okay.
Wilie,
she’s the new friend I was telling you about.
So, BB Goat ’s actually the goat who’s looking for her brother?
He’s your new friend.
So, Brother Wilie was actually my new friend?
Yay! I have a new friend!
Beautiful!
BB Goat ,
make a wish.
It really will come true.
I hope I find my brother soon.
I hope BB Goat  finds her brother soon.
My wish will come true very soon.
My wish will come true sooner than yours will.
Mine will!
End