Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
War of Dumplings
What?
You’ve never made dumplings before?
What are “dumplings”?
Dumplings are a very delicious food.
Have you made them before, Brother Weslie?
Well…
Mom, Dad,
look at this dumpling I made!
Not bad!
Look at you. You look like a kitten.
Mom,
Dad,
you guys are Papa Cat and Mama Cat!
Of course I have.
I want to make some, too!
Okay,
I’ll teach you how to make dumplings.
First, we have to make the dough.
Next, we knead the dough.
We also have to make the filling,
roll out the wrappers,
and then make them.
BB Goat ,
is this one of yours
a pig?
No, it’s not a pig!
It’s you, Brother Weslie.
Weslie,
we’re here for the dumplings!
Hey!
BB Goat  made all of these.
I’ll go first!
No,
I got here first,
so I should eat first.
No,
I should!
Enough of that.
I made these with BB Goat ,
so I’ll be eating them first.
No! Me first!
Me first!
Me!
Ew!
Fine, Weslie. You can eat them first.
It’s your favorite, Paddi, so you can eat them first.
Sparky, you got here first, so you can eat them first.
You can go first.
No thanks.
You first.
Brother Weslie,
won’t you try some?
I really want you to.
How is it?
Is it good?
Yay!
You can have all of these!
Oh, yeah, I just remembered that I’ve got something to do.
Brother Weslie! Your dumplings!
Brother Weslie,
finish eating the dumplings first.
Otherwise, they’ll get cold.
Where did he go?
There you are, Brother Weslie!
Brother Weslie?
Where did he go this time?
Brother Weslie!
Where in the world did Brother Weslie go?
Weslie?
Wolffy!
What are you doing here?
Uh… I…
Come have dinner at my place.
Are you sure about that?
Come on!
Where did Brother Weslie go?
If Weslie eats all of the dumplings,
he might get diarrhea.
But as long as Weslie doesn’t show up,
BB Goat  will keep on waiting.
Why don’t we make a sacrifice and help them out?
You’re not thinking of eating those dumplings, are you?
Here’s the plan…
[Translation missing]
BB Goat ,
can I trade these snacks of mine
for your dumplings?
No,
I’m saving these dumplings for Brother Weslie.
Then how about these toys for your dumplings instead?
Want to trade?
Go away!
BB Goat !
All good?
All good.
The dumplings are all good.
It looks like BB Goat  just won’t be satisfied
unless Weslie eats the dumplings.
Brother Weslie,
have some dumplings!
You’re having dumplings today, too?
Yes, I made these myself.
Mmm!
They’re delicious!
Great!
I’ll go make some more!
These dumplings don’t taste good at all!
For his first time making dumplings, Wilie’s already done a good job.
To prevent discouraging him,
we always tell him
that they’re good.
But of course,
we do have to give him some advice
so that he can make progress.
I see.
Ready!
Try them.
These ones are even better than the last!
I think your dumplings taste amazing!
They’d be even better with less salt.
Okay!
Have another one, Daddy.
Sure!
Thanks, Wilie.
I made these dumplings myself.
Have some.
I think that the dumplings you’ve made
are amazing.
I like your dumplings, too.
I’ll make more dumplings for you to eat!
Actually, the dumplings I made for the first time weren’t good,
but my parents would say that they were.
That’s why I had the motivation to keep trying.
BB Goat ’s parents aren’t around, though,
and her brother is missing, too.
If I don’t encourage her…
Thanks for having me,
Wolffy!
Weslie’s full already?
We must capture BB Goat  this time.
Here we go!
Mmm!
What are they eating?
I think they’re eating something called “dumplings”.
Let’s get some for ourselves, Your Majesty.
The last one is for you, Daddy.
They’re all gone.
We’re not here to eat dumplings.
We’re here to capture dumplings.
I mean, we’re here to capture BB Goat !
BB Goat  is right up ahead.
What’s taking Brother Weslie so long?
BB Goat !
Brother Weslie, are you finished with your thing?
I’ve come back to eat your dumplings.
Dumplings!
We’re not here to eat dumplings!
We’re here to capture BB Goat !
BB Goat !
Got you!
Your Majesty,
aren’t we here to capture BB Goat ?
Are you okay, BB Goat ?
Where are the dumplings?
King Bacteria!
These dumplings look quite tasty.
Those dumplings are for Brother Weslie!
Give them back!
Delivered yourself to our door, I see.
BB Goat !
—BB Goat !　—The dumplings!
Get them!
Paddi,
it’s time for our newly designed fatal attack!
Merge!
You’re not going anywhere!
Have a taste of this!
Goldy!
Have a taste of my power!
Paddi! Sparky!
We’re safe, BB Goat .
I got the dumplings!
My dumplings!
Eat the dumplings first, and we’ll have more energy.
Disgusting!
I never thought that they’d use dumplings as a weapon!
Good thing we’re safe.
They said that my dumplings weren’t good.
Actually—
They’re right.
It’s okay, BB Goat .
The dumplings that I made for the first time weren’t good, either.
Really?
Let’s try again!
I’m sure they’ll taste good.
Try out our new and improved dumplings.
Don’t worry.
They’ll taste good this time.
Exactly.
Just try them.
Let’s try them, then.
Mmm!
Yay!
You try one too, Brother Weslie.
[Translation missing]
They’re so good!
Hey, leave some for us!
That’s mine, Paddi!
You’ve eaten too much!
End