Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
The Doll Friend
Ouch!
Who’s there?
Who are you?
Is it King Bacteria?
I’m playing hide-and-seek with Brother Weslie.
Don’t tell him I’m here.
Is BB Goat  here?
I’m not.
Oh, really?
Not here.
Found you, BB Goat !
There you are!
I thought you’d gone missing,
Duo.
Duo?
I sleep with this teddy bear every night.
Yay, I’ve finally found you!
Being that newspaper
almost cost me my life.
Come on, Mommy!
I want to be the first to the amusement park!
Since Wolffy’s not home,
I can take over the place.
Your Majesty!
Who’s there?
I thought it was Wolffy.
Tell me about your undercover mission
of spying on BB Goat  yesterday.
Yesterday
was the worst day of my life.
Ouch!
The goats are always by BB Goat ’s side.
I couldn’t get close to her.
Wolnie always forgets something.
Who’s there?
Maybe it was just the wind.
They must be planning something.
I’ll eavesdrop.
Oh, yeah,
BB Goat  found a stuffed animal yesterday.
She won’t let go of it.
Aha!
I can hide inside the stuffed animal,
and when BB Goat  gets close, I can unseal my powers.
I need to notify the goats.
It’s you!
This is the Dutchman’s Pipe.
Wow!
Some animals love to eat them.
Once upon a time, there was a little bear,
carefree and worry-free.
I’ll be right back, Duo.
I’ll hide in the doll and wait to undo the seal.
Brother Weslie,
let’s play house!
I’m busy. You can play with Duo for now.
Okay.
If only Duo could move.
Duo?
Darn it!
Brother Weslie, Duo’s moving!
Look!
Duo!
Duo?
Why isn’t he moving?
You must have been mistaken.
Wes—
No!
I was sent by the moon to come play with you.
My moving is a secret. You can’t let other people find out,
or I’ll fall asleep permanently.
I don’t want you to sleep!
Keep still!
The King told me to keep a close eye on you.
Oh, dear!
There’s no use in crying.
I’m crying for you.
Me?
You’re clearly more powerful than that King Bacteria.
Why, then,
are you always number two?
Don’t tell me you’ve already conceded and accepted that title.
Of course
I haven’t.
Your Majesty!
What…
What did you call me?
Your Majesty,
let’s leave together to capture BB Goat
and prove that you are the true king!
I’ve been waiting for this day.
Let’s go!
Wait,
aren’t you friends with the goats?
Let me out!
How dare you tie me up!
I’m done with you.
I need to notify the goats.
Come back!
Let me out!
Let me—
How dare you trick me, Wolffy!
Not only did you trick me, but you’re also making fun of me!
If I don’t teach you a good lesson,
I’ll never be able to live with myself!
Keep still.
I need to think of a way to get her handprint.
Done!
Why did she make me pose if she only painted my face?
Great job!
By the way,
can you draw something on my stomach, too?
Sure!
My powers!
BB Goat ,
why is there paint all over the floor?
I was so close!
The doll’s all dirty.
I’ll wash it for you.
But—
Help me!
There you are, Duo.
Brother Weslie isn’t here,
so we can go fly kites together.
Weslie’s finally gone,
so I’m not doing this anymore!
Hold on tight and run, Duo!
Where are we going?
I’m not playing with you.
I’m stuck!
Help me!
Duo, how did you get up there?
I’ll rescue you, Duo!
Roll the line in!
What?
Duo!
Wait for me!
I’ve stopped at last.
I’m coming to rescue you!
Huh?
Grab my hand, Duo!
Oh no,
BB Goat  will cry
if she falls.
If the goats hear it, I’ll be in trouble.
I’ll just
have to
sacrifice myself.
Duo, you saved me.
Are you okay?
I’m
fine.
I used up all of my energy to save you just now.
What can I do to help you?
You can help me regain some energy
by putting your hand on my stomach.
Here?
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
Keep it there.
Weslie!
Wolffy,
how dare you make fun of me being number two!
How fast!
Stop right there!
Stop!
Watch this!
A bomb?
Counting down!
Ten!
Nine!
Eight!
Seven seconds left. I’ll be fine!
Seven!
Two!
How did you speed it up?
One!
Help me!
I’m not number two!
Are you okay?
Yes, but BB Goat  is in danger.
King Bacteria is trying to capture her by hiding in her doll.
No wonder BB Goat  said that her doll could move.
Let’s find BB Goat !
Is your energy done charging?
Just a little more.
I’ll be regaining my powers very soon!
BB Goat !
Paddi?
No big deal.
One versus one is a piece of cake.
What?
Why did they all have to come now?
Even Wolffy’s here!
Where’s Proteus?
I can’t get caught!
You’re not going anywhere!
He’s gone.
Duo!
Duo, why did you run away?
Where did he go?
He’s right up ahead. Get him!
Good thing I escaped from that doll.
Stop!
This is exhausting.
King Bacteria, you have nowhere to run.
What should I do?
Your Majesty, I’ve come to help!
We’ll show you just what we’re made of!
Careful, guys!
Once Proteus recovers from his injuries,
you’ll see just what we’re made of!
Duo, why aren’t you saying anything?
Duo, do you still not have enough energy?
Wake up,
Duo!
I think Duo
went home.
You know about Duo’s secret, too?
Duo’s task was to play with you.
He completed it,
so he went home.
Just keep loving him,
and I’m sure he’ll come back again to play with you someday.
Come back soon, Duo.
Let’s play house together, BB Goat .
Yeah!
End