Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
The Search for the Sun
There’s still no sign of BB Goat ’s brother.
She’s going to feel let down again.
I have an idea!
If we fulfill some of BB Goat ’s wishes,
she’d be very happy.
Yeah,
I have all sorts of different candy.
I can read her all sorts of stories.
I can help her make all sorts of beautiful clothes.
I can take her wherever she wants to go.
BB Goat ’s just a little girl, though.
I’m sure her wishes will be very easy to fulfill.
I want to find Mr. Sun!
I want to know what Mr. Sun does after sunset.
Uh…
Anything else
that’s a bit easier to fulfill?
Didn’t you say that any wish would be possible?
Yes, of course!
Really?
Yay!
What should we do?
The Sun’s almost setting, too.
How exactly are we supposed to search?
Aha!
Searching for the Sun, huh?
Your Majesty!
Can’t you knock first?
What do you want, huh?
Your Majesty,
BB Goat  is looking for the Sun.
I can transform into a sun and get close to her.
And then, I’ll jump in and capture her.
Good idea!
Transform now!
The Sun is round…
It’s round…
Where did my soccer ball go?
There it is.
Here’s my Super Kick!
Ouch!
The Sun glows…
It glows…
Where did I put the light bulbs?
Now, I can switch it.
This is a very strange bulb.
Why must you always disturb me when I’m in focus mode?
You can already glow,
so all you need now is to transform into a Sun-shaped light.
Let’s go get them!
BB Goat  won’t be able to meet him anyway,
so let’s just make up a story about what the Sun does
after sunset.
Good idea!
After sunset, the Sun transforms into the light on an anglerfish’s head,
illuminating the oceans.
Come have a look!
This is the anglerfish exhibition.
Is Mr. Sun over there?
The fish ate Mr. Sun!
I got it wrong.
These are the anglerfish’s own little bulbs,
not Mr. Sun.
Then what does Mr. Sun do after sunset?
After sunset, he becomes Santa Claus,
going out every now and then to send presents to children.
Mr. Sun sends presents, too?
The Santa Claus meet-and-greet is happening tomorrow.
Don’t miss it, guys!
This isn’t Santa Claus.
This is Santa Claus’ identification.
He’s real.
You lied to me!
We’ve run out of options.
What should we do?
I have another idea!
Just wait for me.
BB Goat ,
let’s search for Mr. Sun underground.
Is Mr. Sun really in here?
Mr. Sun has had a long day,
and he’s out of power now.
After sunset, he has to stay in a cave to recharge.
Weslie, what exactly have you planned?
I buried a toy sun in there.
Just have her follow the map I made, and she’ll find it.
I found Mr. Sun!
The toy sun is over here.
Then what did BB Goat  dig up?
Maybe we won’t find Mr. Sun today.
No,
I’ll be sure to help you find Mr. Sun today.
Really?
I promise.
Thank you, Brother Weslie!
Let’s head up the mountain.
Weslie,
have you thought of an idea?
Yes.
Weslie,
what exactly is your plan?
We’ll buy some time with BB Goat
and have someone appear all dressed up as the Sun.
Sparky,
since you can control heat,
you can use a flashlight to add some glow.
You’re best suited for this.
Good idea!
I’ll go right now.
BB Goat ’s right over there.
In a moment, transform into the Sun and lure her over.
Roger that.
Where did Brother Sparky go?
—He’s going to the bathroom.　—He forgot to water the plants.
—He forgot to water the plants.　—He’s going to the bathroom.
I’m hungry.
BB Goat ,
I’ll take you to pick some apples.
Okay!
I’ll join you guys.
Now,
we’ll just wait for Sparky
to finish dressing up as the Sun.
BB Goat , Mr. Sun is right here!
Sparky was quick.
What a realistic Sun.
How are they not suspicious of Goldy?
Also, why did they mention Sparky?
Hold on,
where’s BB Goat ?
BB Goat  and the others went to find food.
They’ll be back soon.
How does he know what I’m thinking?
Here comes the Sun!
You’re Sparky?
Then where did this Sun come from?
Uh…
Darn it. I think it’s over for us.
Yes,
I sent him!
What do you want?
I just want BB Goat  to undo the seal, is all.
SInce she’s not here,
I’ll deal with you guys first!
No way!
Attack them now,
Your Majesty!
That was blinding. I can’t see anything!
Didn’t you bring sunglasses?
I forgot to cover my third eye.
I suggest that you hand over BB Goat
and save yourselves the trouble.
There’s no way we’re doing that!
Let’s split up and attack.
What should we do?
Even if we attack together, we’ll be blinded by the light.
No more chatter.
Let’s go!
How dare he sneak up on me!
Flash him!
Yes, sir!
See what I’m made of?
It’s your chance to attack, Your Majesty!
Where are my sunglasses?
It won’t matter how many times you try!
Ouch! Hot!
When did you take the sunglasses?
That was thanks to Paddi pulling the sunglasses over to me.
We did it!
It’s Mr. Sun!
So, Mr. Sun sleeps in the forest after sunset?
Yes, exactly.
What are you waiting for, guys? Let’s go.
Mr. Sun is tired from providing light all day.
Let’s let him sleep
and not disturb him.
End