Mighty Little Defenders 2: The Intriguing Alien Guests.
The Adventure Legend
This is fun!
This is very dangerous!
What if you accidentally crush her?
No more barbells!
Understood, Mr. Slowy.
Keep up, BB Goat !
Wait for me, Brother Sparky!
Riding scooters this way is very dangerous!
You need to wear protective gear to prevent injury!
Alright, you can continue.
I brought milk.
I’ll warm it up so we can drink it.
Coming right up, BB Goat .
Those footsteps…
Could it be—
That’s very dangerous!
Milk can’t be heated up!
Plus, heating dairy products will cause them to explode!
You’re a bit too vigilant, Mr. Slowy.
What are we even allowed to do?
Welcome to
the sea of knowledge.
Reading is the worst!
I like this picture book.
Nightmare Canyon
is an area that countless explorers have aspired to conquer.
To this day,
there has only been one explorer from Green Green Grassland
who successfully conquered Nightmare Canyon.
I don’t want to live such an ordinary life!
I’m going to conquer Nightmare Canyon!
I don’t want to live such an ordinary life, either!
Yours is already unordinary,
so sit here and keep reading
and be as ordinary as you can.
Sir,
the camping tent is all set up.
You can rest for the night.
Good job.
Keep it up.
From this point forward,
there will only be one leader in the pathogen gang:
me!
Why are you laughing?
Strange. What is he up to?
I was just reminiscing about our past,
like when we went camping together.
Oh, so you want to go camping?
We’ll go.
Thank you, sir!
This is
camping?
Eating delivery
and having AC…
This kind of luxurious life doesn’t come easily, does it?
But…
This type of “camping” is so underwhelming.
Really?
I’ll fix that.
Wolffy!
Who is it?
Who’s there?
What’s the matter?
It’s you again!
Come here!
I just finished cleaning!
How about it?
Not so underwhelming now, huh?
Enough!
Stop right there!
Who exactly is Green Green Grassland’s mysterious person?
I’m sure I can also conquer Nightmare Canyon
if he gives me even the smallest bit of advice.
Head straight,
Let’s find the mysterious person!
arms by your sides,
and feet firmly on the ground.
Smile no matter what.
Hang in there!
Tyger must be that mysterious person!
Lizard!
Tyger!
If he’s afraid of lizards,
there’s no way he’d be able to cross the Nightmare Mud Pit.
Big Humphrey is super strong,
so he must be the one!
Snake!
How could he possibly get through Python Forest
if he’s afraid of a string?
There’s no way that Mr. Slowy is that mysterious person.
Forget it.
I don’t need anyone.
I can conquer Nightmare Canyon on my own!
Sir,
the camping tent is all set up.
You can rest for the night.
You were right.
You need the wilderness to get the thrill.
Exactly.
Come with me!
What’s going on?
According to the book,
Nightmare Canyon should be around here somewhere.
Who’s there?
I’m a little tree.
What are you doing here, BB Goat ?
I want to explore, too!
We’re man-eating plants.
King Bacteria!
Stop!
Let’s go, BB Goat !
—Stop it! Come here!　—Hand over BB Goat !
The shapeshifting banana guy is here.
I’m not a banana!
You have nowhere to run!
Goldy!
Yes, sir!
Come here!
Come here! Stop!
Hand over that little one!
Don’t even think about it!
It’s… It’s a quicksand pit.
Ew!
Help me!
Oh no, we’re sinking!
Help!
Grab it, Sparky!
Mr. Slowy!
You guys came to Nightmare Canyon?
Good thing I saw that book and followed you.
I’m sorry, Mr. Slowy.
Hold on.
Mr. Slowy, are you saying
that this is Nightmare Canyon?
Yes.
Also, after I got in, the entrance closed,
so we’ll just have to keep going ahead.
But it’s a quicksand pit.
How are we supposed to cross?
Don’t just look straight ahead,
but in all directions.
Look up.
Vines?
Follow me.
How are you so fast, Mr. Slowy?
I do tai chi every day, you know.
Help us!
Goldy, turn into—
We’re out of the cave at last.
It’s a river!
Stop, Sparky!
There are so many crocodiles.
I’ll fight them!
No. Impulsivity is not the answer.
Sparky,
collect some branches.
Distract them with the branches first.
Now,
jump!
You’re so smart, Mr. Slowy.
Let’s just get out of here first.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Sir…
Help!
The exit must be right up ahead.
Be careful, though.
It’s a huge bug!
Sparky!
Don’t worry! I’m fine!
But
this thing has a lot of power and size.
Take this!
What?
Darn it,
I messed up.
Move.
Move!
—Mr. Slowy?    —Wow, Grandpa Slowy!
We’re safe.
The little one is mine!
Out of my way!
One more time!
I’m going to get you!
You can do it, Your Majesty!
We’ve gotten out at last!
Mr. Slowy!
BB Goat !
I never thought I’d also conquer Nightmare Canyon!
Me, too!
Mr. Slowy,
you carried us through.
How did you know all of that?
Just read books and study well,
and you’ll be just like me.
I guess there was a deeper reason
for why you wanted us to read books earlier.
Does this mean that you’re the hero
who conquered Nightmare Canyon, Mr. Slowy?
Who knows?
I bet I look rather cool responding like this.
End