Exposed
Children, do you seem to need help?
I’ll help cut vegetables! Fast and fast
The sword goat is great!
The dishes are cut
Why did they cut faster than me? It was even more!
Old man, help me hold it
It depends on mine when it’s done
This is my newly developed smart grill
Really real fireless cooking
360 degrees of shooting and roasting
Ensure that every part of the food is heated evenly
Colorful gold yellow, external burnt and tender
I want to eat roasted sweet potatoes!
no problem!
You’re fine, Mr. Master!
Is it flickered to the waist?
no…
But there is no electricity here and I can’t use my grill
Come and eat sweet potatoes
It’s actually baked! ?
And so many?
Be careful
Very burning!
Why were you so careless?
I remember there are herbs for treating wounds nearby.
I’m looking for it
Village Chief
No need to be so troublesome
The young people are so terrible now
You can’t accept old age
I’ll hand it over to you here
We went for a walk three of us
The King
I thought of a way to catch BB Goat!
The food is cooked and the village chiefs go where are they…
Keep searching
Isn’t that the Master’s Water Body?
Is there an accident?
We’ve followed
Prepare it
You have to go to the next location quickly
Walk the small road
…
Keep up with everyone
This is the knife in front of the sword goat…
It hurts so much
It’s going to stop. Stop!
BB Goat, stop playing
Let’s take a look at it in front
It hurts so much!
I have to go to the next place
There are two roads ahead
Which line should I go
Can’t let them go
So tired…
You see, it’s the village chief’s crutch
Something happened to the village chief!
Why are you still dripping water?
Everyone, come here
The village heads must be in trouble now!
Save for our friends Cheers!
Cheer!
It’s getting late
If the children don’t go back, they will be anxious
Who is there!
What’s going on! ! !
King Bacteria
What happened to the village chiefs?
Don’t mislead your village chief
My goal is BB Goat
Where is BB Goat?
Here!
It seems we’ve figured it out
I just realized it’s too late
BB Goat
Let me melt this broken pot
Useless, this is my specialty
Let me use my clone to go out!
No use either
The gap in this syllable is also my good
Little Butterfly
Is it okay to go find the village chief to save us?
no problem!
These butterflies seem to be from Tibbie Sect
Butterflies, do you want to dance with me?
They seem to be telling us something
Are you thinking too much?
No
Does he mean to let us go?
Could it be that Weslie and others have something to do with them, right?
Take us over quickly
They’re leading us
The road was blocked
Leave it to me!
Let’s go
Daoyang Your sword technique is still so darn
Help
King Bacteria!
Who are you talking about?
No time to explain
It’s just a bad egg
He can’t be able to unlock it successfully! but
How can we go on?
Fortunately, I haven’t forgotten
Look at this
You brought the flying vehicle too
The Three Guests of the Grassland
Depart!
I wonder if the village chief received the signal?
We’re here!
King Bacteria, take the call!
Come on! Village Chief!
未分! Why are you on the wall?
I’ll go and save the mutton king.
good
Xiao Huang
Bladey!
You two still have time to care about others
You are too weak!
No one can stop me now!
Master, Village Chief!
Haven’t been moving for a long time
The reaction has slowed down
Yes, it’s time to move
Lift your head and Weslie!
We are just getting hot!
Master, Village Chief!
Very resistant to punching
But I just can’t stop me!
Catch you!
Please start your performance
Mountain Crush Special Upgrade Edition
Village Chief, you are so terrible!
Children, let’s go back
Village Chief, why are you so bad!
Let’s talk about our story slowly when you go back
good!
That time I got my knife down
At the same time, the three cannibal trees were left to the end
Then we went to that cave
I saw the big spider…
Why are you falling asleep