Loved dad mom
Although you are not by my side, I have many friends who are with me
Let’s play football together
Share food together
Read the book together
We spend every happy day together
Weslie
Go to play football!
Come right away! You go first!
They are my most important friends
This is
Aerospace school records to win the letter!
Aerospace School is a school that studies outer space in the Aerospace
So as long as I read to the aerospace school
I’ll have a chance to meet my dad and mom
That’s right
But this school is very difficult to take
It doesn’t matter
To see my dad and mom
I will definitely work hard!
Great I want to tell you this news right now
Brother, this room is so beautiful
Where is it
Aviation School Boarding Guide
Request a lodging
Isn’t that just separate from everyone?
Brother, what’s wrong with you
No... nothing
Then let’s go and have fun with everyone first
You can’t escape
Give me the chocolate!
No door! !
Where is the soap...
Success!
I ate this piece of chocolate!
I should have eaten this hole I dug
It’s not me who turned into soap
How can Wolffy fall into a hole?
It’s not me chasing him
How could he step on your soap?
I didn’t find chocolate first, why would you chase the gray wolf
I am the king and I should eat it!
If you hadn’t stopped me from studying in the Dark Army
The king now is me!
How could I stop you
It’s just that you can’t get diarrhea
That’s because I got my stomach up after eating the candy you gave me!
You can’t go back anyway! Just be my subordinate!
No!
I won’t be your subordinate anymore!
From this I am the king myself!
Leave the chocolate to yourself!
I don’t care!
Don’t eat it for nothing
Don’t be stupid! Weslie
How should I tell them
Weslie and Goat follow!
Weslie
You’re fine
Nothing is OK
Weslie, look at your hair!
Brothers Brothers
I’ve come and eaten watermelon!
I’m here! !
Let’s leave some for Weslie! !
Everyone can play together
Weslie, come and eat it too!
Otherwise, they will be eaten up...
What about Weslie
Is he uncomfortable?
He’s been absent-minded
Did you just kick him?
Can you finish eating two of them?
Sister Tibbie
Brother Weslie has lost his letter
This is
It turns out that Weslie is going to read on the grassland
It must be because you keep stealing his cake
You’re talking! ! !
You must be the one who always played football! ! !
It must be you
It’s you!
Sister Tibbie Goat What’s wrong with Brother Weslie
Weslie He is going to a very far place
Will leave everyone for a while
I don’t want Brother Weslie to leave! ! ! !
I want to play with him
Don’t leave!
BB Goat, don’t hurt
Let’s ask what Weslie first
Weslie
Weslie Brother
Have you found Weslie?
no
Chief, found it?
I went to the place he often went and didn’t see it
Didn’t go home either
What about Sparky
Village Chief
I just received the letter from the college
Yes
That’s great. The Astronomy Institute...
It’s a Sparky!
Boiling...
And there are also complete space equipment
As long as you study hard
yes
I dreamed of dreaming even
I’m really happy to go there to study
but……
I’m not allowed to leave my friends
I’ll give you this too
Tibbie, let me come and move it
Thank you Weslie
Don’t come here!
Flat mouth flat mouth...
Weslie, you’re fine
I got the signature, Chief
Thank you for Weslie
Weslie sacrifices itself for us every time
He went to the astronautics college
Then we should support him!
This time we did something for him
Blue sky White cloud
How can I eat chocolate without music
Xiao Huang sang a song to me!
I forgot that he had left...
Xiao Huang…
I will be the king from now on!
No need to help him catch goat, sing, and change his weapons...
you
When you’re bored, you can read the book
If you are tired of reading books, go and see the plants
Helps the eyes
Don’t just read books and continue playing football
Otherwise you won’t win me
If you’re tired of playing football, eat the snacks I’ll give you
Then you will think of me
You all know
Although we can’t let you go
But as a friend
We should support you
Go and realize your dreams!
I have the chance to come back and see us!
Everyone
You are my best friends!
I don’t want Brother Weslie to leave
You don’t want to leave
- BB Goat...
BB Goat
Weslie Goat Go to School
I don’t listen! I don’t listen!
BB Goat! !
You’re all bad eggs
Can you please apologize to him?
Do I apologize to him?
- Xiao Huang
Why are you here
I have to care wherever I go! !
I can’t control it! !
you…
You don’t have anything to tell me?
no! !
-right…
-sorry
we
Reconcile! ! !
No, I don’t want to separate from Brother Weslie
BB Goat! danger!
BB Goat grabs tightly! I won’t drop yours!
Weslie Brother
It’s OK
Very good!
Weslie Brother….
You... will you really not let me down...
Of course! Whether I’m in Yangcun or the Aerospace Academy
I promise to come back to tell you the story as soon as the holiday is over
Go to the grassland to play football together
There are also paintings together
You said! ! No doubt I’m going to be cheated! !
Very touched, I remember to come back to see me often
Why are you here too, Big Wolf
All are harmful to bacteria
You are here!
We found Weslie and the others!
You’re fine!
You’re more
I have one thing to announce...
I decided...
My brother is going to a new school!
congratulations! Weslie!
Thank you everyone
We haven’t watched Xiyang together for a long time
I didn’t expect that Weslie has been gone for a week
I think Weslie has lost its appetite even though it has become smaller.
I also thought he had an illusion...
Weslie Brother!
Why are you back
Because the Academy of Aerospace Sciences aims to popularize astronomical knowledge
Branch schools were opened throughout the grassland
In other words, Weslie doesn’t have to leave the Goat Village!
I’m not dreaming!
real
Very good!