Been discovered!
King, run away! !
There is actually a helicopter!
Xiaohuang quickly transforms!
No way out!
Where do you want to run
This time, I won’t completely eliminate you!
Launch!
Do it! Not here! !
What’s the situation
Stop quickly! !
How could this happen! !
This is
I’ll catch BB Goat and go back
He finally arrived
Who is he
Our new helper
Why don’t the lights open
We came in with the village chief
When the light is opened, you will be discovered
Then what are we going to do here
Of course, I’m here to see the super big TV newly bought by the village chief!
It’s a waste to watch animations! !
Yes Yes!
What is this sound
Is it the sound of a TV?
But we haven’t opened the TV
It’s too dark here
I’ll go open the lights
Why did the lights open by themselves! !
This! That’s it!
King, it’s been so long
Your new helper hasn’t caught the goat yet
Can he do it alone
Don’t underestimate him
He came and shot a single gun
I once controlled an entire planet in an instant! !
Such a darn
Could it be that he has also come to win the position of King?
Then I will never be the king
But we still have to support him
Because he has a very fatal weakness
This is the latest game
I couldn’t find it before if I wanted to play!
Fun Fun!
This butterfly looks so beautiful!
nice! nice!
Buy Buy Buy…
Buy all buy
I’ve pushed a fitness tutorial here!
It’s a fitness record of the Wolf Corps!
I’ll try it too!
There are so many interesting videos in this app!
Very delightful
Like a little like a little like a little like!
Buy…
These low-headed people in the big data era
I can’t escape my clutches
What is this
you…
How did you come
Don’t you have information on your phone that attracts you?
It looks so strange
I’ll tell you to see this! !
It turns out that everything you see is what you have developed
But these pictures are watching
What a bad thing it was broken
It seems delicious! !
How about a small program like this!
The program invented by the village chief would not be so feasted
Who are you
What’s wrong? Goat
Look at it
Is this TV poisoned?
Now that you have discovered it
Then I won’t hide it anymore
I’m the subordinate of King Bacteria
Digital virus!
Everything here is controlled by me. You’ll be obedient
Kids, don’t press the appliance
It seems that he must appear on the illuminated screen
If we turn off the phone, he won’t show up
Then we’re shutting down, too
Underestimate me
Do you think this will destroy me?
What’s going on
It seems that he can be between digital products
As long as there are electric and electrical appliances
I’m just invincible!
You want electric, right?
I’m here!
I’m here again
Here… Here… Here
Continue here! Here
You’re going to be quick
Please
You’re very weak
Close the total gate and see where you can still run!
Is it successful?
Always calm
Where is the virus here? It’s so difficult to deal with
We rushed to tell the village chief
Wait a minute.!
BB Goat is missing! !
what!
Stop and don’t run!
So many snacks!
There! !
It was indeed him who caught BB Goat!
Don’t eat it! It’s all mine
BB Goat are almost released!
I’m catching up soon!
Don’t leave!
Weslie!
Weslie, you’re fine!
It’s OK
But he ran away
This digital virus is too harmful
What are we doing now
Leave it to me
He’s a culinary guy
Only I love delicious food can deal with him
Come with me!
Finally got rid of them
Very delicious
Why did you eat up all your snacks? !
I want to eat too
Lots of snacks! !
It must have been the sky that fell to compensate me
What’s going on
It’s you!
You really got my guess
what
How dare you mess with us
Let you take a look
Our harm!
Sure enough, he still can’t escape the intimacy of delicious food
King!
What happened to you!
Of course I came to save my partner!
See what I brought you
Dare to deceive me
Let’s see how I teach you!
superior!
The three of us join forces and there is no enemy in the world!
He doesn’t seem to have powered
Don’t turn off the machine!
Move to other equipment quickly
All the equipment is broken! !
The king cheers up, and I’m
We will definitely come back!
Remember to come back next time
Help! !
Who can help me stop it! !