What is the situation with Xiao Lü?
I found out that the little lambs went to find Brother BB Goat’s search
A remaining old goat protects BB Goat
The success rate of the operation is now as high as 98%.
good
We’re on!
I like eggplant the most!
It hurts so much!
Really!
Wow! It’s eggplant!
Eggplant! How did you come?
What eggplant
No matter what! Let’s unseal the seal first!
What’s going on? Why didn’t there be any reaction?
Big... King...
I’ve...
I’m here, what else do you want to unzip the fingerprints?
I just use the virus to help the king unblock it!
Oops, it’s bad!
So what should I do now?
Give me half a day
I must fix it!
What are these?
Eggplant!
What exactly is eggplant?
Where does this little eggplant look like this king?
Eggplant! I want to be a hero, too!
Don’t come and laugh at me Don’t come and laugh at me
Yes, the belt has not been repaired yet
If she is trained to become a bad egg
good
Let this king not
I’ll come and train you carefully!
Really? Very good! Thank you for the eggplant!
What happened! ?
Now I will teach you the hero’s title!
OK Eggplant!
Call me a teacher!
Yes, teacher!
First, I will teach you the external temperament of a hero.
As a hero, your eyes must be full of wickedness
No matter how it’s like a little coquettish
Let’s make a surprise box
Shocked me!
You’ll try it
So cute, how scary...
Just do what I teach you
Done very well this time!
The rest are the slightest trip of King Bacteria.
It’s been so stressed
I dared to sleep so well!
Hello! ! ! ! !
Evil bacteria
Wait for me to come up with a secret weapon
What secret weapon?
What qualifications do you have for your young follower?
Call your boss
I’m not a young follower!
I want to become the new king!
Hand over the secret weapon!
I’m not a hard person
You’ll have no effort
It just made you very hard
As long as I get the secret weapon
Then leave the green grassland to conquer other planets
All right
Is this the secret weapon that can defeat King Bacteria?
That’s right!
Old Goat, you’re cheating me!
Who told you that you were so anxious
What bad things are good to do?
It looks very precious...
It’s time to test your cultivation results
There is a regular fried egg hidden in that package
Throw it in the trash can
OK, teacher!
BB Goat
Thank you for throwing the trash
It seems that this picture is very important...
Tyger is painting
You can use the pictures on his body to help him paint and give him some spirit
OK, teacher!
Oh my God
It is a long-lost painting of the wild beast school!
Too wild
You are such a genius!
what!
Block the road and don’t let him pass!
thank you
Dig out all his dishes!
Thank you Thank you
BB Goat, you disappoint me so much!
Teacher! Wait for me!
Don’t follow me!
The king’s waist belt has finally been repaired!
I’m a little tired after repairing it for so long
I’m going to rest
Is the virus going to rest?
BB Goat
I still need you
It’s all my fault for being useless...
No!
Your performance is excellent!
Really? Teacher! What do you want me to do?
Let’s massage my waist first
OK!
Let go of BB Goat!
How come you’re here
The carelessness made the old goat slip!
what!
Still not chasing?
yes!
Slowy
Why do you want to attack Eggplant?
Eggplant?
Heroes who have been installed for so long
He shouldn’t be able to find us now
I’m going to find eggplant!
Wait, what eggplant is there?
It actually delivered to the door by myself
Have you seen eggplant?
Eggplant is the original...
No
Eggplant has been dealt with by this king
The next one is you!
You are such a bad egg!
Look at the trick! Eggplant surprise box out
Use what I taught you to deal with me?
What’s the use?
Help! There are monsters!
Help!
You wake up and these are just dolls!
As the apprentice of Eggplant
Look at the trick!
I’ll teach you this trick
I won’t be caught
Launch!
Too much score!
Fight you first
I have a treasure
Hello! Weslie Come soon...
You think it’s the king
You don’t want to hurt the Slowy!
BB Goat, go quickly!
It depends on whether you are worthy of your cooperation!
Eggplant saves me!
If you scream, no one will come to save you!
What do you want to do?
I actually want to bully such a good kid
People who are willing to take the initiative to help others and get trash now
She has found a new creative spirit for me
You don’t want to bully her!
What do you want to do?
What do you want to do BB Goat?
No... What am I not doing
I’m just joking
look! Flying disc!
No
Is it okay? BB Goat?
Duoyuan Eggplant Teacher
Who is eggplant?
What is the situation with Xiao Lü?
There is still only one old goat left
And the king’s demeanor has not been understood
You can use the hero again
Very nice little
Prepare the clothes of the hero that BB Goat likes
Why a skirt?
Princess Tomato!
Don’t look at eggplant anymore?
My favorite thing now is Princess Tomato!
King, don’t hesitate
Children’s interest is fast
The success rate this time is as high as 99%.
This king doesn’t know how to wear skirts!
What a joke! What a joke!