There is no dirty person on the entire grassland
I can’t find anyone to control me!
Little green! Search for someone I can control
It’s better to be strong
Or agile
Have you heard it clearly?
Have you heard it?
The user you are calling is not in the service area
please…
Is there anything wrong? Not here at the time of the key! !
Where is Xiao Huang?
King, to help you better
I’m going to attend the International Weapons Exhibition
There wasn’t a single person! !
In the end, it’s up to me!
I’ll leave my house to you for the past few days
It’s wrapped in me…
Wilie wants to hear his father!
- See you again
How many days has the Red Red been away from home…
Finally, I can study my bacteria cleaner with peace of mind
This time, you must completely eliminate the bacteria!
Dad, let’s go out to play!
Be good, son, please play yourself first
Dad will play with you when he is done. OK
Be good, son, go out to play first
But I want to play with my dad…
It seems that I am the only one who plays it myself
I have found a dirty one!
The child is still in good health!
Very powerful
I’m going to try this kid’s ability tightly!
Just it!
It hurts so much! !
Does this kid like to play football?
That must be running very fast
Try it out!
Why don’t you look at the road?
It was you who bumped into me first!
So cute! !
Forget it, forget it…
You were also accidentally, do you want to eat ice cream?
Little brother, see you again!
That’s OK…?
It turns out that this child’s ability is cute
Brother and sister of the lamb
I’ll play together too!
It’s Wilie
Weslie Brother
I want to play your treasured remote control
So cute!
I’ll get it now!
Brother Sparky
Can you help me pick up a flower?
Where is it?
Where is it!
no problem!
Brother Qingyangyang I want to eat cake!
good! I’ll do it now
Sister, I want a rag doll
good! Let’s get it!
Now… no one will come to fight me!
BB Goat
Come with me, okay?
Brother Wilie…
Your eyes are so big, is it because you have entered the sand?
BB Goat is so cute!
No! What? What’s going on?
Why is it useless for younger children?
It seems that I can only get tough!
Come with me!
Small gray
Weslie! ?
The remote control you want
Small gray
- The flowers you want!
The remote control you want
The toy you want!
I want to play together, too!
It’s over!
Let me play alone with BB Goat! ! Is it OK?
Of course it’s OK
BB Goat, let’s go!
Let’s go to a more fun place
no
Brother Weslie said that you can’t go back too late…
That…
Then you come here tomorrow and I will take you there!
OK OK OK!
Don’t tell anyone else
These are our two secrets
The bacteria cleaner is made! It depends on where you run away!
Scan complete No bacteria found
What’s going on?
germ! Come out if you have the ability!
no
Could it be that they moved away?
Very good! Finally, I can calm down!
No
This is too quiet
Right! Where is the son?
Little Huihui! Where are you?
I’m back
Son…where have you been?
Why is your body so dirty?
How about dad help you take a shower
How can I control Wilie after washing it!
Don’t wash! I won’t wash it!
no!
If you become dirty, you have to wash it
I won’t wash it!
Son! Stop being rude! Go and take a shower!
It’s absolutely impossible for Wolffy to succeed!
I don’t want to take a shower, okay?
Of course it’s OK if you want to wash it
Get some food quickly
How can you talk to your dad like this
I’m tired!
OK OK OK OK…
I’ll make you a meal!
It seems that controlling Wilie is also good!
My son is so abnormal today
Dad, let’s go out to play?
You go outside to play first
Is it hard to tell if I didn’t play with him so I was angry?
I will definitely accompany him tomorrow!
BB Goat
Brother Wilie! You are here!
Finally, it can be unblocked!
Then let’s go!
good!
Wolffy! What are you here to do?
What did you call me?
I won’t call you Wolffy! Do you want me to call you dad? !
No!
Son…
This will be discovered…
Dad… Dad
Son, Daddy has been playing with you all day today. OK!
You go and do the invention
I’ll just play with BB Goat
No, it is more important to accompany you!
Then help me get that ball!
Son, the air ball you want
I want to have ice cream!
Son, the ice cream you ate is here!
I want to eat fruit!
Son, the fruit is here!
Don’t want it!
Son, slow down! Be careful of falling!
Then don’t chase us!
right! Don’t chase us!
Not good! Weslie!
Little Huihui! Wait for me!
Don’t chase us anymore!
Son!
Save us now
Don’t be afraid, I will save you!
It’s a little bit short…
Very…
You’re fine! ?
We’re fine
If you too much, we’re fine…
What… What?
Frustrated bacteria We won’t let you catch BB Goat!
It seems that I can’t unblock this time. I’ll find a chance to withdraw
You are calm!
This… This is my new invention
We won’t be cheated by you
I’m not controlled!
Look, I’ve said that I’m not under control!
sorry! sorry
Where are my sons going?
Son? Where are you?
Little Huihui! Why are you back by yourself!
People… They want to go home
My son is so good
It’s daddy who is wrong
Bacterial cleaner?
Yes, just press it lightly
Discovered bacteria
what!
It turns out you are on my son!
It’s hard to blame my son for being weird before! It turns out you are controlling him!
I’m so cute.
Make a dream!
Don’t run