Choose a perfect angle
A sentence with another sentence...
Seaweed and durian is absolutely suitable
Send
What a poem this is...
I’ve taken it!
You should try my new work
You’re not saying this
Will eat a stomachache
must
These are you
I don’t know how to appreciate my food!
The big bun looks delicious
You immediately liked the noodles
I’ve replied to my poem!
Why do you have to show your dismissive look!!
The noodles are also put on your online
Of course
Xiaowu is my loyal fan lover
It seems that he is a very knowledgeable food
You might as well keep it for him to taste
Done beautifully
Yes!
I can get the noodles out
Send!
You don’t need to taste it for me!
goodbye!
You are willing to come out and taste the noodles
He..., he asked me out!!!
What to do?
Go!
Master, please suggest that I go and see my friends?
But I haven’t prepared yet
I’m asking you to lure BB Goat over!
My stomach hurts again
It’s all because of last night and
I’ll hand it over to you here
come on
All right…
No reaction here
It seems that I’m going to do something wrong!
That’s...?
Get on the hook
Why is it Ugly not me!!
Will the car talk?
Haven’t replied yet?
The toy car will still talk now
What does a toy car say?
BB Goat Stop
Want to guard me?
BB Goat!!
Just hate you
I want to win me too!
I won’t win you
But I have a trick!
Weslie, come quickly!
What... I actually called for help!
Paddi!
Don’t leave if you have any worries
The king and the others are not here
Have to withdraw first
The little kid, if you can’t win, ask someone to help
I will definitely not let you go next time!
what
Didn’t you run away too?
You’re the strength
Don’t let me meet you again!
Fortunately, I run fast
There is a message!
I sent so many messages
Is the mobile phone intact?
Is the signal bad?
Is it hard to tell that he doesn’t want to see me?
There is a reply!
Lovely little cake...
Your fee is less than 10 yuan. Please recharge it in time
What to do? !
It’s a noodles!
Lovely little cake I miss you too
It’s just that something has happened
So that’s how it is
What happened?
Today I met a guy who was having sex
If he can’t beat me, I will call for rescue
What a strength! strength!
Such a coincidence
Today I also met a strength
I ran away if he couldn’t beat him
I’ll teach you a trick
Next time he wants to run, you can use it
Boulder-pressing crab
Then I’ll teach you a trick, too
He shouts again next time
You just use a terrible finger to him
He kept laughing and couldn’t call for rescue
I really want to meet you soon
That afternoon, see it on the tallest tree in the forest
I will bring you seaweed and durian nuts to taste
good
Don’t get along if you don’t see it!
So what clothes should I wear?
No! I don’t have a body!
How
Have you caught BB Goat?
no
Are you still playing with your phone if you haven’t caught it? !
It’s all my fault
It’s all my fault for not having a body
If I had a body
A hundred BB Goat have been caught back
That’s right
I’ll help you build a machine body
The King
I want to be a little older
Hair style should be more fashionable
Add six abdominal muscles to it
It’s done
I’ve made you one
Fashionable hair roll
And strong arm
I still don’t want such a body...
I don’t care, please come in quickly!!!
My stomach hurts again...
never mind
Let’s go see the cake first
It smells so good
no!
This is for the noodles!
Even though that’s what it means...
But when will the noodles come?
Hello, I’m Xiaoba
First time meeting, please take a closer look
No, too serious
I am your friend Noodle noodles!
Isn’t it too hot...
That’s...
Small cake!
Very... So tight...
I hear the deer in my heart
I’ll go to the bathroom and you’ll leave
What to do with when you walk so quickly?
What are you looking at?
I’m trying to catch BB Goat
So you thought so
This king is very pleased
Then let’s go out now
Big... King...
You... your stomach doesn’t hurt
It’s okay, I’m taking medicine
Let’s go quickly
I think I’ll go to the hospital for another blood test
Making an ultrasonic...
- What’s the radiation treatment...
We’ll come back to check after catching BB Goat
Let’s go, you’re
All the lambs are here, let’s watch it first...
Listen to me first!!!
Resolve them tightly and have time to see the cake!
Where is the robot?
Danger! Danger!
Who are you!
This is the digital virus that I created the machine body!
Digital virus?
Even if he becomes a robot, I’m not afraid!
Yes?
Let the lamb see your evil spirits!
Tibbie!!!
Sparky? !
I’m fine
This is...
District oil
Look at me!
Sparky  Stop
Oil is a flammable substance
When you heat up, the oil will burn yours
Is this still happening? !
It was actually discovered!
But it’s OK
Get rid of them!!!
Come and untie this seal
BB Goat!!
We’ll save you!!!
Please go and call the Goat
Noodle noodles?
Where are you going to take me?
The seal can be unveiled immediately!
You’ll be dealt with soon
who?
It’s you!
Paddi!!!
It hurts so much!! My head hurts so much
Honey!!
We’re meeting again!
Butterfly help!
Want to bring reinforcements again!
Look at mine...
No! No! No!
!One finger!!!
One finger?
It’s up to me!
Boulder-pressing crab!!!!!!
Why do you get a big rock to squeeze a crab?
How could you be so stubborn?
It’s hard to tell!
Can’t you tell me?
Seaweed and durian is absolutely suitable
The puff looks so delicious!
Noodle noodles!
Small cake!
Please take us out
What’s going on?
King Bacteria
You actually escaped
Little Green, come on!
This king is tired
Get rid of them next time
Noodle noodles…
Why is the small cake a goat?
That’s...
Seaweed and Durry Lotion…
I really want to taste the cake
But I don’t have any taste...
Then I’ll tell you...
It’s you?
I didn’t expect you to be a noodle
But I promised you to taste it
Let’s eat together I’ll describe it to you...
Don’t think too much about it, I’ll leave after I’m talking
Start
Crispy seaweed wrapped in durian
It tastes crispy on the outside and tender on the inside
Fresh and beautiful seaweed
Then it can only be described in two words
Difficult to eat!
It’s hard to eat, it’s hard to eat, it’s hard to eat...!
The sticky smell of seaweed
To stop noodles tightly
Already eaten!!!
That...
Do you feel how delicious it is?
Feeling...
It’s the smell of short circuit
I don’t deserve to eat, it’s all you blame!
Don’t run! Huh!
You are the strength!