I bought the most important left and right hand to my pass!
The most important right and left hand? It must be talking about me!
Who do you go and help me get the express
I’ll come I’ll come!
This is the gift that the king bought for me?
I’ve got this one
Or I’ll get it
I’ll take it
Are you doing?
Be careful not to hurt my express!
I’ve got it myself
You can’t do such a small thing well!
King, I’ll help you!
Fight with me?
We used to fight back to back
Two enemies!
Do you have it?
What’s so amazing about this…
I and the king also played games together
Watched the TV series together!
You dare to tell me trivial matters!
I…
Once, the king was cramping in the sea
I traveled 10,000 meters in one breath before I rescued the king!
Then I’ll take the king to the sea to catch fish for 20,000 meters.
Despicable villain
Taste the taste of crazy elevators!
Is it fun?
The King
I’m here
BB Goat
Today is the first children’s festival you have visited the Goat Village!
What do you want today we can do to you!
Really!
You said!
I’m going to take risks!
simple!
I want to fly to the sky to find the sun to adventure!
Want to experience the volcanic eruption!
I also want to venture in the deep sea
BB Goat
These places seem to be too dangerous…
BB Goat, okay, should you play this first?
Brothers and sisters will definitely help you find your wish!
Then I’ll go to start the car first!
Let’s prepare quickly!
King, I recently learned about the latest massage chair!
Should the king try it?
OK! My waist is indeed a little sore!
King, is this strength appropriate?
Can
Master, what do you think of my left and right hands?
very good!
That king, you are ready…
mean!
It hurts so much. Stop
Stop quickly!
You’re fine, king!
Fortunately, you caught me
I’m the left and right hand!
You will definitely not be in danger!
Master, let’s go play games!
OK!
What’s going on! ! !
I’ll know!
It must be you, a despicable villain, who is doing it!
You started playing tricks first!
Big… King?
You two! A massage chair to fold me
One thing that made me unable to play! You bring me out!
It’s all your fault that you stopped the king from playing games!
It’s your first massage to destroy the King!
I am the king’s right and left hand!
It’s all… strange… you…
Strange…you…
If I catch BB Goat!
The king will definitely punish me!
You may not be able to get rid of me!
Car?
Brother and sister! The car is on!
Don’t open too far!
Did you hear the car? Can’t open too far!
The car is so fast
I caught BB Goat!
Waiting for you for a long time!
Flying Flying!
danger! Why is BB Goat there?
Xiao Huang, please let me go!
Why is my aircraft out of control?
Stop
Give me BB Goat!
not good!
Help!
Didn’t you say that you and the king caught fish at the bottom of the sea for 20,000 meters?
Why are you still afraid of water?
I want to catch fish too!
What we are talking about is the undersea fish in the game!
But you also said that you are so terrible when you swim
Then take us back!
Great
That’s…
Help!
King! I’ll save you!
What? It seems that the water flow is getting more and more urgent?
Look ahead!
It’s a waterfall!
Change the motorboat out quickly!
well!
What is this!
Turning into a motorboat!
I… am tight
OK, sit down!
Maximum horsepower!
Where did BB Goat go?
Very fun!
BB Goat!
Oops! The lambs are here!
Speed up quickly!
Don’t want to run away!
Don’t be afraid of BB Goat! We’re here!
Look at me!
Flying Flying!
BB Goat!
Quick change aircraft!
good!
See you again!
If you don’t control it
We can’t come back smoothly, either
If you weren’t a boat and a plane,
We’ve all fallen into the river
The king’s surprise should belong to you!
Give it to you! Give it to you!
Why not let us go together?
good!
The king will definitely like the gifts we prepare!
You are here!
King! we…
I won’t be angry with you anymore
You see
Hand cream and hand sanitizer I bought for my left and right hands online
After using it, are my hands smooth and clean?
Hand cream?
handwashing fluid?
What are you talking about?
It’s my left and right hands!
There is still a small block that has not been found.
what! It’s not for us!
You go!
BB Goat
Brother and sister!
BB Goat, are you okay?
I’m fine Brother Weslie
I had a lot of fun!
What happened?
OK OK Don’t worry about that much
It’s good that people are fine
Go home and have a meal!
Amazing
What is this?
Is it for you again?
No no no no…
It’s for you two to prepare
The king…
But you have to wait for you to catch BB Goat
This kind of motivation is good!
Blame you!
You sent the lamb out!
It’s all your fault!
Your door opens!
what!
I’ve fought with you!
BB Goat Sorry
We can’t realize your wishes
No!
My hope has just come true!
This is my best children’s festival!
BB Goat is so cute!