Which one is better to wear
Wolffy has been busy in the laboratory for several days
It must have been prepared for today’s wedding anniversary
Change your clothes and see him
Eat it, too
Take it, and take it
Go back and have a good time to sleep
I want to eat too
What’s wrong with you, Master?
The wolf just passed by is very scary
I wonder what gift Wolffy prepared for me
It doesn’t look scary
Stop it
Go back quickly
Why don’t there be potato slices
I’ll go back to get it
You go back first
I’ve been preparing for this long just for today
The final details are very important
Can’t make a difference
Cable gun! Finish!
With this gun, I can run away the bacteria
Take a box and put it in. It’s not good if you find it out by bacteria!
What’s the special box
Red?
See you this important wedding gift
I’ll feel relieved
gift…
I forgot that today is the wedding anniversary!
Even though they have been insomnia for a few days
But as long as you have the heart
Gifts aren’t important anymore
Wolffy! ! !
Red This is not a gift
Actually, I hid the gift
I want to make you surprised to find me to prepare for it myself!
Really
No doubt I’m going to be cheated!
It’s really really...! !
Is it romantic to find gifts like this?
Gifts… Gifts…
You have to prepare the gifts carefully...
Red
I’ll be back soon!
I like to eat potato slices the most!
Has anyone come?
Is it hidden here?
What is she looking for?
There is no...
Where is it hidden
I don’t want to find it
Been discovered...?
Why are there so many potato slices here?
Put it back
No! ! !
Don’t take my potato slices away! !
Who are you, how come you were here?
I…
I am…
Say it quickly! !
Otherwise I’ll...
I am a deformed spirit that can become anything!
Deformed spirit?!
Who is the cheating!
If you don’t believe it, you’ll be optimistic!
This…
Diamond ring?!
So amazing
Could it be that this is the gift that Wolffy gave me?
Since that’s the case
Can you become something else, spirit?
Of course
All tired of playing
- Change the air to cool me up
The king said it was right!
This wolf is indeed very scary!
Come and save me!
It’s hard to come back yet
Who is not good to mess with?
King, what are we doing now?
Is the strength OK?
More force, one above
Xiao Huang is so frustrating!
Right
I can control the TV to attract her attention
Let Xiao Huang have the opportunity to escape
Good idea
Want to lose weight?
Come with me to learn how to lose weight
Fat do?
Almost forgot the time!
One Two Three Four Two Two Three Four
Run quickly
The King
Finally I can take away her!
I need a hula hoop
Failed...
cockroach! !
Very dirty! !
Girls are usually afraid of cockroaches
This king went to scare her
One Two Three Four
- The King
This queen is the most annoying cockroaches!
Who is it?
quilt…
Been discovered...
I…
I am…
A spirit that can realize you want
Really hope...?
Yes...yes
I can’t tell this is also the gift from Wolffy to me
Wolffy is going to be surprised
Then you help me make the house super big!
no problem!
Be nervous...
Dare to cheat me
Who are you?
You don’t want to bully my king!
you…
Who are you...?
Spiritual! Help me to clean up him
yes…
I’ve suffered!
what…
Xiao Huang!
Little green!
We three to one
I’m not afraid of you!
Take the call!
Too much energy was consumed today
Please let us go...
- Give me a clean place!
What is this?
I’ll analyze it
This is a gun that can shoot a rope to tie someone else’s body
Cable gun?!
Can it be used?
It looks like a toy gun
What are you doing?
Dare to steal
Can really ejaculate the cable
If you have this gun, you won’t be afraid of her
you…
Do you want to do...
You’ve been hiding this
Don’t go too far!
Mom, I’m back!
Son, leave here!
mother!
Son!
Wait until Wolffy returns
Let’s see how he deals with you!
I’m back!
Red Red Son
Why are you being knocked up?
It turned out to be you!
I didn’t expect this gun to be quite useful
How will my rope gun be in your hands!
What do you want to do!
Let me open Red and my son!
Otherwise, you will feel better
Very verbose
Look at me sealing your mouth!
Where is the gun?
I’ve been tortured for so long
-Let me come!
I found the gun first
Give it to me!
That is the gift I have worked hard to prepare!
gift?!
My gift?
What a broken thing
But it’s fine. There’s a broken piece
Otherwise the butt will bloom
How can the snail be relaxed
How dare I mess up my gift...
Xiao Huang, hurry up and shoot her! !
It’s really useless!
Let me come!
Been...been opened...
I won’t... let you go!
只… 只火!
You’re fine
Red, you’re so terrible...
Wolffy
Who are these three people?
I was afraid you were in danger before
So I haven’t told you
actually…
That’s how things are...
So that’s what happened
Almost forgot
My Memorial Gift!
flower?
The real gift is definitely below
Red...
Sorry Red
Actually, I’ve been busy inventing it recently
Forgot today’s wedding anniversary
This is what I went out to find at the moment
Is there only flowers?
And this one
Didn’t you say you haven’t had a good sleep for a few days?
So I took honey that can help me sleep
Even though they have been insomnia for a few days
Wolffy
Your hand...
There is nothing stinged by bees
I’ll give you a medicine
Red...
You destroyed our wedding anniversary
Still want to run away?
Sorry... We are willing to make a cow and horse for you
That’s not necessary
Really
Give me a good supplement!
yes!
Red
Wolffy
When I unblock the seal, I will make you look good!