That’s it!
King: That’s it!
We have dug up the Yangcun School
And based on the Yangcun course I obtained through the Internet
The lamb and BB Goat are not in the same classroom
If there is no accident, the lamb must be in class now
Let’s continue to find BB Goat’s brother
And BB Goat must be at this position on our heads
As long as we dig through our heads
BB Goat will definitely fall
Little Green is well done!
Not a little bit! Let’s go down!
Why is it the Lord Baobao, BB Goat?
Mr. Baobao suddenly wants to check your school student
Weslie and the others are looking for your brother again
You’ll play at my house
OK OK OK!
We can play together again
Wilie shared the toys with BB Goat
What a beautiful aircraft
My toys are made by my dad
He’s playing with me
He is the best dad in the world
Of course
What I gave Wilie the best
BB Goat’s mother is not here
Only a group of lambs are taking care of
I definitely haven’t played any good toys
- Give him one too
Brother Weslie has just prepared this kind of aircraft for me
His aircraft!
Very… beautiful!!!
dad
Dad, you’re fine
Dad is fine
You play with BB Goat, Dad is going to have a meal
Have eaten
The grass salad made by dad is the most delicious
BB Goat’s parents are not here
I definitely haven’t eaten anything nutritious
Give her more food
But Brother Qingyangyang helped me prepare lunch
Her box of vegetables is of wide variety and balanced nutrition
I failed again
Bingbing…
Riding on a bicycle!
Brother Sparky also helped me prepare for my bicycle
See you again
Uncle Big Wolf sees you again
BB Goat See you next time
All my stuff was sent to a flock of goat
Dad, let’s play
Small gray
How can I get angry!
I must give Wilie the best one!
dad…
dad
Dad, teach me how to draw
Good Dad will teach you after he finishes his work
dad
Let’s play chess
OK, Dad will play with you after he finishes his work
Why is Dad so busy?
Dad will definitely give you the best!
This time, is it true? !
Believe me!
I just heard the phone number of Wilie and BB Goat
They made an appointment to play together again. As long as we ambush it…
Good job, we will act!
Someone has come
Why is it wrong again! ! !
I
you!
Don’t run away! ! !
This time
I want the whole Goat Village to know
I prepared the best stuff for Wilie
I want you to say it!
-Wow! This is the most fun thing I have ever seen!
This is the best toy I’ve ever seen!
I haven’t taken out the toy yet, so what if I do!
Wilie, my brother and sister made me a edible aircraft
A edible aircraft?
Very delicious!
It’s really OK to fly!
He actually made the aircraft a combination of playing and eating
I’ve sent it to the lamb again…
Dad, have you brought me a toy?
Let’s play together
I…
Forgot to bring it, I’ll go back to get it now
You will definitely find the best toys now on the Internet!
Computer What’s wrong with you! !
Quick… Wake up! !
Why…
Why is it useless for me! ! !
Why are you in my house again!
well…
Go quickly!
Stop lamenting! Alas, I feel resentful when I come to my house! !
well! ! ! !
What are you thinking about?
I failed again when I made a plan for the king
My experience is almost the same
Something I made for Wilie
Not as good as the one made by the lamb for BB Goat
well…
BB Goat…
Since our experience is so similar
Let us help each other!
Help each other?
As long as you use my precise calculations, you will definitely be able to make the best things!
Wait a minute.! Then what do I want to help you
It’s hard to meet a fellow traveler
Let me talk about my affairs later
Wolffy Where are you going? !
He doesn’t want to cooperate with me and wants to run away from me!
Just say it
Brother Wilie
Are you unhappy?
well…
Because…
dad
Son!
Dad brought the toys!
A very bad aircraft
His harm is not only
It’s candy!
My dad is the most harmful!
Dad finally gave you the best Wilie
Thank you, digital virus!
This aircraft can also take us to fly
Wilie!!!
What’s going on? Do you want to do a digital virus?
Didn’t you say that you would help each other?
Thank you for helping me get close to BB Goat
I can finally make contributions to the king
BB Goat? !
Little Huihui!
BB Goat’s brother
stop! Don’t run!
Wolffy!
Stop me!
Not overestimating one’s ability
Little Huihui!
Little Green You finally started to chant!
This time it was done well
Next is the unblocking ability
What’s going on? !
Let them go! !
Soon I’m catching up
The little lambs look at the trick
Jonie
- Tibbie
It’s useless if you have too many people
What should I do now?
I have a way to get you to catch up with him!
Go!
Don’t want to catch up
Look at the trick
Help!
It’s okay
It’s OK
Is this butterfly?
Weslie! I’ll send you to the plane!
Please! Tibbie
-dad
Let them go
Don’t think about it
The place is so small, it’s so tired to fight
This is whose hat!
This is whose hair is it!
This is whose rod!
The airplane’s slamming rod was actually shut! ! !
Digital virus Let’s stop the aircraft together!
good
You work hard, we’ll leave first
You just want to be blessed
Kill!
Come back
Can it be repaired?
I can only try to minimize the loss
dad
Little Huihui!
Wilie, don’t be afraid of having a father protecting you
There is a dad here
Wilie is not afraid!
My son
Weslie Brother
Wilie, you’re fine! ?
dad
It fell into the candy pile
Escaped again
Thank you for taking goat
Weslie
You’re fine
We’re fine
My dad and I are fine, either
Sorry, Wilie
Dad didn’t protect you
I can’t give you the best
That’s not!
Dad has been with me!
Dad just keeps with Wilie
It’s the best dad!
It turns out to Wilie
The best thing is my company
Sorry, son!
Let’s play together!