No! Can’t move anymore!
I didn’t expect to find it in Wolf Castle
Don’t slap it. Hand over BB Goat!
Don’t be afraid
I’ll protect you
I’m quite hiding!
It depends on how long you can hold it!
Good opportunity
Next, we are going to catch BB Goat!
I’m here!
Wait a moment!
Do you want this? Give it to you!
Who made you act? !
Don’t be tempted by my command!
Brother Weslie is so terrible!
Weslie!
Have some trouble, let him take a break
You go and find some anti-sweat medicine
good
BB Goat?
What are you doing here?
It’s bad to infect you
Weslie Brother, you are sick
Mom said she should apply a towel when she was burning
Drink more water!
Also, you need to reduce the heat and reduce the temperature
Prepare something delicious
Take this
And that one
Right Yes Right Yes And this one!
Also...
What else do you want?
Have a rest!
But I want to take care of Brother Weslie
Make him quick and good!
I need a good rest when I am sick
Don’t beat him up...
Village Chief! All the anti-burn medicines are used up!
Let’s find it together
good
Orange heat-reducing fruit...
It’s all your fault for slapping me
It was obviously you who snatched me!
I’m so embarrassed to say!
It’s all your fault! It’s all your fault!
Have you seen any orange heat-reducing fruit?
Haven’t seen it
BB Goat!
Then I’ll find it myself...
A great opportunity!
Hurry up and catch her!
Wait a moment!
What are you doing!
Have you forgotten what the king said?
I won’t be able to do anything if I have no orders in the future!
Let’s see what she does first...
Orange! It’s a fever-reducing fruit!
What kind of anti-hot fruit
Isn’t that just an ordinary orange?
Let’s help you
Picked!
Weslie Brother Eat Eat the Heat Reduction Fruit
What happened to him in Weslie?
King!
It turns out that Weslie fell ill
The lambs also went to find the hot-reducing fruit
The sentence says now
How did you know?
This was what BB Goat told us in private!
Did BB Goat tell you privately?
We met the single BB Goat in the Forest
And she found some heat-reduction fruits!
We are in the process of helping her
Is it harmful?
This time we didn’t act without permission!
what!
Then why don’t you catch her back directly!
You let us not be scattered!
It’s really not enough to succeed.
Weslie Brother!
BB Goat Why do you make it so dirty?
This is the heat-reducing fruit
You eat it, it’s okay!
Isn’t this an orange?...Silly kid
Thank you BB Goat
Weslie Brother, you will get better soon
It’s all up to BB Goat’s care. I’m much better now!
It seems that Weslie is really sick...
Our plan to wait for a moment is...
Small green
You dive into the room and control the cooling first
Reduce the temperature to a minimum and make Weslie weaker
I will then enter the room and unblock it!
Xiao Huang, you are responsible for sealing the window and locking the door
Let BB Goat escape without a chance
Then throw the key away
Then no one can come in to stop me from unblocking!
Let’s move separately!
yes!
How did the cold turn off?
What happened to Brother Weslie?
The cold is bad, let’s go out first
No! Go quickly, BB Goat!
All finished!
Why are you still here?
I haven’t gone in yet! What are you locked up!
Quickly turn into a key and open the door!
It hurts... My waist is about to break!
What should I do now?
Go and get the key back!
There!
I didn’t expect that after searching for a day, I couldn’t find the anti-hot fruit...
So tired...
How to be so...
What a coincidence...I’ll leave first!
Don’t want to run away! You must have something to blame!
I think I’ll let it go first!
Help me quickly, Xiao Huang!
Don’t pull me up!
It hurts so much!
Resist quickly!
Very burning!
Last hit!
Don’t beat the big guy! I surrender
Weslie and BB Goat are in danger
You go back quickly
what!
Is it warm or not...
BB Goat, don’t be so...
But it’s still very cold...
Come on, let’s move together
Then it won’t be cold
So tired...
Don’t sleep, BB Goat
Brother Weslie will dance to you!
good…
OK!
Come to BB Goat, let’s jump together
So cold...
BB Goat... BB Goat...
The cold is too high and it’s impossible to get close to
If he could get close to him...
Not good! He pulled out the cold power supply!
The lamb is back! Let’s go quickly!
Weslie! Weslie!
Save BB Goat quickly...
BB Goat is in a row again! Get on!
BB Goat Why did you run out by yourself again...
Weslie Brother I’ll pick the hot fruits for you again
Isn’t this an orange?
All depend on BB Goat
Weslie Brother is ready
No need to eat anti-heat fruits anymore!
So what should I do with these heat-reducing fruits?
Leave it to me!
What’s so funny about eating something...