Come and chase me!
You can’t escape!
Let me go!
BB Goat…!
I want to unseal! !
No!
It turns out to be a dream!
Xiao Huang, I have insomnia
oh
Why don’t I tell the king a bedtime story
Help you fall asleep
From now on, the goat pen has been disrepaired…
Can you say that you have feelings?
From now on
The goat pen has been disrepaired over time
The farmer has not gone to refill
Until a wolf caught the goat
Only farmers go to fix the goat pen…
There are loopholes! Why don’t the wolf run away when the goat come?
How did I know!
Go and ask Xiao Lü
He can check anything!
It says on the encyclopedia
Goat can’t see clearly in a light-free environment
The wolf has the ability to watch the night, so he can easily catch the goat
It turns out that this is…
Red
Red Red Is it OK?
Wait a little longer…
You have to dress up beautifully when you go to see the lunar eclipse
Wolffy
What do you think of my night pearl chain?
Good looking Good looking…
Let’s go up the mountain quickly. The lambs are all waiting in a hurry.
Yes!
Yes! Then let’s go!
There are many mosquitoes on the mountain. I’ll get anti-mosquito liquid.
It turns out that they are going to see the lunar eclipse with the goat!
I thought of a way to catch BB Goat
Come with me!
What are you doing sneakily
Oops, I’ve been discovered
Run!
There must be something wrong with you. You have to remind the goat to go!
Wolffy?
Wolffy! Why not bring me!
The goat…
What’s going on…
Come and play together…
A strength
Why do you want to scare me
Stop being rude
The flashlight has no power
We can’t see clearly during the lunar eclipse!
sorry
Look, the lunar eclipse has begun!
The moon has no light
The grassland is no longer clear
What’s going on?
It’s okay, there’s a flashlight!
King! The lights nearby have been completely drained
You can’t see such lambs
Is it King Bacteria?
Be careful, everyone!
Enter the darkness
Everyone, run away!
Go and catch the goat
BB Goat Catch me
I’ll save you! ! !
Sparky?
A goat?
Jonie?
Tibbie! Sparky!
Weslie Brother I’m really scared
Don’t be afraid that I’m here
Let’s go quickly!
Weslie Brother!
You just stay here
It’s your turn!
BB Goat!
You know you’ll be out and chaotic
Wolffy? !
Strategic retreat!
Don’t run! ! !
Uncle Gray Wolf, please save your brothers and sisters.
I can’t get their three bacteria
That’s so black
We can’t see it either
Can’t see it?
Then let’s go back to Wolf Castle to get lighting tools first
They’re walking here and tell the king quickly
I see
Let’s catch up with you
You stayed and looked at the goat
I’ll just go and catch BB Goat
All right
Looks delicious
Jonie, what’s wrong with you?
Too dark, I fell down if I couldn’t see the road clearly
Yes, I can’t see anything…
I’ll try to heat the wooden head to see if I can make a torch, right?
Sorry Sorry
I went to call the fireflies to come
Why didn’t you react?
Useless
All the firecrackers nearby were captured by us
Just put Wolffy’s automatic trap
Captured all the nearby firecrackers
We can catch the goat with peace of mind!
I’ll stop slapping
Don’t be too proud
Have to care about you
I’ll continue watching my food program
Food program?
Forget it, let’s eat something first
What about those strawberry bags?
In this
Strawberry bag?
One person, one
It seems delicious
It smells so good
Don’t watch No watch
Do you want to come one too?
Very delicious
Strawberry bread call
BB Goat! You’re fine!
It’s OK
What is this?
Isn’t this my catcher?
No…we can’t be so procrastinating!
Ballrooms Does anyone want Ballrooms?
bright!
Do you want to buy a basin?
Uncle Big Wolf has a balls sold there
careful
Maybe it’s a trap
So alert
It seems that I can only be serious
Buy one get one get one today
There are ballasts!
I want to buy a basin! I want to buy it! …
It’s a trap… Let’s go quickly
It depends on where you run!
Still want to run away?
stop! ! !
stop!
Let’s go now
So bright
That’s the night pearl?
You will destroy me and dare to come back now!
Red
I know it’s wrong!
Don’t be angry
Please tell me
OK, I’m sorry
Very good!
Wolffy! You left me alone
Everyone is fine, right?
There is no light, there is no way to walk well
Weslie!
Wolffy!
Weslie Brother We Found Guang!
Very good
You’re here too soon
yes
I’ve come in time, too
The red night pearl!
It just won’t let you have any light!
Let me teach this stinky stinger!
King!
-Let me come!
Everyone should be careful
The King
Catch BB Goat!
Good do!
It’s time to have a serious business!
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go!
It’s a snail!
How do you have my catcher? !
There are so many firecrackers!
yes
And see clearly
No!
Chase quickly!
Stop them!
Firefly
Let me open!
Look at the trick!
Very burning! Very burning! …
Very burning and very burning!
-No, I don’t feel the heat
I…
King!
Save… Save me
Now that the power has been restored
Then… Then I’ll leave first!
It feels so good to have light!
That’s right
Why do you feel dark again?
Wolffy! You left me and ran away!
And make my night pearl like this!
Are you fat?
sorry!