The monster "roared" and sprayed flames
Little Huihui appears-
I want to protect my mother…
child
What are you painting?
I’m painting my mom!
Is mom like this?
No
This is a monster
Mom hasn’t painted yet
Then what are you doing in front of monsters?
I’m protecting my mother
Dad said, "A real man should protect his mother"!
Then you have to make your mother look good!
I’m here
Don’t even want to slap my son
stop!
Screw me out of the Wolf Castle and don’t come back!
No hearing!
It depends on where you are going!
It’s all the appearance of that group of bacteria
Only then did Wolf Castle have such a lot of fun to see!
I must get rid of them!
Mom, what are we going to do this?
Clean up the garbage
What are these purple gases?
It’s a killer!
The "poisonous atmosphere" leaks. Escape quickly!
Don’t pull me
I can’t hear it again
What’s going on with you
The King
Yes… Yes, Wolnie!
you…
Bring me out of the Wolf Castle!
I am the king of bacteria
How can I recognize it!
Xiao Huang!
good
Since that’s the case
I had to do something wrong…
The Queen is dead!
That’s now!
He actually defeated me with his breath
The Demon King is so scary
This is simply a female devil
Who is here to save us?
It turns out that they are afraid of frogs…
You can enjoy paintings with peace of mind
Mom, go and clean up those cysts!
no
I need to find weapons to defend myself!
Why is there a cypress in the pot?
It seems to be wrong
no
Crazy Killer Crazy Killer!
In this
Female Demon King, you have today too!
King, you are so smart.
It turns out that you are doing it!
King, go ahead!
Xiao Huang Next!
No, I’m so happy
I want to rest…
King, why are you crying?
I’ve been bullied by this female devil before
We’re so worried
Let us suffer as much
Didn’t expect
We can finally turn over
The King
It seems that the female devil has retreated
What should we do next?
She was so to us before
Of course it is a victory to chase!
How to do it?
Walk
What a big strength!
Mom Mom
Mom, you’re fine, right?
Son
Mom is fine
That fleece is coming again!
Son, don’t be afraid
Mom will protect you!
Don’t bully my mother!
So terrible!
Small gray
It’s a child indeed
Just run away!
Son
You’re a man
If I’m not at home
As a man, you must protect your mother
I will definitely protect my mother!
I must protect my mother!
What’s the best way to do
This is…
There is a way!
Devil’s Female Demon King
You made me so wolfish in the morning
I want you to pay for it!
You’ve also damaged my robot body
You don’t turn on the cold weather when you are hot
I want you to pay for it!
What do you want?
That’s my high-end perfume!
don’t want!
This is the price that angers this king!
That’s my limited edition lipstick!
Not finished yet
mother
I’m here to protect you!
Wilie…
Don’t go over!
It seems that you want to play with Maomaoya!
How?
Do you want to escape this time?
I will definitely protect my mother!
What do you use to protect her
I…
I have a trick!
Just a little chicken
What are you afraid of!
Small gray
mother
You give me
I’m not a stinger
Don’t peck me!
Very dirty
I want you to see my evil spirit!
Xiao Huang transforms!
Xiao Huang, please change quickly!
Xiao Huang…
Female Demon King!
No more stings
Do you think you still have a way out?
The Queen’s life
Man Han
protect
mother
My good son