The forest seems to have appeared recently
The search for tourists from outside
I’m suspected to be BB Goat’s brother
You go search
Where is the brother of BB Goat
Everyone should be careful
So beautiful ~
careful!
Weslie!
careful
Don’t go past
quick!
Paddi!
Weslie: You’re fine, right?
not good
It’s okay
Wake up, Jonie
You wake up quickly
It’s all my fault
Everyone is tired
It’s okay
There should be herbs nearby…
Do you know why we can’t catch BB Goat?
That’s because you
Not brave!
What should we do to be brave?
Like me, I’m brave
You actually laughed at this king!
You’re such a big strength…
This familiar feeling
Poisonous?
It won’t
She’s here, right? !
she?
She is my other subordinate
She was attacked by a large circle of enemies before
She was so shocked
Unexpectedly released a lot of poison
Defeat a large number of enemies in an instant!
What’s scary is that she can’t control her abilities
Regardless of the enemy
As long as she encounters her poison, she will be hit
So terrible!
Don’t be stunned!
Escape quickly!
yes!
The grass trotters said by Nuanyang Goat
Where is it?
thank you
You are welcome
you
Are you a mushroom?
Mushrooms actually move
My name is Mushroom
It’s an alien
Come here just now
Please give me some advice
alien?
Are there such good aliens?
Why I’ve seen aliens
All of them are of this type
My name is Tibbie
What are you just doing on the cliff?
My friend sucked poison from the forest
I’m about to help them
Pick detoxification herbs
Poisonous?
It’s hard to say it’s morning
Those I let go when I ran away again
Please bring me with you
Go and help you
Help?
right
I can release my healing ability
Healing ability?
That’s right
Healing ability
Can quickly cure injuries
Really
It would be great to have you help
No No
I’m not good at all
What’s going on
Not doing well
Did the king mind me
Don’t want me anymore
It’s okay
The king won’t want you
King?
She won’t be
Let’s share with King Bacteria
The king is my idol!
He often does good things
Helping the old lady cross the horse road
Please eat lollipops for kids
and
He’s still very…
Such a good person
It’s definitely not King Bacteria
It seems that I’m so worried
But
I can’t find him now
But now
It’s important to treat your friends
Then the treatment is over
I’ll help you find it!
While the mushroom mushrooms are not found
Get out of here quickly!
yes!
Leave this to me
What’s going on!
It’s almost time to get my friends to rest
Still rely on yourself to be more stable
I can become King Bacteria
In addition to having strong abilities
It’s also very important to see straightforward
Go here
This flower can help my healing ability
Then let’s go quickly
King: You’re fine!
Why do you have her everywhere
I have an idea!
Just mushroom mushrooms
Learn about the king I worship
Being defeated
She will give up chasing you
Good job!
Tibbie…
you…
It’s finally nothing!
I’ve hurt you
sorry
It’s all bad for me
Tibbie
It’s OK
We didn’t blame you
And we made mistakes before
You didn’t blame us either
sorry
Breaking your flowers
It doesn’t matter
Excuse me
Eat your food
It doesn’t matter
This is for you too
Tibbie
Friends should not be tolerant of each other
Do you understand each other?
Thank you
Their relationship is so good
The King
I shouldn’t blame me for my mistakes
I must find him soon!
Mushrooms that you can talk about
She is mushroom
She has cured everyone
Thank you
I…I…
I’ll leave first…
She wants to find him
Let’s go and help her!
Keep up and take a look
The King
No matter how
I must find you!
Are you looking for him
yes
You know
Where is he?
Your king has been beaten by me
He can’t wake up again
You won’t see him in the future
actually
I’m more harmful than him
You’ll get along with me in the future…
Impossible
The King
It is impossible to be defeated!
What’s going on? !
I can’t tell what poisonous weather in the morning
Mushroom fungus
Stop quickly!
The King
It’s impossible to be defeated!
The king of mushroom fungus
Is it King Bacteria?
Tibbie
Don’t get too close to her!
King!
Be careful, everyone!
Tibbie
Return soon!
This time I’m here to protect everyone
Please let you dig out these poisons
Tibbie!
Mushroom fungus
Cold and quiet
Tell me what happened
And me
King!
Unexpectedly, she suddenly lost control
Stop talking
Let’s go quickly
stop!
You can’t run!
Mushroom fungus
Not your friend?
You haven’t seen it
Did she cause such a big trouble?
but
Friends should be tolerant of each other!
OK Don’t cry
Eat this sugar
I will be your friend from now on
Xiao Zi
The King
Only you!
Can help her recover!
Xiao Zi!
Only the king will call me
Xiao Zi…
King?
That’s right
It’s me!
Xiao Zi
Come back as my subordinate!
King!
It’s fine if you’re fine…
I’m King Bacteria
How could something happen!
King!
Why are you getting smaller?
Don’t worry about these trivial matters
Let’s go
Back to the base!
The King
And we!