Village Chief
We heard an explosion sound from the experiment room
I’ll never touch the inventor again
What’s going on
Is this?
Rubik’s Cube Analysis
It seems that the village chief’s Rubik’s Cube Analysis
Research and development failed again
Since that day...
I finally developed it!
Rubik’s Cube Analysis! !
Just put the super cube in for analysis
You will definitely find it
A trace related to BB Goat’s parents!
What’s going on! ?
Village Chief
Are you okay?
I’m fine
Just a little bit short
It will definitely succeed next time!
Village Chief
Don’t be angry
Yes
Maybe it will succeed next time
I’ve tried it 9987 times!
If you succeed, you will be successful long ago!
Village Chief
Where are you going?
No invention
It must be going home to rest
How can I cheer up Murasuke?
But we give the village chief
Eat and drink
Sing
Dance
Have tried it all
Village chief still has no reaction
Weslie Brother
How to read this word
Fruit of faith?
Telling about the deep mountains
There is a fruit called the fruit of faith
Just eat it
You can regain confidence
Regain confidence
Maybe find it
It will allow the village chief
Boost again!
But
This is just a storybook
Is it trustworthy?
Then I must try to find it.
We’re going, too!
Is that here?
I’ve checked the data
The most likely
It’s on the top of this high mountain!
Very tall
Can we go up?
I can only go up and take a look first
Let it open quickly!
I can’t stop
This is
rest assured
I can catch him!
Come on!
Is this heavy?
Can’t hold back
Finally stopped
Thank you, the squad leader!
The class leader is so powerful!
I don’t want to do it because of this
Being praised
what
Are you going up the mountain to find the fruit of confidence?
It’s so dangerous on the mountain!
What exactly is on the mountain?
that is
It will rain heavily suddenly
Then hail suddenly
There will be a big flock
Heavy snow
flood
This mountain
So strange
Impossible
It’s true!
I originally
It’s coming out for medicine
I accidentally got lost on the mountain
It’s hard to find a way out
and
The fruit of faith is just a saying
No one has seen it
You’ll go back
Village Chief
Thank you for your reminder!
We’ll be careful!
Let’s go
Little pig
Don’t get lost on the way back
Have you just heard what I said?
For the village chief
We are willing to take this risk!
I won’t touch any inventions in the future
Take good care of BB Goat
未分
Can you help me fix the car?
build
Repair the car
No No
I won’t do these in the future
All right
Toolbox!
Then I will fix it myself!
stop
未分
Where is the wrong one?
Nothing right anywhere
or
Or I’ll teach you
You have to open the car first
then
The King
No other lambs are here
I caught BB Goat while I was now!
The King
No door
Of course I know!
I’m just an activity to activate my muscles!
Go in!
We’re on!
Is this one?
No No!
Need a flat screw knife!
That’s this?
Not really
This is not either
This is too big
BB Goat
Don’t throw things up!
Found it!
It’s one word!
This is too big
It’s a little smaller
Finally found
Next we will put the screw down
I must catch you!
Xiao Huang!
Turn into a shield!
I’ll deal with you when I’ll find the little green!
Fixed
This is the most beautiful car I’ve ever seen
BB Goat
Don’t cry Don’t cry
Come to help you
Help me repair
Help you find a new one
All right
Who comes to pull me
I’m out of breath
We’re all the same
Come on now
Finally arrived at the top of the mountain!
The little pig said nothing
This mountain is really strange
But
What about the fruit of faith
Nothing
It seems to be a waste of energy
Village chief…
How could this be the case
All blame the goat
You’re too fat!
Where can I have it!
Everyone, see!
This is
Fruit of faith! !
Finally found it! !
BB Goat, slow down
Small green
Go and stop their cars
receive!
Xiao Huang
Turns into a car to catch up with them!
good!
The car stopped moving?
Hand over BB Goat! !
King Bacteria
Why is it here
BB Goat
Let’s run quickly
Useless
Small green
Have taken your car
Controlled!
what
Chase up
If you have the ability, just chase it!
BB Goat!
Slowy
Let go of BB Goat!
what? !
Weslie!
You’re back
It was just that time
Xiao Huang!
Turn into a weapon!
good
Take the call!
Hide away
No
All fell down
Have walked so many roads
I’m exhausted
I can still fight!
All are tired like this
Still want to fight?
Give up!
This is
No problem!
That is the confidence we finally found for the village chief!
original
You secretly went to me for the fruit of confidence
That’s why I’m so tired
You goat
True filial piety
Since that’s the case
What are you going to do
I’ll help you send it to the village chief
No
Fruit of faith
The fruit of confidence that children finally find
Stopped
How did this happen
Such a hard-to-get faith fruit
You’ve got it all
I can’t give up, either
Have it!
Now
What else can you do!
You got a toy car after you had enough juice! ?
What’s the use of this little thing!
opportunity
Xiao Huang!!
You actually! !
Don’t run! !
Small green
It’s your turn!
I will definitely come back!
Children
Brother and sister
The village chief’s invention
It’s really bad
Unfortunately, the confidence fruit I found for the village chief was gone
Children
actually
There is no fruit of faith in this world
Then we are not in vain
No
I have my own faith
That’s you
Thank you for letting me
Regain confidence
I won’t give up on the invention
Very good!
I will definitely succeed this time
Village Chief
The parsing instrument cannot
We can think of other ways
Completed!
Come again
This is
It’s popcorn
My popcorn machine
Research and development successfully
It’s quite delicious!
Right