Don’t run
stop
Let my food down
You are such a bad mouse!
This Wolffy
It makes a big surprise every time!
Isn’t it just a mouse
Can it mature?
The King
Things are not going well
Our food was stolen by rats
what!
Let me go
Let me fly it
The King
You are a little cold!
Xiao Zi What’s wrong with you?
You see what I’m here
Is there a blue bag?
Didn’t see it
It’s over
Where have you gone?
I’ve thrown it
Your trash
Dirty and smelly
Don’t put it at home
Dirty and smelly garbage
That’s the king
You gave it to me with your hand!
When will I send you this trash?
You don’t remember
Then you can’t just let my things go
Xiao Zi!
I’m still wrong with helping you and trash?
Being angry with me
Don’t come back if you have the ability
There are no trash cans in the house
Where did you go
Stealing something again
Catch you!
I can’t run away this time!
Why is it getting dark
This
What is this! ?
I’m not something
My name is Mushroom
Mushroom fungus
Are you bacteric too?
I’m not a germ
But I am the subordinate of King Bacteria
It turns out that it’s not bacteria
No!
You are the subordinate of King Bacteria
yes
It seems that it is another one who eats and lives for free
All right
See how I deal with you
It’s too late
Xiao Zi hasn’t come back yet?
You won’t encounter any danger
The King
Why don’t we go find Xiao Zi
Don’t go
How to say
Xiao Zi is also our friend
Don’t you worry about her?
friend
Isn’t mushrooms your friend?
Friends should be tolerant of each other!
King, where are you going?
The King
Are we going to find Xiao Zi?
Who’s going to find her
I’m just going to get the express!
But I checked it
The king didn’t buy anything!
Please stop talking!
who?
Xiao Zi!
Don’t run
Xiaohuang Xiaolu
Prepare for a fight
yes
Put Xiao Zi
Come out
You come out to me
Xiao Zi
It’s all my mistakes
I shouldn’t have a fight with you
Don’t worry
-I’ll take you back
The King
Don’t bother me
Didn’t you see that I’m feeling hurt?
The King
This looks like an ordinary mushroom
mushroom
Actually, I’ve known it a long time ago
Then are we looking for Xiao Zi?
Who is looking for her! ?
Suddenly I want to take a walk
So thirsty
Please use juice
I’m tired
good
You wait a moment
Please use
Very delicious
You are really hurt by mushrooms
Thank you
I should thank you for yours
See how I’ll clean it up
You are a guy who eats and lives for free
Be careful to snatch
You’re fine, right?
alright
Foot injury
Don’t touch the water or the trouble
thank you
Need not
It’s all my fault for making the kitchen
You’re like this
Since you’ve been injured
Why don’t I help you clean up
This mushroom is really good
Where did Xiao Zi go?
I’ve been looking for a day and haven’t eaten anything
I’m so hungry
Too silly
You are my subordinates
How can I get tired of a stomach
Very comfortable
I’ll go to the bathroom
Let me help you
I’ve been looking for her for so long
She actually gave Wolffy a servant?
You finally admit that you are looking for Xiao Zi!
The King
I’ll teach her for you
You are the traitor
Accept the sanctions obediently
See
Xiao Huang is indeed my most loyal partner
So delicious
Xiao Huang
you…
Little Green, please help me with teaching
Where is the little green?
It looks so good
Aren’t you feeling unpleasant?
You need to take care of it
It’s so delicious
The King
Come and have a bite
This food is so delicious
My King Bacteria is just hungry
Can’t recover
I won’t eat anything from Big Wolf
The taste is really good
It smells good
No!
These two guys know how to eat
Although delicious
But that’s not the case!
who!
This is…
What’s wrong with you?
No one dares to approach me
Dislike me
Why
Because I was hurt
It will dissipate poison and harm innocent people
So no one dares to be friends with me
alright
Stop crying
After eating this sugar
I am your friend!
Isn’t this the candy I gave to Xiao Zi at the beginning?
It turns out you stole it!
Come back soon
He actually hid
Let me give it to Xiao Zi
He actually played this king
See I control you
Give me the same…
Get it…
Xiao Zi…
Isn’t this something I don’t see?
So that’s what you are talking about?
I helped you get it back from the mouse
It turns out that it was not what you threw away by the king
I haven’t!
How could you throw away the candy I gave you?
original
You still remember
Xiao Zi
You run so fast
original
Did you bring her?
That’s right
We told her everything
Including the fact that you found her overnight
Who told you to talk too much
The King
Thank you for caring about me so much
No
I’m tired
Xiao Zi
You prepare for dinner
yes
The King
Wait for us