Ice skating is so fun!
We have something more interesting!
Paddi!
BB Goat is optimistic!
More interesting!
Super!
Rotate!
pain…
Why don’t you grab my hand?
Who knows you are going to change your position suddenly!
I’m stupid and blame me! ?
- It’s your problem!
You are stupid!
Stop quarrel
In fact, they quarreled in public
It’s really a gift
That’s it
The opportunity is here!
superior!
The king, I can’t tell you
Don’t…Ice skating
What a fool to say
I’m just warming up
You go quickly
Give me the ultimate digital supersonic spiral spray cannon!
what
Final digital supersonic spiral spray cannon
Don’t know
Then you will change the weapon
The weapon you said
Who will!
Help!
Change back quickly!
How
Don’t you use tanks?
Weslie Brother I’m tired
Then let’s go eat
Eat something
I’ll go too!
Don’t run!
germ
They’re inside
He actually fights in public places
True lost
Anyway, we’re leaving
You’re here to have fun
I stood up!
you
Stop hitting!
Where is the goat? !
It’s you
You can’t catch the lamb!
It’s all your stupid ones!
You are not educated!
Stop quarrel
Give you gifts
Make peace quickly
Then go catch the goat
Reconcile?
No door
Stop hitting, stop hitting
Don’t eat wine if you toast!
Try the new invention of Wolffy
"Control stickers"!
I’ll see how to use it
shake hands!
Shoulder and smile
Finally reconciled!
Don’t argue again in the future
What are you holding my hand?
Let go
It was you who hugged me first!
It started to quarrel as soon as the machine was closed
Recover me quickly
Keep this
Let’s go catch the goat!
After eating
It’s even more quarrel
Stop quarrel
BB Goat
Why not wait for you to try
Brother Yangyang, Brother Feiyang, Brother Yangyang
Let’s play together
good
I’m a Lion
Sparky  and Brother Baiyang Goat
It’s my big lion
Brother Xiaoyang and Sparky
Come together too
Come on!
Add the handle too
Have fun
It seems
This way can make them reconcile
Sparky
You’re fine!
Will you skate?
You bumped into me!
Come again…
Don’t you control it…
It’s been arguing for a few hours
BB Goat
What are you doing
I want to continue using my method
Let Sparky and Yanyangyang reconcile
It’s bacteria and they
Oops
Why don’t you hide
Not like you normally
Don’t want to touch BB Goat
But it’s OK
Just one button
Small green
Will come back soon
Xiao Lü Why don’t you come back yet
Wolffy’s destruction
There is actually a scope of acceptance
Don’t leave!
Come again
Why does he seem to be manipulated
I’ll be back
BB Goat, are you okay?
I’m fine
Brother Sparkyyangyangyangyangyangyang
Give you
Soda?
I and Sparky are painting above?
The two brothers drank this can of soda
You can’t get angry
Two brothers in my heart
All are friendly
I won’t get angry about trivial matters
Quick and good
Let’s play together
OK
Brother Yangyang, Brother Feiyang, Brother Yangyang
we
Some goat were taught by the lambs
Where is it!
BB Goat!
them…
Why is it coming again!
Finally come back
Don’t run!
BB Goat!
Not that easy!
Weslie!
I don’t want to be nervous!
You go and save BB Goat!
It’s a good time to escape ~
Don’t try to escape
I won’t be beaten!
Boiling…
Goat
Be careful
The same to you
I’m so angry!
Throw BB Goat to me directly!
Is King Bacteria here too? !
Don’t leave!
Want to get rid of me!
Let go of BB Goat!
Very slippery
Oil again
Have you no new tricks?
You only have
Let’s open BB Goat!
Then let her go
We won’t say it anymore!
Open BB Goat
That’s now!
not good!
Escaped!
Let me come!
Brother Sparky!
It’s mine in the end!
goodbye!
No!
Let’s go together!
Don’t want to chase me!
Middle! Left!
Right!
Sparky!
Catch you!
Left
Right
Come up!
Middle!
Jump!
This is…
Super rotating!
Isn’t it just a skater?
But you will never hit us
Super rotating does not have fixed movements
Fixed pace skills
It turned out to be a non-sense skill? !
No!
This is a skill that can only succeed if you work together
You can’t escape!
Get the iced goat
Come back!
Your random skills have failed!
Am I doing?
Where am I?
I’ll be back!
It turns out that I’ll fall down too
Paddi
I’ve said this to you before
sorry
I seem to be really
No effort to practice
That
Let’s practice together in the future
OK
My brother’s move is so bad
I want to see it
Say back
You don’t think
Does King Bacteria look weird?
They’re weird
It seems to be a little…
It’s you
The plan to catch the goat failed!
It’s you!
Stop quarrel…
King!
I’ll go catch the goat as soon as I’m here!
Don’t learn what I say!
Don’t catch them today
Have a good rest
I’ll continue to help you
The king is so nice!
The king is good to me!
You go!
Go open!
After all, you are injured
I have a responsibility, too…
Master, who are you good to me!
I can’t catch a goat, but I want to treat you well? !