Very good
Finally made the cake
Just add a little more sugar!
How do you know it’s not sweet
My cake
So delicious
Can’t help but taste
Paddi
This is the gift I want to give to someone
sorry
Weslie
Sunny
careful! !
It’s okay!
apple!
Shouldn’t you catch me first?
sorry
Mr. Slowy
Are you doing a new invention?
right
Just right
I’m going to the bathroom
Please help me see this machine
Don’t make people irritated
good
Why haven’t you come back yet
OK
thank you
This is
corn
sorry!
You’re so ate
I don’t know how to use the little green
Can you find the weakness of the lamb?
Don’t worry, king
Even if he can’t do it, I’ll be there
The King
I’m back!
The following are the daily routines of lambs I have seen
They’re very fulfilling
So what’s the weak
The King
The lunch is ready
Haven’t you seen the king busy?
Are you the king a goat?
Just eat all day!
That’s right
Just eat! ! !
Your lunch
I’m talking about letting the lamb eat
Just put the lamb
When you only eat
Then they will have no time to see BB Goat
But it seems that only Paddi are eaten
Then why did others eat too?
Look at this king!
Wolffy! !
- I’ll lend you something to you! !
The King
What are you?
I’ll introduce it to you all
Eat and eat
Streaming type bullet!
Big mouth
Hidden spray mouth!
and the most important inside
Have a gas! !
Just absorb for a period of time
Everyone will be eating
No more mind to take care of things
The king is so bad, so bad! ! !
Will that affect us?
I don’t want to be ate…
I’ve been ready for a long time
Look through this light
We won’t be affected
now!
Have fun! !
Depart! ! !
That fish is so long?
Yes Yes!
The goat is really too ate
I’ve had this cake for a while
strangeness
Where is my cake! ?
At least leave some for me
sorry
Suddenly I couldn’t help but want to eat
That’s right!
Very hungry…
There is Apple there!
Paddi
Let’s help you
No need No need
I can do it alone
Be careful! !
Nothing bad! apple!
Shouldn’t you catch me first?
This sounds so familiar
There’s only Apple in my eyes
sorry…
yes
I’ve always seen food lately
I couldn’t help but want to eat
Can’t control it at all
You’re too swearing
This is not the case in normal times
Don’t know
That’s good too
Everyone eats the same
No one said to me
I can finally get my treasured snacks
Take it out and eat it with all your heart!
Where is my snacks! ?
Sorry, goat
We finished our snacks
So I want to borrow some
You have your snacks!
you
Too much
These days have passed
The lambs should all be
It’s a natural thing to eat!
But the king
Why do we have to put our own food
What about bringing those lambs?
These are the food compliments we have experienced
gourmet food
Delicious food
Want everyone to share
what…?
condition?
…It seems to be coming to eat food
It seems that the effect of eating and breathing
It has spread to the entire grassland
yes
See how happy they eat
See also
Go and pick it up quickly
It’s the king
Give us the same
Not allowed to eat
Bagba?
Bag!
Someone snatched our food to eat!
You should take care of it!
That’s it
Then I’ll give it to you…
Forget it, forget it
It’s still for you to eat!
Very sorry
I didn’t eat like this before…
How can they
I ate all my snacks…
Paddi
Where are you going here?
Weslie and the others
Have finished all my snacks
So I’ll buy snacks
Go and see everyone
They changed
What happened?
Come with me
You see
Everyone is very edible!
Eat all my snacks
You come and review!
Your snacks
Did you mean these?
These are mine, too
Mr. Slowy
Why do you do the same!
Don’t know why
I want to eat too
I’m almost finished eating
Why not order popcorn
Mr. Slowy
You’re not saying
Is this your new invention?
I see you use this
The popcorn is pretty good
don’t want
This is such a dangerous situation!
Everyone has popcorn
What’s wrong with everyone
Brother Yangyang
Do you want to have snacks together?
Why did you become like this?
What’s going on with everyone?
The lambs have become very edible, too
we
superior! !
Hand over BB Goat!
King Bacteria is here
Be careful
Look at my special flying bullet!
BB Goat Don’t snatch
I have a lot of delicious food here for you
Success!
I won’t let you succeed
Where do you want to go?
Hand over BB Goat!
don’t want!
Then don’t blame me for being rude!
Look at the trick!
banana?
Don’t like eating bananas?
I also have apple pear
Orange Candy
Why?
Did my food and gas have no effect on him?
Because the goat are very edible
So eating and gas will not work for him
It turns out that everyone is eating
It’s all your fault! !
Want to help the slept with goat
But I just can’t control myself and want to eat
Let’s go help the siege goat!
You can’t let the Yangyang goat face it alone!
Let’s go help the goat together
Everyone
We’ll help you after eating
Paddi
Don’t want to run away! ! !
It hurts so much
What is that?
It’s hard to tell…
Why
My food and gas
Didn’t it affect him?
It seems
That’s the thing that happened!
Destroy him
Everyone should be able to return to normal!
BB Goat Benefit
Hidden here and don’t be discovered by the sterilized kings
I’m so useless!
You have to quickly destroy the device in the sky!
No!
I’m catching up soon!
What to do?
See where you run
There is a way!
Hand over BB Goat! !
You can catch me before you say it!
The opportunity is here!
look! I! of!
you!
We’re on!
Very tired
Paddi! ! !
Brother Qingyangyang, you are awesome!
The Goat, I’ve missed you so much this time!
Paddi
That was really amazing
Very hungry
Let’s go eat!
good!
Wait for me to reward everyone!
All the food is fine
Let’s start eating~
It’s so prosperous!
So happy! ! !