Too unusual
Radha actually searched
Life reaction on volcanoes
It’s normal to have animals on the snowy mountain
That’s not an ordinary snow mountain
This snowy mountain is called Qifeng Snow Mountain
Its temperature ratio
Ordinary snow-capped mountains are lower
And it’s better than ordinary snow mountain
More easily snowy
It sounds so terrible there
And the trapped people
Maybe it’s BB Goat’s brother!
Because Radha is
I just found someone there recently
elder brother?
But it’s so dangerous there
How can we save it?
No need to take risks
My strongest here
Send me somebody
no!
This rescue operation
Let’s go together!
If you have any questions, solve them together!
OK!
This is what I developed
Cold-proof spray
Just spray it
The body will automatically develop
No longer afraid of the cold
Everyone spray it!
and
The mountain of the strange snowy mountain
There is a very dangerous ice lake
As long as you step in, you will get ice
There is no way to prevent cold sprays
Don’t get close to that one
Village Chief
Even if there is spray
You will still encounter danger when you go up the mountain
Let me go alone
Don’t underestimate the strange snow mountain
Never move alone!
good
We’re going to arrive
This is a cold place
Search for Xiaolu
My last subordinate
It’s here
We must find him
come on!
There is another rival
When will I be able to
Become the boss
He must not find that person
It’s so cold here
He may have been ruined into ice long ago
It won’t
He has strong defense capabilities
and patience
Can resist various attacks
Even if he is in the lava
It can also be intact
We climb snow mountain
It’s dangerous not to wear a gear
Or go back first
rest assured!
I’ve set it up
Safe route
And Xiao Zi was arranged
Stand at any time at the foot of the mountain
In summary
This trip
Very safe!
good!
Then we will come out with urgency!
What’s up?
Snowball! ! !
Avalanche!
The big snow on the tree hits!
Xiao Lü, you said it’s safe!
The King
This is so dangerous here
We might as well go back
OK!
The plan was successful!
The King
I have planned the route to the mountain, too
This time it must be very safe!
Is it really safe this time?
It’s safe
Just like the protected BB Goat
Let’s go out!
Even if something is sprayed
Still very cold
How did you get here at once
Radha has a few more people…
Village Chief Your invention…
It must be too cold here
Causing some loss of spirit
Just in case of
Let’s go up and take a look
good
Tibbie!
Everyone has come here
So warm
Let’s continue to develop!
Step on me!
I can’t go on like this
Let’s start here first
Wait until the snow passes before leaving
As long as I save the people on the mountain
You don’t have to work so hard
Brother Sparky
What are you doing?
That’s what you said
Is it a safe route?
I want to go home…
The king…
Who is it
Strike me
Extremely cold and nurturing
Finally found you
Little red!
Little red?
King Bacteria? !
Don’t call me a little red!
Little red!
He said, don’t call me Xiaohong!
I haven’t seen it for a long time
I’m here!
The King
Why did the king become a little purple potato?
My experience will be discussed later!
Introduction to you
His name is Guqingjian
You can call him a little red
Everyone will do it in the future
Stay together well!
Little red
Next is mine
That’s it
You want to help me catch goat
Unblocking ability…
He’s so old
Is it OK?
Say I’m old?
I’m willing to give up!
Come again! !
Run!
Go in and hide!
Micacaria
This person is so tricky
More protections should be made in the future
The little red is really awesome!
Small red chrysanthemum
Can prevent all attacks
Don’t call me a little red!
OK little red!
Let’s go catch the goat quickly!
Xiao Huang!
Open Digging Open Digging…
Who is it!
BB Goat!
Why did you come out alone
Very dangerous
Brother Sparky came out to play secretly
I want to play together, too!
I’m not here to play
It’s difficult to go back now
We’ll still be the first
Find a place to hide
Leida points to the tent
Difficult to tell
BB Goat’s brother is trapped in the tent
Can go out!
Finally came out!
It’s you
It turns out that the detector
Life reaction signal is yours
No more
Don’t leave!
Now that’s coming
Don’t try to escape
Catch BB Goat!
I’m here
It won’t hurt you
A wool
Anti-suppression shield? !
Who are you? !
My name is Guqingjian
Are you a goat?
yes
Then just surrender!
My hot punch
It’s useless
I’ve been soaked in the rock
What is your temperature?
We can’t get in at all
Just watch quietly
The watermelon is so hard
Since the temperature is not good
Then continue searching
The weakness of this hood
Break! !
My husband’s Milkycetes
But the strongest defense
You can’t break it
Too weak
The King
I caught BB Goat!
Come and unblock!
Brother Sparky!
BB Goat is that small!
Small?
BB Goat run quickly!
Chase!
King, wait for me
It’s even colder here
Can’t run anymore!
Just surrender
Is it iced? !
Be careful, lord
Here is the Ice Lake
Go in
Will be stopped immediately
Didn’t you say it earlier?
Are you not here to save us? !
Come now!
I’m looking for solutions online now
You’re a machine
Why are you afraid of the cold?
We crawled back by ourselves
One and two…
Little red
Catch BB Goat!
It’s really a little cold
Micacaria
BB Goat is in danger!
Is this the village chief said to be the ice lake?
Don’t even think about hurting BB Goat!
See your situation clearly
Discussing endurance
You’re not as good as me
I’m in front of you who can’t beat me
Behind is an endless ice lake
As the saying goes
Independent difficulty
Be good
Leave the little sister to me!
If it weren’t for me, I’d come out alone
Nothing this will happen!
Have you been crazy?
Melt the ice
You’ll fall into the lake!
just me
Will fall
Escape
BB Goat!
The water is so cold!
It’s biting cold
It’s really nonsense!
The village chief’s spray is useless
Never do it alone
Sorry, village chief
I haven’t heard you
BB Goat
Hope you can escape
Everyone
See you again
what?
It’s okay?
BB Goat is fine
I’m fine
We have something to do!
Save us!
Not safe here
Let’s go quickly
No! !
This guy is a little bit interesting
What are you feeling grateful for?
Come and save us!
Help!
I… Sparky
Ask everyone from now on
Never again
I’ve moved by myself!
BB Goat also swears
Don’t sneak out
Thank you brother Sparky for saving me
BB Goat…
This time it’s all up to Sparky
BB Goat is fine
Thank you Sparky
Remember what happens later
Let’s solve it together
OK Village Chief
Actually my work
Not finished yet
So can you help me solve it?
Solve it yourself!