The new king is thousands of years old! The new king is thousands of years old!
Xiao Huang
No
New King
Anything to tell the younger ones to do
For the sake of friends
Just let you brush the bucket
Thank you, King!
I’ll definitely brush the bucket
Flashing shine!
The new king is thousands of years old! The new king is thousands of years old!
Stop dreaming!
Wake up quickly!
The king doesn’t see it anymore
You are in the mood to sleep!
What!
It turns out that it’s just a dream…
It’s been so long
Where did the king go
I searched for the monitoring videos of the whole grassland
I didn’t see the king’s sight
The king will not encounter danger, right?
The king is not here
Isn’t this my chance to be the king?
Don’t worry
Do you know where the king is?
have no idea!
But I can be your new king!
Let’s go find the king
Wait for me!
Let me show off
Let you believe it
By then I will be the new king!
Wolffy!
Where did Wolffy go?
We made us look for him…
Don’t complain, look for it quickly
Wolffy!
It’s all you!
I was trapped here!
Who told you to run away!
He was in trouble again in Wolf Castle!
Don’t run away!
This king is going to run away, who can’t hold back
Or you can pull me first
We continue to chase
You think beautifully
Let me send you down!
Tell you not to pull me up
It’s all your fault!
You didn’t chase me at the beginning
It won’t be like this
Use my little fist to hit you a big head
I’ll call…
There are so many complaints
Why not find a way to go out!
King!
Where are you, king!
Why is there a fork in the middle?
Where should I go?
It’s an opportunity!
I can definitely pass myself
Excellent leader
Only to motivate everyone
Successfully ascend the position of the king!
Go here!
Are you sure?
Believe me
Are you really sure it’s here?
The King’s One Movement
I know everything!
Believe me!
Stone Head Stone Head Stone Head!
A stone head!
The opportunity is here
I can definitely use my own strength
Save everyone
Arrival smoothly
The position of the king!
Be careful, everyone!
New King, I’m determined!
Everyone is fine
Are you pushing us
look
The exit is right in front
What export!
Isn’t this just a fork in the road! ?
It’s a little bit close!
Work harder
Just climbed up!
You can’t get out if you try hard…
Wolffy!
Why is there a pit here?
It’s the sound of Tibbie
I
Can’t be discovered by the lamb!
Otherwise I would be jealous!
Who cares about you!
no
How dangerous this pit is
You have to fill the pit tightly
Tibbie
Be tight when looking for someone!
Let’s fill this pit another day!
The lamb ran away
Just stay here with me!
Can you please tell me carefully
Why bother
King!
Bacteria Army!
Can’t be discovered by them
I beat the bacteria like this!
I…
It hurts so much!
How dangerous this pit is
Just fill the pit tightly
Xiao Zi
You need to be tight when you find the king
Keep up quickly!
It’s all your fault…
I’ve fought with you…
If it weren’t for you
I’ve been out long ago!
It’s all your fault!
Where did the king go?
He always gives us trouble
That’s it…
If I say something bad
Everyone’s impression of him was bad
Then I can’t replace him
That guy did
There are many bad things
Candy for kids
I am still old and love to pick up the chest
After going to the bathroom, I don’t wash my hands
The only good advantage
What if I don’t feel sick when I’m sleeping?
What’s up?
You are such a ruined king!
Yes
The king is definitely snoring when he sleeps!
Beat him!
I said something wrong
Can’t I change it yet?
Where is the person
It’s hard to fall down?
Very tired Very tired Very tired
How about my bacterial army
Haven’t come to save me yet…
King!
Finally found you!
But why are you here
Can you get up and say…
-You have come to save me…
I’m controlling some machines now
Save us out!
Please! Little green!
Helicopter
You are not in the service area
Please give it back later
There is no signal here…
It doesn’t matter
As long as we work together
Can definitely go out
First grade, second grade
You can hit the exit right away!
You’re funny
Why did you all fall down?
- Xiao Huang!
There is rescue here!
This group
Xiao Huang!
You’re going to change a ladder
Let us climb out…
Yes Yes
knew!
Sure enough, I’m gone
They can’t do anything…
alright
Hurry me up and climb up!
Still little yellow reliable
but…
It’s too short…
My legs are only so long…
Don’t waste time
Please help the lambs!
No more fun
We all die of dying here!
All right
Where to find lambs here
Wolffy!
There will be no accident
Found it!
Wait a minute.
Let them stay there
I can justify it
Become a king?
Xiao Huang Xiao Huang
When will you come back?
Miss you so much!
It’s been three hours
Are we being
That deformed bacteria was cheated
He just kept saying you bad things!
He won’t let us down
Did you run away by yourself?
shut up
I don’t want you to say this
I believe Xiao Huang
Always
No matter how difficult the mission is
What a no-no requirement
He’s all from here
Didn’t disappoint me!
Wolf Castle is mine!
The bed is mine!
Snacks are mine!
The horse bucket is mine too!
Start now
I’m your new king
Let’s talk about it
I don’t seem to have any subordinates either.
mushroom! orange!
The King
You’re not talking about Xiao Huang
It won’t disappoint you…
Xiao Huang will never come again
We are afraid we will give it to Wolffy to eat it!
Big mushroom
Light
dad…
Did you pick me up?
Wolffy
Don’t go with him!
You’re fine
Wolffy seems to be hungry
Catch the snail quickly
We’ll pull you up!
Xiao Huang!
come on! come on!
Just save Big Wolf
No matter how many bacteria need to be saved…
It turns out to be
Did the morphine bring us over?
If it weren’t for the fact that there were no subordinates
I don’t want to worry about them…
It’s time to exit
Small
It’s time to get to the exit!
Give it to me!
Thank you for your help
but…
Just defeat you!
No one
It’s okay to disturb me!
The king is wise!
It’s even more despicable than me…
Good guy
Want to find a hole to diamond in
We are your life-saving benefactors!
We will never trust you again
Wait a moment!
Don’t talk to them
We’re on!
Is there something just falling into the hole?
That’s not the point
Impossible
Disinfect them
Be careful
King!
Very hungry…
I didn’t expect you to be merciless about your revenge…
No…
Not like that
I…
Strategic retreat!
Don’t run! Don’t run!
You all ran away
Then what should I do
See if I become the king
I’ll punish you to give me all of them to brush the horse bucket
banana!
save…
Help!