Village Chief
Sorry, village chief
I…
I’ll help you
Game machine?
Ah yes...
yes
Walking around to play games is very dangerous
Hit me this time
What should I do next time I hit the car!
I know, village chief
Village chief sees you again
Put down the game machine and walk well!
knew...
I’ll talk about it after I finish this
Sparky
You come and explain this question
Sparky ...
What’s the matter?
Let’s talk about it later
I’m about to win this
What do you mean
A small break in class
Also play games
Village chief...
You give me...
you!
village…
Village Chief
You three!
Give me a look at the corridor and face the wall!
Yes, village chief
sorry!
It’s not bad
Can you know how to reflect
You three!
Too much score!
Stop being addicted to games
You should go out for a walk more
I know, village chief
The kids nowadays are really...
Hello
The express delivery of your goat village
OK Thank you
But I don’t seem to have bought anything lately
What is it?
It’s a game machine again!
Playing with things!
I want to see what’s fun
Can make children so addicted
Don’t know the lamb
Start playing those games without
What game machine?
The game machine is my designed game
Travel at home
Suitable for both young and old
Definitely good price
Be addicted quickly
What’s the use of making games
As long as the lambs are addicted to games
No one cares about BB Goat
We can catch her as soon as possible
Want to play games so much
Want to eat some food
Play games around
You know how to eat
Let’s talk about it
We haven’t eaten yet
Another
Village Chief
What are you doing?
I’m here...
Have a break here
Now I’m going to leave
Village Chief
How come you have a game
I…
I’m working on game machines
But today
Isn’t you a village chief, do you make food?
right
I’m going now
Oops
It’s almost done
This…
Village Chief
Is this a black sesame wrap?
yes
All right
Very hard to eat
No
Don’t pick on food for kids
Have a quick meal
I’m still in trouble
Let’s go first
Village Chief Sorry for the time being
Come in
The village chief has not come yet
Why did the village chief sleep later than me today
Students
We are preparing...
Let’s go to the class
All have finished classes
Just came...
Village Chief Is the village chief well?
Is the village chief well?
I’ve been waiting for a long time
The village chief has always been weird lately
Hiding behind a tree and playing secretly
All the dishes are cooked
I’ve still been in class
Difficult to tell
No!
Nothing will happen!
Village Chief!
Going to go
Sure enough, the village chief is addicted to the game
Village Chief
We just care about you
What are you looking at!
Do you want to kill me on the game?
Not to give
Village Chief
Why did you suddenly run so fast?
Don’t play games when walking
Village Chief
This is very dangerous!
Let me go
You go home and do it
This game is so scary
Even the village chiefs are so addicted
Village Chief
Have a break
Don’t snatch my game machine!
Not given!
That’s the case!
Then I’ll suck the game machine
Village chief…
Village chief…!
Don’t get closer
I’ve beaten my game!
Village Chief, be careful
Come down soon
What should I do
Butterfly Butterfly
Help bring the village chief down
Go on quickly
Why there is only one game machine
And was he taken away by the old goat?
It shouldn’t be written by the recipient
Who is this Ma Hu?
Didn’t you send it to me?
Look at it again
Village Chief
Let’s have a picnic
Don’t go!
You didn’t suggest us before
Go out for a walk more?
I definitely suggest
Then we’ll prepare
We’ll help
Slowy
Slowy!
未分!
BB Goat
Go play with me
All right
Very good
Plan continue!
Catch you!
It’s a small matter!
Want to play with me?
Can you be afraid
We villains have no respect anymore
Slowy
It’s a small matter
Quick...Run Run
Right
This reaction is right
Don’t want to run away!
Run... Quick... Run
Don’t you want to run away?
What to see
Run quickly
Run away!
run!
Give it to me!
Run quickly! Run! Give me...
Don’t forget our purpose, king
Give it to me
Give it to me! Give it to me!
All right
Then let’s go first
So many fruits
It should be something for everyone to eat
Give it to me!
Give it to me
Not good!
Bacteria to make BB Goat
Both the village chief were captured!
It’s time for me
Give me quickly
Wait and play another game
It seems
The king is also addicted to the game
Let’s go and get the king
King!
You can’t continue playing...
This game is so cool!
This character looks so powerful
Let me try
How
All of them are killing my game!
Give it to me quickly!
mine! be mine!
The King
Unlocking it must be tight!
What games are they playing
I want to play, too!
BB Goat! We’re here!
Give it to me
Look quickly
The village chief must be protecting BB Goat
It’s here!
Village Chief
BB Goat
-You are fine, are you?
The village chief is
Let’s go back and play first
Wait a little longer
Just be fine in a moment
Give me the game machine!
The village chief is already fascinated
It seems we can only take the game machine away
The village chief will leave with us
Get it!
terribly sorry!
Please leave the game machine
Weslie!
Receive it!
I got it!
Brother Yangyang
Very good!
The mantis stalks the croaker behind
The class leader is great!
I see who can still fight me!
Very burning
careful
Game machine
How?
Smashed
Not back
Slowy?
BB Goat
Let’s go back soon!
My game machine!
Village Chief
Why don’t you come to class yet
There will be no postmortem
Should we go and see the village chief?
Children are early
Village chief is early!
You’re fine, right? Village Chief
It’s OK
Thank you for your hard work these days
I forbid you to play games
Instead, I’m addicted
sorry
So we’re out of the household today
Let’s go to the preview class
Is what the village chief said true?
marvelous!
Brother and sister
Let’s play!
OK OK OK
BB Goat What do you want to play with?
I want to play this one!
Why would you want to play this?
Because it’s so fun that you throw it in
So I want to play, too