Is this an earthquake?
What
It turns out that my express has arrived
You don’t have to be so irritable when knocking on the door
Express
Very good
My express finally arrived!
Xiao Huang, let’s go catch the goat!
Almost forgot
They all went out today to train
As the subordinate of this king
It must have good physical abilities
Since they are not here
Then let’s see it today
Check out this cool home merchant
What did you release
How come it is a group of strange creatures?
So cold
Very worthwhile
What’s going on?
It’s hard to tell
This must be
The latest bioenergy technology
Cooler!
Bioenergy heater
Bioenergy generator!
It’s a must-have at home
Cool set
It can actually do anything
This is the charm of science!
Conquer the universe depends on it!
Ninety-nine eight
Just ninety-nine eight
The most powerful weapon in the universe is taken home!
Action is not as good as action
Pick up the phone and order!
Such a terrible thing?
Buy it!
The strongest weapon in the universe!
This dazzling light!
This!
What are these
Why didn’t there be any instructions?
never mind
As long as it works!
Red and small gray
I’ll love these amazing things
In the future, there is no need to pay the water, electricity, and coal fees
Why is it so noisy
How could this be done!
Isn’t this a refrigerator cooler?
Whatever monster you are
I, Wolffy, is the king of Wolf Castle!
All guns are in place
Turn on fire!
I know my strength is hurt
Wait for me to call someone!
Reverse
The furniture rebelled!
Help!
Has anyone saved me
Who can save me!
The village chief said
Finished today
This foggy room
All have been idle for many years
So much dust
When should I go to clean it up?
Your heating ability
Can you remove oil?
Promise
Your ability is also very helpful for removing the trash
No need No need
take a break
The whole wall is clean?
Is Weslie the Goat?
What garbage!
It can only spray water
Is this a weapon that dominates the universe?
Such a powerful robot
You can definitely catch goat!
Get it!
There was no power when the key was in the future?
Weslie Brother
I’ll sweep it!
Shred up really dry!
The last weapon!
All of them will disappear to me!
I must sue that unscrupulous business!
I’ll be back!
It only took half a day
Just clean it
Very good!
Isn’t this the thing of Wolffy?
It’s almost noon
Let’s send it together
Rushly eat
What happened!
What are these things!
I’ve also followed it!
Wolffy?
Save me
What’s going on?
The home appliance rebelled
The unlucky merchant has released some
A strange creature gave me!
These
It seems to be our alien creatures
We must have missed it!
Look
What did you buy
Think about it quickly!
Quick!
quick!
Don’t worry
I bought these
As long as I whistle
These alien creatures
They will all hear it very much
Wait
I’ll go back
Come back so fast
That’s what you said
Listen to the conversation?
It must be the environment of the earth
Let them make a difference
Who doesn’t hear now
And let them develop
It’ll be bad by then
Then what should we do?
No
What should you do
I’ll let it go first!
Tell me!
Don’t leave!
Who is here to save me
Weslie
Sparky
Wolffy
What kind of monster is this?
monster!
It actually destroyed Wolffy’s home
Let me deal with you!
Very good!
so
What are you here to do?
You put your stuff in our warehouse
We’ve sent you...
Weslie
What should I do now?
Those three monsters are still crazy
Not afraid
There are these things
We can win!
Come and hit me!
The first one!
So terrible!
The second
careful
I’ll help you
Success!
Very terrible!
Is this still possible?
Finally sent away
I have to buy some stable next time
And next time?
I’m saying it’s too dangerous
Finally sent away!
Yes... I’m sorry!
I...I’ll never again
Don’t buy strange things!