We’ve been here recently
There is a strange male goat looking for her sister
Maybe it’s the goat you’re looking for
Really?
We’re here right now
Very good
We’re about to find your brother!
I’m going to find my brother!
Let’s go out quickly!
Village Chief
You have a good rest
Let’s go
I’m fine
All right
Village Chief, see you again!
Where are the cold medicines?
It seems that someone is following us…
Village chief?
I’m still worried
Let you go by yourself…
But you’re still sick…
Is my illness bad?
Let’s go quickly!
It seems they have no doubts…
The king successfully got in
We follow the plan
I’m slow to get close to BB Goat
You’ll delay the lambs
Give me time to unblock
Yes, king!
I heard the strange goat looking for my sister
Have you been around here recently
Let’s find it in a quick way!
I’m in my old age
It’s a bit tired to run…
Why don’t I stay here for rest?
Yes
We ran around with BB Goat
Not convenient
BB Goat
You stay here
Is it good to accompany the Slowy?
OK!
Then we’re leaving!
You must be careful
King Bacteria!
knew
Finally all left
Wait a moment
Why don’t you go together?
I’m in my old age too
Stay here to accompany your children
How to take BB Goat away…
BB Goat caught a cold
I’ll take her back to take medicine!
Don’t be that irritating
I have cold tea here
There are so many mosquitoes here
Let’s go back and get the mosquito drive liquid!
I have!
Is there any shading?
have!
Is there any food?
water! Lighting bubbles!
have!
Rub…the washboard!
It seems that this really doesn’t exist…
Ice…BB Goat
Let’s go back and get it…
But what to do with a washboard?
Yes
What to use it to do?
Washing clothes?
Said it earlier
I brought a washing machine!
You think so thoughtfully…
Always slow
Do you still remember this place?
When we were young…
Can’t cause suspicion
Remember we’ve been there
No
That time I was the only one who came
Because you…
I’m sick and can’t come
No
You said you want to have a test
Why are you wrong?
Old
My memory is really not as good as yours
Come BB Goat
I’ll play with you
Why did Lao Ku call me Bladey
It’s acting weird
It’s hard to tell…
Brother BB Goat?
Brother BB Goat!
Everyone knows how to act!
Procrastinate!
Have you ever seen BB Goat’s brother?
How do you feel
Always come back to circle here?
Let’s talk about it
Just now those people look familiar
See how you find Brother BB Goat
Bingbing!
Are you looking for a sister?
Yes! but…
Great, finally found it!
elder brother!
Little Bingbing!
This is…
This is my sister
I’ve found her
Thank you for caring
It turns out that something is wrong…
Go back…
They are going back!
Find a way to hold them back!
They will recognize ours
I have a way
It hurts so much…
You’re fine, right?
My feet twisted…
Why do there seem to be two sounds?
My throat is a little uncomfortable
Come
I’ll help you up first!
thank you!
How come there are three hands!
You…you’re wrong?
It hurts so much…!
It’s you!
Since it has been exposed
We had no choice but to…
Go and report to the king!
No!
BB Goat and the others are in danger!
How can I capture BB Goat?
Old and slow!
We haven’t tried Mountain Crush Special in a long time!
Come and practice!
What is Mountain Crush Special?
Wait…wait for a moment!
You don’t even know Mountain Crush Special
You must be that King Bacteria!
Look at the trick!
Since you discovered it
I’ll
Where is this?
Am I at home…
Old Bladey?
Why are you here?
Don’t think I’m old Bladey
I just believe in you!
King Bacteria!
King Bacteria?
Lao Dao, are you wrong?
Stop installing it!
Sorry
The King
Take BB Goat away!
what
The lambs are chasing!
The sword goat!
Don’t worry about me
King Bacteria controls the old man
Captured BB Goat
You’ll chase…
We’ll come back to save you right away!
The kids depend on you!
Where is this…?
You’re so terrible, lord
Finally, I successfully caught BB Goat!
I’m not your king!
I’m a Slowy
No need to install it again, king!
Don’t want to run away!
I almost put BB Goat and the Village Chief!
Sorry!
Very burning!
King! You take BB Goat first!
Who called me?
King Bacteria?
That…
I’ve said I’m a Slowy!
What’s going on…
You will release the village chief and BB Goat quickly!
You will release our king quickly!
We’re getting closer
Let go and fight together
good…
BB Goat, let’s go quickly
BB Goat!
How can I let it go
This is a great opportunity!
Everyone, cover me up!
They seem to be unable to do it…
It turned out to be rebellious…
I will definitely catch BB Goat…
King!
Still, I couldn’t find BB Goat’s brother…
Don’t worry
Your brother will come and find him soon
I feel happy when I’m with you!