The weather is so good today
This weather is indeed suitable for mountaineering
Mountaineering!
BB Goat seems very happy
BB Goat likes to go out with her brothers and sisters
The king, they’re here
See it!
It’s true that it’s like Xiao Lü’s story
They took BB Goat to climb the mountain today
You see
The scenery here is still so good
Take advantage of the situation now!
Who dug a hole in the top of the mountain?
Xiao Huang
Cable!
yes
King Bacteria
BB Goat
Get on the hook
Don’t want to succeed!
Help me quickly
Let’s go and help
Relax your hands
Not bad
You put BB Goat first
impossible
This will not be good for everyone
I won’t be able to say anything
Easy to do!
Not bad
Easy!
Don’t…
Stop talking
I’m almost out of energy
You dare to plot against us
Stop talking!
Hand over BB Goat
Xiao Huang
Let them taste our tragedy!
Wait… Wait a moment
I’m not ready yet
A quagmire?
Weslie
My body is so heavy
It’s about to sink
Oops
In this state
Can’t use skills
Help!
It’s so dirty here
I want to vomit
Don’t be nervous, king
This will get deeper and deeper
Let’s make the little yellow cord
Xiao Huang
Where is Xiao Huang?
not good! The class leader doesn’t see it anymore
It just happened that they fell down together
How to…
Weslie
The King
you…
You’re fine
-Second leader!
We’re fine
You come down and save us
Very good they can hear it
My deformed bacteria and I fell on the cliff
I’ll save you right away
good
We’re waiting for you!
Xiao Huang
BB Goat is here too
BB Goat!
If the Jonie saves the goat
BB Goat has to run away again
no! I have to be faster than her
King, I’m here! !
Wait a minute.!
Just a fool is waiting for you!
The downhill road ahead is very dangerous
Don’t run too fast
danger?
It’s not that easy to cheat me
I must arrive before you
What a strange setting
Why does there be a tree on the downhill road?
Everyone said you’re waiting
You’re fine
How could it not be…
Have it!
I know it’s wrong
Save me out
What I’m doing
Just want to save the king first
No other malicious
So that’s how it is
It doesn’t matter
I’ll save you
Let’s continue working together
OK
Thank you, the Jonie
No thanks
Let’s go and save them
Amoetic bacteria! you…
Just stay here slowly
Jonie
See you again
You don’t keep your promise
It seems she can’t have arrived before me
There is a river here
Let’s go over the boat
Yes
No one helps me
How did I cross the river?
Have it
And my slaughter
You thief
I didn’t expect to use this downhill
Very convenient
Cliff
Shocked me
How to continue
Have it
OK
I’m so smart
The King
I’ll save you right away
I’m going out…
Don’t stumble
You’ll get deeper and deeper
Xiaohong, you are so terrible!
Sad
I just found out that there is room for activity on both fingers
Always planning
I didn’t expect it to be planned out
Anything is OK? !
It’s worthy of being a little girl
After we go out
Just grab BB Goat
what
Come on, Xiaohong!
Come back to you!
Is there anything wrong?
How can you do this
You think I’m stupid!
If you go out, BB Goat will suffer!
Paddi!
Suck the vines there quickly!
Yes
Eat dirt, you
Come on, fight again!
Just hit, who are you afraid of!
Stop it!
Oops
Have been misled for so long
I must be quicker!
Let’s go
What happened?
There is a banana that stole my shell
It must be a deformed bacteria
I’ll help you
thank you
Jonie!
No thanks
goodbye
What happened?
There was only one banana
Stealed my home
Let me catch him
I’ll never let him go
It’s the deformed bacteria again
I’ll help you
thank you
Jonie
goodbye
Don’t throw it away
We’ll all sink
Class Manager
Come and save us!
Xiao Huang
Follow your call
I’m here
Xiao Huang
This is bad
Weslie
Think about it quickly
Why are you so slow?
The King
I’m from the mountain
After many circles, I came down
You can’t become a landing trait
Jump down?
Yes
Why didn’t I think of it?
I’m here!
Chief!
Can this be achieved?
It seems I have to save it quickly…
What happened to you?
We saw you running so quickly
Something must have happened
So we’ve come and have a look
What can help you
Thank you
The bad egg that snatched my shell
He is here too!
Are you going to do?
Put our stuff
Come back!
sorry
I’ll give you right away
You dare to fool me!
No…
I didn’t!
sorry
I’m wrong
Apology is useless
Wait a moment
Everyone thinks he regrets
Just tell him
Right!
I’m wrong! I never dared to do it again!
Please tell me!
For the sake of the Jonie
I will give you this time!
thank you
Jonie!
alright
Let’s go and save people
The King
I’m here!
Finally saved
You’ve helped our house
For small yellow
Let you go this time
Let’s go
The class leader is too kind
Whether it’s a good person or a bad person’s busyness
She helps
This is our class leader