Small green
This is the entire game
Is the highest place?
I noticed the lambs today
Will definitely come to the park
See it!
It’s there!
Let’s go down quickly!
OK
Just jumping into the building
What’s there to be afraid of?
You don’t even feel it!
Of course you are not afraid!
I want to know too
What do you think of
Wear a body-sensing eyeglasses
Give you the pleasure of climbing mountains and crossing mountains simultaneously!
The pleasure of climbing mountains and crossing ridges!
Body-sensing eyeglasses?
Synchronous feelings?
Have it!
-goodbye!
The body feels the lens!
Where have you gone?
It’s coming soon!
Let’s go quickly!
Pay attention to each unit!
Enter the park soon
Pay attention to all suspicious persons
Decorate as a staff member
It’s unquestionable!
Xiao Huang!
Let’s go!
Completed
Sensory experience hand ring!
Just hold the handle
Put it on the hand of the lamb
Just a hand ring
Target sensory message
Transmitted to my body
This is
I can feel it
It feels like someone else!
Hello
Please give me a ticket
Excuse me
This is your ticket
I wish you a happy trip!
Welcome to the glory
This is your hand
Just take it
Have been playing all day
OK
Thank you!
So many fun!
Then
We’ll play all today
The whole game venue!
good!
I wish you a happy game
You can experience it immediately
It feels like someone else!
Not sure
You can also eat a variety of delicacies!
Then let’s start with Sparky …
Let’s play this first!
Shocking the house?
This is so fun
But
Brother Sparky, I’m afraid
It’s okay
You just need to follow me!
Then let’s go in quickly
The King
They seem to have entered it
We’re going in too
Just catch BB Goat when you see the time!
So dark
Will there be monsters here
Do you believe this?
Those are all things that cheat on children
Brother Sparky
This is just a mess
Look
The exit is there!
Just open this door
We can go out!
exit?
There is danger ahead!
It’s the lambs!
God really helps me!
Look, everyone
It’s the exit!
Is it true?
I believe I’m sure this time…
This time it’s right
Don’t step off!
I can’t catch your goat this time
BB Goat Here!
It’s really amazing
Fortunately, everyone avoided it
Or else you’ll be caught
I’ve said it long ago
You don’t listen
As I say
Now, go and eat something
good!
Next
We went to the food area…
Right!
A mountain car next to it!
what?
There is also a jumper
There are also sea rafts
These games are too scary
Please don’t play
Go and eat something
They didn’t seem to hear my voice!
I’ll never be surprised again
So scary!
The King
Look!
It’s BB Goat and the others!
Watch the performance!
Walk faster
We’re going to die
You two are so cute
What’s the jump here
Let’s go
Wait a minute.! Don’t leave!
We also have other performances!
Watch my belly dance…!
You two are so cute!
Are those two actors
The staff who were surprised came to the wrong scene…
have no idea
Let’s go and play with something else
not good
The lamb is about to run away!
You can open it quickly!
Don’t touch it!
Xiao Huang!
receive!
Lamb, don’t run away!
Successfully upgraded!
Then they can hear me talking!
Choose this time
You!
Just those are small subjects
Next
We’ll experience the most harmful…
Zhang Yu Touching…
Why are you the same?
The food area next door!
Departure…
It’s worthy of being a goat
Very delicious
What to eat?
Noodle
Very good
Just eat noodles
Said to eat noodles
How come sauerkraut is missing!
I’ll go to the queue to get the noodles
BB Goat goes there to get pickled vegetables
Where are the scattered goat and BB Goat?
Yes
It was clearly behind me
There
Hello
I want a bottle of sauerkraut…
I want two bowls of noodles
Add four bowls
Thank you
Are you here?
Don’t ask us to eat noodles
I forgot about it for a while
Right, where is BB Goat?
I just let him get the pickled vegetables
How can you let BB Goat go there alone?
not…
It’s okay
look
Come back
Brother Yangyang
I got the sour…
BB Goat!
Don’t run!
Open BB Goat
See you again
The little lamb
How did he start the car
Such a dangerous thing!
Miss
My sauerkraut!
Can’t let him escape!
Run to the left quickly
You can catch him by passing the guardrail!
Who is talking
No matter
It is necessary to save BB Goat!
Seen
Stop quickly
Get up quickly!
Don’t let him run away!
Go and jump on the bed next door!
quick!
He hid!
Really useless
Let me come!
Why did you drive?
My sauerkraut…
Why does it seem like there are always people
Always talking in my ears?
Paddi!
Are you okay?
Nothing is OK
The racing car is flying every day
Fun Fun
Where are King Bacterias?
They’re going to play in the water
Let’s go back and have noodles soon!
It smells so good…
I’m going to start!
Finally started eating
So delicious!
Smooth taste
Add to the combination of sauerkraut
Simple
The goat’s best!
The hand ring has broken
Partial sense function
Message will not be accepted
Switch to other goat’s hand ring
Very delicious
It’s getting late
Then let’s go back
I want to eat noodles, too
The lambs wait for me
This time I must get the delicious food!
What a bad luck!
Such a sophisticated plan
It actually failed!
Are we covered here?
King, wipe it first
Thank you
Right
Where have you been going all day?
I feel like you’re a little weird today
I…
Right
I thought of a plan yesterday
Please see, king
This is the Wolf Castle underground connection
There are five levels in total…