It’s really a bad news for the teacher
Want to find BB Goat
Found a rhino
Big brother, don’t run away
Come and have fun!
Little red!
You think about it quickly!
Don’t call me a little red!
I have a way!
what?
What are you pushing me to do?
The King
You come in first to avoid it
I’ll deal with him!
You can’t first
Tell me if you want to act again…
But say back
Where is this?
Post-school training for primary school students
The lamb stuff?
I remembered it!
It is the secret base of the lamb!
There must be hidden here
The secret of the lambs…
But compared to practicing
Or should the comic be better
No!
Am I trying to find out the secret of the lamb?
No No
Can’t distract yourself!
no
Play a game and look for it
There is nothing to do with it…
King!
The rhino has been beaten by me!
big…
The King
good…
It hurts so much!
King!
Didn’t expect
This hard work is practicing…
That…
I’ll help you to guard it outside!
It won’t let anyone beat you up!
Then I’m as you
Stay here for a little longer…
The King
Wait for you to practice
You must go through two tricks with me!
I’m here to guard
Don’t even want to fight the king
BB Goat
Let’s play with us
A little bit of a voice
BB Goat fell asleep
It doesn’t matter
We play games calmly
Wait until BB Goat wakes up
Oh well
You can’t play like this
But it will also wake up BB Goat!
That’s better than we play
Let’s have a food competition!
Is eating a game?
Then I might as well play the game myself
Right
My game is still at the secret base
My snacks are…
My comics are also in the secret base.
I seem to have forgotten it, too
The secret base has been spent
Let’s go to the secret base together
waist…
Very sour
It’s been half a day
The king is still there
The king is working so hard!
I can’t transfer either!
It’s so good for one person!
Running with goat
It’s actually faster than Weslie!
Because I want to be quick
I saw my snacks!
Paddi…
I’m guarding here now
No one should get close to you!
Paleomic bacteria?
This is our secret base!
What can’t we go in?
No, no
Then don’t blame us for being rude
Give it to me
Micacaria
Weslie and Sparky  are really unreliable
I have to look at my key moments
Go
You’re fine, you’re goat!
Why is this Thousand Fungus Armor so hard
This is not a solution
Let’s go back and think about the solution
You’ll wait for me
Young people
Let’s practice for a few years!
What is he doing?
My snacks are missing me…
My comics
I just didn’t read the last chapter…
My flowers are not yet…
My game plane has just been updated
Haven’t played yet
My post-school practice
There is still a single unit that doesn’t do…
But the anti-bacterial bacteria
Too bad!
No matter how bad people are, they are weak!
So he must be weak!
Can you know his weakness?
Mr. Slowy
What are the weaknesses of ancient bacteria?
Paleomic bacteria?
How do I
Mr. Slowy?
What happened to Mr. Slowy
We’re tightening
Look at Mr. Slowy!
Mr. Slowy!
What happened to you?
Mr. Slowy
You’re fine…
It’s OK
Just old
A little pain in the waist
That…
Let’s help you up first
I’ll help you with ointment
Very comfortable
Now I’m like I’ve been slaughtered
The bird is as free as it is
It feels much more comfortable in one go!
This kind of pain sticker is indeed effective
Mr. Slowy
Will older people suffer from low back pain after standing for a long time?
Usually it will
I have a way…
So sour!
Very sour
All finished
Then buy some more and come back
Thank you very much
good…
What a bad thing
The King
Have you practiced?
Almost done
I’ll buy something and come back
You keep guarding here!
It’s the king!
Almost can’t hide it
Wait until I buy some food and come back
Open the game again
So sour…
Why are you not acting in a state of discomfort today?
It was indeed the same as Sparky’s prediction!
Let’s see mine next!
Why is it coming again
This time
I’ve come here
It’s the same many times!
Thousands of C. agaric! !
Take the call…
This…
What kind of weapon is this…
Please try our Goat Village
Special town pain stickers!
unnecessary!
Why are you so solid!
The body is the most precious wealth…
This…
Are we not enemies?
The pain in our town in Yang Village
But the secret recipe of ancient method is used
Combined with more than 20 famous natural medicines
After 77448 days
It is made of low temperature and slow
Not forty-nine
After posting
Good waist
Good legs
Good spirits
Let your whole body be washed
Eat the fragrant food!
Great body!
this…
It sounds pretty good
I don’t know if I use it
It’s you again!
Run…
stop!
There is a broken bit! ! !
This feeling of tranquility comes in an instant
It stimulates every pore behind me…
The effect of the medicine penetrates the entire body
The pain is slowly
Slowly disappearing…
It’s really comfortable…
You just enjoy it here.
Let’s go in now!
All my snacks were eaten!
My new game
It’s almost closed!
My comic book!
My flowers!
Fortunately, my post-school training book
It’s pretty good
You lambs dare to steal me!
What’s going on…
Have you touched my game
My snacks
My flowers
My comic book…
I’ve been out again
Keep the king’s efforts!
How could it be me
The king…
Buy this many things
Why not call it a bacterial army
Let’s play together!
Small…
Little red?
Don’t call me a little red…
Are these all you did?
This…
You discovered it…
Say it well
Say it carefully…