My name is morphogenic bacteria
It’s a dream to become the king of the universe
A man who accomplishes something
But it is actually…
Today we must catch BB Goat
Discover the goal!
Xiao Huang
Turned into a catcher!
apple?
Little yellow
These apples I found are so sweet
Please pick some more
Only after eating can I catch BB Goat
Enchanting
Xiao Huang
Become a baby
I’ll beat you out and catch him!
Catched!
Get it!
Take away all these foods together
I’m always forced to do these
Tired and unintentional…
Get it done!
Xiao Huang, look
These are our loot today
I’ve suffered!
I’m not doing anymore!
Shocked me
Are you going to rebel?
right!
I want to rebel
Things are good in the morning
Chocolate was good before
All made me see clearly
You’re still like that, indeed
I know how to use me
It didn’t change at all!
You are no longer qualified to be my king!
These are what I made
I’m going to take it all away!
Don’t chase it!
Just let him go!
Anyway, it’s not long
He will run back by himself
Come
The third place
A steal happened
Please help me investigate
yes
What a big man
It’s also mysterious
Amazing news
The King of the Universe
Recruiting new people!
Recruiting newbies
It’s been so long
No one has come yet
It seems that it’s good to add some
Only then can they attract them
Amazing news
Just be my subordinate
You can enjoy this bunch of delicious food!
I want to join! I want to join! I’ll join…
Everyone is so desperate
My life is no longer long as I am the king
good!
Which powerful person
Want to show yourself?
I’m here
So powerful!
Look at me!
Record! Record!
Help!
Keep going like this
When will I become the king
Have some big things
now
Hand over the lollipop!
Have a lollipop!
You finally appeared!
You dare to snatch our lollipops!
What is a lollipop
As long as you think I’m the king
Those foods
It’s all yours!
The King
I’m a morphogenic bacteria
I finally became
The king of the universe
Right
The King of the Universe
What should I do first?
Our team
The first thing to do
It is to occupy the grassland!
Haven’t eaten yet
How can there be no force to invade the grassland?
As long as you follow me to invade the grassland
I’ll take you to do it
More delicious
Then let’s find something delicious!
Go and invade the grassland first!
Find something delicious first!
I’m the king
You have to hear me!
Then you are not now
Help us get honey!
Go and pick apples!
Don’t steal it!
I haven’t got any rice grains
Very tired
I didn’t expect you to care about me
What
I just ate apple and bit my arm
Come and help me with cream
It’s time to eat
Finally had a meal
I asked you to make a meal
The three evildoers are so overscore
This is…
The King
I found the footprints left by the thief!
Excuse me
It’s my footprint…
Weslie
Honeycomb Fruit Gardens and Valleys
Lost again
Lost again?
Who is so cunning?
Fortunately, they were bacteric
Haven’t come out lately
Otherwise we’ll be troubled
Lollipop
BB Goat!
Put down BB Goat!
Run apart!
Chasing King Bacteria!
It should be thrown away
See
Xiao Huang is not here, there is no problem
The King
Big King
Are the kings still suitable?
No matter how powerful it is
good
- Deformed rod bacteria
Are you looking for a call?
stop
Let him go
The king…
Are you his king?
Go away, lord
You can’t beat them
Packed in me
You’re so clean
Of course
We are…
Love it very clean
Leave aside
King!
Look at the trick!
Don’t think about it
And give it to you
No one can help you now
And we!
who?
Same?
It’s the same as many!
The king who dares to bully us!
Run quickly!
There is no good luck to bully people
Stay at your own pace
Good to meet in the future
Where did you stay
Success!
-you…
The King
I
I…
Let’s go home
I can’t see my brother
Being bullied
I apologize to you
I was not right before
I’m sorry for you
so…
Are we going home?
But I’m not loyal to you
For so long
I always want to be the king
I…
I’m sorry for you
King!
Then I’ll let you be the king
As long as you can come back
This king will do it for you
What’s the relationship
King!
From now on, you will always be my king
I will never have a second thought again
Then let’s go home
yes
Wait a minute…
Where is BB Goat?
BB Goat!
The lamb is chasing
Forget it, don’t look for it
Go home to help you with injuries and get tight
Next time we’ll catch it together
Let’s go…
The footprints were printed in the cave
BB Goat
Where are you?
Weslie Brother!
I’m here!
You’re fine
It’s OK
What about that group of bacteria?
Take a closer look at these things
Aren’t those stolen?
A lot of piles
You see
The three major tyrants? !
It seems we have found it
The loss case is really
You gave me a hundred trees
Stealing honey Stealing fruit
Stealing rice
I stole it twice in a row!
We only stole it once
Also telling lewd
Give me two hundred trees!
Who did that time…
No matter who it is!
God will definitely punish him! !