All ready
Prepared
The installation is good too
These are not enough
Continue preparation
These guys bring such multiple equipment
It’s hard to catch BB Goat
Why don’t the lambs answer the phone!
Look for Slowy
What’s the matter? Wolffy?
what!
Weslie and the others
Take BB Goat to the Game Park
I have to use my magic
Notified the lamb
It hurts so much!
Go
So beautiful
Wolffy’s Dirty
Not good
Wolffy said that bacteria are coming to catch BB Goat!
Let’s notify everyone quickly
But
It will take us some time to land
Have it!
Help us fly to the ground
Tibbie and goat Jonie!
Have you seen BB Goat?
The bacteria are going to catch her!
BB Goat and Weslie
Go play the rat ball
Let’s go find them!
Is it fun? BB Goat?
Fun!
Weslie
The bacteria are coming to catch BB Goat!
There are too many people here
Bacteria can attack us while it is a problem
Let’s go back to Yang Village first!
Come
I’m here to deliver the letter
What’s going on?
It’s been a whole afternoon
Why didn’t you see BB Goat?
BB Goat is sleeping
King Bacteria may be coming
Wake up, everyone
Hey Haitaro
Sorry, the news is wrong
It turns out that bacteria said in the morning
It’s a roasted meal
I’ve made a mistake
Wolffy!
This is the fifth time this week
The duck is tired
This is why I’m so scared
All food has been greatly reduced
Wolffy
I won’t figure it out next time
Let us know if it’s good
OK
Where did eggplant go?
Not found
Eat something else
No grilled eggplant
What’s more to call it?
And I’m obviously ready for eggplant
Why don’t you see it
It’s hard to tell…
It’s so early
I’ll send Wilie to school
I will never let him go this time
Is it hard to discuss catching BB Goat again?
Maybe I’m too careful again
This time we must
Kill them as much as possible!
No living sensation!
Maybe I’m preparing to bake again
I’ve prepared a booth
Move right now
Casino?
It’s impossible to use it for baking
Just inform the lamb with urgency
Why doesn’t the phone sound?
Seal all entrances and exits of Wolf Castles
-Don’t let anyone leave Wolf Castle!
Can you tell me that my identity has been exposed?
Or use flying bird books!
It seems that it won’t work
Think of other ways
Let’s notify the lambs!
Could it be difficult to stop me like this?
We must first solve this digital virus
Have it!
It looks delicious!
It hurts so much
"Ship-Time Rescue" is so touching
The door is there
How did I go through?
A child is a child
Who is it!
Don’t know the wolf
Will it come today
Those who come will definitely say…
Not good!
You imitate it very much
Not my voice
Wolffy is really here
Bacteria built a cannon
Maybe attack the goat village
Big Wolf, you’re here again
Did you miss it
That table is not a concentrating light
It is said that the bacteria are gathering
This time it’s true
Believe me
Your eyes look at me
All this time
Is it true
You’ve heard it too
The story of "The Wolf Comes"
Let’s believe Wolffy again
Weslie
If the bacteria really build a cannon
It’s not safe to stay here
It’s better for us to develop first
Go and remove the cannon
good!
Everyone has been having a good time this time
There is this casino in most places
- This king…
There’s really a cannon
Remove the cannon
What are you doing
The rat that this king has caught with hard work!
mouse?
It turns out that you stole my eggplant!
Don’t try to slip away
Launch!
This king catches a mouse
How did you offend you!
sorry!
I’m wrong again!
Feel sorry
It’s wrong for you
Apologize with sincerity
For example
Give me a guilty cry
This is the
To deal with you tomorrow
Since you’re delivered to the door
Then it’s better to hit the sun than to hit the sun
BB Goat leaves quickly
See where you run
Weslie Brother…
BB Goat!
Wolffy, you…
Don’t worry about me
Save BB Goat
Trouble us to catch rats
Also interfere with my ability to unlock
Don’t think about it
It’s all my fault
Causes BB Goat
Almost caught by bacteria
yes
You keep reporting errors
We’ve lost many times
I haven’t finished talking yet
At least he was because
Are you tight to Zhang BB Goat
And it’s all up to you
We’re fine
you…
Uncle Big Wolf is awesome
Is it good-looking?
nice