- Good morning Brother Weslie
Who is it
Who would you like?
Weslie
It’s the village chief
I received
A help call from the mountains
Help number?
Then I called Sparky and the others together...
They go to other grasslands
I’ve found the search for Brother BB Goat
I’ll go with you this time
The village chief is no longer
Just go with BB Goat
-But…
Even if you encounter danger, you can
Escape easily with BB Goat
Oh well
You must be careful
BB Goat
We’re going up the mountain
Going up the mountain?
I’m going to bring my toys and snacks
We’re going to save people
There is also Brother Weslie
Maps and guides
And water
All of them are what I want...
Decorated
BB Goat
alright
Then let’s go
good!
Let you see today
My gene tracking damage
My King Bacteria
Are you afraid of you?
I just need to scan
Useless
He will chase you wherever you run
Something interesting
Success!
what?
Being beaten down? !
Then come a few more!
My Milkycarba
It’s indestructible!
Have you dropped it all?
Wolffy
Your invention is good
But it’s mine right away!
He actually used the weapon I worked hard to develop
Copy it in one go
After so many times of grinding
I’ve grown too!
It’s your turn...
Wolffy
I’ll definitely come back
The King
Follow your plan
Weslie and BB Goat
Already already
Now, as long as we go
They can be slammed on the planned mountain
Well done, small green!
Then we will set out right away!
Display according to positioning
The person who sent a helping call
Just on the top of the mountain here
Just keep going up!
Mountain road dangerous, be careful
Weslie Brother
Watch quickly
Very tall
The scenery is so good!
alright
We’re looking for someone else
BB Goat!
Shocked me...
BB Goat
Stay well with me
Encountering danger
Be sure to catch me!
look!
We’re at the top of the mountain
But
The person who sent a helping call
Where is it?
It should be nearby...
Digital virus?
Weslie
You finally come!
It’s you
How are you here
That’s because of a help call
It’s what we sent out
You’re here!
How…
How could it be...
It’s hard to say that the phone calls from the beginning are all fake
Just discovered it now?
Too late
I’m not in vain for a lot of hardships
Climb this mountain
Thank you so hard!
It’s obviously me
Is it good to load yours?
Thank you for your hard work!
Now God can’t save you!
Hand over BB Goat!
I have to find a way to leave here!
please…
Leave BB Goat...
Stop him!
There is a cave there!
Can’t let him run into the cave!
Xiao Huang!
yes!
Don’t run away!
They actually hid in
So what should I do next?
Or maybe that’s better!
BB Goat
You’re fine, right?
I’m fine!
What should I do next
The phone was damaged just now
Can’t call for help
Will there be other exports?
You can’t escape!
Target locked!
Useless
This guide records your genes
No matter where you escape
It will always follow you
Even such a small hair can be followed
Weslie Brother...
You can’t let BB Goat have any trouble
BB Goat
Stay here obediently!
Wait for me to pull them out
I’ll come back to pick you up
But…
Don’t worry
I’ll be back soon!
Be good
Weslie Brother...
Where did you go?
I’m here!
Where is BB Goat?
Don’t stumble
Hand over BB Goat!
I can catch it before saying it!
Hurry up and catch him!
yes!
Even the entrance of the cave was kept...
How to do it
What about leading them out of here
You go find BB Goat
I’ll deal with Weslie
So you are here
The King
Xiaohong found BB Goat
Good do!
Can’t run anymore!
BB Goat was also caught
It’s really a kill of two birds with one stone!
King!
BB Goat!
Get it and unseal it for me
Let me go!
Don’t be tempted
Let them run away again!
I’m angry!
How did the guide fly back!
Xiao Huang!
What’s going on?
I don’t know either
Run!
What is this?
Little red!
Where is your Milkyrup?
Yes!
What’s going on
Failed again
Where is the king?
There
The king is really bad
Get up so quickly
Start thinking about the next plan!
Let’s go and take a look
Look at this time
How to report you
Get it done
What are you doing?
It turned out to be in the turtle...
It seems like someone...
Feeling a bit similar
It’s the goat you said before
It seems to be called wise...
Small green
Help me quickly check who is the father of Weslie
good!
They are indeed father and son!
Since they are father and son...
Weslie and BB Goat
Just brother and sister
Brother and sister
While Weslie has not yet discovered the truth
I’ll pack it first
BB Goat’s brother
Then you can be open and upright
Take her away
But how do you put it into
Where are their brothers?
The lamb is so cunning
It will definitely not be easy to plot
Unless there is a clear evidence
The King
I have a way!
Let’s do this first...
This way...
That’s the plan!
Good green!
That way we can
A new plan has been implemented