This is the mission given to us by the king
That’s right!
We must be in
The king finished the work before he returned
What about the big king and the little green?
The king went very far away…
Very far away on the grassland
Go there to catch the goat
Can
Looks very similar
My plan is perfect
Little green!
Give him a new look
no problem!
Please
Have you seen my sister?
Who are you?
I’m here to find my lost sister
Your sister?
Brother and sister!
younger sister! !
It’s so hard for brother to find you!
elder brother?
Is BB Goat your sister?
Yes
I’m his brother
Really
What’s your name?
Where to live?
I’ve prepared it
My name is HH Goat
Living in Guagua Village
My sister’s name is BB Goat
Brother is called HH Goat
Really quite like a sibling
I’ll call to Guagua Village to make a testimony
Have been called!
Hello
Is there a name in your village
The villagers of HH Goat?
That’s right
Yes
So does he have a sister
Called BB Goat
Yes
I confirmed it with the village chief of Guagua Village
What he said is true!
Very good!
BB Goat
You found your brother!
Then I’m going to take my sister home
Wait a minute.
To ensure accuracy
I want to compare your genes
All right
Match successfully
They have blood relationship!
There is a little green to help
Surely matched!
BB Goat
Found your brother!
Very good
Wolffy
I’ve gone to buy vegetables
good
What are you doing
I can’t tell you it’s wrong
Come again
What are you doing!
never mind
Be cautious of you
It’s almost done
Let’s dig tightly
It turns out you are digging holes!
Been discovered!
Can’t let him destroy the plan
what
dad
Small gray
Catch them!
Don’t blame me!
I’ll ask you in the future
Don’t worry!
I’ll take good care of BB Goat
Don’t want you to hold hands
good
Don’t turn hands
Wait a minute.
Before BB Goat sleeps
Like to hear stories
You remember to listen to her
Will it Will it
Wait a minute.
Remember to dress her when it’s cold
I’ll give her something delicious when I’m tired
OK OK
Wait a minute.
Are you finished?
No No
I want to control myself
Is there anything else?
BB Goat likes to eat candy the most
This gives her
Thank you
We can finally go home
No No
Weslie Brother!
I don’t want to go home
I’m going to play with you
But your brother came to pick you up
BB Goat
What exactly should you go
Before BB Goat left
Return the super cube
Researched
It’s a mess
Look, everyone!
I’ll do one in the future
Can speed up
Can be hot
Can also collect matter from the air
Even communicate with animals
and clone
Such an unrealistic thing
How can it be done
Don’t be discouraged!
teacher
The teacher believes you can do it!
I won’t leave
Listen
Go back
I won’t leave I won’t leave!
You take her back
I won’t leave
I want to play with everyone!
BB Goat, stop beating
right
Go home with your brother soon
I don’t want it
You come and chase me
Very fun
Stop running, sister
Come and catch me
You’re so small
BB Goat
BB Goat, stop running
Don’t be rude
Go home with your brother soon
I won’t leave!
I’m going to play with you
Who’s going to play with you
We’ve always
I’ve worked so hard to find you brother
I finally found it now
You said you won’t leave
You’ll be like this
Neither of us will
I like you again!
I’m the most trouble with Brother Weslie
I will never play with you again
Sister, wait for me
Finally got it
BB Goat
younger sister! Slow down
It’s so good
You can finally return
My brother
Back to my dad and mom
It hurts so much
How did I dream about the past?
This is
Ash’s sketch?
Why does it look like a super cube?
Grass picture
Super Magic Cube
Difficult to tell
Xiaozhi is
The maker of the super cube
If so
Weslie is
BB Goat’s brother!
Weslie goat walks away BB Goat
It’s for her good
Hopefully she won’t be too difficult
yes
I hope she will always be happy
Weslie
That goat is not BB Goat’s brother!
what?
Haven’t we confirmed it?
No!
The goat is likely to be
King Bacteria is under control!
King Bacteria!
Then we are not BB Goat
Give it a sterilization king!
You go chase it!
I’ll explain it to you on the way
good!
Are you ready?
Prepared!
Let’s start!
What are you doing?
Let us go soon!
dad
Son, don’t be afraid!
What exactly do you want to do
Let me tell you later
We hide underground
It depends on how you can stop me from unblocking!
Weslie
That’s how things are
so
Weslie, you are BB Goat’s brother
BB Goat is my sister
What about dad and mom
Why didn’t I come back with my sister?
Nothing will happen
Weslie
You’re fine
I’m fine
Don’t worry
We will definitely rescue your sister
Thank you
Let’s go
Wolffy’s father and son are really
I’m not here
Just messed up the house
If you don’t clean up, you dare to leave
Wolffy
You feel good when you come back
Have you come back with no choice?
It turns out they are lambs
Excuse me
It’s OK
That
We have something urgent
Stop it
BB Goat Where are you
BB Goat
It’s already so chaotic!
You’re still worried!
right…
sorry
Keep the change, please
BB Goat is not in Wolf Castle
Where are the lambs and the others?
lamb
Miss it!
It’s hard to tell!
Bag! Not good!