You’re not here
Don’t be afraid
The lambs will come to save us soon!
Will Brother Weslie come too?
I don’t want him to come and save him!
Don’t think differently about the sky
I’ve renovated your home
Each level of the connection
They keep it all
We’re at the bottom now
Even if
The lambs really come to this layer
Nothing to do
Because
The complexity of this terrain
Not what you can imagine
Come on, lambs
Where is this
When is Wolffy’s house
Is there this basement here?
Here
It should be to catch BB Goat
Newly created places
Let’s go down quickly
Here…
Many old electric appliances
There are also many snacks
Be careful
Here
It may be a digital virus ground!
Don’t eat the goat in a row
Something here
There may be many machine followers in it
The lights are lit
Paddi
You’re fine
Paddi!
Wake up Wake up!
You’re fine!
Paddi
I…
Success!
Paddi
You’re fine, right?
Why did you suddenly fall?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
It’s nothing!
Let’s go quickly
We need to keep up with the time
Found BB Goat
Weslie…
Wait for me
My hands
I’m obviously still there
I’ve exchanged my body with the digital virus
Such words…
really
I don’t feel anything to eat…
Don’t leave!
Give me your body!
Seafood
It seems like I’ve dived into the sea
Go quickly with the fish
So wonderful!
This…
This touch!
Try the taste again
Feel the whole fish
Jump to my tongue
This taste…
Stimulate every cell in the body
Then take a look at the smell of the body
-Too delicious!
Stop playing, goat!
We need to keep up with the time!
Come here
It’s so delicious…
Let this king unblock it obediently!
BB Goat
Lower your head!
Run!
Don’t run!
Where have they been going to Weslie?
BB Goat!
Taste my opportunity to stop!
It’s you
You mean guy!
Replace my body
Who are you talking to, Baiyangyang?
Everyone!
I’m really…
I’m the real goat
This is a fake goat
I just exchanged his body
Do you think we will trust you?
It’s okay, goat
Let’s go find BB Goat!
Don’t leave
I…
The friendship between you
Not so
I’m the real goat
It’s time to do a serious business…
I seemed to hear the sound of BB Goat!
There!
This is…?
Is the trap map of digital viruses?
Everyone is in danger
I’ll never let you have any trouble
Paddi
Are you sure you didn’t hear anything wrong?
You no longer have the chance to
I saw BB Goat again
Why does it suddenly appear
Their recollection is here
I also feel this heartache
There is also a little bit of hearing the phone
Is this body a problem?
Be careful, everyone!
It’s you again
Paddi
Everyone is fine, right?
You saved us?
Thank you, Goat
No need No need
Let’s go quickly
I just saw BB Goat
Running to that side…
I won’t let you hurt my friend
The exit is right in front!
I have more than one machine!
Take the call!
Come again
This time it hurts more than the last time
Why do I prepare to press every time
Difficult to tell
This is because you want to harm your companions
Feeling heartache
Keep up quickly
Paddi
but
The mission assigned by the king
Don’t fail
Disappear!
Digital Virus
No
You…you are the goat
what
Very hard to bear
Did I make a mistake?
I
Crying
No wonder we every time
In danger
This robot will appear…
Sorry, goat
We didn’t believe you before
That’s what you do
No…No
That’s it…
Tibbie
Can you call your Kunzi partner to help?
no…
Here is a newly built place
And the entrance is closed
It takes time to come in…
Paddi
let it go
Otherwise you will fall down
BB Goat must be very scared now
Waiting for us to save her
You must carry our hope
Save BB Goat successfully…
No!
I don’t want it
I…
I will never let go
No matter where to go
We all want to be together!
Very hard to bear
It turns out that I lost my friend
It’s so difficult
Everyone
We all have the people we cherish the most
Don’t want them to be hurt
-I shouldn’t be quarreling with you
I’ll take you back
You think so too
Right, goat
Digital Virus
My body has changed back?
Thank you, Goat
Thank you
Digital Virus
Although you
I’ve suffered a lot
but
Change your mind from you
When saving us
I’ll know
Actually, you’re not that bad
You go
BB Goat is not here
you…
Why
No reason
You are cheating!
You must be
After being exchanged
What I felt was moving
The robot
It really doesn’t feel like it’s not good at all
Leave aside!
You won’t leave again
I’m going to change my mind!
That…
Thank you Digital Virus
If there is a chance next time
I’ll lend you my body to you