This is completely different from the previous one
Simple and straight like the forest outside
This time I’m going to get the goat
otherwise…
Can’t complete the mission
Don’t come back to see me
Help!
You’re good
What is this
They’re flying
It turns out that there are also slaughter underground
They say
Go here to the next level closer
Then let’s go
Wait a minute.
I’m here
The lambs are gone
I can’t complete the mission
The king doesn’t want me anymore
This is
careful
It’s poisonous
Poisonous
It’s hard to tell
Mushroom fungus
What’s wrong with you
Tibbie
I’m very painful
You’ve been injured
I want to help you…
Be careful of having a good idea
It’s discovered that it’s over!
It’s okay
Mushrooms won’t hurt me
You go first
I’ll catch up later
Oh well
You must keep up quickly
All left
Then you can only pour out Tibbie first
This flying squirrel is controlled
It’s pretty good
Talking about Wolffy and the others
Where did you go?
So here it’s
Where is the person
Fortunately, it’s just a little skin
Just apply some medicine
Tibbie is good to me
No
I want to complete the task assigned by the king
But the medicine will feel tingling
you…
Have to bear it
It hurts so much!
Sorry Sorry
I didn’t mean it!
alright
Just about to take it
Tibbie
sorry
I can’t betray the king
it hurts
you…
Why are you injured again…
It’s too big here!
Where is the path to the ground?
That’s…
aisle!
It may lead to the ground
Dad Dad
I’m tired
Me too!
All right
While there is no one now
We went to find something to eat
Very hungry
I have to go to the kitchen to find something to eat
Finally found the kitchen
what
So much food!
It must have been stolen from Wolf Castle!
Take it all back to me
Find something to eat
Fill the stomach
Can’t keep a single one
what?
Nothing to eat
There is an apple
It’s you
Have done it
Be careful
Don’t be hurt again
It’s because I’m tired
Just fine
I have a cake given to me by the goat
Don’t be polite to me
I’m not tired yet
You eat
beg…
Please!
Please
Don’t be that good to me!
What?
We are friends
No…
We are not friends!
Mushrooms What are you talking about?
Haven’t we both been very good all the time?
I don’t want to disappoint the king
No
Isn’t it very good to run?
Run
Can’t run away
I won’t let you go easily
No
What’s going on…
Has the control been lost?
King Bacteria
Wait a minute…
It’s good to say something! It’s easy to say something!
It’s an elevator
We can finally escape
Open face identification
Verification does not match
Start the defense system
There is actually such a multi-defense system
Don’t be afraid
I’ll deal with it!
It’s you!
Thank you!
Wake up quickly! Mushroom fungus!
Don’t listen to King Bacteria
he…
He is a bad person!
bad…
people…
No
The King
He’s the poisonous mushroom that I have
Those who are willing to accept
I’m willing to make friends with me
Such a person!
Why is it a bad person
I don’t know you
Why are you so good to me?
Because
I think you look very similar to me
So I understand how you feel
Nonsense!
The king is not a bad person!
He’s doing something wrong now
To get strength
In the universe
We all know
No…
No
The king is doing this to make it stronger
I won’t be bullied anymore
Strengthened?
Although I don’t know
What did he experience
but
Injure others in order to become stronger
It’s just not right
Injuring innocent people
I don’t listen!
I don’t listen! I don’t listen!
The king is the only one who accepts me
Is my only friend
you…
I don’t know anything at all!
I don’t allow you
Let’s talk about his bad words!
Mushroom fungus!
Let’s go quickly!
no
I can’t put her down
She was in pain for mushroom mushrooms!
You go first
Mushrooms, you’re cold
Mushroom fungus
you…
King Bacteria is not
Your only friend
Me and the digital virus
It’s also your friend!
I believe you don’t think so
Wake up quickly!
Tibbie said it was OK
You are all my friends!
But
Very scared
I’m afraid of losing control
Fear of hurting others
So I never dared to really date you
but
I really want to be your good friend!
Mushroom fungus
We’ve been good friends for a long time
good friend?
As long as you don’t close yourself
Open your heart
All
All can be your good friends
Really?
real
Mushroom fungus
You’re awake
Really
Very good
Tibbie
sorry
Cause you to be hurt
Don’t think this will trap me
- Uncle, hello
Continue
-Uncle, hello!
What happened again!
Why did it get out of control?
Want to run, no door