The King
I’m here on the fourth level
The lamb will definitely not pass
Why do you still have to make such a multi-machine connection?
You’re my last line of defense
Must be reliable!
Finally got to you
Jonie!
You’re fine
It’s OK
These five holes on the ground
What is it for…
We don’t know either
More than one question
There are similar buttons in these holes
There is also a door leading to the next level
It’s actually in front of us too
But it just can’t be opened!
How to get out of this layer
No matter what the machine is connected!
My hot fist
Can handle everything
You can’t be too crazy when you are a goat!
who…
Ancient bacteria!
Tell us how to get out
Just five of you
Entering five pits separately
Press the button at the same time
You can open the door to the next level
But there is only one chance
Once you can relax
The door will never open
you…
Why tell us
Because I won’t let you press the button
So you know that there is nothing to say
Run and press the button
Let him be helpless
You’re just so crazy
I’ll beat you
As long as you can break through my Milkyria
I’ll let you press the button
OK!
Sparky
Don’t hinder
Let’s go together
It’s OK
This is my decision to fight him
You go and press
I’ll fight it
This…
Believe me
good
Then let’s press the button first
Be careful
BB Goat Where are you!
BB Goat
I heard something wrong
BB Goat, don’t run away
Uncle Gray Wolf, look
I’ve lifted many beautiful stones
What are you doing with these things?
I saw these beautiful stones along the way
Just pick it up and give it to your brothers and sisters
That’s the biggest
Give Weslie Brother
That’s not!
This largest
It’s for my brother
Which one is for Weslie?
That…that…
this
I just
Must have heard the sound
We switched to hide
I haven’t recovered yet
Otherwise, you can help your clone and press the button
It’s okay
Just press the button for each person!
Walk
There is a screen here
You can see the situation of Sparky !
Sparky
Sparky  is moving
Let’s act, too
I pressed it!
I pressed too!
It’s just about Sparky!
The popularity rises! The popularity rises!
The popularity rises!
You can’t break my Milkyne Armor
The heat rises again!
You can’t break it
Sparky
Be careful not to fall
dad
You’re fine
Dad is fine
Son
Let’s hide here!
Where is BB Goat
You’re fine
Don’t be slapped! Go quickly
I’ll just pick one
Quickly pick up
Where is it?
Where is it
Found
Where is the goat?
Can’t let everyone wait too long
The popularity rises! The popularity rises!
- Sparky
What happened!
The wall suddenly poured water!
So are me here!
Unexpectedly, King Bacteria
This trap is also set
Didn’t it be your and my decision?
You actually set this trap!
These are all set by King Bacteria!
I’ll save you right now
Wait a moment
There is only one chance
Let’s let go
The door will never open!
Sparky
We believe you can press the button!
Sparky!
come on!
come on…!
come on…
come on!
Ancient bacteria!
I’m here!
what!
Wait for me to save my companion
Let’s call again
No, let’s do it!
Sparky
I said
Only defeat me
Only press the button
Then I’ll fight you
Sparky
come on
- 未分
Too weak!
Is this your power?
Sparky!
Although you have perseverance
But it’s still too weak
The Sparky  will not give up!
Weslie…
In a crisis
You are everyone’s shield
Tibbie!
Anything
You can be ahead
Jonie…
Sparky
Let’s go to the next floor together!
come on! Come on…
Come on… Come on…
come on!
come on! come on!
You give up quickly
Rescue your friend quickly
It’s time to die
I regret it too much
give up?
How could I give up?
Behind me is my favorite companion!
I’m going to the next floor with them!
What kind of companions are different!
You can’t break my Milkyne Armor
If it were just me, I might not be able to break
what
But I have the power of a companion
companion
Breaked! ?
Sparky  Thank you for your hard work
I believe you can definitely do it!
Thank you Sparky
thank you
Thank you for your trust in me
Let’s go quickly
Wait a minute.!
Do it
Are you still going to play tricks?
Young people
You’re obviously no longer able
What made you regain your strength
Did you realize some secret?
No secret
Just because of the trust of the companions
Give me strength
companion
trust
It seems that I was taken to class by these lambs!
The lamb is a respectable opponent
BB Goat
The sound is just around here
I
I caught Weslie!
happiness!
He cheated on someone
Weslie is so terrible
It’s impossible to be caught
Are you really not coming out to see him?
My Weslie
But your brother
Weslie is my brother
Then do I not have to leave?
He must have cheated on us again
Hide and seek are discovered!
Come out quickly!