I found you
Come out quickly
The lambs are here
How did they do it
It was actually broken
No matter
Unlock first
Have you heard the sound?
The machine here is closed
You can’t escape, even if you ask
Let me catch the lambs
It depends on whether you can still come out!
Is this the fifth level?
There are so many doors here…
BB Goat Where are you?
BB Goat…
BB Goat
BB Goat…BB Goat
Good thing that will make you hurt me!
Don’t even escape today
BB Goat…
What’s up
Everyone, run away!
What the hell is going on!
Run!
That’s it?
King Bacteria!
Want to save BB Goat!
Not that easy
That’s not necessarily
you…
you
Get it quickly
BB Goat
Hand over it!
you!
Come just right
You beat me up on these lambs!
What are you waiting for? Quick
The King
actually…
The lamb is pretty good too
Yes
They also helped us…
Not as good as
Let them go?
alright
Don’t make jokes
Get on now
strength
It’s not that important either
There is no need to harm the lamb
you…
What’s going on!
Have you been washed by these lambs?
The king…
You will always be our king
But we really don’t want to
It hurts the lamb again
you
Even dares to betray me
Then I…
I had to take out my ultimate invention!
Take action by yourself!
Wait until I control the goat
No one can stop me!
careful!
King!
Don’t make any mistakes or mistakes!
Anything wrong or not?
Since you don’t listen to my orders
I’ll control you first
- Mushroom fungus! Amoetic bacteria!
today
Don’t even want to run away either!
Come in!
Look!
There is an exit in front
Son
Don’t run around
dad! Quick
dad!
Son!
Brother Wilie
dad!
There is a dad here
Not afraid
Scared Dad
Fortunately, I was caught tightly
If you have any danger, you have to catch me
Weslie Brother…
Be careful
Let me come
Please help us
Leave it to me here
You want to stop the sterilization king
good
You must be careful
Didn’t you say it’s helpful to us!
They lost their mind
Now it will only serve the orders of King Bacteria
You will all disappear for me!
You hold them
I’ll go to the helmet of the sterilizer king
good
Leave it to us
Digital Virus
To eliminate the goat
Since that’s the case…
Sorry for the digital virus
Really useless
Stop it
Come
Waiting for you for a long time
kid
Has anyone taught you
Running depends on the front
Weslie
It’s you next
Mushroom fungus
You wake up quickly
See you again
The little lamb
How…
What’s going on…
I am
It won’t hurt them
Mushroom fungus
Everyone is fine
It’s OK
We’re fine, either
How…
It’s an earthquake
Run quickly
Uncle Big Wolf
How long does it take to do it
Have you seen Brother Weslie?
We escaped here
You can see Weslie
What’s going on
- BB Goat!
Uncle Wolffy!
BB Goat
BB Goat!
elder brother
elder brother…
BB Goat?
Weslie
Why don’t you leave?
You leave here first
I’m going to find BB Goat!
Weslie!
I must
Unlocking ability!
There is no need to be a problem for BB Goat
- BB Goat!
Wolffy!
You’re not injured
Where is BB Goat
Weslie!
sorry
I didn’t protect BB Goat
she…
She was buried behind
Weslie
I…
I’m still
Or…
not
It’s time to…
Weslie Brother…
It’s BB Goat!
I must be waiting for me to save her!
Weslie!
You’ll leave with Wilie first
Weslie Brother
I’m here!
Weslie Brother!
I knew you would come to save me
Feel sorry
Have you been waiting for a long time
From now on
I just have the strongest power
King Bacteria
Let me go!
You shouted
No one will come to save you…
BB Goat!
Weslie…Brother
Brother is here
Brother is here to save you
It’s all my brother’s mistakes
Weslie Brother
I’m going to take you away
I’m the one who puts you in danger
I didn’t protect you well
No matter what!
I want to save you!
I will never let you go again!
BB Goat
Weslie Brother
It’s nothing
Let’s go back to the green grassland together