Bag adult
They suddenly disappeared here
It’s an earthquake
When did you have more authenticity at home?
It turns out you are here!
Do you know how worried I am about you...
Run quickly
The wolf castle is about to collapse
What’s going on?
Let’s talk about it after leaving here
The power finally came back!
The king has restored his original appearance
The little lamb
Taste this
The lambs…
And you are too red
Dare to bully the king before
Look at what I have prepared for you
It’s my rope gun
Weslie is you
You’re fine
King Bacteria is so strong
We’re not his opponent at all
Let’s go back to find the village chief first
See what’s going to do to deal with him
Then I’ll bring the red first
Leave here with Wilie!
Lord Baobao, go quickly!
The lambs are fine...
Let’s go and help the king to unpack it first!
unnecessary
Weslie
The king’s mighty power
They actually ran away
Wolffy
Take Wilie away quickly
Don’t be stupid
Go together
There are still no one here
Village Chief!
I already know
King Bacteria has unsealed the seal
Come with me
After my research these few days
Finally find a new line on the Rubik’s Cube
Can it be opened?
dad
mother
Uncle Smarc!
Aunt Lily!
We’re on a planet
When preparing to seal an evil power
unexpectedly
The sterilized king takes the lead
This power
Has horrible side effects
Power will swallow his sanity
Make him more and more evil
Become a violent destructionist
This…
That’s right
King Bacteria mentioned by Smarc
King Bacteria who fought with us is the same
Fortunately, we arrived in time
Use the magic cube
Stop King Bacteria
Next
Execute the sealing procedure for him...
It seems to be in the process of sealing
Escaped by the sterilized king
What does the king want to do to them
It’s fine
The king is not bad in nature
Run!
Wolffy
Let’s play with me again
You can’t escape
careful
What’s causing me to come
Don’t hurt my family
Wolffy
You walked away with Wilie
I’ll hold him
no
This is too dangerous
No matter how big he is, it is still germ.
I can
Listen to me! Go quickly!
no! Listen to me!
-You go first
Dad, mom, you go first
I’ll hold him
Small gray
Why are you not afraid!
I’m reporting you
You’re fine
Have you gotten empty?
So what about this trick?
This…
not good
If this continues, it will hurt Wolffy and their
You run
His goal is me!
no!
Go together
No time
Red Quick...
Run quickly
Wolffy
It’s you
King, let them go
They’ve already suffered a lot
I see
You’re going to betray me together
This power
The king is really good
You go quickly
but…
No matter what, he is also our king
We’ll find a way
I’ll notify the lambs too
Then you should be careful...
Dare to fight me
The King
Cold and quiet
A group of traitors
The King
It’s us
They won’t have anything to do
What should I do
Red
Hold on for a little longer
Once caught up by the sterilization king
We’re in trouble
It’s too late. Big gray wolf
What’s wrong?
You should do it now
Things you should do
I know you really want to stop King Bacteria
Then go
But
All the lambs with equipment failed
And I don’t have any ability
How could it be the opponent of King Bacteria!
I’m simply incapable of fighting!
Not like that
I believe my husband is the best
You are the first inventor
but
I only know the gray wolf I know
Not the one who gave up
I trust you
But…
OK OK OK
Don’t worry
We’ll take good care of ourselves
Red
Small gray
That’s right
I’m the first inventor on the grassland
It’s my son’s hero
I won’t be transferred to the District King Bacteria!
That dad mom
Where did you go
In the sky
In the sky?
Then they
not good
Digital virus says King Bacteria loses his mind
I also want to hurt Wolffy and others
Then we
Go and help them
BB Goat
You and Slowy
Stay here
Don’t run away
Village Chief
My sister, please ask you
Let me see what threads there are in the Rubik’s Cube
You’ll be a little sober
Mushroom fungus
You traitors
Where have you gone
Wolffy!
I’ll go home and get a weapon to save you
The king is completely out of control
He couldn’t hear us at all
He wouldn’t have been like this to us before
There must be a way to make him settle down
It turns out you are here
It’s useless!
Wolffy
I didn’t expect you to come back
Good courage
Oops!
The flying vehicle has lost its spirit!
you are done
I’ve come and helped
And we
you…
There is a way
The King
Restore your original appearance
OK
You actually resisted me with Wolffy
Unforgivable!
All disappear!
No way to communicate
Mushroom fungus
The King
Sorry
My eyes
I’m here
It should be OK now
- Two guys!
You wake up!
I’m Xiao Zi
Oops! Xiao Zi is in danger!
what
I’ve suffered
Try this trick
What’s going on
Did it succeed?
Not finished yet
I also need one of the most powerful weapons!
You give me
Go down!
This kind of king can’t come around
Let’s find a safe place first
Think about it again
Wolffy Back!
Wolffy!
It’s okay
I’m fine at all
Let’s leave here first
Leave
Don’t even want to leave