Everyone
You’re fine
It’s OK
But I didn’t see the gray...
BB Goat
Why are you here!
We were sterilized
Sucked into its belly
Is there a bacterial stomach here?
What a dangerous
Very scared
Can’t eat anything
What a pity
What’s the matter
Weslie
You’re so terrible
So where is this
We seem to be in the bacteria
What bubbles are these
Very strong
What happened
The king is sneezing
We are in the king’s lungs
Bubbles here
It should be possible for us to escape
Where are the lambs?
They have a lot of chance
It fell into the king’s stomach
There is also rotten stomach acid
Poisonous again
Very dangerous
danger
Then I have to save them
you
The little lamb
Also our friends
right
They are all our friends
Wait a moment
It seems there is something wrong
Be careful
What are these?
Weslie!
What’s wrong with brother?
This…
Maybe it’s just the poison
Let Weslie fall
It should be fine if you take a break
Poison is coming again
What’s up
We’re finished
Some tiles in the river
maybe
We can suck them up
Make a face wall to hold the poison
Leave it to me
It’s all right
Brother, what’s wrong with you!
elder brother
Weslie
It seems to be more difficult
Brother, wake up!
elder brother!
This is me
Where is it?
strangeness
I’m obviously in the bacteria
Weslie
What bacteria
Let’s sweep together
I’m not afraid of germs
Weslie
Don’t be stunned
Come and help
OK
Let them go
Weslie
Help
Let my friends go
lamb
I’m here
Wolffy
Save everyone
Go quickly Wolffy
Wolffy
What’s wrong with you
Save you
I ate you, it’s almost the same
we
Not a friend
friend
That’s what I’ve cheated on you
No
Stop playing
Come out quickly
Everyone...
Where have you gone
What exactly are they?
Analysis by me
They may be the king
The incarnation of evil energy
Is there any way to defeat them?
I can only fight with them with my head
Micacaria
Even the schizoa can’t stand
What should I do here?
There is a way to do it
But one person is needed
Do a sensation to lead them
Let everyone jump to a safe place
What is this?
Only fools do this
A bunch of bad eggs
Come and catch me
He actually...
What are you coming back to do?
Because
We’re all like you
It’s a fool
Then we
Let’s deal with these bacteria together
Keep going like this
We’ll be digested
If Weslie wakes up
When will my brother wake up?
He may be in a coma for a long time
Don’t listen to the slander
Weslie will wake up
Everyone, think of a way
Wake him up
I’ll try to stimulate his acupoints
Brother moves
It’s not Weslie
It’s the whole stomach...
They’re all moving
Stomach acid is coming again
The little lamb
Do you miss us?
Weslie
dad?
mother?
It’s great to see you
I just seemed to have experienced some terrible things
A friend was caught
Wolffy comes to eat...
Weslie
We’re here this time
I want to tell you
We’re leaving
That…
You’re this time
How long will it take to go?
We don’t plan to come back
You
Just stay in the green grassland
I don’t want it!
I want to be with my dad and mom
- See you again Weslie
dad!
mother!
Don’t drop me
Don’t drop me...
elder brother!
quick…
Can’t hold back
Every time it’s my brother who comes to protect me
This time I came to protect my brother
BB Goat
Is it hard to tell if BB Goat has the ability?
elder brother
elder brother...
Wake up quickly
Awake
elder brother
Come with me...
younger sister..
younger sister
There has been a reaction
elder brother
Walk
Brother, wake up
And we
Everyone
Let’s go together
Weslie
Wake up quickly!
Wake me up!
Brother, you finally wake up!
You screamed so loudly
How can I wake up?
not good
Stomach acid is coming again!
What kind of storm we haven’t seen
As long as we all go together
You will definitely get out of trouble!
Get out of trouble together!