There is a channel above
Let’s go up and hide first
Very good
Let me bring you out
Come on now
Come here!
Go quickly
Ancient bacteria!
Oops
Weslie!
Don’t be relaxed
Finally left
Fortunately, I informed everyone in advance
The grassland has been destroyed by him
What will we do in the future
mother
I’m so scared
Don’t worry
There are father and brother Weslie and others
It will definitely beat the bad eggs
Don’t be stupid
They’ve been long ago
Swallowed into your stomach
Oops
See where you run
It seems safe at the moment
Time is tight
Let’s find the exit quickly
Look quickly
There is a channel here
What are these floating light balls
Uncle Big Wolf is in the ball
Isn’t this when he was at my house?
How can I see it here?
These should be the memory of the king
Memory?
The King
Mushroom fungus
This King Bacteria looks like
Why is it weird?
This must be the body of the king
The light ball here
It’s black
Didn’t say
Can’t you take this path?
It’s the king!
Look quickly
Have you talked to us?
No…
Don’t bother
You say this every time
But trembling with fear
Who are these people!
He dares to bully the king
I see
This should be
The King’s painful memory
what!
Yes
The king
Tell me these things
We’ll play with you
The little devil is here
Why do everyone talk about me like this
I…
I’m so scared
It’s all because I’m too weak
I want to be stronger
Only this
You won’t be bullied
Didn’t expect
King Bacteria will have such a thing
The King
Let’s put this sterile king together
Rescue it too
We want him to know
Become stronger
It’s not based on evil power
Come and help
Then
Let me finish it all
The head hurts so much
What happened
One two pull
Everyone please help
Are you?
King, wake up!
Keep going like this
You’re going to be completely controlled by this force
What are you talking about
How can I be controlled by my own power
Weslie, you’re fine
I’m fine
careful
These evil clones appear again
They reacted so much
It seems this King Bacteria
It’s its weakness
What are you waiting for
Strictly stop them
Don’t worry about the energy
It’s impossible for you
Fight against me
I can
I also have the greatest strength
Just hate you
No
It’s us
Mushroom fungus
Leave the clone to us
We’re here
good
Impossible
You don’t know at all
How harmful is this force
In this world
Have great power
Just have everything
Not
Strength is not everything to you
Do you still don’t understand?
You’ve had it
The most powerful force
what?
Xiao Zi?
King!
Wake up quickly
The power of evil
It will only cause more people to be hurt
This kind of harms others
Follow the person who hurt you at the beginning
What’s the difference
The lambs always
Can overcome all kinds of difficulties
Always beat us again and again
It’s not their possession
What powerful power
But they trust each other
Help each other
Sparky
That’s them
The power of possession
The head hurts so much
I don’t need you anymore
What’s going on
I want to devour you
what!
Don’t think about it!
The King
I’ll still be reused by you when I’m a year
Really my blessing
From now on
I will always be you
The most realistic shield
Little red
The king is the best for the little green
There are delicious and fun
Always give it to me
Little Green made a mistake
The king doesn’t blame me either
No matter whether the king is weak or not
Who would bully the king
Little Green will definitely not be able to exorcise him
Small green
And me!
Xiao Huang
The king needs strength
So I’m here
Think about us together
Facing opponent
All of us are a combination of double dramas
As long as you need me
I’m willing to be
Your worst weapon
Xiao Zi
The King
thank you
Appear when I need help
Encourage me
I’m still willing to be my friend
So this time
Let me help you
Because
We are your strength
What’s going on?
What to say
You’re not my power
You are my friends
The King
Everyone puts their efforts
Everyone hold on
He doesn’t seem to be in a match
Everyone, hide
It’s them!
Red
Small gray
Mr. Slowy!
Children
Very good
You’re fine
Is it over?
This is…