How…
How did this happen
This evil body
How could it be resurrected
My body
It’s obviously separated
Maybe stay in
Your original body
You’re leaving now
Instead, it can completely occupy that body
Run away, everyone
Everyone
What a powerful force
It seems we still want
Fight him to death
Are you ready?
Tibbie!
Everyone
Please help us
Let me cover you up
Deformed rod bacteria
-Pleasant Brother Goat
You’re fine
Don’t come over
What a powerful force
We’re simply unscrupulous
Weslie Brother
You’re fine
dad!
Red
Take Wilie away quickly
That guy is too powerful
I don’t want it
Our equipment
All have been destroyed
Sorry, BB Goat
I can’t protect you anymore
You run away quickly
Escape quickly!
I don’t want it
I don’t want to lose my brother alone
You’re such a bad egg
I don’t want you to hurt them again
- Little gray
And me
And me!
And me…
This grassland is our home
Even if the strength is
We won’t give up our companions either
Our home
That’s right
This grassland is our home
I found this question
No matter what difficulties you encounter
No matter how difficult this difficulty is
We all want to protect this home together
rubik’s cube
Why did it appear here
Everyone
With everyone’s strength
We can definitely fight evil
Protect our home!
I didn’t expect that the super cube has this ability
Sure enough, evil cannot fight for justice
It’s so good
sorry
All of my thoughts on power
Have done so many mistakes
I’m tired
I’m really sorry!
Don’t need to say sorry to us
In fact, each of us
There will be times when you do something wrong
As long as we know there is something wrong
And corrected
Be brave to take responsibility
Then everyone won’t blame you
The power of evil
Finally, it was destroyed by the super cube
King Bacteria
Also change the evil and become righteous
Take us back to our original state
The place where dad and mom is frozen
Dad Mom!
Let’s unblock them quickly
good!
-Dad Mom!
Weslie Goat BB Goat!
There is also the teacher of Slowy
And the lamb
Can see you again
It’s so great!
Mom, I’ve won
I found Brother Weslie
BB Goat is awesome
Right
What freezes us is
King Bacteria!
Be careful
This is the king of bacteria
He’s very dangerous
The evil power in his body
It has been wiped out by everyone
Now
He is our good friend
sorry
I was blamed for being powered at first
Blinded by both eyes
You’re in space
Frozen for so long
Weslie!
Your mission is completed
More outstanding than us
It seems that we have been away these years
You’ve grown a lot
Weslie
Why
You clearly said that space is dangerous
I’m willing to bring BB Goat around
Don’t bring me?
I want me to be alone in the green grassland
BB Goat
Mom, take you out for fun
I want to play with my mother!
Weslie
Things are not what you think
Once
My mother and I
Performing a very dangerous mission
Suddenly, the monster was hit
When I beat it
In its body
I found a child
Estimated
It’s the baby who was eaten by the monster
Her name is…
BB Goat
Her dad and mom
Must be worried about her
We have to find it
Her dad and mom
That’s it
Us
In these years
Take care of BB Goat
Going to find her parents
But until now…
We still haven’t found it
About BB Goat
Any trace of life experience
That’s it
BB Goat
That’s right
She’s not your sister
but
During these days of caring for BB Goat
We’ve already taken him
It’s ours
My daughter is the same
I don’t know you, Weslie
Will you accept this sister?
I thought you didn’t want me anymore
Silly kid
Where can I have parents
Will you like your own children
elder brother
Let’s go play together
Why did my brother cry?
I have such a cute sister
So happy that I cried
Then
It’s not just Weslie that can play with you
We’ll all play with you
Very awesome!
Then let’s play games together
good
What game do you want to play?
I want to play, too
A cosmic crisis
That’s how it ends in terrible
The Bacteria Army also returned to their universe
Before repair
The planet that was destroyed by them
Wolffy finally returned to Wolf Castle
But it seems
A little lonely
dad
Come
Everyone’s life
All returned to its original form
The course of the course
What to play
And my summer vacation
There is a little change
I’m going home to have a meal
You ask me what changes have happened
Dad, mom, I’m back
Come back
Go wash your hands and eat
Your mother has done a lot
What dishes do you like to eat
I want to compete with my brother who eats faster
good
I’ll be your referee
Who would win
I’ll take him out to play on the electric car
Brother, go wash your hands and eat
- We are going to start the competition!
-I will definitely not transfer it to you!
Come
Prepared
three
two
one
Start!