Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
I Want to Play Basketball
Come on!
Stop him!
Oh no!
Come on!
After Lone Wolf’s plan failed,
The grassland have regained its former tranquility.
The Grassland Basketball Game is about to start again.
The Grassland Basketball Game is a major event held once every ten years on the grassland.
Teams from various clans compete in basketball on the court.
Each team will show their best basketball skills
on the basketball court with hard work and sweat.
Basketball has become the most searched, the most discussed,
and the most talked about sport of great popularity.
The entire grassland is abuzz about it—
besides the Goats’ Village.
Come here!
Weslie, you still run so fast.
Watch out! There are banana peels on the ground.
Good opportunity!
I got the ball!
Wolffy, you’re still as cunning as ever.
This is called winning by surprise.
You’re clearly just trying to cheat.
Okay, okay.
Here, take the ball.
What have you been busy with lately, Wolffy?
I’m just staying home doing nothing. Nothing to be busy with.
Oh, I see. No wonder you came to me to play soccer.
Weslie!
It’s Sparky.
I have a great discovery.
Great discovery?
That’s right, you’ll know once you come with me.
Wait, don’t rush.
Wolffy, let’s play again next time.
It’s Wolnie.
What?
Sparky, where are we going, running so fast?
Almost there.
See my new discovery,
a basketball court!
This is the great discovery you were talking about!
I searched the whole village before I found it.
Right now, Basketball Game is the most popular on the grassland.
Why don’t we participate together? They say if you win, you can have a wish granted!
If we win the championship, I will wish that each of us will receive a—
game console!
Da—Dama.
Why are you moving my blanket?
We’re sorry…
But this is a basketball hoop, not a place to hang blankets out to dry.
It’s such a waste not to dry things here!
I haven’t seen any villagers playing basketball in a long time.
I can’t play basketball either.
It doesn’t matter,
I’ll teach you.
With such terrible skills, I thought it was someone else.
It turned out to be a goat.
Who are you guys?
The coolest flames on the field.
The sky is our limit.
We are the most prestigious contenders for the Basketball Game,
Champ, Shu Er.
You have no taste!
Get out of the way, this basketball court is ours now.
No, this is our Goats’ Village’s basketball field.
Everyone knows that Goats’ Village doesn’t play basketball.
Do you need the basketball court to dry your clothes?
Who says we can’t play basketball?
Watch my explosive dunk!
What?
With your short arms and legs, Goat Clan has absolutely no advantage.
What makes you think you can play basketball?
You’d better hurry home and do your homework.
We might not necessarily lose. Let’s have a match!
Alright, we accept your challenge.
I’m back.
Come on!
Daddy, come and eat!
Wolnie, where did you get all these great things?
These are all free, aren’t I awesome?
Could it be another expired product?
This time it’s not.
I ran into the Wolf Clan’s basketball team recruiting players when I went out today,
where you can get this much food by signing up for the recruitment test.
Wolnie, are you going to play basketball?
I filled in your name.
Just go for a moment.
It’s fine as long as you don’t pass; it’s not dangerous.
Not bad.
There’s a match to watch!
Hurry up!
What happened?
What?! Champ and Shu Er are going to play basketball with the goats?
—Goats’ Village even has a basketball court?　—I never knew that!
Isn’t the Goat Clan known for not playing basketball?
Why are so many people suddenly here?
I called them.
Our Team Rats’ superb skills
definitely need to let all the grasslanders see it!
Great!
We’re playing two against two. First team to ten makes wins.
Okay.
Bring it on!
Let you go first.
The match begins!
We’ve finally arrived.
Is this the test site?
It’s really unique, like a prison.
This place is quite big.
Run!
If they catch us back again, We’re finished.
Catch them back? What does that mean?
Never mind. It’s none of my business.
This must be the training ground.
Faster, faster, even faster!
Something feels off.
Are you new here?
New here—
Yes, I’m here for the test.
Very good.
Let me introduce myself, I’m the team’s manager.
Congratulations, my friend!
Starting today, you are a reserve player of our team.
A reserve player?
Wait a moment.
You’ve misunderstood; I was just here for the test.
I didn’t come here to be your player.
What did you say? You came for the test to join our team, didn’t you?
You’re really lucky that our team is short-handed.
No, no, this is a misunderstanding.
I think I’ll quit the test.
Quit the test?
Based on the test form you signed earlier—
If you break the contract, you must return all the food.
What did you say?
It’s so small, who could possibly see it?
So, do you want to join the team, or do you want to return the food?
This wolf is even more cunning than me!
How can I return the food if we’ve already eaten it all?
Do I have to join the team?
Join the team?
Alright, let’s start training right away.
Wait…wait a minute!
I haven’t agreed yet.
I don’t want to train.
I didn’t expect it to end so quickly.
You guys are too weak.
Okay then, you win as long as you score one make.
Simple enough, right?
But I think it’s so difficult for them.
Weslie.
Weslie!
Such a strong sense of oppression!
I’ll definitely dribble past you this time, just you wait and see.
How can I score with this?
Sparky!
You can’t dribble past me.
What are you doing?
Where’s the ball?
Even if you run fast, you can’t even dribble the ball steadily.
What’s the use of that?
Team Rats won.
Team Rats played really well.
Is this the level of you Goats’ Village? So boring.
—Let’s go back and celebrate!　—I’m so angry!
There’s no more show to watch.
Let’s leave.
—Let’s go.　—Let’s leave.
Weslie, are you alright?
Sparky.
I never knew basketball could be so interesting! Let’s work hard together!
I want to prove that our Goat Clan can play basketball well too;
I want to participate in the Grassland Basketball Game;
I want to play basketball!
Well done. Continue with the plan; we must win the wish.
Roger.
I’ll definitely live up to your expectations.
To be continued…