In the previous episode,
Grassland Basketball Game sparked a basketball craze in Green Green Grassland.
Weslie and Sparky were ridiculed and outmatched during practice.
Wolffy unexpectedly joined the Wolf Clan basketball team.
What stories will unfold between the wolves and goats because of basketball?
Goats’ Village Basketball Team is officially established!
Wow, that’s amazing!
You guys can’t just be doing a simple basketball performance, right?
That’s right, we’ll also be participating in the Grassland Basketball Game.
We want to prove that the Goat Clan can also play basketball well.
You are the pride of Goats’ Village! We have high hopes for you!
Anyone want to play basketball with us?
No way!
Please leave me alone! We goats are no good.
Nobody is interested.
Let’s sign up for the Basketball Game first, we can find teammates later.
Okay, let’s go.
Why aren’t you leaving?
You need to tell me where to sign up.
Where to sign up?
You know nothing and yet you’re talking about signing up.
It’s at the streetball court in the forest next door!
So what do we need to prepare for signing up?
Just go to the venue, pick up the registration form, fill it out, and submit it.
Since you know everything, why don’t you join us?
Don’t be ridiculous! We goats’ physical fitness is that bad.
Participating will only invite ridicule.
We want to prove that as long as we work hard,
Goat Clan can also play basketball well.
Good luck to you guys. I’m rooting for you!
Am I really going to have to stay in this prison-like place?
Let me slip away from here quickly.
I… I didn’t intend to slip away.
I’m sorry, I’m sorry.
Training is about to begin; from now on, you’ll be called No. 99.
No. 99?
Are there any other numbers?
No. You’re our 99th player.
They even offer massage services here!
Of course! We have excellent benefits.
Excellent benefits?
Speaking of which, the flooring here is high-grade mahogany wood.
The cafeteria’s meals are comparable to those of a Wolvchelin five-star luxury restaurant.
There is also a scenic rooftop surrounded by mountains.
Actually, living here for a while wouldn’t be a problem.
Please make way.
What happened to him…?
It’s nothing, getting a minor injury during training is perfectly normal.
Injury? Is the training difficult?
Don’t worry. The training is simple, but there are always unexpected things that can happen.
Good it’s simple.
Can’t you even do something this simple? Lift it up faster!
Can’t you even avoid something this simple? Be more serious!
Yes, ma’am!
Can you get caught this simple? Run even faster!
It’s not rest time yet, get up!
Didn’t you say the training is very simple?
Who could endure this kind of training?
Our captain always finishes it with ease.
What? Finish it with ease?
Is this team’s captain a monster?
So many people signing up!
Let’s hurry up and line up to get the registration form!
What?
Wow, so fast!
Who are you guys? Why are you stealing other people’s things?
They don’t even recognize us Champ… and Shu Er?
It seems you… have limited strength.
It’s them again.
Return the registration forms to us.
You got a problem with that?
Let’s have a game. If you lose, you’re going back home.
Don’t waste the registration forms.
Go ahead and play, do you think we’re afraid of you?
There isn’t a single one who can play basketball.
Anyone else want to try?
Do you want to try? Do you want?
That’s just too much!
They play much better than us.
You can’t win even if you go.
Who else dares to come?
Give me a registration form.
Please wait.
Hey! That guy over there!
You didn’t even beat us, yet you want to sign up? Don’t you know the rules?
I’m talking to you.
Really?
Then I’ll play with you guys for a bit.
So fast.
Did he just disappear for a split second?
They appeared in front of me in an instant!
I won’t be so easy for you to pass.
What?
Stop him, Shu Er!
Don’t even think about passing me!
Completely unable to keep up!
But don’t forget, this isn’t a formal game.
No one will call a foul.
Let’s see how you run now.
That was a foul.
Haven’t you come to terms with reality yet?
Still trying to be stubborn?
The gap between us
is an insurmountable chasm that no means
can bridge!
It’s a dunk.
In the end, you are just two rats.
Don’t get too cocky, we just had a bad day.
You’ll definitely regret it when the Game starts.
How thick-skinned are they?
That wolf actually managed to dunk despite being blocked by two people.
He’s amazing!
However, if we encounter him in the game,
can we beat him?
Is there something we’ve forgotten?
The registration form!
Next!
This will probably take half a day to queue for.
One, two.
Why are you lying down again? Get up and keep training.
This will lead to my death.
I need to think of a way.
I have heatstroke! It hurts so much!
Then go and rest in the captain’s training room.
Then I’m going to rest now, to prepare for the next training session.
Wait a minute.
This training room is amazing!
There’s delicious food, all kinds of massage chairs, and game consoles.
But…
These are none of my business.
Why do I need to carry a rag and a bucket while resting?
Cleaning is also a form of rest.
When you get tired of cleaning, you go to training; when you get tired of training, you go back to cleaning.
Come back as soon as you’ve rested.
What kind of basketball team is this? It’s hell!
I almost got buried here.
Reserve player files?
Reserve player No. 1 suffered a comminuted fracture of his arm during training.
Reserve player No. 23 suffered from intellectual disability due to training.
No. 62, blind in both eyes.
No. 98, paralyzed in both legs
Why is there nothing written for No. 99?
No. 99 is me!
I need to get out of here quickly, or I’ll be next.
Here you are.
We got the registration form!
Now all we need to do is gather the players.
Then we can participate in the Game.
But where can I find teammates?
Sorry.
The registration form!
Excuse me, could you please return our registration form?
Aren’t you the wolf who played basketball really well just now?
Goat Clan?
Are there any more goats that can play basketball?
What are you doing? Give us back the registration form right now!
That’s all you are capable of; you’re not even worthy of participating.
We will definitely prove you wrong on the basketball court.
Our Goat Clan is also very strong.
Once I get through this door, I’ll be free.
How can this door be so sturdy?
What is that?
It turns out I need to press the button.
Wolffy, you actually tried to run away?
Bye now!
Don’t run!
If you run slowly, I’ll admit defeat.
Why aren’t you watching where you’re going?
Captain.
Are you alright?
Captain?
Captain always finishes it with ease.
He’s the monster captain!
Get back!
Another player lacking perseverance; Team Wolves doesn’t need him.
He also seemed to be in a bad state of mind.
No. 99, suffering from neurasthenia… left the team.
I’m so angry just thinking about that wolf when I close my eyes!
Weslie?
Why aren’t you asleep yet? It’s so late!
The wolf we encountered this morning was so strong.
We are simply not qualified to be his opponents.
So, take advantage of the time I can’t sleep to practice.
And during the actual game,
there will definitely be many opponents as strong as him.
Thinking about this makes me incredibly excited!
Let’s get started!
A whirlwind pass suddenly came to mind.
Catch it, Weslie!
Bring it on!
Weslie, wake up!