In the previous episode, Weslie and Sparky were signing up for the basketball cup.
But he was not favored by his clansmen.
They bumped into the impressive Victor at the registration site.
He humiliated me again.
The two goats therefore made up their minds
To prove that Goat Clan can also play basketball well.
Will they succeed?
The weather is really
Children, what’s wrong?
village head
What are you going to do?
We want to play basketball and win the basketball cup championship.
But our Goat Clan doesn’t have much of an advantage in basketball.
But we’re confident the village chief will teach us basketball!
I don’t know much about basketball either.
That’s true, the village chief is only good at studying.
Basketball
Who says I’m only good at reading?
It reminds me of that person again.
That person
That person is really good at basketball, but he always calls me a bookworm.
ridiculous
Okay, then let me be your coach.
You need to learn the basics of basketball first.
I remember we were going to play a game at the stadium.
Yes, we should have a competition.
Let’s go
Wait, our basketball theory class hasn’t even started yet!
They finally escaped; the village chief always talks about theory.
I don’t know when I’ll be able to practice.
Yeah, why don’t we have a sparring match right now?
Good idea
careful
Don’t shake them, they’re those two mice.
What are you doing?
It turns out it was Weslie and someone else…
Who? My name is Sparky.
What are you doing to our basketball hoop?
What, your basketball hoop? This is our basketball hoop.
Since you lost the match to us, the field naturally belongs to us.
Yes, whatever we want to demolish has nothing to do with you anymore.
It was a mistake last time, let’s have another match!
Do you want to lose again?
If you guys lose again, you might as well quit playing basketball.
Why are you silent now? Are you too scared to compete?
Continue dismantling the rim
Compare if you want
But the village chief
Don’t worry, with my guidance you won’t lose.
This old goat looks like something special.
Next
1 2 3 4, 5 6 7 8, 2 2 3 4, 5 6 7 8
Look, there’s a match over here!
Goat vs. Mouse
Finally, I don’t have to train anymore.
How should I explain this to Wolnie?
Let’s ignore that for now.
Wolnie, son, I’m home.
dad
You’re back just in time! Quickly, help me take in the clothes.
good…
not good
These actions have become conditioned reflexes.
Let’s tell her now.
Wolnie, I
I’ll come over when I’m done with my work.
good
I’ll go help too.
Dad, I helped Mom with a lot of housework today!
Really? Aren’t you tired?
Not tired, Dad’s an athlete now.
Regular training is definitely more tiring.
Wilie, Dad is no longer…
Completed
Come on, Wolffy
Here’s something for you
What is that?
This is
A towel, you can use it to wipe away sweat during training.
When it’s hot, just wet it and shake it to cool it down.
Dad, look
My mother embroidered our family on it.
Let me see.
The embroidery is really ugly.
What did you say
I…this
Dare to say it again?
The embroidery is very good.
Thank you Wolnie, thank you Willie
I will definitely train hard.
Is it okay for GOAT to be the referee in Ten-Ball?
No problem, absolutely fair and just.
Weslie, keep a close eye on the mouse.
yes
Sparky, keep a close eye on Shu Er
Let you go first.
Then I won’t be polite.
Goat’s dribbling has improved!
Weslie, over here
Oh no!
What a perfect start, little sheep (goat)!
There’s still nine balls left.
It seems Goat Clan is still not up to par this year.
The mouse scored its second goal.
There’s still a chance, come again.
Eight to zero, the GOAT is really suffering!
Ultimately, it’s just two kids playing house.
That’s right.
You guys still haven’t improved at all.
Goat Clan wants to play basketball? They should go back and swat mosquitoes.
Don’t go too far, there are still two goals left.
What
Such a fast speed
Who says the Goat Clan can’t play basketball? Let me play with you!
Don’t underestimate us.
Watch my steal
SSSC
Your ball control is amazing!
No matter how good your ball control is, you can’t get past the defense of both of us.
strong
That dribbling, speed, and shooting motion…it’s just like that person’s.
Good opportunity
That was a three-pointer, right?
yes.
Wow, my idol is amazing…
You’ve lost, go back.
The captains, only those four were selected as official players.
Another one, number 99, escaped.
If you can’t even stick to this much training, you don’t deserve to stay here.
But then there would be no substitutes.
Five players are enough; no substitutes are needed.
Is there anyone else who doesn’t want to practice, or who can’t stand it?
Get out of here now.
We will persevere.
Me too
Number 99, I thought he had run away.
Please give me another chance. I promise I won’t run away again.
Go run 500 laps around the track first.
Captain is truly brilliant
Dad is an athlete now.
With this, you can wipe away the sweat during training.
I ran
Everyone, please continue practicing.
good
Masked Hero, are you participating in the Basketball Cup?
So handsome… So cool… So amazing…
Thank you so much for saving our stadium!
That was so cool, especially that dunk!
What’s wrong with you
How’s your old injury to your right knee? Old Lie
I thought you had stopped playing basketball a long time ago.
Village chief, you two know each other?
Yes, he is my classmate Blazey, who said I am
Idol, please sign your autograph for me.
Waiting for a senior
Wait a minute, senior.
Idol.
If he were to become the coach, he might have a chance to win the basketball cup.
What, based on him?
impossible
Village chief, we don’t want Goat Clan to continue being ridiculed for not being able to play basketball.
I can be your coach too!
It’s gone.
Yes, the village chief only knows how to read books.
We only want Blazey as our coach.
I’ll give you his address, and then I won’t go.
Very good