In the previous episode, we talked about
Weslie and Sparky want to ask Slowy to become the basketball team’s coach.
During this time, Champ and Shu Er came to take over the Goats’ Village basketball court.
Suddenly, a masked expert appeared and defeated Champ and Shu Er.
It turns out he was Slowy’s old classmate, Blazey.
The map the village chief gave us showed that it was in this vicinity.
Look!
There is a house there
Finally found
Wait for me
Great! I’m about to meet the mighty Blazey senior!
You’ve arrived.
This imposing figure
He was still holding a basketball in his hand.
It must be
Before Blazey
generation
What are you doing?
Hello, grandpa
My name is Weslie
May I ask who you are?
Who I am is unimportant.
The important thing is
You’re blocking my way home
Sorry, we’ll be leaving now.
etc.
You said this is your home.
yes
What
So you’re Blazey senior?
Blazey senior? You’ve mistaken me for someone else.
Sorry to bother you.
Weslie, it seems we’ve come to the wrong place.
Let’s go
What’s wrong
Is he really not Blazey’s senior?
Weslie, what are you doing?
What exactly happened?
It’s you guys again! You all said you’d got the wrong person.
I’m sorry, grandpa.
The goat needs to use the toilet urgently. May I borrow it?
Can’t
Please!
You need to finish this quickly!
Thank you, grandpa.
Surprisingly, this old man’s house was quite tidy.
The toilet is over there, hurry up!
Okay… okay
This outfit looks so familiar…
let me see
This straw hat
Is this yours, grandpa?
What do you want to say?
Sorry, going to the restroom was just an excuse.
Actually, I wanted to come in and confirm something.
Blazey injured his leg after helping him that day.
And like you, he also has an injury to his right leg.
Plus this straw hat
It’s exactly the same as the one Blazey wore back then.
It really looks like it
You’re Blazey’s senior, right?
Please be our coach!
This is not a straw hat.
Look
It’s just a raincoat, an essential item for home use.
As for this…
I’m getting old and my legs and feet are having some problems.
Applying medicine is normal, right?
Sorry, I made a mistake.
Sorry to bother you
If there’s nothing else, hurry up and go, I need to sleep.
This is.
Basketball game
Grandpa, you still play basketball games?
Isn’t this a football game? It’s really popular lately.
Look
This soccer game is so much fun!
Isn’t that a basketball?
Okay, let’s go.
You don’t mean to tell me that it’s football, do you?
Isn’t that a soccer ball?
Who are you kidding? Any normal person would know that’s a basketball.
Is anyone there? Could you help me retrieve the soccer ball?
There really are people who get it wrong.
I’m going out to return the ball, you guys should hurry up and go too.
Be careful when you kick next time.
Go have fun!
let’s go
I think he’s really not a Blazey veteran anymore.
goodbye
I still think he’s Blazey’s senior.
Weslie
old man
Grandpa, what are you doing?
I’m tidying up the room and cleaning.
You clearly wanted to shoot.
You must be Blazey, please be our coach!
Get up!
Senior, you promised us.
no
You’re the ones blocking me from sweeping the floor.
Let our seniors feel our sincerity.
Senior, why don’t you take a nap?
Let’s clean up.
Then I’ll leave it to you.
Leave it to us with confidence.
Senior?
He ran away.
Senior, wait a minute
senior
That’s really troublesome.
Don’t be afraid, senior, we’ll help you.
I’ve saved you.
senior
Are you alright, senior?
Oh no, could he have fainted from his injuries?
We need to hurry up and find a doctor for our senior.
How can you fall asleep like this?
As expected of a master
We need to find a way to get up there.
Leave it to me, I can climb up.
Wait for my good news
Just a little bit more
Do you have some misunderstanding about the concept of “a little bit” white?
Are there any other methods?
There’s a tree branch on that cliff.
As long as we tie vines to the stones
Then put the stone through the hole and tie it to the tree.
We were able to climb up easily.
But that circle doesn’t seem easy to throw in.
Watch me this time!
My footwork is pretty good.
Pain… Oh, it hurts!
Watch me
Let me try again.
It’s still too difficult to hit the target.
How about we try a different shooting form?
Yes
A proper shooting form will definitely increase your shooting percentage.
But my shooting form doesn’t seem to be quite standard.
Shooting is also inaccurate
I’ll teach you
Is it reliable or not?
It’s definitely reliable; I’ve studied many basketball stars.
They are all like this.
Should I put my hands like this?
No, it should be like this.
Okay, jump up and throw it.
So this is what shooting feels like!
I felt my hands starting to boil.
Again and again
Don’t be so tense, relax a little.
I’ll do it.
So tired
It’s too far away
The stone fork was so heavy that my hand shape changed when I threw it.
Yes, as long as we don’t give up.
It will definitely succeed
I will not give up.
Senior, you’re awake.
Oh no!
senior
You really are
Luckily
Thankfully, Blazey was there just now.
By the way, the senior asked us for advice on playing basketball.
We will definitely study hard.
I will absolutely not give up halfway.
Please be our coach!
senior
senior…