In the previous episode,
Weslie and Sparky are asking Blazey to be their basketball coach.
To everyone’s surprise, an old goat opened the door.
His identity was only revealed after
the three goats fell off the cliff and he saved everyone with his pitching skills.
The two goats wanted to persuade him to come out of seclusion, but Blazey turned around and ran away.
Blazey senior!
Blazey, don’t run away!
I will not be your coach.
Blazey, please stop!
I said, I’m not going to be your coach.
Blazey senior!
Who exactly is that masked man? He’s so good at basketball!
Whoever he is,
if I ever see him again, I’ll catch him first.
How could you just meet a master like that?
Is he going to fall from the sky right now?
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
Blazey senior!
Are you alright?
They caught up so quickly.
I’m sorry, both of you.
I’m leaving now.
Blazey senior!
It’s those two goats again.
Brother, don’t you think that old goat’s voice sounds familiar?
He is that masked man.
Catch them!
Blazey senior!
What do you guys want to do?
Of course, we want to invite you guys to discuss basketball.
What are they trying to do by trapping us here?
They’re making a move.
First boil the water—
Boil the water?
Then add rock sugar.
Add rock sugar?
Sharpen the knife, quick!
Sharpen the knife?
Rats are eating goats!
Sparky, calm down. Rats don’t eat goats.
Blazey senior, what should we do now?
He can fall asleep at times like this.
As expected of a senior!
They’re eating goats!
Senior Goat, please try the broccoli I cut myself!
Senior!
What exactly do you want to do?
Please become our coach!
What’s going on?
On the day of the Basketball Game signing up, we suffered a crushing defeat to that wolf.
For us, it’s an absolute disgrace.
Until we met you, we felt you were even more formidable than that wolf.
If you’re willing to teach us basketball, we’re sure we can beat that wolf!
I’m sorry, I can’t agree to that.
Do you want to be their coach?
Don’t waste your time, they have no chance of playing basketball well.
No, it’s not that Goat Clan could never play basketball well.
Of course, you’re an exception.
Those two are definitely not a good match.
Their skills are so poor, they are utterly helpless.
How about this, you two have a match with them.
If you two win, I’ll become your coach.
If they win, you’ll release us.
What?
There’s no need to compete anymore, we’ve already won.
Since you have the ability, why not win again and show me?
Okay, let’s show Coach our strength.
Weslie, you’re better suited to small forward work.
Small forward?
Small forward is the key to scoring.
Your speed and explosiveness will become your powerful weapons.
What about me?
You have some basic basketball skills,
strong with good jumping ability, making you suitable for attacking under the basket.
You can do power forward.
Power… forward?
Power forward is primarily responsible for rebounding and defense.
Leave it to me.
How did you know our unique characteristics?
Have you seen us play?
No time to explain.
I have a trick here that can help you.
Listen carefully.
As usual, whoever scores ten makes first wins.
You should start at your own pace.
Can we win like this?
I believe in Blazey senior.
You still have time—
chatting here?
Don’t worry, there’re still chances.
It’s only their second make; there’re still chances.
Score two more makes and you’ll lose; the coach will be ours.
We must defend this shot to have a chance.
Chance?
You’re overthinking it.
Don’t underestimate us!
He’s about to shoot.
Don’t even think about it.
It’s a feint.
What about me?
You?
No way.
Nine makes.
What to do? We’re losing!
Okay then.
Here he comes!
You’ll definitely get blown 9-0 by the Team Rats.
However, given the arrogant nature of the Team Rats,
they’ll definitely say that when they’re leading by a large margin—
Okay then.
As long as you score one make, you’ll win.
This is your only chance to win.
Quick, get started!
I won’t let you pass.
You can’t get past my tight defense.
Weslie!
Even so, with our current strength,
it’s not guaranteed that we’ll make it.
I don’t expect you guys to score ten makes at all.
But I have a trick that will make you score one make.
They’re using a pick-and-roll.
A pick-and-roll is when the ball handler dribbles towards the player who is about to set a screen.
At the same time, the player setting the screen moves to the position and then remains stationary,
blocking the opponent’s shoulder impact
and screening to help the ball handler escape the defender.
Get back on defense quickly, Shu Er!
Do you think you can score against me just with a pick-and-roll?
Don’t forget I’m here to defend!
Feint to pass the ball!
Weslie, this is the only chance.
Go!
I won’t let this opportunity go to waste.
Oh no!
Blazey senior,
Please see our determination.
It’s in!
This is my only chance!
You guys won.
I keep my word.
You can go.
No more freebies next time.
We don’t need your freebies; our Goat Team will win again next time.
That’s right, it’s our Goat Team.
Our?
So, you’re willing to be our coach?
Coach, wait for us!
Coach!
Mr. Slowy, we’ve found Coach Blazey!
Long time no see, Slowy.
You’re—
Mr. Slowy, what’s wrong?
Isn’t this the coach you asked us to find?
Is it really you?
The little goat over there,
do you want to join the basketball team?
Basketball is very interesting.
What has happened to you, senior, over the years?
I want to know too!
Let’s go train.
Okay, Coach.
Goodbye, Mr. Slowy!
Goodbye.