In the previous episode, Blazey guided the goats to defeat the two mice.
And agreed to serve as the coach of the Goat Team.
But when Slowy returned to Goats’ Village, he didn’t recognize the people in front of him.
Blazey’s appearance has undergone a complete transformation.
What exactly happened to him?
That won’t work.
Listen to me
Ignore
Mr. Slowy, coach, please stop arguing.
Tell me, whose opinion do you listen to?
We want to hear
The basketball team’s next steps
This must be Xin’s.
According to big data analysis, all the top teams
There are many essential conditions.
Training grounds, meeting rooms, lounges, etc.
Not one can be missing.
What do you know?
In my experience, you can just recruit people and start training them directly.
We are now in the data age
Data is king, you have to listen to me.
But you’ve never even touched a basketball, what right do you have to give orders?
To help everyone build a basketball team
I’ve really mastered all sorts of basketball knowledge these past few days.
Mastered various key data for winning the game
Sports are not games; they cannot be measured by data.
Anyway, I need to build the basketball facilities first.
I’m the basketball team coach, so I need to recruit players first.
Whom do you help?
this.
What should I do now?
They’re so stupid.
If you can be lazy, why bother doing anything seriously?
Number 99, how dare you slack off!
Do 1,000 more
What about the others?
They were all seriously injured during training.
Looks like we’ll have to hire new people again.
The chance to escape the training ground has arrived.
This arduous task is entrusted to me.
I promise to complete the task.
Just make sure you complete the task; there are no prizes for this registration.
There probably won’t be many people signing up.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Then you can continue training.
No, watch how I complete the task.
Coach, tell me a story.
Mr. Slowy, why is your relationship so bad?
What happened before?
At the time, I was the top student in Goats’ Village.
Slowy, you’re so good at studying!
yes
What’s the use of just studying? Basketball is the best!
Blazey, you’re amazing at basketball!
yes
Is being able to play basketball really that great?
Is being good at studying something amazing?
That’s amazing!
We argue about everything, and neither of us is willing to admit defeat.
Oh, I see.
Even so, there is still one person who hopes we can become good friends.
That person is
Stacy
You’re just being stubborn.
You are the one
Okay, stop arguing.
Can’t you two just give way to each other?
Isn’t it nice to be friends?
Stacy went to great lengths to make us friends.
One day, Stacy invited me and Blazey…
Let’s go to the tree at the station.
But I didn’t make it.
Why
I’m sure I’ll have to say nice things about him again.
I won’t listen.
Unfortunately, Stacy left the next day.
Oh, and she also gave me a gift.
I’ve been carrying it on my person.
I have one too.
Coach, can I see the gift Grandma Stacy gave you?
Thanks
I’m really curious what Grandma Stacy gave the coach back then.
What is this…?
how so
How come your gift is the same as mine?
Give me back
None of you went to see Grandma Stacy that day.
Don’t you want to know why Grandma Stacy gave you these gifts?
Mr. Slowy.
If you go back together now, you might still be able to find some clues.
I won’t go with him…
Whether we find them or not, let’s rest enough first.
We want to join the basketball team
Sign it yourself
Wolffy
Why is it you guys?
Let’s join the team.
Basketball training is too brutal; I can’t let them suffer like this.
No, the spots are already full.
Stop lying, you just asked us to sign your autographs.
No, basketball team training is very tough.
You definitely won’t be able to stand it.
This is what you mean by “hardship”
I came out lazy, really.
We can do it too!
Anyone can be lazy.
That’s not true at all.
Don’t think we don’t know, you’ll receive a gift just for signing up to join the team.
Do you want to keep all the gifts for yourself?
Let’s go, everyone! We’re going to sign up!
I will not let you pass under any circumstances.
Wolffy, what exactly are you trying to do?
Uncle, I really didn’t lie to you.
The basketball team’s training is just too brutal.
Many people were seriously injured and had to leave the team.
Wolffy, we believe in you.
That’s precisely why we came!
Because you’re here, we can’t let you suffer any injustice.
Third Uncle
You’ve been complaining about feeling lonely and uncomfortable on the team.
We’re here to keep you company.
We are family; we share joys and sorrows.
Everyone
I didn’t expect you guys to be so kind to me. You really are good relatives of the Wolf Clan.
Finally, registration is complete.
Walk
Wolffy, we’re teammates now.
See you at the next training session
Stacy, I’m sorry.
I’m late.
This is Stacy’s letter.
I need to find something to take it down.
Isn’t that Stacy’s letter?
Yes
Finally got up here and got it.
You actually came too?
Why can’t I come?
Don’t try to swallow it all alone.
I took it down
this
Let’s watch it together.
Put your petals together
Then insert the stick from the letter to assemble it into a bamboo dragonfly.
You’ll see my message to you.
stick
This is a bamboo dragonfly.
Stacy
I had already left when you released this bamboo dragonfly.
Do you remember that time we were playing in the forest, and I almost got caught by a wolf?
I was terrified at the time, but you guys worked together to save me.
At that time, I firmly believed that you, my collaborators, were the best.
My greatest fortune is meeting you all.
If possible, please make up.
Even if I’m gone…
Finally, I hope you can fly higher and farther like bamboo dragonflies.
Let’s work together.
but
The letter and the bamboo dragonfly are both mine.
childish
Don’t run away!
Why is this basketball team working so hard?
I told you this a long time ago
You’ve been slacking off again. You’re punished by having to do another hundred.
No way!