Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories
Paddi joins the team
In the previous episode, we talked about
The goats finally got Blazey as their coach.
However, Blazey and Slowy have a lingering grudge.
The goats accidentally discovered
Stacy a few years ago
A video left for them
This video
Blazey and Slowy reconciled
Do you have any dreams?
Want to reach the pinnacle of a goat’s life?
As long as you join the Goat Basketball Team and win the championship
You can get a wish
Your dream has come true.
No need, goodbye.
Winning the championship would be beneficial, so who would participate?
Your methods for recruiting new team members
It’s really ineffective.
village head…
Come and see, you’ve successfully joined the Goat Basketball Team!
You will receive these gifts
Gift?
I want
We want to join the Goat Basketball Team…
A goat that only seeks profit, I…
Don’t cause trouble
You need to pass two tests to join the team.
The first test is a physical fitness test.
It must pass
Only then can you participate in the second round of shooting tests.
Are you satisfied now?
Why is leaving so troublesome? Never mind.
The gifts seem quite plentiful.
Why don’t you give it a try?
Okay, let’s register.
Those who have registered, come over.
This is…
My great-aunt’s latest golden cake
Coach, I want to play basketball too!
Paddi…
Alright, let’s begin the physical fitness test.
First is the strength test
This test is very simple.
Go lift your own dumbbells.
Paddi failed the strength test.
Next up is the running test.
Why are they running so slowly?
You’re the one who’s slow; they’ve all crossed the finish line.
Paddi also failed the physical fitness test.
It doesn’t matter, there are other tests.
Failed the jumping test
Thank you, Jonie.
This type of test is too difficult.
Why not have an eating contest?
I’m sure I’ll pass this.
That being said, you really need to work out more.
Not a single item passed
Could it be…?
Am I destined to never have a golden cake in this lifetime?
No, you have to wait for me, you delicious golden cake.
I will definitely eat you up.
Coach, please give me another chance.
The coach is very strict
Why would I give you another chance so easily?
Okay, come back and test again tomorrow.
They actually agreed?
Thank you, coach.
Paddi, where are you going?
You must have seen his persistence.
That’s why I gave him a chance, right?
Hopefully, he can channel that same dedication into basketball.
Want us to help train you?
Yes, I can do it no matter how I train.
In short, I absolutely must eat the golden cake.
No matter what your reason is
As long as you make the team
So, our three grassland musketeers
Then we can play ball together.
However, we are all beginners.
The training methods may be unprofessional.
Don’t worry, you definitely won’t be worse than me.
This doesn’t seem like something to be proud of.
Go train right away!
Training begins…
We haven’t even started, and you’re already hungry?
Let’s eat something first.
It would be better if you ate while training.
Is it really possible to eat and train at the same time?
Weslie, what do you mean by saying that?
You’ll find out soon.
My breakfast
You can eat it once you catch up with the toy car.
So you wanted to turn Paddi’s appetite into motivation?
breakfast
Let’s try other methods.
To successfully perform a pull-up
Only then can you eat bread
Keep it up, Paddi
It seems our training methods are effective.
This will incentivize Paddi to do it more often.
I know the trick to this training.
Keep training
Paddi is rarely seen
Will you persist in doing one thing?
He really doesn’t look like him at all.
But when I think about what he did…
Just for eating cake…
This is what our Paddi should be like!
Paddi, we’ll run with you too!
The Grassland Trio, chasing their basketball dreams
come on
It’s for the cake
nice shot
Paddi, are you alright?
It’s nothing, I’m just a little hungry.
Paddi has tried his best to practice.
Maybe I can pass the physical fitness test.
Are you serious?
My golden cake, wait for me!
Okay, let’s start the test now.
one time
Two times
It’s okay, much better than last time, just a little bit more.
Yes, I will definitely pass the second running test.
Paddi, what are you doing?
There were no snacks in front this time.
I have absolutely no motivation to run.
We’re almost at the finish line, just hang in there!
Let’s cheer for the cake!
It’s okay, there’s still a chance.
Paddi, you’ve improved a lot this time!
Yes, Paddi, you’ve done a great job.
Really? Show me the grades.
Bad test
I’m going home to eat snacks.
goodbye
Paddi…
Wait a moment
If you shoot free throws and make five out of ten…
We’ll make an exception and let you join the team.
Coach, Paddi is a beginner in basketball.
How could you possibly make the shot?
I’ll try anything as long as there’s a chance to eat cake.
Could it be…?
It really didn’t work.
It seems there’s little hope left.
This time it’s for real.
It actually went in!
So this is what it feels like. Okay.
Another shot made! Paddi is really amazing!
Paddi, an outsider
It has such a great feel!
As long as he is trained properly
Will definitely become a team
An indispensable member
The team is indispensable
One member?
Paddi, how did you make that shot?
I don’t know either, because I was just so hungry.
So I mistook the basketball hoop for a winter swing.
Think of basketballs as chocolate.
Pour chocolate over the tomato sauce
It will definitely taste delicious
As expected of Paddi
Barely passable
Congratulations on joining the basketball team!
Let’s eat cake together!
good…
These cakes are the result of your hard work.
Are you really going to share some with us?
Without your help in training me
I won’t get the cake either.
And cake tastes better when everyone shares it.
That being said, Paddi
If there is no cake as a gift
Do you still play basketball?
It’s okay, I can try playing too.
And win the championship later
I would wish for an endless supply of cake.
By the way, I’m going to see Tibbie soon.
She’s not even home, what is she doing?
I don’t know either, maybe she’s busy with something?
(to be continued)