In the previous episode, we mentioned that Team Goat was facing difficulties in recruiting.
Paddi passed the team entrance test because of his love for food.
Showcase his pitching talent and become the first new player on the GOAT team.
But the Goat team’s recruitment process has only just begun.
Start dribbling practice
Start passing training
Watch me
Everyone, you’ve worked hard. Take a break.
Thank you, Jonie.
So tired
Our dribbling and passing skills are terrible.
Let’s take a break, but the three of us should continue training.
Your technology definitely needs improvement.
However, judging from the training results
Our immediate priority is to find a point guard.
point guard
There are five positions on a basketball court.
I am small forward
I am power forward
Then I’ll be the center forward.
You’re playing shooting guard, which is also known as a shooting guard.
They are responsible for scoring.
What is the point guard for?
The main duty of a point guard
Ball control, dribbling past opponents, and passing to teammates for points
There is a good point guard
The team will be able to play more easily.
There should be no delay
Continue tryouts to select a point guard.
Trial training ended
With so many people, not a single one was suitable to be a point guard.
Point guard is essential; more tryouts tomorrow.
Wait a minute.
Tibbie
Coach, Mr. Slowy
I want to join the team.
Great! We were just thinking of getting a cheerleading squad.
What cheerleaders?
I want to join the basketball team.
Tibbie
You play basketball
Yes, I want to compete on the same stage as my idol, Leopardess (elder).
That way I can get a little closer to her.
Have you been missing these past few days because you’ve been chasing after celebrities?
But getting into a basketball team is not easy at all.
First, you must pass the trial training.
Trials are tough.
Maybe we should start as cheerleaders first.
I’m not afraid
Coach, Mr. Slowy
Please give me a chance.
Anyone can play basketball once they pass the tryouts.
Thank you, Mr. Slowy. Thank you, coach.
I will definitely work harder.
Tibbie barely passed the physical fitness test.
Now let’s begin the dribbling test.
I didn’t expect Tibbie to be such a good dribbler.
I often watch videos of Leopardess (elder) playing basketball.
Dribbling pass
Next up is the passing and receiving test.
good
His passing was also good.
Connected
Help!
You are not suited to playing basketball.
Tibbie, are you okay?
Tibbie, although your other test scores were quite good…
But to become a basketball player
You must not be afraid of basketball
I didn’t even dare to catch the ball.
Tibbie, don’t be too sad.
yes
There are actually many other ways to get closer to Leopardess (elder).
You absolutely must join the basketball team!
If you can’t get close to this celebrity
You can also change the celebrity.
Leopardess (elder)
The trial and selection process will continue tomorrow.
coach
Give me a little more time.
I am confident I can overcome my fear.
Three days later, test again.
Please pass me the ball.
Keep going! You can definitely overcome your fear of basketball.
The power of idols is truly immense.
bring it on
I’m sorry
It’s fine
Go Tibbie!
Yes, keep it up!
Just try more.
It still failed.
marvelous
You bravely reached out and took the first step.
Success is inevitable.
Again
Tibbie
Are you alright?
I think I’m almost overcoming my fear.
Keep passing the ball to me
Let’s stop practicing for now.
Yeah, it looks painful to me.
I’ll pass the ball to you if I’m okay.
You’re injured and need to rest properly.
We won’t pass the ball to you anymore.
Then I’ll ask someone else for help.
Mr. Slowy, please help me!
I won’t make you a passing machine.
Look at you, you’re all injured.
She still wants to keep practicing, just to chase after her idol.
Mr. Slowy. That’s not how it is.
When I was a child
I am weak
She cries at the slightest difficulty or setback.
I really dislike this version of myself.
But I don’t know what to do.
Until that day…
I saw Leopardess (elder).
No matter how many times she fell on the court
They will all get back up and save the ball.
I just realized that girls can be this brave.
So strong
I want to join the basketball team.
It’s not just about being closer to Leopardess (elder).
More importantly
I want to become as strong as Leopardess (elder) through playing basketball.
Mr. Slowy, can you help me?
So that’s how it is.
Silly child… wait
This passing machine can mimic the force and angle of a real pass.
Use it to practice.
However, you must take care of your health!
Thank you, Mr. Slowy.
Please help me start the ball machine.
good
continue
Weslie, think of a way to help Tibbie!
No need, trust Tibbie.
She has this spirit of never giving up on her goals.
Success is guaranteed.
Paddi is an example.
That’s right
Tibbie, keep it up!
Thank you, coach, for giving me another chance.
Are you ready?
Tibbie, keep it up!
We believe in you
come on
here we go
Tibbie, believe in yourself.
come on
Coach, Tibbie
Tibbie, point guard
Don’t be late for training tomorrow.
It passed.
I passed the trial.
Tibbie, you did it!
Leopardess (elder), I did it!