Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories
“Guardian Angel Under the Basket”
In the previous episode,
Tibbie volunteered to join the team.
However, her ball skills failed the assessment.
Tibbie encouraged himself
You should resemble your favorite basketball player.
So brave and strong
After a lot of hard training, I finally joined the team.
There is a point guard.
So where is the right center?
Come on over and have some tea!
Thank you, Jonie…
Congratulations on joining the basketball team!
I made some healthy salads.
Blazey, come and have some too!
Me?
You don’t need to count me in.
Our Jonie is truly like our guardian angel.
They prepared everything for us.
Jonie, why don’t you take some time to do your own things?
You always take care of us.
I was also a little embarrassed.
Actually, I don’t have anything of my own to do.
If I really want to do it, it’s to encourage you.
This is what I want to do most.
Jonie is really good.
Jonie, why don’t you join the basketball game too?
Then we can play together.
right…
Me? I think I’d rather not.
I don’t have a talent for this.
It’s more like I’m cheering you on.
Everyone, I have some very important news.
I just received a notification
The day after tomorrow, I need to take all the goats to the registration office.
If by then we haven’t collected enough goats…
The team will be disqualified from the competition.
What? Cancel…
Eligibility for the competition?
We now have small forward and power forward.
Shooting guard, point guard
We still owe…
center
Where can we find a center?
A genius like me…
It’s not impossible to hold several positions.
You can’t.
The center is the hub of the entire team’s offense and defense.
Not only must one have a tall stature and extraordinary strength
They also need to be able to protect the rebounds.
He can be described as the guardian under the basket.
Guardian deity?
Should I switch to being the center?
Those who are capable are often given more work.
Your height is insufficient for this position.
We need to conduct another open selection.
Select center player
If even I can’t do it, who can?
Okay… don’t be angry anymore.
Neither defense nor strength is good.
Neither height nor jumping ability is good.
I have to report for duty soon, what should I do?
If there is no suitable center
Our team has a fatal flaw.
It definitely won’t go far.
The only option is to look again for a goat to choose from.
Let’s continue practicing.
It’s back
Thank you
Sparky, are you alright?
I’m fine, thank goodness you’re here.
But Jonie, you’re really strong!
It’s good that you didn’t get hit.
Weslie, do you think we can really…?
How to assemble five suitable team members?
All Goats
Still can’t find a suitable goat to choose from
Coach, give me one more night.
I will definitely meet your standards.
Wake up!
Even so, there are only four goats.
actually…
We also have suitable goats to choose from.
She has no problem with height or strength.
Coach, please tell me who it is!
You finally acknowledge that I have talent?
Make way
She is her.
As expected of Jonie, she passed most of the tests.
Sparky, why don’t you have a match with Jonie?
Compete with Jonie? Forget it.
Don’t you really want to be the center? Give it a try!
I’m sorry, Mr. Slowy, I…
I really can’t play basketball.
It’s okay if you don’t know how, just come with me.
Let me show you what I’m capable of!
This rebound is mine.
It’s mine.
So tall
In the game
Your height will give you a greater advantage in getting the ball.
When the ball is in mid-air
Imagine you’re helping a child get their money back.
A kite that got stuck
Helping a child carry a kite?
Since you have the advantage of height
You just need to jump as high as you can.
We can definitely get the rebound.
I…I got it.
Jonie is really amazing…
Of course
Oh no, danger!
The key to protecting the basket is to constantly block the opponent.
Like protecting friends
Don’t let him run into the ladder.
Remember, you just need to do what you normally do.
Protect your friend, don’t crash into the ladder.
Jonie’s defensive foul
The match is over; it’s a draw.
Squad Leader
Lead us to victory!
Me? I don’t think I did anything.
I was just doing what I usually do.
He’s already this good just by playing casually.
I’m so envious!
Jonie, why don’t you join the team too?
Then the five of us can spend all day together.
I…
Come on, Jonie!
Always protecting their teammates from behind
Protecting the basket at all costs
The guardian under the basket
This location is very important.
Will you always protect everyone?
I’d love to give it a try
Awesome…
Goat Team
One, two, three, four, five
Okay
Good luck in the game!
Come take your photos here after you’ve registered!
Three, two, one, laugh
(to be continued)