Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Basketball Star Player
As mentioned in the previous episode, the registration deadline is approaching.
Blazey discovered that Jonie, who was helping out from the sidelines, had center talent.
Invite her to join the team
After winning the one-on-one match against Sparky
Jonie realized he could protect his friends on the court.
He then agreed to stay.
Everyone finally registered successfully.
Dear Wolnie, Son
How are you?
I am training hard every day now.
I recently made another beautiful three-pointer.
Fans are all chasing after me for autographs!
No. 99
It’s laughable that he hasn’t even made it into the reserves.
My teammates all like me a lot, and we chat and laugh together.
As the team’s star player, I even got to stay in a VIP suite!
When did you become the commander-in-chief?
I just didn’t want Wolnie and the others to disappoint me.
What if Wolnie and the others find out you lied?
Won’t you be even more disappointed?
Wolnie
You liar!
I won’t let them know.
Are you very free, No. 99?
They’re actually chatting.
You’re punished by having to clean the entire training camp.
Why am I the only one being punished? He was chatting too.
When did you arrive?
I was working so hard and didn’t notice at all.
gather
Saint Capital sent me out for running training.
yes
You guys hurry up and finish cleaning, then go for a run too.
Yes, sir.
Move your leg a little
Wolffy
The list of your opponents for the first match has been released.
Our first match will be against Team Rats.
It’s them again.
We have grown a lot during these days.
We must defeat them on the court this time.
Team Rats’ strength should not be underestimated!
Champ’s attack was incredibly fast.
Shu Er’s defenses are tight.
The other team members were also experienced.
All the data shows that our win rate is very low.
We have a coach, he will definitely help us achieve this.
Now that you’ve finished talking, let’s go train.
Why are you here?
I brought food for Dad.
Surprised?
This is something that Wilie and I put a lot of effort into making.
Wilie is amazing, this is such a wonderful surprise!
Wolffy, didn’t you tell me you were the star player of the basketball team?
Why are you mopping the floor?
I’m not mopping the floor, I’m working out my arm strength.
As a basketball team captain
I have my own unique training methods
We’re all here, aren’t you going to show us around?
Cannot enter
Because the team needs to go into seclusion for training.
Outsiders are not allowed to enter.
What about Wilie?
I can intercept the ball.
Wilie is amazing!
It’s time for Wilie to go back.
No, I want to watch Dad play ball.
I also want to see the style of the basketball team’s star player.
Basketball star
Yes, Dad is super good at playing ball.
Please cooperate.
What’s wrong? Your eyelid is twitching.
I beg you, please act in a play with me.
I don’t want to disappoint them, mother and son.
I can fetch the balls for you, and I’ll clean up for you every day.
Please
No need to say more
We’re all family, how could we not help you?
You guys are so great!
But since you insisted on helping us clean up and pick up the balls…
We have no reason to refuse.
I just went to warm up.
Next, let me show you the might of the basketball team’s star player.
Go Dad!
Wait, let them serve first.
Wolffy is so handsome!
I’m going to steal your ball!
Received it a little later
Beautiful!
pretty
They got the ball.
Wolffy is amazing! Dad is amazing!
I’m making a feint.
Too fast
Wow, what a brilliant feint!
That’s great, that’s fantastic!
That’s amazing!
Don’t block it
Explosive Dunk
As expected of our commander!
Dad is awesome
It’s nothing.
Could you help me down?
The coach only had us practice the basics.
How can you win a game if you only know the basics?
If I master this move
Maybe we can finally put up a fight against Team Rats.
Go Weslie!
Go, basketball star!
Go Dad!
Commander, you’ve had your moment of glory, time to clean up!
Wait, let me score the last goal.
Basketball star Wolffy scored another spectacular basket.
No. 99, shouldn’t you be cleaning?
I’ll go now
You’re as useless as those goats.
They don’t deserve to play basketball on the court.
Why do you say that I and goats are not good enough to play basketball?
I want you to take back what you just said.
They’re getting really excited, as long as they can get the ball from me.
I’ll pretend I never said those words.
This is what you said.
The shadow couldn’t even touch the ball.
I was so focused on watching the game that I forgot to bring your lunchbox to your dad.
If you can’t even get it like this, aren’t you the team’s star player?
That’s outrageous! Let’s go help!
Mind your own business
Wolffy, you
Sweep the floor more often when you have time.
Don’t just call him the star player of the basketball team all the time.
dad.
Wolffy
Where are we going, Dad?
He’s not here.
Mom, isn’t Dad the star player of the basketball team?
The silly boy’s father said he was the basketball team’s star player.
Then he must be…
But why did Dad lose just now?
Everyone experiences failure at some point.
But as long as you don’t give up, you’ll definitely win next time.
I believe Dad will win back.
Because he is the most outstanding basketball player.
I believe him too
He will definitely become the best basketball player.
Wolnie, son
I will definitely become the basketball star in your hearts.
To be continued…