In the previous episode, we talked about
Wolffy lied and claimed to be a star basketball player.
Unexpectedly, Wolnie and her son suddenly visited the set.
Wolffy put on an act to cover it up, but his teammates saw through it.
Who would have thought Wolnie would see through it but say nothing?
I firmly believe Wolffy will succeed.
This strengthened Wolffy’s confidence in becoming a star basketball player.
Collected
Having gone through so many difficulties
The basketball team belonging to Goat Clan has finally been established.
The start date of the competition is not far away.
Everyone needs to keep up the good work!
yes
Do you have any words of encouragement for everyone to say?
Less talk, more practice
And so, everyone trained basketball under Coach Blazey’s guidance.
Learning basketball skills under the village chief’s guidance
Everyone practiced day and night.
Basketball skills are also constantly improving.
And the long-awaited day has finally arrived.
Today is the opening day of the Grassland Basketball Cup.
Everyone is about to face a series of formidable teams.
Every match was tough
Your performance will change everyone’s opinion of the Goat Clan.
Are you all confident?
have
So, what’s our team’s name?
Oh right, we don’t seem to have a team name yet.
Let’s call them the Super Muscle Team, because they’re strong and powerful.
That’s too rude.
Call them the Butterfly Team, that sounds so nice!
Am I right, Jonie?
No. Too girly.
Let’s call them the Grass Cake Team, Yixin’s cake is delicious.
No, the Super Muscle Team is good.
Butterfly Team is good
Grass Cake Team
No, that’s not good.
Everyone, please stop arguing.
Don’t let a team name affect our relationship!
Listen to me, let’s call Weslie and his friends team!
Why is it only your name?
No, stop arguing.
Let the captain decide.
Hurry up and get on the bus, the opening ceremony is about to begin!
So, who is our captain?
It seems like it hasn’t been decided yet.
I am the team leader
I’ll do it. I’ll do it.
Then you shouldn’t take a car, run to the venue.
Whoever arrives first becomes the team leader.
I accept the challenge.
Let’s compete, who’s afraid of who?
To avoid letting you choose such a vulgar name
We girls won’t give up either.
Right, Jonie?
Come on, don’t lose to Weslie and the others!
I think I’ll just take the bus; the team name isn’t that important.
By the way, the captain is the core of the team.
Besides deciding the team name, you can also decide what to eat each day.
Being a captain is an honor and a responsibility.
I must take responsibility for this.
Jonie, let’s keep up the good work!
We can’t lose to them
Let’s all ride together.
What about the captain and team name?
Village chief, don’t worry.
You will take a car to the competition venue first.
Help us see who arrives first!
Ready to go
Look over there.
The captain’s position is mine.
Then you might need to run faster.
You should lose weight.
I’m leaving now.
come on
I’ll go first.
Wait for me!
Only the first place winner can be the team captain? Who would fall for your trick?
Why do we have to climb mountains?
Move aside, don’t block the way.
Team Wolves
We’re rushing to the basketball cup competition, don’t block our way.
What’s with the fuss? We’re the same.
you.
Don’t run
They have great stamina.
Wait for me
Wolffy
What are you doing here?
I’m now a reserve player for the Wolf Clan basketball team.
I’m on my way to the competition registration.
What? You got into the Wolf Clan basketball team?
Yeah, you guys too?
That’s right, we want to achieve great results representing Goat Clan in the Basketball Cup.
Let everyone take a new look at our Goat Clan
Let’s hurry to the venue!
Why are you still here?
We’re waiting for you!
What? What exactly do you want to do?
It’s nothing, I just wanted to give you a warning.
The bridge is broken, you might not be able to get to the venue.
Give up as soon as possible
I’m not there yet, don’t leave me behind!
Those wolves went too far, even abandoning their own teammates.
We must defeat them on the field.
But the bridge is broken, how are we supposed to get there?
Follow me, everyone. I have a solution.
Wait for me
Why haven’t the children arrived yet?
children
I’m sorry, I admit my mistake.
You’re also on the Goat team, right?
What’s Goat Clan doing playing basketball? They should just go home.
What? Our coach is incredibly skilled!
Old Lie, Old Lie!
The coach probably deserted at the last minute, and the players can’t come either.
What does it mean that the players can’t come?
On the way here, we accidentally broke the bridge.
Your little goat can’t come.
What? The children are in danger?
Don’t worry, they will definitely get here safely.
What are you worried about? They’re still just kids.
No, I have to go see them.
Do you really have that little faith in them?
Aren’t you more worried? Your palms are sweating.
I just finished using the toilet and washed my hands.
So filthy
Let’s collect more vines together.
What’s the point of collecting vines when the bridge is broken?
As long as we unite
Even if the bridge is broken and the road is gone
We can also forge new paths.
Yes, we definitely can.
Third, keep going!
Once we cross the river, we’ll be at the venue soon.
Let’s all cheer each other on!
Let’s go quickly!
Don’t walk so fast, it’s too dangerous.
It’s okay, the water isn’t deep.
Sparky
Oh no!
Everyone
As long as we unite, we have nothing to fear.
That’s right, let’s all go together.
Everything will be alright.
The venue is just ahead.
children
How did you get so dirty? Is everyone alright?
fine
Didn’t you arrive together?
Who should be the team leader?
you
We all agreed that Weslie should be our captain.
When everyone is in danger
You always encourage everyone to unite.
You are the perfect candidate to be the team leader.
Everyone
team leader
nice shot
I’m so glad you’re all alright.
With me, Wolffy, here, what could possibly happen?
What are you doing here?
Wolffy also participated in the basketball cup.
Oh, I see.
I need to hurry and meet up with those reserve players.
What? Those wolves were Team Wolves’ reserve members?
Otherwise, Victor and the others would have arrived at the venue long ago.
So, Team Wolves’ starting lineup is even more impressive.
No matter how strong they are, we will definitely be able to defeat them.
Okay, let’s hurry up and register for entry.
What is your team name?
Captain, it’s your decision.
We must protect the dignity and dreams of the Goat Clan.
Let’s call our team the Guardians.
good
This place is so big
There are so many queues!
Welcome everyone to this year’s Super Basketball Cup
7. This year’s participating teams are truly outstanding!
Each team has its own style of basketball.
The upcoming matches are sure to be exciting!
To make things easier for the players of each team
We specially built this basketball city.
In addition to the competition venues, there are other facilities here.
Each team also received accommodation, training facilities, and other amenities.
Athletes who have traveled from afar can also rest and train here.
Make sure everyone is in top form for the competition.
I hereby declare the Super Basketball Cup officially open.