In the previous episode, how the goats were choosing a captain and a team name.
The decision was made to race to the venue to determine the winner.
When the goats were locked in a stalemate, they encountered Team Wolves reserves.
After realizing the gap in their abilities
The goats learned to work together and arrived at the meeting place on time.
These are the tactics for dealing with the Team Rats.
You must remember
This is our [number] match.
Only success is allowed, failure is not permitted.
Do you all have confidence?
Don’t be so tense, relax a little.
Coach, wait a minute
Do you remember?
During the previous match against the Team Rats
I took the ball and wanted to break through the defense at high speed.
But it failed, I was thinking…
If I could master that move…
Perhaps it can help the team.
That move…
If you can master that move
That would definitely be a great help to the team.
However, the ball always seems to lose its control when I accelerate.
What exactly am I lacking?
After this period of training
You’ve already developed a certain feel for dribbling.
You’re missing an opportunity right now.
Opportunity
This opportunity will come when it’s meant to; there’s no need to rush it.
But tomorrow is our first match!
You just need to practice more and relax.
The opportunity will come naturally.
No, I still need to practice some more.
We absolutely cannot lose to them.
I need to work harder
Only then can we continue to play ball together.
Opportunity
What does it mean exactly?
Why is it still like this after practicing so many times?
Who threw the ball around like that?
With your short arms and legs, Goat Clan has absolutely no advantage.
Why should I play basketball?
You’d better hurry home and do your homework.
No, we absolutely cannot lose.
The Guardians’ journey has only just begun.
It can’t end like this.
I must lead everyone to victory in the game.
So handsome!
Wolffy, what are you doing here?
I now go for a run every night to train.
You’ve become a starting player.
not yet
But now that I’ve made the choice, I’m going to give it my all.
My goal is not just to play.
I also want to be the captain of the basketball team.
In order not to disappoint Wolnie and Wilie
I want to prove to everyone that I can do it.
I believe in you, I know you can do it.
Are you training too?
I’m practicing breaking through defenses, but I just can’t seem to get it right.
Don’t you have a really great coach?
How did he teach you?
The coach simply said that the opportunity was lacking.
But what exactly is this opportunity?
The coach didn’t tell me.
Does “opportunity” refer to breaking through your own limitations during a critical moment?
You’ve always been like this, haven’t you?
At a critical juncture
You guys have a match tomorrow, right?
We absolutely cannot lose
As the future main basketball player of Team Wolves
I’m looking forward to a basketball showdown with you!
good
Stop! Stop right now!
You’re so handsome! Can you teach me that move I just used?
I learned that maybe we can win the game tomorrow.
Sorry, I’m tired of playing.
I’m going back.
If no one teaches me, then I’ll learn on my own.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
I’ve been playing basketball for so long and I still can’t master the moves.
Italy won!
Can you teach me a powerful trick that guarantees victory?
Please
There are no magic tricks in basketball that guarantee a win no matter what you learn.
But tomorrow is our team’s first official match.
If we lose, my basketball team and my teammates’ games will end.
Our dream was shattered.
What you need right now is not a magic trick.
Z
Instead, adjust your mindset.
mindset
Enjoy the game no matter what.
Focus on the game and do your best in everything you do.
This is the strongest version of you.
Do you do your best in everything you can?
I understand
By the way, what’s your name?
Help!
Help…help me!
Wolffy, hang in there!
I’m here to save you.
Be careful…
N
Weslie, watch out!
Weslie 00
What are you doing with the ball at this hour?
This feeling
Here we go again…
You come over here and hide for a bit.
Haste makes waste; don’t overthink it.
Relax and the opportunity will come naturally.
Weslie
I see
What happened? How did you dodge in that instant?
I think I’ve mastered the feeling of breaking through at high speed without losing the ball.
Squad leader, so you’re out training too!
But I feel I still haven’t practiced enough.
How can this help everyone?
I’m back
Coach, what are you doing here?
You guys go back and rest.
But we still feel it’s not enough.
Coach, could you give us extra practice?
Believe in yourselves, you have done enough.
Also, trust your teammates.
Basketball is a five-player sport.
You shouldn’t try to take everything on yourselves.
Only one night has passed
You’re like completely different people.
My mental state is much better.
What we need to do is enjoy the game and focus on the game.
Do your best in everything you can
That’s how we become the strongest.
Let’s all cheer each other on!
come on
Set off
Paddi?