Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
The Intense Debut
In the previous episode, we saw the goats have their first competition.
They were all very nervous.
And four of the goats all went out to train separately, without prior arrangement.
And each of them made some breakthroughs.
Only Paddi remained soundly asleep.
Today is the Guardians’ first match.
Keep it up, everyone!
Blazey and I prepared a surprise in your backpacks.
It’s a jersey.
And the sneakers are so cool!
Try them on!
Okay, let’s go.
Hello everyone, welcome to the Basketball Game competition!
I’m your host, Moki.
The highly anticipated first match is about to begin.
Please give a warm round of applause to welcome our first team.
Team Defenders
Go, little sheep (goats)!
Don’t waste the space I gave up for drying clothes so you could practice!
There are no spectators, what are you nervous about?
And you, you even wore your jersey backwards!
Next, another team was arrogant and agile.
Team Rats
It’s all your fault for being too weak; no one’s watching the game anymore.
Coach, if they lose
You should teach us; we have much more potential.
It’s a promise.
alright
The competition is finally about to begin!
Go for it, kids! Just do it like you do during practice.
Okay, the referee is ready to serve.
Both teams’ centers are very focused.
Who will have possession of the first ball?
Oh no, I jumped too early.
Team Rats gained possession of the ball.
I won’t let you score.
feints
Passing you is as easy as crossing the street.
Team Rats scored the first two points of the game.
Overestimating one’s abilities
It’s okay, we just need to play steadily and score points.
Okay, so how will Team Defenders retaliate next?
I can do it.
Team Defenders was dispossessed.
Team Rats scored two more points.
It seems Team Defenders aren’t in very good shape.
You need to time your shot correctly.
Paddi, run! Everyone’s starting their attack!
How did I make another mistake?
A newbie is a newbie; they’re already this nervous at the very beginning of the competition.
Withdrawing from the competition earlier would have saved you from such embarrassment.
We need to break through this situation quickly.
Too slow
We succeeded! We finally…
Yeah
Team Defenders were dispossessed again.
Team Rats executed a difficult spin layup.
They went on a 12-0 run.
Is there no other way?
It seems you two are about the same as those other players who just made up the numbers.
One-sided, how boring!
I should have gone home and watched MLD 3.
How dare someone so weak participate in the competition?
Exactly, isn’t this just adding unnecessary workload to us?
Cheer up and don’t let other things distract you.
Keep it up!
Hey Blazey, why don’t you talk about them too?
It’s no use, they’re all too nervous right now.
What should we do then?
Why are you watching that Goat Team’s game?
I’m watching Team Rats.
You guys better keep up the good work, Weslie!
Don’t let down the time I spent practicing with you all night.
I need to work even harder.
See you in the finals, little goats!
left
Oh no!
You guys are too easy to fool!
Team Defenders requests a pause.
We’ll lose if this continues.
Coach, what should we do?
What should I do? Didn’t I tell you all yesterday?
yesterday…
I remember now.
We were so nervous just now that we forgot everything.
It’s normal to be nervous during your first official competition.
The important thing is to adjust your mindset afterwards and unleash your true potential.
That’s right
If things get any more tense, we might as well pack our bags and go home.
Aren’t you just making them more nervous?
Didn’t you want to prove to everyone that the Goat Clan is also very strong?
Then go out there and use your skills to conquer those who doubt you!
Have some confidence
yes
Everyone’s expressions changed; I didn’t expect you to be so good at motivating people.
It’s alright, a bit better than yours.
What
The timeout is over, back to the game.
Let us show you our strength!
What good would calling a timeout do?
We’ll probably be down by ten or so points at the start of tomorrow’s game.
What should we do then?
First, use Weslie’s speed to break through their defense.
They certainly didn’t expect your speed to be such a threat.
Go and surprise them!
yes
This guy has a different aura.
nice shot
Team Defenders finally scored!
That breakthrough was like lightning, so fast!
Now you know how powerful we are, right?
That was an amazing shot, Weslie!
They only scored one goal, what’s there to be happy about?
These two points will change the course of the game.
Isn’t that obvious?
What
Let’s press our advantage and keep scoring!
The first half has ended, and both sides are now in a break.
Team Defenders has suddenly become incredibly powerful!
This match is going to be interesting.
Our Goat Clan is very strong.
yes…
Seriously, these two goats are so much better than last time!
Don’t rush, brother, how about we do this?
Okay, the second half has begun.
Let’s wait and see.
The second half began with a duel between the two team captains.
Is it coming? Lightning Breakthrough
This…this is
Team Rats were trying to defend against Weslie’s lightning breakthrough.
They actually used a three-man swarm.
Sparky was also double-teamed.
Team Rats stole the ball.
Fast break score
The Team Rats has started targeting Weslie and Sparky, their two leading scorers.
These little mice are so cunning!
How should Team Defenders counter this type of defense?
You guys shouldn’t have brought in teammates just to fill the roster for the game.
As long as we can stop both of you, we’ve already won.
Who told you that?
Who told you the rest of our team were just there to make up the numbers?
My teammates are really strong.
The Team Rats will definitely use double-team defense against Weslie and Sparky next.
Tibbie, Jonie, Paddi. It’s your turn now!
Yes… Coach
I succeeded.
Jonie, you’re really amazing!
Yeah, yeah!
I was careless.
Keep up the good work, everyone!
good
We must hold this ball.
yes
We’re just one point away, let’s go!
What a bold statement!
Can Team Defenders turn the tide and win?
Time is running out for them.
To be continued…