Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
The Mysterious Ace
In the previous episode, we mentioned that the Goat Team faced the formidable Team Rats in their first match.
The Goat Team was initially at a disadvantage due to tension.
Fortunately, the Goat Team showed their true strength in the second half and tied the score.
At this point, only ten seconds remained in the game.
The last 10 seconds
I won’t let you pass.
Sparky
Don’t even think about it.
Team Rats are keeping a close watch on them.
We deliberately left your shooting guards unguarded.
The purpose was to intercept the ball.
How did the Team Rats Center end up there?
It seems Team Rats anticipated that they would pass the ball to Paddi.
Oh no, they’re about to get the ball stolen.
Paddi actually used his weak body
Blocked Team Rats’ center
What? It wasn’t sent to Paddi?
Just like the coach said.
Tibbie, you’re the one to throw this ball.
I’m not good at shooting.
That’s why they overlooked you.
They’ll definitely assume we’ll give the ball to the shooting guard, Paddi.
You just need to imagine the small rim on the backboard as…
You just need to pass the ball to the right person.
Team Defenders wins
They won
nice shot
Well played
You guys played amazingly!
SS
I can’t believe we lost. You guys are so weak.
We’re not weak at all; you’re underestimating us.
S SSL Basketball is a five-player sport.
As long as the five of us unite, anything is possible.
Looking forward to playing another match with you guys next time.
I have to train right after the competition, can I have a break?
how
Champ and Shu Er What are you doing here?
Are you upset about losing and want to cause trouble?
They were the sparring partners I hired.
You lack practical experience
That’s why I specifically invited them to play practice matches with you.
That’s right
Okay, let’s begin the basic training.
Run 20 laps
yes
It’s really surprising that Champ and Shu Er would be willing to help us.
If they can win the championship
Losing to the champion is not shameful
Can they really win the championship?
You have many more games to play, so don’t let your guard down.
yes
After two months of competition
Everyone’s strength has also improved.
But we must not be complacent. We still need to continue strengthening our fundamentals.
yes
Looks like I still need to learn how to dunk.
Then I’ll be the coolest player on the field.
As expected, my skills weren’t up to par.
They were unwilling to teach me.
Brother Champ
I want to learn how to dunk, can you teach me?
Dunking - Of course
no
Why?
First, master the basics. Go practice your dribbling.
Coach, I want to learn how to dunk.
Can you teach me?
Dunking - Of course
no
Why?
Let’s build a solid foundation first, one step at a time.
Learn to walk before you run, otherwise you’ll easily fall.
I must find someone to teach me.
All the chores are done
Can I go on stage now?
Go ahead and clean the court.
It’s just cleaning, isn’t it?
I, Wolffy, am the king of cleaning! Watch me!
This time the entire court is mine.
team leader
I… I packed up immediately.
The captain is really amazing!
3 n
Team Captain Good Morning
How come there are only a few of you left?
The captain and all the other second-tier players have applied to leave the team.
And those relatives No. 99, I wonder where they’ve gone to slack off.
A bunch of useless wolves, you guys come and practice!
yes
No. 99, give us the ball!
C
Wait a minute.
Clean that
Come practice together!
Are you calling me?
Are there other people cleaning?
Yes, I’m here.
Finally, I can rest. I’m going to buy some good food.
All I want to do is eat
It was him
I’ll go first.
Lion Jay - Invincible and the Most Handsome
Next up is Lion Jay.
Lion Jay is awesome!
His name is Lion Jay.
Hello fans, please go over there.
OK…
Lion Jay
With a quick-drying towel, you won’t have to worry about sweating a lot.
Buy… handsome…
Thank you everyone for joining our event.
Now, Lion Jay is going to give his fans a treat!
The person who caught the quick-drying towel thrown by Lion Jay
You can go on stage and take a photo with Lion Jay.
Do you guys want it? 52
What do you want?
Lion Jay
Prepared
Don’t take mine…
Don’t steal mine.
mine.
Lion Jay, do you still remember me?
My name is Sparky
Who wants to know your name? Just kidding.
Give us back our towels!
Sorry, have we met before?
That night at 11 p.m., you came to the streetball court to practice.
He even showed me his amazing dunking skills!
You’re just talking nonsense, why are you pretending to be an acquaintance?
Lion Jay would never practice basketball late at night.
Yeah, our Lion Jay would never stay up all night practicing.
Okay, this fan
You probably misread it.
Lion Jay is a health ambassador who goes to bed early and wakes up early.
It’s impossible for him to practice late at night.
Exactly, you fake fan.
that is
Okay everyone, remember to go to bed early and wake up early!
That way you can be as healthy as me.
Good Lion Jay
Okay… Lion Jay
It’s clearly him, why won’t he admit it?
Lion Jay is so handsome!
You also like Lion Jay
Of course
You’re finally starting to grow up and know how to understand your opponents.
Team Lion Heart is our opponent in the next match.
What
Oh no, Lion Jay is so amazing!
Isn’t our chance of winning only 1%?
Yes
However, this 1% win rate is theirs.
Our win rate is 99%.
How could that be?
Team Lion Heart is very strong
But they have a fatal weakness.
That is, their coach is also their agent.
He didn’t care about winning or losing; he only cared about Lion Jay’s image.
All I want to do is make Lion Jay a popular idol.
So that’s how it is.
I would be so grateful if someone could teach me.
I wonder if Lion Jay will come here tonight?
Lion Jay
Sorry, you didn’t mistake me for someone else yesterday.
However, the agent was nearby.
So I didn’t admit it.
Why is that?
I’m an idol, and many things are beyond my control.
It seems the coach was telling the truth.
Why did you sneak here?
Practice, my agent has too much work to do.
I had no choice but to sneak out at night to practice.
So that’s how it is.
By the way, Lion Jay
I still want to learn how to dunk from you.
To be continued…