Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
The Lion’s Dream
In the previous episode, we learned that after the goats defeated the Team Rats…
Blazey continues to train his fundamentals as always.
Sparky wants to learn cooler basketball skills.
So he trained alone, but unexpectedly ran into the popular idol Lion Jay.
Sparky was completely convinced by Lion Jay.
Little did they know that he would be the next team’s opponent.
Sparky, stop running away!
Sparky completed 100 laps
I’m going now.
He leaves right after practice these past few days, I don’t know what he goes to do.
I don’t care what he wants to do.
I don’t want to do anything anymore, I want to rest.
children
Your task tomorrow is to observe the Lions’ training session.
Only then can you know yourself and your enemy.
No training tomorrow
Let’s begin.
What’s wrong
I’m curious why you’re willing to teach me.
Everyone else thinks our Goat Clan is weak and looks down on us.
I admire people who genuinely love basketball.
Thank you
So, will you teach me how to dunk today?
No, learn to play with your back to the basket.
But I don’t want to learn this.
I want to learn how to dunk.
Judging from your height and build, this back-to-the-basket one-on-one attack style seems suitable for you right now.
Learn the basics first
You haven’t even learned to walk yet, how can you learn to run?
How come you said the same thing as my coach?
Try to stop me
Steal the ball
You need to use your body to apply appropriate pressure to the defender.
Although you need to exert force with your body, you must keep your center of gravity stable.
When you push the opponent’s back-to-the-basket game to a certain extent…
You can then choose the method you are best at to score.
This is a back-to-the-basket post-up.
Me too
Lion Jay
Lion Jay has so many people
Master
Lion Jay
Lion Jay, stay close to me, don’t get separated!
It would be great if Sparky came too.
He’s so strong, he could pull me in.
Lion Jay… Sparky has been acting all mysterious lately.
I don’t know what they’re doing.
Lion Jay
Jonie, etc.
Don’t push
Lion Jay
I’m so dizzy
Paddi, are you alright?
This fan is so enthusiastic!
Let’s get to the last photo.
alright
This concludes today’s fan meeting.
Please leave in an orderly fashion.
Yes, thank you everyone for coming to see me.
See you next time
Wait, we’re not fans.
We are Team Defenders, your next opponent.
Whatever
Let’s go, Lion Jay
Grassland’s best-selling magazine wants to interview you.
S 5 5 j
Hurry up and find it for me.
yes
Try dunking again.
Sparky, are you alright?
pain.
Didn’t I tell you to build a solid foundation first?
Forcing a dunk can easily lead to injury.
All right
You look very tired.
I have too many things to do these past few days.
I went to practice again tonight, so I have dark circles under my eyes.
If you don’t want to do those activities, you can tell your agent.
Why must we listen to him?
Because my agent is my benefactor.
One day, we will play basketball on a bigger stage.
That was amazing! You’re a born star!
Who are you
I’m a basketball idol’s agent. Do you want to play real basketball?
I’ve been observing you for a long time.
Your basketball skills are absolutely beautiful.
I can help you get on the court and become a basketball idol.
Can I?
Of course
Lion Jay
Please take a look.
Lion Jay…
Lion Jay
Get ready to style!
If this continues, we will lose.
Image competition second
You guys should pass the ball to Lion Jay more often, make sure he can dunk and score.
I thought being an idol would be easier.
Why don’t you leave your manager and quit being an idol?
He’s the one who made it possible for me to play basketball on the court.
I don’t want to be ungrateful.
Later, one day
I heard you’re really good, let’s have a match!
You go first.
It turned out to be just empty talk and no real skill; it was easily defeated.
You don’t deserve to be on the field at all.
It’s okay, as long as you have a good image.
Strike another cool pose
good
One day I will prove that my basketball skills are not just empty talk.
I am qualified to stand on the field.
Therefore, being a good coach is not important on the field.
The fundamentals are the most important.
As long as you keep training, dunking will be a piece of cake.
Yeah.
Come on, today I’ll teach you the most important technique of Power Forward.
The most important skills
That’s right
It’s about grabbing rebounds.
Cricket
The most important thing in rebounding
It’s about predicting where the ball will land after it bounces off the rim.
Start one step earlier than others
You’ll have more chances to get the rebound than others.
Get back the ball you missed.
Create more opportunities for teammates to attack
This is the rebound.
Whoever controls the rebounds can dominate the game.
Really
Of course
Let’s get started! Basketball is so much fun!
Sparky has been disappearing lately, what has he been up to?
Lion Jay
Where are you, Lion Jay?
Lion Jay is just like Sparky.
Do you like to slip away by yourself?
Lion Jay
I finally found you
Hurry up, the best-selling magazine on the grassland wants to interview you!
Wait a minute.
At this rate, Lion Jay won’t have time to practice basketball.
It’s you goat again.
If you’re weak, don’t drag others down.
If you want to practice, then practice on your own.
Walk
Lion Jay, say something!
Sorry, I’ll go back with you.
Don’t associate with these weak people anymore.
Being photographed by reporters will damage your reputation.
We, the Goat Clan, are not weak at all; I declare war on you.
Declare war
If we win the next game
You need to let Lion Jay play real basketball.
Stop forcing him to become an idol.
boring
We will definitely win.
When did you arrive?
We arrived a long time ago, we all heard it.
Don’t look down on people.
Don’t regret it if you lose.
Winning or losing doesn’t matter, let’s go.
To be continued…