In the previous episode, we talked about
Lion Jay taught Sparky many power-forward techniques.
Their friendship deepens
Sparky realized that Lion Jay didn’t want to be an idol.
Encourage Lion Jay to be brave and be himself
But Lion Jay was forced by his manager’s gratitude for his talent.
They still gave in.
We have such a large audience!
We must have won a few games.
So everyone started paying attention to us.
Does this fan want an autograph?
Let me
They’re here.
So you’re all fans of Team Lion Heart!
I can’t believe you don’t even have a single fan.
Then we’ll reluctantly pretend to be your fans.
Let’s not do it.
Lion Jay is about to enter the arena to prepare for the match.
Please go to the audience seats.
Let’s look forward to Lion Jay’s performance!
Sparky
Good luck in this game!
The same to you /
See you on the field!
Why would Lion Jay greet you?
Please let me go.
Ladies and gentlemen, the competition is about to begin.
The stands were absolutely packed today!
Team Defenders were the first to take the stage.
Go Team Defenders!
Next up is the one everyone’s been waiting for!
Team Lion Heart
Lion Jay, the ultimate cool guy.
Lion Jay (Lion Jay) is a cool guy.
Lion Jay, my favorite.
Lion Jay
Lion Jay…
Team Lion Heart’s fans are more enthusiastic than we imagined.
Lion Jay, the ultimate cool guy.
Lion Jay, my favorite.
Team Lion Heart is now acting like they have home-court advantage.
Home advantage
With the cheers of the fans in the audience
They played with the same ease as if they were playing on their own training ground.
Meanwhile, fans also sometimes do things that disrupt our team’s morale.
The match is about to begin.
The entire venue was filled with cheers for Team Lion Heart.
Team Lion Heart will win!
The game began, and Team Lion Heart gained possession of the ball first.
Do you think you can stop me all by yourself?
Team Lion Heart, keep it up!
The opportunity has arrived
My body won’t obey me.
Oh no, I was definitely influenced by the audience.
Shi Laina easily defeated Tibbie.
Yes, just like that, drive and lay up.
Shi Laina’s dribbling breakthrough suggests the ball is almost certainly in the net.
Quickly pass the ball to Lion Jay for a stylish alley-oop!
What
Two to zero, that was so cool!
Team Lion Heart scored the first goal.
Sorry, I lost focus while defending.
It’s okay, we can get it back.
Sparky
Defense
Watch me score this goal!
Jump - Can’t jump
The hot pot Lion Jay treated Sparky to was so fragrant and spicy!
Under the fierce attack of Team Lion Heart
Team Defenders were completely overwhelmed and unable to fight back.
The score has quickly reached 10-0.
The children underperformed
Blazey, hurry up and call a halt, think of a solution!
Blazey, say something, Blazey!
Don’t worry.
Now they can only rely on themselves to overcome the influence of the audience.
Play to the expected level
That’s how we’ll have a chance to win.
Do these goats even know how to play ball?
It’s practically adults bullying children!
I need to find an opportunity to score.
Don’t even think about succeeding.
Sparky drew a foul from Lion Jay and was awarded free throws.
Will he be able to score the team’s first goal?
It doesn’t matter if you commit a foul, as long as you look cool?
Great, Sparky! Our chance to score has arrived!
This can’t possibly be a fake fall.
Diving
I didn’t fake a fall!
Watch me score the first point of the game!
Not entering
What
Hugh
Referee, I want to file a complaint.
They are interfering with me.
The referee indicated that the complaint was invalid and the game continued.
It’s okay, we still have one ball.
Keep it up!
I must score this time.
Not entering
Catch
Unexpectedly, Team Lion Heart called a timeout.
Interrupted his fast break
Why did you call a timeout when you had such a good scoring opportunity?
Your hair was messed up, you need to redo it.
But if we had launched a quick attack just now, that ball would have been a sure thing.
You are an idol
Every goal must showcase your most handsome moment.
Such a big deal as having messy hair
It wouldn’t be good if the fans found out.
Children, don’t be nervous.
Next, let Blazey explain the tactics to you.
I have nothing to say.
Facing the psychological pressure exerted by the audience
You’ll have to overcome this on your own.
The game continues
easy
Wait, look at the camera.
Lion Jay is so handsome!
We can’t let the point difference widen any further.
Go Lion Jay! Go Lion Jay!
No, you can’t stop him at all.
He became so timid and hesitant after just a few words from someone.
This is nothing like me!
let me
Sparky.
OMG
Lion Jay got blocked!
Well done! You truly deserve to be my disciple.
Well done
foul
He knocked Lion Jay to the ground, but that wasn’t a foul.
Yes, that was a foul.
This isn’t even a foul anymore! A foul! A foul!
It’s already 10-0, what’s the point of continuing?
Go back
Go back, go back quickly!
S
You are the ones
If you don’t like it, go back.
Quickly launch a counterattack!
Quickly return to defense
Whenever
We should all enjoy the game.
Focus on the game
Do our best in everything we can.
Such are us
That is
strongest
That’s right
Wow, so fast!
And me
We were already being questioned by everyone, weren’t we?
ridiculed
Limiting our space
But they’ve still managed to keep playing until now?
The rest is up to you, Sparky.
You can do it.
bring it on
Lion Jay
This kid’s pretty good at backfights.
Keep him away
Lion Jay
I’m going to use this ball
Let everyone open their eyes wide and see clearly
This is
Our basketball
Team Defenders scored!
The real competition has only just begun.