Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories
“Basketball with all your might”
In the previous episode,
In the match between Team Defenders and Team Lion Heart
The goats faced their first…
The incredibly popular Team Lion Heart
Influenced by their fans, they fought with restraint.
Fortunately, Sparky, with its latest training results
Breaking the deadlock
The first half has ended in the blink of an eye.
Team Defenders tied the score at 30 points.
The competition is getting more and more exciting.
Team Defenders, go for it!
Lion Jay, the epitome of handsome men.
Lion Jay, I love you forever!
Let’s continue fighting as we just did.
good…
The second half has begun.
We can’t let them score anymore.
Listen carefully
It’s time to use our rehearsed defensive moves.
What kind of move is that? It’s the first time I’ve ever seen it.
They’re so handsome, I’m dizzy!
This move is very powerful.
Want to surpass me? Not so easy.
Watch how I surpass you!
Putting your hands in your pockets, or one hand in your pocket, looks cool.
Remember to always look handsome.
Lion Jay
Pay attention to your appearance, remember to put your hands in your pockets.
Didn’t you say you would take every game seriously?
Team Defenders’ offense was very aggressive.
In the blink of an eye, the score has widened considerably.
Lion Jay, the epitome of handsome men.
Lion Jay, I love you forever!
Pay attention to your appearance; you must look handsome.
Lion Jay
Will Team Lion Heart simply hand over victory?
What am I doing?
It turns out it’s just pretty but not practical.
You are not qualified to play in the game.
Lion Jay, we like you very much.
Can we get your autographs and take photos with you?
Sorry, I lost the game, I’m a little…
Even if you lose, we still like you very much.
Because you are handsome
Come on, look at the camera.
I got Lion Jay’s autographed photo.
You see, even though we lost the game…
But your fans still love you.
The problem is I want to win
It’s impossible to win every game.
But I can assure you
In terms of popularity, you absolutely reign supreme.
Actually, I…
It’s okay, as long as you look good, come on!
Strike another cool pose
Is this really the basketball I’ve been pursuing?
Catch
Remember to put one hand in your pocket
The score is now 28 points behind.
It seems the overall situation is truly settled.
You didn’t intend to
Will the game continue like this for the whole time?
Didn’t you tell me before that I should enjoy the game?
That’s great, Blazey!
Is this what you mean by a 99% win rate?
Remember to pay attention to the camera.
Pay attention to your image
Let’s get a cool dunk!
A cool dunk
Lion Jay
team leader…
This look
I really want to have a serious fight with him.
Captain Sparky
Lion Jay
They fell down together.
That last shot was really amazing.
Enjoy the game and focus on the game
You are at your most powerful in this state.
I…
Game paused
Go and take a rest.
How are you? Are you hurt?
Should we call in a medical team?
Team Lion Heart requests a pause
Come on, stick it on.
This piece…
This is a medical adhesive bandage sponsored by an advertiser.
I never thought I’d have the chance to use it.
The captain was injured in the collision; applying medicated bandages didn’t help.
I don’t care whether it works or not.
Remember to show the medical tape more often later.
Is this really the basketball I’ve been pursuing?
Enjoy the game and focus on the game
You are at your most powerful in this state.
Please let me play a real match.
Aren’t you already in the competition?
What I want is a competition where I can showcase my abilities.
This is not the kind of performance.
Our score has fallen far behind.
It’s okay, your fans won’t blame you for losing.
Look
Lion Jay, the epitome of handsome men.
They’re too busy caring about you to even think about it.
But if you change your style
You will lose all your fans
Then you will no longer be a basketball star.
I don’t want to go on like this anymore.
I want to play well as a player.
Instead of being an idol
What? You…you dare to disobey me?
Who kept you on the team?
Who nurtured you to become a basketball star?
What kind of attitude is this? Manager
Please let Lion Jay play a serious match.
We also really want to play basketball seriously with Lion Jay.
Please
you
Everyone played very well.
We’ve got this in the bag.
sorry
Thank you for your continued guidance.
but…
I want to try to forge my own path.
team leader…
Do you dare take another step?
He will no longer be a player for Team Lion Heart.
You, you better think this through.
Keep up the good work, everyone…
sharp
Weslie breaks through Team Lion Heart’s defense.
It looks like Team Defenders can score again.
Up, Weslie
You better think this through.
Lion Jay
Lion Jay, looking at the camera.
Lion Jay, you’re so cool!
Is this all you’re looking for?
If this continues, you will lose.
But it’s okay, no one will blame you.
This is not what I wanted.
People like the way you play.
You are on the biggest stage
Just show your most handsome side.
no
Passing
yes
Hurry back to defend
team leader
Don’t worry, leave it to me.
Give me…
We’ll see.
This is the real me.
This…this is Lion Jay?
how so?
What happened to Lion Jay?
That’s too rude.
what happen?
It’s all over. All my years of hard work have been for nothing.
That’s impossible, don’t do that, calm down.
He has changed.
Could it be that Team Lion Heart also…?
Let’s score another goal together!
Listen up, Team Lion Heart, from now on…
We need to catch up, point by point.
We have only one goal.
It means going all out.
Win this game
team leader
good…
too…
This is so inspiring!
Lion Jay after the pause
It’s like a complete transformation.
Team Lion Heart is about to launch a fierce counterattack.
Lion Jay
Finally, the real you has appeared!
I will defeat the strongest you.
We’re so far ahead, we should be fine, right?
uncertain
That 1% chance of losing appeared.
(to be continued)