In the previous episode, we discussed how Team Defenders overtook Team Lion Heart by a large margin.
Team Lion Heart’s problems are gradually becoming apparent.
Captain Lion Jay felt a huge crisis and was constantly struggling with his inner thoughts.
When Lion Jay sheds his idol image
Its strength is breathtaking
How will the Goat Team hold onto their score?
Here
Can’t see the ball
Receive
good
Team Defenders requests a pause.
You probably already know this.
Lion Jay’s awakening is the one percent that makes you lose.
Pay attention now.
Coach, I just want to beat Team Lion Heart when they’re giving it their all.
Giving your all is the greatest respect you can show to your opponent.
You are not wrong.
Okay, now I’ll talk about the last three tactics.
It’s all about defense, defense, defense.
Just hold onto our current lead.
I understand, coach.
Alright, the game is now restarting.
Don’t think about the past.
Weslie is preparing to break through Team Lion Heart’s defense.
Will his composure allow him to score a goal?
Lion Jay is Lion Jay
A suffocating sense of oppression
Can Weslie get past his defense?
The ball was intercepted.
As expected of Lion Jay, what amazing reflexes!
Come back to defend
This way
Bad
The ball hasn’t even hit the ground yet.
Lion Jay
Lion Jay, are you alright?
It’s okay, thank you for your support.
Lion Jay is really going all out!
Go, hurry back to defense.
Actually, this is Lion Jay
Next, we’ll use man-to-man marking tactic 52.
Remember, you must defend well.
He’s handsome too!
Lion Jay has given us so much all this time.
But we dislike him because of his change.
Winning or losing doesn’t matter, as long as you look good.
Who made you stay in the team?
Who trained you to become a basketball star?
Such are us
Too selfish
Yes, we should cheer for the real Lion Jay!
Come on, let’s cheer for Lion Jay once again!
Lion Jay… The ultimate cool guy
Lion Jay, the ultimate cool guy, Lion Jay, my favorite.
Am I being too selfish?
The score is getting closer and closer.
careful
This is Lion Jay giving it his all.
Sorry, I’ll go back with you.
Don’t associate with these weak people anymore.
Being photographed by a reporter would damage your reputation.
It’s so good that he can be himself again.
Therefore, being a good coach on the field is not essential.
The fundamentals are the most important.
I want to prove myself
My basketball
Not just fancy moves
Me too
I will not lose to you.
Oh no!
Tibbie
All-out defense
The goats finally scored again, breaking Team Lion Heart’s scoring run.
nice shot
brats
If you’re going to play seriously, you shouldn’t lose.
Don’t embarrass me.
Go
yes
Go enjoy basketball!
Keep it up!
What’s going on?
The match between Team Lion Heart and Team Defenders was so intense!
The score is so close!
Are those goats really that good?
Team Goat is not so easy to deal with.
We made a promise.
See you in the finals
Only 10 seconds left
Team Lion Heart has come back from a large deficit to be only one point behind.
This match was so intense it almost took my heart out!
Paddi
Who will ultimately emerge victorious?
Team Defenders’ crucial shot was blocked by Team Lion Heart.
Lion Jay is Lion Jay
Lion Jay has received the ball and is attacking Team Defenders.
Return to defense, quickly return to defense.
Team Defenders quickly rotated back to defend.
Can Lion Jay withstand it?
This might be Team Lion Heart’s last offensive play.
time
Lion Jay
Outstanding Teacher
Score this goal, Lion Jay!
Lion Jay
Leave it to me.
This was an opportunity I had finally managed to seize.
No one can stop me now.
Then what reason do I have?
Stop here
What
My dream is to become…
Fighting for victory
basketball player