In the previous episode, we discussed how Lion Jay launched a powerful attack.
The fans were infected by Lion Jay’s enthusiasm
The agent’s attitude also changed.
This greatly encouraged Lion Jay and others.
The two teams were locked in a high-octane battle, with only one goal separating them.
With one second remaining, Lion Jay successfully scored a layup.
Lion Jay, well done!
What a pity, it was so close!
Did we lose?
Is this the end?
Has our basketball dream come to an end?
Goals are disallowed if time expires.
Lion Jay made his final shot after time had expired.
Therefore, this ball doesn’t count.
The winning team in this match is
Team Defenders
We won…
Win
win
Thank you for finishing this match for me.
I will leave the team.
team leader
To quit
I wonder how Lion Jay is doing.
It should be me.
All along
I forced you to do things you didn’t like just for my own selfish desires.
They believe this is the best approach.
Until I saw how seriously you guys were playing on the court…
I just realized
I’m such a terrible agent; all I see is profit.
I’m sorry to you all.
No, everything we have now
It’s all because of you.
Without your kindness back then, we wouldn’t be where we are today.
This team can’t do without you.
Please stay.
Can I, in this state, really still lead you?
Of course, no one but you can do it.
Please continue to guide me in the future.
Congratulations Sparky!
Thank you, Lion Jay. I look forward to our next all-out match.
I won’t lose again next time.
The match between Team Wolves and Team Wild Boar is about to begin.
Let’s wait and see.
Today is Wolffy’s debut, let’s cheer him on!
Look, they’re out!
D
marvelous
I’ve been practicing day and night for so long
It’s all for today.
Wolffy, keep it up!
Why are they here?
I’ve finally become a substitute player! Maybe I’ll even get a chance to play!
Little goats, let me show you the results of my hard work!
Please pay close attention to the movements and characteristics of each player on Team Wolves.
yes
She is Yu Tailang, point guard
She was agile
Skilled at breaking through and passing
come on
He is Ning Tailang, shooting guard
He is good at long-range shooting.
This is Zhuang Tailang, center.
Very tall
The power is quite astonishing
This is Chang Tailang, power forward.
He has an excellent jumping ability.
Their rebounding ability is also terrifying.
CV
Victor
He is the core of Team Wolves.
small forward, Victor
His speed, jumping ability, shooting, strength, and skill
All of them are top-notch.
Victor
come on
When will I be able to play?
Number 99, quick
Towels, water
yes
You can play the rest for me.
I
They actually let number 99 play.
So why aren’t you getting ready? Do you even want to fight anymore?
I’ll go right away.
This is my first game in my basketball career.
Wolffy, keep it up!
come on
Did you notice? Victor has been looking in our direction the whole time.
Do you also think so?
Want to know why?
It’s you.
Long time no see, Master
Master and apprentice
You heard right, Blazey was once Victor’s mentor.
Actually, Blazey led the Goat team to the finals of the Basketball Game back then.
At that time, Victor was still his apprentice.
hateful
For some unknown reason, they severed their master-disciple relationship from that day on.
They went their separate ways.
Blazey was also unable to participate due to injury, and the result was predictable.
The Goat Clan suffered a crushing defeat, and that’s when the Goat Clan basketball team began…
U has become so decadent
Oh, I see.
By the way, village chief
How do you know everything?
As a professional basketball manager
Of course, we need to check everyone’s information thoroughly.
I will not lose again
Yeah
Want to have another one-on-one fight?
Forget it.
Yes, you’re not the number 42 you were back then anymore.
I will show you with my actions that my basketball skills are the best.
That’s not necessarily true.
You’re still the same.
Wolffy
Team Wolves are absolutely amazing!
They were already leading by 40 points, but the Wild Boars still hadn’t given up.
Team Wolves played exceptionally well in the second half.
What impressed me the most was indeed…
Wolffy #99
Although he only scored 6 points
However, he contributed impressive statistics of 9 rebounds and 8 steals.
Well done, that’s quite an achievement for a debut!
Wolffy, you’re really amazing!
I never expected Wolffy to be so amazing.
That’s right, we can’t let our guard down.
Are you ready for dinner?
Congratulations to Team Wolves for winning this match!