Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Bunny Crisis
In the previous episode, Lion Jay erupted at the last moment.
However, the Goat Team narrowly won by a single point.
Later, the goats went to see Wolffy’s debut, only to discover an astonishing truth.
In Team Wolves, the highly skilled Victor was actually Blazey’s apprentice.
I can’t go on anymore, I need to rest.
If training continues like this
I collapsed from exhaustion before I could even achieve my goal of winning the championship.
I want to wish for lots and lots of cake!
All you think about is eating, so what are we going to do next?
Next, go to the warehouse outside the village and get some food.
The village’s food supplies are almost exhausted.
good
What about them?
They went to the warehouse to get food.
I’ll go find them right away.
It seems Paddi has grown up too.
I want to eat too.
There haven’t been any fruits on the trees lately.
Keep moving
We’ll help.
Thank you
What’s inside such a big package?
This is the trash we collect. Then we hand it over to them for sorting.
Your environmental awareness is really good.
Let’s go, we still need to get some canned food.
can
We’re running out of food; we need to go to the warehouse to get more.
Let us help you move.
You helped me just now, we should help each other!
Thank you
This is enough for us to eat for a long time.
They walked so fast; I should have eaten something first before setting off.
Eat
Thank you, Auntie
It’s a steamed bun.
Aren’t you Paddi, the sharpshooter from Team Defenders?
You know me, you are…
I’m Bucky, and I’m your fan.
You’re amazing at basketball!
It’s not that powerful.
Why did that auntie give you bread?
They said I’m cute.
Yes, so cute!
chubby cheeks
A pale yellow bib, and fluffy hair.
so cute
Here, Auntie will give you some candy.
Thanks
Let’s eat!
By the way, idol, what wish do you want to make after Team Defenders wins?
I want an endless supply of cake to share with my friends.
I also want to have an endless supply of food.
We are truly kindred spirits.
Superman
What
Zero snacks
I’m leaving now.
Give me back my snacks
Why did you take all the food?
Sorry, I’m so hungry.
I haven’t had a proper meal in days.
Be careful, there’s a trap up there.
trap
There really is a trap.
Be careful, there may be traps ahead of the officials.
You noticed that? That’s amazing!
These traps have been played for thousands of episodes.
Who set this trap? It’s so basic! Can’t it be a little more challenging?
Be careful, get out of the way!
Are you all alright?
Oh no, they stole the canned food!
It turns out those rabbits were thieves.
We can still walk here; we must get the canned goods back.
Those goats are so easy to fool.
stop
How can you run so fast?
So you were planning to steal our canned goods from the beginning.
No…it wasn’t what you told us.
How would we know?
Let’s go, we still need to get some canned food.
We’re running out of food; we need to go to the warehouse to get more.
We only started making arrangements after we heard you were going to get canned food.
Let us help you move.
So those childish traps were set by you.
So what if it is?
No, you’re the childish one.
Give us back our canned goods.
Who said this belongs to you? 1. Do you have any evidence?
Of course, it has a goat symbol on it.
Now the canned food is ours.
It’s amazing how accurate the message is, even without looking at it!
Because we have good hearing!
Why explain this to the enemy?
Then I’ll just have to interfere with you guys.
Naïve, the noise from the stadium is even louder.
Does that mean we can’t send it?
Each person is responsible for one.
good
well done
There’s one bag left.
what to do
Over here… I’m undefended.
good
Catch
Oh no! Hurry and chase after them!
Give us back the canned food!
They’re here again. Hurry up and get to the other side of the river.
The river is so deep! How come they can jump so far?
Gone
These annoying thieves
Let’s take the rest of the canned food back first.
It’s okay, you can have all this food.
But you must not steal anymore.
Thank you for forgiving me
By the way, why did I come out today?
I remember now, I need to go to the warehouse to get the canned goods.
can
Can we still play together?
certainly
Brother, what are you doing here?
I should be asking you guys. What are you all doing here?
We just managed to get some canned food from a bunch of silly goats.
Goat (canned lamb)
Could it be…?
What’s wrong, brother?
Come here for a moment.
To be continued…