In the previous episode,
The goats went to the barn for canned food because they were short of fodder for training.
But four seemingly harmless rabbits stole the can of food.
On the other hand, Paddi and Bucky become like-minded friends.
Who knew he was the leader of those four rabbits?
Yesterday was so thrilling! I never expected to run into people trying to steal canned food.
It’s good that everyone is alright. Be more careful in the future.
yes…
Paddi, start practicing your three-point shot today!
Three-pointers - I’m not good at them.
That’s why you need to practice!
The shot just wouldn’t go in.
Paddi, are you alright?
Because I was hungry and had no energy.
I knew it
I can’t take it anymore, I’m going to find something to eat.
It feels so good, it would be even better with a breeze.
Cute
Paddi
Where are you going? You seem to be in a hurry.
Come on, I’ll take you to see some fun things.
What is this doing?
There is a box of milk here.
A magical transformation
It’s just magic.
Anyone else want to give it a try?
I
Can this be changed?
When did he bring the banana?
certainly
A magical transformation
The master is amazing!
Could it be fake?
It’s true.
It’s true… it must be hidden under the table.
Let me see what tricks you’re playing.
There is nothing
Little friend, what are you still doubting?
Do you think this is just a simple magic trick?
Is it really just magic?
A magical transformation
The master is too strong.
That’s simply… amazing!
A magical transformation
I actually conjured up a Sparky!
Paddi, stop playing around and come move the canned goods!
What canned food?
Did you go get some canned food again?
We brought all the canned goods back from another warehouse.
To prevent Fang Yi from being stolen again
Let’s go eat one first.
All you do is eat
Okay, I’ve locked it.
Everyone go back and rest for a bit, remember to come to training this afternoon!
good…
There are no fruits at all.
My stomach is so bloated!
Are you hungry? Have something to eat.
Bucky, thank you
I wanted to find more food, but I couldn’t find any anywhere.
A magical transformation
I wish I could double the food!
You don’t need to know how; just find a master to perform the transformation.
How could I not have thought of that?
This is a great idea; this way we can have plenty of food.
Master, can you help me increase the amount of food?
Of course, bring it over.
It was a whole warehouse of food.
The whole warehouse, that’s… a bit difficult.
Master, please help him!
Please, Celestial Master
It still doesn’t work; it’s such a waste of energy.
Master, Master, please!
I can give you a back massage all day long.
I can help too.
Okay, okay, stop hitting me.
Master, did you agree?
I’ll give it a try.
Very good
Can I borrow your key for a month?
How is the master? Do you have confidence?
I’m confident, but there are a lot of them.
Give me two hours
However, I need absolute quiet.
No one is allowed to come near here.
Is it possible to make absolutely no noise?
Okay, I’ll definitely do it.
No one is allowed to come near here, and there must be no sound.
Don’t shout yet.
Paddi
Paddi, what are you doing? Go train!
Oh no, we can’t let them disturb the master.
Nothing much, let’s go train.
I’ll come again later.
I have a surprise for you.
Let’s begin training.
So positive today
Paddi
Soon we’ll have lots of delicious food!
Paddi, are you alright?
All this food is ours.
Time’s up
What happened to the warehouse, Paddi?
Stop asking so many questions, just come with me.
I said I’d give you a surprise.
What’s all this mystery about?
Stop talking and go inside.
Impressive, right?
Okay, okay, you’re welcome. Eat whatever you like.
Eat, what are you eating?
The food is gone.
There’s nothing left.
What happened?
We should be asking you that!
I’ve found a master today to help us increase our food supply.
It’s the master’s hat. Has something happened to the master?
What kind of master is he? He’s definitely a fraud.
There are footprints
Look!
Bucky
The rabbit that stole our canned food
Yes, it’s us.
We meet again.
Give us back the canned food.
Come and get it!
So… all those so-called masters are frauds.
You’re all in cahoots.
yes
Bucky, I trust you so much.
Aren’t we good friends?
How is that possible?
So you lied to me from the beginning.
You’re wrong. Dao meeting you was just a coincidence.
At that time, it suddenly occurred to me that maybe I could take advantage of you.
As it turns out, fate was on my side, and you were indeed able to take advantage of it.
Thanks to you, I didn’t know your village had so many canned goods.
So my companions and I devised a magic trick.
I didn’t expect you to be so easy to fool.
Not only are they bad at basketball, but their intelligence is also lacking.
Goodbye, little goats.
Come back here
I have none of my canned food.
They’re so awful! What am I going to eat tonight?
What time is it? Still only thinking about eating?
Everyone’s canned food is gone.
It’s because you’re greedy
Okay, okay, stop arguing.
Let’s go tell Mr. Slowy quickly and see what we should do.
No way! Mr. Slowy will definitely give me a piece of his mind if he finds out.
So what do you suggest we do?
Okay, you guys go back to training first.
I will definitely bring all the canned food back.
Paddi
What should we do?
Let’s do as Paddi says.