Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories
“Underground War”
In the previous episode, we talked about
Paddi wants to get more canned goods for the team.
Who knew I’d win Bucky
A trap set by a mysterious magician
They tricked us out of all the Team Defenders canned goods.
Found so much food again today!
I think that should be enough for everyone to eat for a while.
Wait, Bucky, I’ve finally found you!
Hello, stranger goat
Goodbye, little stranger (goat)
Stop playing dumb, you thief!
Give me back my food right now!
It is clearly a
Cute and kind little bunny
How could I possibly steal your food?
Never make statements without evidence.
Darn it, you think you can get away with pretending to be stupid?
Give me back my food right now.
This bag of food doesn’t belong to you.
I tricked him in another place.
And if you have to blame someone, blame your own greed.
I will absolutely not apologize.
You won’t get your food back. Goodbye.
Give me back my food.
Weslie to
Tibbie to
Jonie arrived
Sparky to
Paddi…
He’s been slacking off again; how many days has he missed training?
Don’t tell Mr. Slowy or the others.
If they find out, they’ll definitely scold me.
I’ll ask Bucky to get the food back.
You guys go back to training first.
Remember to keep this from them for me.
Paddi…
Everyone, it has been announced.
Our opponent in the next match.
It’s Team Jumper
It was actually them?
Let go, I won’t let go
Let go or not
Let go, you’re such a nuisance.
Give me back my food and I’ll let go.
This food isn’t yours; it belongs to me.
Team Defenders, it’s them?
This is a good opportunity to test Team Defenders’ capabilities.
That’s enough.
You’ve come to your senses? Then give me back my food.
Listen carefully, tonight at 7 PM.
In the venue of the street fighting arena
Play a three-on-three match
A three-on-three match? Yes.
If you win, I’ll give the food back to you.
If you lose, don’t bother me anymore.
The food itself is mine
What reason do you have to give it back to me only if I win?
I’ve already given you a chance, if you still won’t take it, then forget it.
What’s wrong? Don’t you have the guts?
If you don’t have the guts, then forget it.
How could I not have the courage?
Okay, see you at the stadium tonight at 7 PM.
It’s a deal.
With Paddi on the team, we’re sure to win.
I wonder how Paddi is doing now?
Tibbie, Sparky
You’re finally back? Let’s go to training together.
Let’s not talk about that now, come with me.
Where do you want us to go with you?
Go play a 3-on-3 match with those rabbits.
Let’s talk as we go.
There are more matches to watch.
I came over right after I finished showering.
Which team will play against which team today?
Today’s date is Rabbit versus Goat.
Go for it…
For food, we must fight them to the death.
Is it inappropriate for us to compete privately?
If something goes wrong, what do you suggest we do?
It’s fine
Let’s get started!
here we go…
With me here, I won’t let you score.
Very high
They scored easily.
I won’t let you score so easily this time.
Then you need to keep going!
Stop!
That’s a foul.
resorting to underhanded tactics when you can’t win a fight? How despicable!
Is this how you play ball?
Is it playing dirty or fighting?
If you can’t play ball, go back.
Again
Don’t be so arrogant
Paddi
If this is all you’ve got…
In an official match, just concede defeat.
We will absolutely not admit defeat.
What to do now? Sparky
Why don’t we try the single-block technique the coach had us practice?
but…
I’m too tired, I’m not practicing anymore.
Paddi, we haven’t finished practicing yet.
You guys practice, I’ll come over when I’ve rested enough.
I can do it… Come on!
Don’t let him shoot.
Good opportunity, Paddi passes the ball.
Tibbie drove in single gear to the front.
You should have passed the ball to her, sorry.
Is what you just did considered a single-block tactic?
Let me help you with single gear this time, okay?
I won’t let you get past me.
Paddi
Tibbie…
It hurts so much!
How is your wrist?
I twisted my ankle when I fell just now.
American…Tibbie
You should take her to the emergency room right away.
It’s okay, Tibbie.
I’ll take you back to Goats’ Village for emergency treatment.
That’s really terrible, getting injured by your own teammate.
It seems they are also unable to participate.
Then that match
To make such a basic mistake
It’s obvious that there’s a lack of regular training.
Let’s go…
You’re a real failure.
I really feel sorry for your teammates.
You’re a cancer on the basketball team.
I said it’s all your fault
It’s all your fault for stealing our food.
Don’t make excuses if you played poorly.
I’m fine, don’t worry.
Fortunately, this injury wasn’t too serious.
Paddi
You…
I always slack off during training.
They even dared to compete in private.
What if Tibbie gets seriously injured this time?
Mr. Slowy, I…
I’m sorry, I’m sorry…
Also, why do you…
Would they secretly compete with rabbits?
sorry
Actually, the thing is this:
So that’s how it is?
I’m sorry, Mr. Slowy
It’s my fault that everyone has no food.
The food is gone
Let our goat figure it out.
Your most important task is to practice hard.
Did you know? We know…
Paddi
Do you know why Tibbie got injured?
It’s because you’re too greedy.
Master, could you please conjure up more food for me?
And also, you acted on your own initiative.
No animals are allowed near this place.
I made a mistake and I’m afraid to take responsibility.
alright…
He has realized his mistake.
Forget it, stop scolding him.
Blazey
Slacking off in training again, not taking it seriously.
That’s why Tibbie got injured.
Do you know about injuries?
What does it mean for an athlete?
How serious is it?
The team doesn’t need a goat like you, you can leave.
coach…
Coach, I’m fine.
I was too careless at the time, and I also bear some responsibility.
Please don’t drive Paddi away.
Coach, please don’t send him away.
Coach, Paddi didn’t actually mean to do that.
Give him another chance, coach.
Paddi
Calm down and take a deep breath
Paddi…
Look, your brother is back.
elder brother…
Sorry for getting back so late.
You must be very hungry.
We are not hungry, not hungry
She said she wasn’t hungry.
It’s canned food… Thank you, brother…
Very good…
(to be continued)