In the previous episode, Bucky wagered canned food.
Paddi was invited to a 3-on-3 underground streetball tournament.
Paddi challenges Sparky and Tibbie
However, due to a lack of training, Tibbie suffered an injury.
After learning the whole story
Blazey angrily rebuked Paddi and kicked him out of the team.
These two are for you and Tibbie.
Coach, Mr. Slowy, aren’t you going to eat?
We’ll eat in a bit.
By the way, haven’t you found Paddi yet?
Paddi
Not found
Okay everyone, let’s finish eating quickly and get to training!
good
The food I borrowed from all over the place isn’t enough to last two days.
All the canned goods nearby were sold out.
Let’s think of another way.
Faster, even faster!
Your steps must be steady and not swaying.
When going for a layup, your arm should be straight.
The force applied must be gentle.
Straightening is more important
Softness is more important
Listen to me
I think comfort is the most important thing.
What do you know? Listen to me.
Stop giving me this nonsense.
What kind of nonsensical guidance is this? It’s clearly your lack of skill!
We’re helping you improve your skills.
Keeping your mouths shut is a huge help.
You dare throw me?
You guys are just slacking off all day; you might as well quit the team and go home.
This is disturbing my training all day long.
Don’t pretend in front of me. Weren’t you just as lazy back then?
X
Are you guys planning to pack up and leave the team?
country
Everyone hurry up and go out to move the canned goods.
Is dinner served so soon?
If you want to eat it so badly, then you should eat it all!
You can’t stop eating until you finish!
Why did you buy so many canned goods? We haven’t finished the ones we had before.
I received the message
Recent incidents of food theft have led to food shortages for many people.
As a qualified team manager
Just in case, I’ve bought all the canned goods in the neighborhood.
Just in case it’s fake
Taking advantage of the situation to reduce the number of competitors is the real solution.
What are you talking about?
Our manager is really good-looking.
So thoughtful!
Enough talk, let’s get started.
Those food-starved troops might try to take advantage of us.
You all need to keep a close eye on things, don’t let your guard down.
By the way, I recently heard that the goats are also short of food.
It seems so
Won’t you be too hungry to play ball?
Then withdraw from the competition
That way we can win the championship more easily and achieve our wish.
I wonder where Paddi is now?
He must be very sad right now.
Little goats, look what King Wolffy has brought you!
This is
I heard you were short of food, so I brought you some canned fruit.
Wolffy, that’s awesome! You’ve solved a huge problem for us!
Wolffy, where did you get so many canned fruits?
Well, you don’t need to worry about that.
I’m really looking forward to playing against your team!
You guys continue training, I’m leaving now.
Thank you, Wolffy
Paddi
We have plenty of food now.
Please come back soon.
Don’t underestimate me just because I’m a mother goat; I won’t go hungry because of me.
King Wolffy is truly unrestrained and bold, not to mention he’s a basketball star.
So handsome!
When will you be able to do something meaningful like I do?
Instead of lazing around here every day
Waste of “wolf life”
Have you ever seen anyone lounging around and slacking off under the scorching sun?
You’re so capable, hurry up and help us find the thief!
We don’t need to waste our “wolf life” here.
Wolffy
You’re back.
Why are you sighing at such a young age?
You’ve squandered all the good weather with your sighs.
Dama, what are you doing here?
Come air out your quilts!
Now things are much better, it’s time to collect them.
sorry
Why are you so listless?
I…I did something wrong.
I caused everyone’s food to be stolen.
return…
It also injured Tibbie.
I’m so useless.
How can someone so young say they’re useless?
But it was indeed because I was greedy.
Because I was lazy, I dragged everyone down.
And… I can’t help at all.
Now that you know where you went wrong, just go and correct it.
Instead of running away
But I’m too ashamed to face everyone.
True friends don’t need to talk about being embarrassed.
Haven’t you always supported each other?
They are not only your friends, but also your family.
Keep going, one more time!
Eat more, you’ll have more energy to train after you eat.
You can have mine too.
Everyone makes mistakes sometimes.
The important thing is how you correct yourself afterwards.
Paddi
You need to recognize your own shortcomings.
Then try your best to make up for it.
One day you will become a player capable of shouldering heavy responsibilities.
Okay, you should go back now.
Everyone must be very worried about you.
Thank you, Dama
I’m looking forward to seeing you in the finals!
It’s a deal.
Keep it up, young sheep (goat)!
Only the eight of you knew there was canned food, so the thief must be among you.
All seven of them said they didn’t take it, that thief…
It’s you!
What should I do if I admit I’ll be fired?
If you still refuse to admit it, I’ll fire you all.
Those who know what’s good for them will obediently step forward.
Xiangze, don’t blame me for being impolite.
If this continues, it will drag everyone down with it.
I can’t drag everyone down with me.
Wolffy is really amazing.
I take responsibility for my own actions
I did it.
Okay, it really is you guys.
I’m going to kick you all out of the team.
Just go
Even if you beg us, we will never come back.
That’s right
Get out of here
You…you all…
It wasn’t you who did it.
Why do you… admit it?
It doesn’t matter who did it.
Anyway, I’ve long since run out of time to stay in this hellish training camp.
I still think it’s more fun to make clay figurines at home.
We’re going to write a song about this training experience.
I’ve already thought of a song title.
It’s called “Until the End of Training Camp”
Absolutely hot
Didn’t you say you wanted to get that wish?
It’s too difficult, I don’t want it anymore.
You work much harder than us, you have a much better chance of winning.
From now on, we’ll cheer for you as spectators.
Take good care of yourself.
Gone
Thank you everyone.
No, this is something that could be solved by a wolf stepping forward.
Why do we all have to stand up?
I’ve made too many mistakes.
I can’t keep making mistakes.
I wonder how Paddi is doing now.
I hope he can pull himself together.
Paddi
You’re finally back!
It’s good to be back… It’s good to be back.
Coach, Mr. Slowy
I’m sorry to have worried you.
I’m so glad you’re okay.
Everyone, I’m sorry.
I was too willful before.
I don’t want to leave the team
I want to play basketball with everyone.
I will definitely correct my mistakes and strive to become a player who lives up to the coach’s expectations.
Please, coach, give me another chance.
Raise your head, Paddi
You have to promise me you won’t do it again.
yes
In other words…
Paddi can rejoin the team.
Very good
I will definitely work hard.