In the previous episode, we talked about
Wolffy helped the Goat through a difficult time and almost got kicked out of the team.
Paddi ran away because he felt guilty for doing something wrong.
Encouraged by Yang Dama, I mustered up the courage to face everyone.
I sincerely apologize to everyone.
How will Paddi perform in the match now that he’s back with the team?
They’re here.
So handsome!
I never thought we’d have a fan club!
We’re fairly well-known now, aren’t we?
Could you guys please move aside?
Cute
Another team’s fan
Go Bucky!
Hello everyone
Cute in real life, even cuter than in photos!
I’m melting.
Their cuteness is all an act.
Don’t let them fool you.
Rabbits are so cute, they couldn’t possibly be scammers.
It’s you who seem like swindlers.
you
Let’s ignore them and worry about Paddi instead.
The match is about to start, and he still hasn’t arrived.
Thank you everyone for your support. We’re definitely going to win this match.
Let’s go on the field first, and good luck in the match!
Paddi isn’t coming because she’s afraid of me?
No way, Paddi isn’t afraid of you.
So where is he now?
coward
What’s wrong
Haven’t seen me for a while, already missing me?
Paddi, you’ve arrived…
Seeing that I still had some time before the competition, I went for a run to warm up.
Is it a good act?
Actually, he went to slack off, right?
How many teammates are you trying to drag down this time?
You’re the one pretending.
You big liar, give me back my food!
Okay Paddi
Let’s not waste our breath on them, let’s go.
We’ll see.
Cute, keep it up!
What, they jumped so early?
So high!
In the high jump, you are no match for us.
Stop him quickly!
One ball in hand
You can’t beat me in terms of speed.
The ball that was so cute and hard to get
How can you bully such a cute bunny?
Our little goat is cute too!
Cute Bucky Goat
Can’t we just watch the game properly?
Stop him
Go, Sparky!
You are no match for us in the high jump.
Oh no!
Be careful, get back to defend quickly.
What about me?
You think you can stop me?
Oh no!
Goal
Team Jumper scored first.
brother
elder brother
Of course
Paddi
There is an opportunity
I messed up
Score
Goal!
Paddi, get back on defense!
You’re just relying on your teammates.
Is it worth being this happy?
Paddi
If you want to steal it, then come and steal it!
It’s clear you’ve been working harder than before.
He’s working even harder than before, dragging his teammates down.
nice shot
Paddi couldn’t stop Bucky
Blazey, you’d better switch players to defend against the cuteness!
I want to pause
Blazey finally listened to me this time!
You will now execute this tactic.
And Paddi
You did a great job.
Continue to defend against Bucky
yes
Did you understand all the tactical steps?
Understood
Sparky will be the primary scorer during this period.
The first step was for Weslie to break through.
Weslie faked a score and then passed the ball to Sparky.
Return defense
He needs to pass to the right.
Hurry up and score!
Aren’t you the main target?
How did you know that I was in charge?
It feels like my tactics have been exposed.
It should be the ear.
They eavesdropped on our plans.
They are so sensitive that they can determine their teammates’ locations simply by listening.
Now you know, the gap between us is huge.
I don’t take you seriously at all.
Team Defenders requests a pause.
Let’s hear what they’re planning this time.
First, start from the backboard and then enter the paint.
Then step back from the three-point line
Go get free popcorn
What
Free popcorn is available.
Wait, what is this even saying?
Captain, it seems we’ve been seen through.
Did you all remember that?
Forget it, even if we don’t follow their tactics…
We can still easily defeat them.
We’ll proceed according to the tactics in a moment.
Paddi, you can definitely do it!
They’re watching very closely.
As long as each of us keeps a close watch, that’s enough.
Even if you have excellent hearing, it will be difficult for the message to get through.
Captain, what do we do if we’re all blocked?
But they still have a loophole.
I was so close to getting the ball.
I can’t even touch the ball a few times
You’re always the one causing trouble for everyone.
Are you still not giving up?
What should we do?
Don’t rush
I believe Paddi can adapt to Bucky’s offensive style.
Paddi
Right now
What
Well done, Paddi
You got lucky this time; you won’t have another chance.
How did you become so difficult to deal with?
See how you defend
CCVC V opened an umbrella
It’s a really evenly matched contest.
elder brother.
I won’t let you score easily.
Paddi, I admit you have indeed made progress.
But you will still lose, and lose completely.
What happened?
V is going to shoot a three-pointer.
It flew up
What incredible jumping power!
Team Jumper can even dunk from the three-point line!
Referee, referee, please give the score.
Three points
nice shot
My brother is amazing!
Team Jumper’s score was miscalculated.
How can you score three points with a dunk?
No, only scores from the three-point line.
Theoretically, all three can be counted as three points.
Dunk from the three-point line
It seems Team Jumper has pulled out all the stops this time.