Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Each One’s Determination
In the previous episode, how he didn’t want Bucky to look down on him.
Paddi, contrary to its usual practice, went all out.
Under the pressure of the opponent’s consecutive goals
Even when ridiculed by Bucky
Paddi continues to defend Bucky tenaciously.
This forced Rabbit to unleash her signature three-point dunk.
That’s amazing, invincible!
How do I fight this?
It’s okay, as long as we score more goals than them.
Tibbie
Tibbie, watch out!
Oh no!
Quickly return to defense
I won’t let you dunk on a three-pointer.
What should we do? We’re blocked.
Yeah, right.
What? He can also dunk three-pointers?
No, he can’t reach the rim.
That’s amazing!
They can’t all score three points, right?
What should we do?
They will make mistakes sometimes.
As long as we can keep scoring
There will definitely be a chance to catch up.
The first half ended
You’ve really worked hard.
They’re trying so hard to catch up, but…
The score has widened.
If we can shut them both down, we’re guaranteed to win.
Don’t be so discouraged, it’s only 11 points away.
We only need six more goals to take the lead.
No way.
They kept hitting three-pointers, while we could only score two.
How do I chase after him?
Just don’t let them do it.
Then… why not let them take action?
We need to use full-court press and man-to-man tactics.
As long as you keep them close to the defense, they won’t have a good chance to jump.
Close defense
Close marking means sticking close to your opponent while defending.
Make it difficult for the opponent to pass and shoot.
So that’s how it is.
This will allow us to block their three-point dunks.
We can catch up if we score another goal.
but
They knew that Weslie and I were the main scorers.
They will definitely come to surround us.
Don’t worry… we also have a secret weapon.
secret weapon
Come on everyone, we can definitely score this time!
come on
Still not giving up?
Captain, the match has begun.
Sparky
Leave it to me.
Defense, defense
I won’t let you keep scoring.
They’re guarding me so closely, I can’t jump.
Really annoying
Sparky, are you alright?
Don’t worry, the coach’s methods really work!
Yes, they were all anxious just now.
But everyone, stay calm, we’re still 11 points behind.
good
Weslie
We won this game.
That was just now.
Sparky
Want to make a layup? Dream on.
Let’s get past us first.
You should all keep an eye on me.
I
Our secret weapon is Paddi’s three-point shot.
But what if I miss the shot?
It’s okay, if you miss, I’ll definitely get the rebound for you.
So just go ahead and cast your bets with confidence.
One day you will become a player who can shoulder heavy responsibilities.
Stop him quickly!
What, that is…
He can shoot three-pointers
No.
No…
All I need to do is shoot without hesitation.
I can do it.
X
Three-pointer
Well done!
Paddi, you’re so handsome!
That little goat scored!
Brother, keep it up!
Paddi, you made it!
It was just good luck.
Paddi, this is not luck.
This is your hard work!
I will keep working hard.
You’ll only have eight points left. You won’t be so lucky next time.
Team Jumper is now launching an attack.
I managed to snag it!
Return defense
Watch my three-point shot
Do you think you’re me?
I was just kidding.
You guys are amazing!
That little goat is pretty good, isn’t it?
pretty
Well done
Just one point away
come on
This can’t go on.
Team Jumper requests a pause.
Are we going to lose?
My brothers won’t lose.
How come they’re getting stronger and stronger as the fight goes on?
yes
And now they have an extra three-point shooter, making them harder to defend.
And they maintained close defense.
We didn’t even have a chance to dunk with a three-pointer.
Or, how about we use full-court press to mark them?
No. Full-court pressing is too physically demanding.
This makes it even harder for us to execute a three-point dunk.
Go, brother!
This isn’t the first time we’ve faced a formidable opponent.
For the sake of our people, we must resort to our last means.
Quickly return to defense
Paddi is yours now.
The ball passed back and forth between Team Defenders and eventually came into Paddi’s hands.
Paddi jumped to shoot, but the cute bunny didn’t give up.
He jumped up too, trying to block Paddi’s shot.
But it was too late.
What hit me?
Did he hit me with his ear?
That’s so wrong of me; I actually made such a basic mistake.
Paddi, you committed a traveling violation.
What
How could it be that I fouled?
He was the one who hit my face with his ear first.
I didn’t see them commit a foul, the game continues.
Paddi, are you alright?
Did he really hit you with his ear?
It’s true.
Why resort to such despicable means?
Don’t blame us, for the sake of our people.
We can stop at nothing
To be continued…