Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
A Fair and Honest Victory
Last time we talked about the 3-point dunk against Team Jumper
The goats were beaten so badly they couldn’t fight back.
Fortunately, Blazey’s tight defensive strategy and Paddi’s three-point shooting helped.
Team Defenders switched to the offensive
Team Jumper was overwhelmed and couldn’t breathe.
Decide to use the stealth foul tactic
The score quickly reached 40:41.
Whether Team Defenders can come back depends on this ball.
So troublesome, let’s get started.
Here it comes again…
What a pity!
Paddi accidentally dropped the ball.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
The referee called a foul.
He hit Paddi’s hand with his ear.
They didn’t do that, don’t slander me.
I didn’t see a foul, the game continues.
But… but he
Why do I have this urge to beat him up?
Referee, he committed a foul.
referee
Why… why don’t you punish them?
I will call the foul if I see them commit it.
If you keep pulling me like that, I’ll send you off the field.
Year
Come on, I’m not afraid of your despicable tactics.
Are you looking down on me? I’m not like them.
I would never condone their actions.
Really? Then it seems we’re the same kind.
bring it on
Let’s settle this once and for all!
It hurts so much!
Referee, he hit someone.
I didn’t even touch him.
He fell down on his own, why did they call a foul on me?
Calm down, Sparky
We can’t fall for their trick; there must be a way.
The solution is to go home early; blaming others for playing badly is pointless.
It just so happens that you’re fast, so your family can get back quickly too.
Who are you sending home to calm down, Weslie?
The referee called another technical foul on Weslie.
Team Defenders looks to be in trouble.
Team Jumper is going too far, always resorting to dirty tricks.
Think of a solution quickly!
How come those rabbits are even worse than us?
Yeah, no, that’s not right.
Are we bad?
More or less
That being said, this can’t go on forever.
Are you alright, Tibbie?
I’m fine, don’t let them affect you.
Why can’t we compete fairly and squarely?
Because we can’t lose.
That makes me want to shoot.
What, a feint?
Don’t even think about it.
We also have reasons why we cannot afford to lose.
Well done, Paddi
No way!
Paddi made the shot.
No matter what methods you use, I will defeat you with my strength.
Paddi, well done.
They caught up with the score.
What should the captain do?
The trick doesn’t seem to be working anymore.
It seems we have to be even more ruthless.
Remember to cover your tracks and don’t get spotted.
But Captain
Everything is for our family; this is the only way.
yes.
yes:
twenty two
Forget about being cute, I’m… I won’t let you score.
All you do is spout nonsense.
Do you really think you can stop me?
Team Jumper scores again.
Paddi
It seems Paddi was badly hurt in the collision.
Is Paddi alright?
I’m fine.
It’s good that you’re alright.
Do you really feel happy if you win by doing this?
Will your people be happy?
He clearly has such great jumping talent
Why resort to such despicable tactics in a competition?
Do you think your people would want to see you compete like this?
Basketball is not a tool for you to win championships.
You know absolutely nothing.
In my eyes, nothing else matters except for Yu Guan.
Yeah
Why won’t you give up? Aren’t you afraid of getting hurt?
We are not afraid.
This time it was Team Jumper who committed the foul.
Didn’t expect that, did you? The referee saw you commit a foul.
What
sorry
Take action
Paddi
Well done, Team Defenders have taken the lead!
That’s awesome! So great!
Why aren’t they committing fouls?
Why didn’t you stop him?
I.
Can’t we really compete with them fair and square?
What did you say
I believe we can win against them without resorting to such methods.
But we can’t allow any mistakes to happen in the game.
If we lose the game, the village we want to protect…
Go, brother!
twenty two
You will win! Fight with all your might for yourselves!
Go for it, Jumpers!
Let’s cheer each other on!
Since you have all chosen to believe us, then…
Let’s win the game fair and square!
8 public 288
I won’t let you pass by so easily.
Yeah
Quickly replenish defense
Don’t even think about scoring.
Don’t forget I have teammates!
Oh my god, it’s an aerial relay!
Still a three-point alley-oop
fast attack
My jumping ability has an absolute advantage.
You cannot penetrate my seal.
That’s not necessarily true.
o this game
This game
We will not lose.
The match ended.
I never imagined their true strength would be so great.
It’s all over.
it’s over
It was a really intense match; both sides gave it their all!
In the end, Team Defenders defeated Team Jumper 90-86.
You won! That’s amazing!
marvelous.
Win a good game
They really won.
What to do?
one two three
Put me down!
This time, we can only win because of you.
Just accept the applause from the audience.
I’m afraid of heights.
22 2 4 times 2 22
Captain. We 22 2
We lost this time.
We all did our best, so
Carrying this resentment
Go back with your head held high.
We will become stronger
Next time, we will definitely win a fair and square victory.
Hello
Who are you
I am Bucky’s little brother, my name is Tu Xiaoxiao.
To be continued…