In the previous episode, we discussed how Team Defenders were suppressed by the stealth foul tactic.
But even with countless wounds, they didn’t give up.
Faced with the goat’s doubts and the tribe’s incomprehension
Team Jumper is wavering.
Ultimately, they gave up cheating and competed fairly with the goat.
Despite losing the game
Having lost the game, I have no more aspirations.
What should the villagers do?
What’s there to cry about? There’s always a way.
Or should we go and trick them out of food again?
But I don’t want to lie anymore.
Stop being cute!
What are you doing here? Seeking revenge?
We’re here to help you.
Help us V
Your brother has already told us the truth.
Hello, my name is Tu Xiaoxiao
He is Rabbit’s cute younger brother
younger brother
What do you need us for?
I’m here to apologize.
Apologize.
Yes, there was a reason why my brother lied to you about the food before.
Our clan has always lived in a nearby desert.
Growing food in greenhouses
Life was tough, but fulfilling.
Until one day, a strange change occurred in the village.
The soil quality suddenly deteriorated, and crops could no longer grow.
Everyone is hungry every day
My health is getting worse and worse
At first, my brother borrowed food from all over the place to help everyone.
But that still couldn’t alleviate the village’s situation.
My brother had no choice but to secretly trick others into giving him food.
We’re sorry, please forgive us.
Why do you tell everything to others?
But my brother was only doing it for our village.
We have ways to help you solve your food problem.
Is what you said true?
But first, take us to see your village.
sure
But… I lied to you like that before.
Why are you still helping us?
Did I? I forgot.
Sleeping too little makes my memory worse.
Thank you, Paddi
This is our village.
This place is so desolate.
They’re back.
I’m sorry, we failed.
No, you are our heroes.
Here, my little cookies.
You’ve worked hard.
village head
Cute
These are the seeds of Haloxylon ammodendron.
It is a new variety developed by pioneers of desert farming.
As long as you cultivate diligently
Even barren deserts can be restored to greenery.
This is really
So, we didn’t lie to you, did we?
If you want the village to return to normal as soon as possible
Come and plant them together!
good
Is this really not a dream?
With these saxaul grasses
You won’t need to go out and scam food anymore.
We won’t need to resort to dirty tricks in competitions anymore.
Paddi, come help!
Here
No, we’ll never do it again.
Sorry for keeping you all waiting.
The match between Team Wild Cat and Team Wolves is now starting.
However, Team Wolves captain Victor was absent due to personal reasons.
Hopefully, this won’t affect Team Wolves’ performance.
And replacing Victor
Wolffy will be a substitute for Team Wolves.
Wolffy
alright…
Number 99, come quickly!
Here
What’s wrong with this guy?
His height is such a huge advantage.
I am coming
This way
This number 99 player hasn’t received the ball even once; is he just there to make up the numbers?
Terrible
Have you noticed that they never pass the ball to each other?
My grandma is more agile than you guys when it comes to playing ball.
Too easy
Don’t think you can stop me like this.
here…
Team Wolves are amazing! They managed to score even when surrounded by three players.
I almost stopped her.
But their individual efforts had nearly exhausted them.
Now, it’s time for us to turn things around.
Her reaction speed has indeed slowed down.
It’s not that easy.
Is it really that difficult?
30 Everyone hurry back to defend!
With so many opportunities, why didn’t you pass the ball?
Why pass the ball when everyone is capable of scoring?
We’re a team, not an individual competition.
Forget about teams, just watch how I score!
Nobody can stop me.
then
The wildcats’ offensive came wave after wave.
The score has now turned around and we’re ahead of Team Wolves by ten points.
C
Everyone, please don’t give up! We will definitely win!
They seem to have figured out our attack.
If only the captain were here.
Because the captain is not here, everyone should cooperate with each other even more.
Everyone wants to guard against me
Now?
Give me
Don’t underestimate me, watch me.
Oh no!
No. 99
LI
LL
Go!
It happened! Zhuang Tailang’s earth-shattering dunk!
CI
Don’t even think about me
Wolffy
Don’t just stand there, it’s our turn to fight back.
Number 99 is right, it’s time for us to fight back.
Let the audience see the strength of Team Wolves!
You can’t force your way through me.
Passed the ball
Don’t panic, everyone. We’re not pushovers either.
Go all out!
Wolffy
Team Wolves
Wolffy, you played well!
Great progress
commendable spirit
The technique is just too bad.
Wolffy, come quick!
Back to training
I am coming