Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Heartened and Shattered
In the previous episode, the goats took Slowy to Rabbit Village.
Solved the food crisis there
Wolffy replaced Victor, who had an emergency.
Finally got the chance to play
Wolffy was not favored by his teammates in his first appearance.
But in the end, he led the team to victory and earned the affirmation of his teammates.
What
Our next opponent is Team Sonic!
I can finally play basketball with my idol, Leopardess (elder)!
Not bad, Tibbie
I’ve never seen Tibbie like this before.
Tibbie, it’s okay to like idols.
But you must be rational.
flat
Flat-Beak Allen
Jonie, be rational.
In this competition, I’m determined to show Leopardess (elder) how hard I’ve worked.
Let’s get training started!
Tibbie is really going all out!
Don’t stay tense.
It’s necessary to get out and relax occasionally.
I didn’t expect that they only won three impressive matches.
They have so many fans!
Stop filming… We are positive role models.
Please be rational when following celebrities.
Don’t block the way
You’re blocking my way from taking pictures of the Leopardess (elder) poster.
careful
Isn’t this a team that advanced to the next round by luck, the goat?
Who do I think it is?
So it turns out they were the Wild Boars team who lost the game based on their skill.
We lost because we were defeated by the strong Team Wolves.
A loss is a loss; does it matter who you lose to?
You just advanced by luck.
If you’re so capable, have a match with us!
Come on, who’s afraid of who?
Calm down, calm down
Is there anything that can be resolved calmly?
Furthermore, we need to conserve our energy for the match against Team Sonic.
Team Sonic
M
Their team captain doesn’t seem that great either.
I’ve put all her posters on the trash can.
She only deserves to lie there like a fool.
You are not allowed to speak ill of Leopardess (elder)
Don’t be impulsive
Calm down, calm down. What can you do to stay calm and collected?
Compare if you want
The first team to win by two goals wins.
An angry Tibbie is so scary!
come on
Come on, you’re ready to give up.
Is that so? I’ll wait and see.
ea
2 a
You dare to challenge me to a one-on-one fight with this level of skill?
If an idol’s talent is lacking, then fans are truly useless.
She has a shoulder injury; it’s too dangerous for you to charge at her with the ball.
Only the weak make so many excuses
I’m fine.
Even if he really hurts me, I won’t lose to him.
One more ball
Go Tibbie!
Again
it’s over
You try it.
This move is effective against me.
Useless
What? It was stolen?
good…
good
good.
Tibbie
Tibbie, you’re amazing!
He didn’t hurt you, did he?
fine
You should accept your loss and apologize quickly.
sorry
It’s over so quickly, let’s disperse.
Gone
It’s Leopardess (elder).
Tibbie, where are you going?
This Leopardess (elder) is indeed not simple.
It’s good that Tibbie has an idol.
Can you always be so diligent?
Not necessarily; idols can make or break a person.
You’re contradicting me again.
each other
Leopardess (elder)
Excuse me
I meant no harm
I’m just your fan.
Yeah
I’m here to thank you.
You led me down the path of basketball.
I used to be so weak
It was your appearance that guided me to firmly embark on the path of basketball.
You gave me direction
Every time I see you, I feel full of strength.
You gave me motivation
Your words have always inspired me.
That’s how I got to where I am today.
You also said that as long as you put in the effort
There will definitely be gains.
I will definitely continue to work hard and play well in the game.
I was just saying those things casually.
It’s specifically designed to fool people like you.
What
It means that what I said before was just to appease my fans.
You’re kidding me, right? Don’t joke around, Leopardess (elder)
Why would I lie to you? I hate people like you the most.
What
Tibbie
Tibbie, what’s wrong?
I’m here to thank you.
You led me down the path of basketball.
I was just saying those things casually.
It’s specifically designed to fool people like you.
Why did Leopardess (elder) say that?
Why
How can we help Tibbie?
Or perhaps we should just go directly to Leopardess (elder) and ask her directly.
Why did you bring me here?
Bring you to see Leopardess (elder)!
What do you mean by “see Leopardess (elder)”?
I don’t dare to go.
We’ll talk about it when we meet.
Don’t you want to know?
Why did Leopardess (elder) say those things?
Hello, I’m Weslie from Team Defenders.
Can I go in with my teammates to meet Leopardess (elder)?
Leopardess (elder) doesn’t want to see anyone. You can leave.
We also bought bananas for Leopardess (elder).
Leopardess (elder) would definitely like it.
Look how many bananas we prepared for Leopardess (elder)!
We genuinely want to see her.
Let’s meet, just for a moment.
Leopardess (elder) doesn’t like eating your cheap stuff.
Let’s go, let’s go!
Very good
Tibbie, don’t be sad.
Here, have my banana, it’s delicious!
No need, you eat it.
What are you looking at? Playing the victim won’t work.
We are very principled.
That’s right
get off work
He really has principles!
How did you get in?
Here’s the thing, a friend of ours wants to ask you something.
Leopardess (elder) I
Why is it you again?
Tibbie is your loyal fan
What you said that day was too much.
Is there some misunderstanding you have about Tibbie?
Leopardess (elder), if I did anything wrong before…
I also want to know, and I also want your forgiveness.
I really like you.
Your biggest mistake was playing basketball.
What I hate most is a girl like you who can’t play basketball but still wants to.
But you’ve always encouraged girls to stick to their dreams.
No matter how great the difficulties, we must not give up.
Did I say that? If I did, then forget about it.
Making such a dangerous save so casually
Do you think you’re very strong?
No
You’re making everyone worry about you.
Leopardess (elder), stop talking.
You stubbornly insist on your own opinion regardless of everyone’s feelings.
If you persist in doing something meaningless, you shouldn’t play basketball.
You don’t understand Tibbie at all, so what gives you the right to say that about her?
Tibbie
To be continued…