Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Strange Leopardess
In the previous episode, we mentioned that Tibbie was excited because his next match was against his idol.
The next day, however, he saw his idol, Leopardess (elder), at a street competition.
He then chased after Leopardess (elder) and expressed his worship.
However, Leopardess (elder) treated Tibbie coldly, leaving Tibbie disheartened.
I wonder how Tibbie is doing.
Let’s go take a look.
Tibbie, are you okay?
It seems Tibbie is really sad.
Let’s try to comfort her.
Tibbie
The most important thing about being a goat is to be happy.
Let me share some snacks with you.
Some. All.
Tibbie, please throw this away for me.
You guys go, I want to be alone.
Let’s go
Is it really okay for Tibbie to be alone?
Are you alright? Are you alright?
But everything spilled out.
Let’s tidy up.
Leopardess (elder) said basketball is her life.
That’s way too exaggerated!
It seems Leopardess (elder) is interested in nothing but basketball.
This personality seems to
Victor
Why does the Leopardess (elder) described here look completely different from the one I saw yesterday?
Yeah, and they even insulted Tibbie.
I want to ask and find out.
I’ll go too
Let’s go
Jonie, could you please keep this safe?
Go comfort Tibbie.
OK
By the way, where are you guys going?
We’ll go and get justice for Tibbie.
Where did the security guard go?
He must have been fired for poor performance.
Okay, let’s go in now.
SS
The captain said he doesn’t want to see you.
What
Okay, I’m leaving.
You wait
Oh, right, we can dress up as leopards!
I’ll give it a try.
Sparky
Wait a minute.
I’ve never seen you before.
I’m new here.
Where did your tail go?
I was born without a tail.
You won’t discriminate against me, will you?
Don’t Cry 4 is over.
That said, this is the first time I’ve ever seen a leopard with horns.
And there are so many white hairs
4 How dare they lie to us?
It was time for training, but “the captain was nowhere to be seen again.”
The captain is so amazing, he must be undergoing secret training somewhere.
How could we, mere mortals, possibly know?
What sound?
music
Tibbie, don’t you want these things anymore?
This isn’t something you’ve been treasuring for so long, is it?
Yes…yes
I will always support you
Thank you, little fan.
Your biggest mistake was playing basketball.
Tibbie
Oh right, didn’t I give these things to Weslie and the others?
They seem to have said they’re going to seek justice for you.
I’m going to find them.
But what about these things?
Throw it away
Tibbie, what brings you here?
Looking for you, Paddi and Weslie!
They’ve already gone inside.
Sure enough, I had to go in to find them.
They’re guarding that spot; you can’t get in.
So, how can this be handled officially?
If you want to go in, I can help you.
Come and chase me!
It seems they haven’t had enough of the hardship yet.
Sparky
Leopardess (elder) is dancing!
Wasn’t it said that Leopardess (elder) was undergoing secret training?
Is dancing just special training?
Leopardess (elder) clearly said
She’s interested in nothing but basketball.
Let’s go in and ask.
What are you doing?
Tibbie, what are you doing here?
I also want to ask you guys…
These things don’t matter, Tibbie, look!
Leopardess (elder) is dancing
Does Leopardess (elder) like to dance?
Never mind, it’s none of my business.
Let’s hurry up and go.
Thank you for your concern, but I really don’t need to contact Leopardess (elder) anymore.
Tibbie, you’ll definitely be better than Leopardess (elder) in the future.
You are not allowed to speak ill of Leopardess (elder)
You are a fan of Leopardess (elder)
certainly
Moreover, I’m Leopardess (elder)’s number one fan.
There’s even a signature!
Envious, aren’t you?
It seems a bit strange.
I remember Tibbie’s signature was slightly different from this.
how so
You also have a signature.
real
Something feels off.
Leopardess (elder) is not surprising at all; I will always support her.
Not surprising, not surprising at all, we’re also fans of Leopardess (elder)!
I’m Leopardess (elder)’s number one fan. Please call me “senpai” if we meet again.
Let’s go
Leopard Team, move quickly!
Why should we hide?
yes
I guess I’ve gotten used to being pursued so much.
I finally bought the carrot cookies the captain wanted.
It’s strange, didn’t the captain used to dislike eating this?
Carrot biscuits
What’s wrong, Tibbie?
These carrot cookies were made by hand.
Nutritious and healthy, here it is for you.
I’m sorry, I’m allergic to carrots.
I appreciate your kindness.
Leopardess (elder) is allergic to carrots and would never eat them.
That’s even stranger. Let’s go check it out.
We need to find a way to get in again.
Leave it to me.
Come and chase me again!
Are you getting addicted to being chased by us?
go
Give me back
Give it back to me
I won’t give it to you.
How could this be?
The carrot cookies are all gone; there’s something wrong with this Leopardess (elder).
Follow her
Training is really tiring
Hurry up and take the clothes to be washed.
What should we do? We’ll be found out.
They’re from Team Defenders. They must be here to probe our intelligence.
Sorry, I’m lost.
Catch him
Don’t go, it’s him again.
I really owe Sparky a lot today.
To be continued…