Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Foolish Obsession
In the previous episode,
Tibbie was depressed because of Leopardess (elder)’s scolding.
When the three goats confronted Leopardess (elder), they noticed something amiss with him.
Tibbie who started to not care
It was also discovered that Leopardess (elder) was eating carrot cookies, which she was allergic to.
Isn’t she the real Leopardess (elder)?
So, did you find anything?
This Leopardess (elder) is indeed very suspicious.
Could it be fake?
We’ll go find her and ask her clearly.
Do you think she’ll admit it if you ask her?
We need direct evidence to prove she’s an imposter.
What are the characteristics of a Leopardess (elder)?
Leopardess (elder) has played 246 official basketball games, averaging 34.8 points per game.
4 rebounds, 35 assists, 12.6 steals.
She suffered a serious injury to her right foot during a competition.
Leave a scar
This is what I’m about to say.
As long as there’s no scar on her right sole, it proves she’s an imposter.
Hurry up and take action!
Do we really have to throw these things away?
I love Leopardess (elder) the most; she always gives me strength.
Are you going to throw it or not? If not, then hurry up and leave.
How could you let her take off her shoes?
Leave it to me.
If her shoes get wet, she’ll definitely take them off.
Be careful, pouring water
What are you doing
sorry
I smeared the juice of the sticky fruit on the road.
Her shoes would get stuck and torn off when she walked by.
She’s here.
Success
How could this happen? Could it be that the sticky fruit has lost its effectiveness?
Help me
Leopardess (elder)’s legs are so powerful!
Let me do it.
Weslie, you have a solution!
I have a solution.
What you are
It’s been a long time since I’ve skipped this.
Little girl, would you like to buy a pair of shoes?
Doesn’t Leopardess (elder) like to dance now?
The dance shoes would definitely attract her.
Please help me with my unsold dance shoes!
Success
I forgot I was wearing socks.
We must find out the truth today.
Do you have any other ideas?
Why did you take it back?
These Leopardess (elder) peripheral keychains
Tibbie uses this to motivate himself when he’s feeling sad or down.
She said
These things constantly reminded her of Leopardess (elder)’s unwavering spirit.
Encourage her to cheer up
What’s wrong
These were Tibbie’s most prized goggles, and they’re all smashed now.
They’re all dilapidated and run-down; we might as well just get rid of them.
Why do you always like to put others down?
What should I do?
Why not just fix it?
Coach, you’re right.
Come on! Let’s get started!
I didn’t expect you to be so considerate.
Isn’t this normal…? You’re just really bad.
What did you say
Okay, let’s get started!
Do you know how to invent? Do you know how to repair?
That’s not how it’s done.
Let me do it, I’m better at it than you.
Mr. Slowy, you really love to argue.
This is my serious attitude
Where did Leopardess (elder) go? Could she have already gone back to her room?
Let’s go look for it.
You all stop right there!
you.
One of you
Could it be that we’ve been discovered?
What should I do?
Are you the technicians here to change the light bulbs?
yes…
Why do you need four people to change a light bulb?
Because…you didn’t say how many light bulbs you wanted to change.
That seems to be true.
Alright, you guys go and change it quickly.
It’s in the room right in front.
good
What’s wrong
Keep your voice down.
Why are you making such a fuss?
So this is her room.
There’s a scar on his right foot; this is a genuine Leopardess (elder).
It seems we were overthinking it.
Let’s go quickly, it would be troublesome if she woke up.
What are you doing here?
Why are there two Leopardess (elder) signs?
One of them must be fake.
what is going on
Since you’ve discovered
I have nothing to hide.
The one who is in a coma is the Leopardess (elder) you all know.
SS
And I am her twin sister, Leopardess (younger).
How did Leopardess (elder) fall into a coma?
She’s like this because of basketball.
My sister has always loved basketball.
Not only is she very talented, but she also works harder than anyone else.
Therefore, she also achieved brilliant results in basketball games.
He gradually became everyone’s idol.
but
During a checkup, doctors discovered that she had a congenital genetic disease.
Continuing to play basketball could lead to life-threatening situations.
But she refused to give up her beloved basketball.
Relying on the doctor’s words that treatment would lead to a gradual recovery.
They also made a promise to participate in the Basketball Game and win the championship together with their teammates.
Ultimately, it was because he pushed himself too hard.
He just fainted on the basketball court.
The doctor said she might never wake up.
In order to win the basketball championship and wake up her older sister
I had to replace her in Team Sonic
I have to face this awful basketball every day.
Leopardess (elder) - She actually did something like that.
So you hate basketball?
That’s why I said those things to Tibbie.
He pushed himself to the limit to play basketball, even risking his life.
What’s the point of learning something so stupid?
Leopardess (elder) is not stupid at all.
Is it wrong to go all out for your dreams?
Don’t you give it your all when you dance?
You can leave now, I have nothing more to say to you.
Sorry to bother you.
I will not give up
I want to keep playing basketball
I’m going to prove to you that Leopardess (elder) wasn’t wrong to strive for her dreams.
Wait for us, Tibbie!
Where did it go? Why is it gone?
Tibbie, we’ll help you find it too.
Why can’t I find the box?
Don’t be sad, Tibbie
Look
My box
Great, everything is here.
Didn’t you throw it away?
Jonie knew these things were important to Tibbie.
I couldn’t bear to throw it away
Thank you. Jonie.
You’re welcome; even the broken goggles were repaired by Mr. Slowy and coach.
I’ve made up my mind. I’m going to continue working hard with everyone.
Win the championship
That’s great! Let’s all keep it up!
Okay, everyone together
Let’s train!
It’s already late, and we still have to train.
Nobody trained today, shouldn’t we make it up?
To be continued…