In the previous episode, Tibbie and his group began to suspect Leopardess (elder)’s identity.
The unexpected discovery revealed that Leopardess (elder) had been in a coma due to illness.
Now her younger sister, Leopardess (younger), is playing in her place.
In order to change Leopardess (younger)’s misunderstanding of her older sister
Tibbie is determined to win the game against Team Sonic.
I am coming
good
Wow, so fast!
It’s just average.
Come
Coach, be careful
Slowy, stop showing off.
I did it to save you.
Mr. Slowy, I’m sorry
Okay, you guys stop practicing for now.
Let’s take a look at Team Sonic’s game.
good
Wow, that’s amazing!
It seems I need to work harder.
Although Leopardess (younger) is very fast
But that doesn’t mean we’ll lose.
What should we do?
The key to this match was Tibbie.
That’s right, Tibbie
You are the point guard opposite Leopardess (younger).
But there are still two areas where you need to improve.
What is it, coach?
Your left-hand dribbling and overall court awareness are not good enough.
Come with me
Your next exercise will be this.
Swimming
It’s catching fish
What does catching fish have to do with point guards?
Catching fish trains observation skills.
Treat the fish in the water as players on the field
Don’t overlook any details
Even if he is very fast, he can
Hit the target
If you can catch it, you’ve passed this level.
I will definitely work hard with a good coach.
Great, everyone else, go do some running practice to improve your stamina.
yes
Can Tibbie practice alone?
Tibbie
Are you alright?
I can do it, don’t worry.
But…
Believe me
What happened to Tibbie? Are you hurt?
Don’t cry, we will definitely help you.
I didn’t cry, I just wanted to make some ginger soup to warm myself up.
These onions are just too pungent.
Do I need to add onions when making ginger soup?
Yeah
I’ve prepared a dry towel for you.
They even prepared waterproof goggles for you.
I’ve prepared a fishing net for you.
I’ll help you defend Leopardess (younger)
Thank you
You always appear when I encounter difficulties.
Accompanying me through every difficult time
You guys are truly my best friends.
where
But this time, I want to overcome this hurdle on my own.
But
I want to become stronger.
If I can’t even get through this level of training on my own, then…
So, I will always be the same weak Tibbie I always was.
One, two, keep going!
come on
Treat the fish in the water as players on the field
Don’t overlook any details.
A rock blocked his way.
The fish will definitely change its course in front of the rock.
The tail pointing to the left is the right side.
Caught
I caught it…
They really caught them.
Coach, thank you
I finally figured it out.
Observational skills are really important
Good shot, now we’ll move on to the second part of the training.
besides
Yes, come with me.
Next, we’ll practice advanced ball control.
If you can practice dribbling with both hands through this tunnel
Even if you succeed
Is it dangerous in this dark cave?
Go to the exit and wait there.
There’s nothing inside, don’t worry.
Okay, I will try my best.
Thank you, I can do it myself.
You guys should go train soon too!
Keep going, you will definitely succeed!
Second refueling
What do you want from me?
This is…
Thank you
Tibbie, your hands are shaking from exhaustion.
Use a fork.
No, Jonie.
My hands are shaking because I use my left hand to hold chopsticks, and I’m not used to it yet.
Yes, Tibbie
Why are you eating noodles with your left hand?
I always struggle with dribbling with my left hand, so I want to practice using it more.
I’ll sit here, leaving the left side clear so you can practice.
Thank you
00 That’s great
Coach, I did it!
Thank you everyone for cheering me on.
I am coming
good
I saw it, he’s going to the right.
How did you know I was going this way?
Thanks to the coach
Wow, that’s amazing!
nice shot
Tibbie, you’ve really improved a lot!
I will continue to work hard.