Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Victor’s Memories
As mentioned in the previous episode, the match against Team Sonic is imminent.
Tibbie, however, is the team’s weak point.
In order to improve point guard skills
Tibbie trained hard under Blazey’s guidance.
Even if I get injured, I won’t give up.
Finally, Tibbie learned the even more powerful point guard skill.
000.
Does Wilie listen to her mother at home?
Of course, Wilie was the most obedient.
Then Dad can give me a reward.
No problem, do you want snacks or a new toy?
Dad hasn’t been home in a long time. I want him to take me on a picnic.
Dad will take leave and come home now. Let’s have dinner together today.
But didn’t you say before that the team management is very strict?
Dad is an important player now.
And their relationships with everyone have improved a lot.
Wolffy, you played well!
Great progress
commendable spirit
The technique is just too bad.
What’s the big deal?
Captain, I’d like to ask for leave today.
You want to take the day off.
I advise you to give up.
Why?
Last time
I have a comminuted fracture of my foot and can’t even take time off work.
How heartless!
Before
My house was burned to ashes, and I can’t even ask for leave.
How cruel!
It seems I won’t be able to get leave.
What should I do? I already promised Wolnie and my son.
Why are you still here?
I’m going to train now.
What to train
Today, the team leader took the day off, so everyone got the day off too.
But Chang Tailang and them
You’re messing with me
Unexpectedly, their relationship improved.
Dad played really well in the last game, he must be exhausted.
Eat more
Of course, (Dad is now an indispensable and important player on the team).
I can finally eat with you guys.
I don’t have to see the captain every day anymore
Your captain is that cool guy dressed head-to-toe in all black.
From a distance, it looks a bit fierce and like a very powerful wolf.
Wolnie, your description is so detailed! It’s as if he’s right in front of you.
He’s right there.
Is the captain really that weird that he trains on a cliff?
He’s going to fall.
Wolnie, son
You guys eat first, I have to go rescue people.
Hang in there, I’m coming!
No. 99, what are you doing here?
Are you alright?
Stop, don’t come any closer.
Who ate the banana peel?
More trouble than good
I’m sorry.
I think I just heard Wolffy’s voice.
I hope nothing bad has happened.
Thank goodness you’re alright.
I’m fine.
Captain, I know the pressure of the competition is immense.
But there’s no need for you to be so desperate as to jump off a cliff.
When faced with difficulties, shouldn’t we bravely confront them?
I’m just here to gather herbs.
If it weren’t for you, I wouldn’t have fallen.
Oh, I see.
There were falling rocks.
Are you out of your mind? Is this flower really that important?
she
She… is a rival I greatly respect.
Beware of falling rocks
What
Would I be afraid of just a falling rock?
Are you alright?
Let’s have another match!
What to compare
You ran faster than me just now, let’s run again.
Why are you such a competitive wolf?
Maybe next time, I have a ball game to play later.
match
Basketball game
You play basketball too?
S
What’s wrong? Do you look down on girls?
no…
See you next time
By the way, my name is Leopardess (elder).
My name is Victor
From that day on, we ran together.
Practice ball together
I’ve already said it: you can’t beat me at basketball.
How will you know if you don’t try?
s again
J
CC
So fast
This is what playing ball should be like!
Leopardess (elder)
I didn’t know until that day
It turns out that Leopardess (elder) has always been in poor health and unable to engage in strenuous exercise.
But she never gave up basketball.
During that match, Leopardess (elder) finally succumbed to his injuries and collapsed.
He hasn’t woken up yet.
I recently heard about a “revitalizing flower” that blooms only once every hundred years and can awaken people in a vegetative state.
So I went to pick it for her.
You usually seem so cool, I never imagined you were so loyal and sentimental.
I don’t know why I’m talking to you so much today.
It seems the captain is quite humane.
Hurry up and go, or I’ll leave you behind.
It’s here…
Let it go
When I rushed over to rescue them, I didn’t realize how dangerous it was.
careful
team leader
Hold on tight
Thanks
team leader
Run
What’s wrong? Let’s go!
Captain, go quickly, don’t worry about me.
Hurry up
team leader
Captain, you can’t get across by carrying me on your back.
Why don’t you put me down and go ahead, Captain?
How will you know if you don’t try?
How do you know if you haven’t tried?
Almost there
Captain, you’re amazing!
Captain, what are you doing?
Perhaps there are other ways to wake Leopardess (elder).
There’s no other way.
How do you know it’s impossible if you haven’t even tried?
Didn’t you tell me that?
dad
Wolffy, where did you go?
Are you alright?
It’s alright, I was saved by the captain.
Long, that’s all.
Won’t you stay for a meal?
I’m not hungry
He really seems cold and unapproachable.
Actually, the captain isn’t such a cold-hearted person.
To be continued…