In the previous episode, Wolffy saw that Victor was in danger.
Wolffy saw that Victor was in danger.
The previous episode mentioned
In an attempt to save them, she and Victor ended up falling off a cliff.
Later, Wolffy discovered that Victor had come to risk his life on the cliff.
It was to pick herbs for his friend Leopardess (elder)
I was surprised to find that the aloof Victor is actually quite sentimental.
It’s that time of year again – the match day everyone’s been waiting for!
Today’s lineup is Team Defenders.
Go Team Defenders!
besides
Team Sonic
You shouldn’t be here.
I will carry on Leopardess (elder)’s beliefs in my own way.
To prove to you that the path we chose was not wrong.
Everyone hurry back to defend!
This is
Team Defenders surprisingly used a full-court man-to-man tactic right from the start.
Keep it up!
Do you think it will be useful?
Wow, so fast!
Stop her
Team Sonic’s speed is amazing; they scored right after the kickoff.
You’re all nothing special.
Tibbie, cheer up
We will continue to implement the Zhanhe strategy.
Go Team Sonic!
We’ll talk once you catch up with me.
Unexpectedly, Team Sonic has more than just Leopardess (elder) who is fast.
The speed of the other teammates was also astonishing!
Team Defenders adopted a man-to-man defense strategy from the start.
How long can they keep up with Team Sonic’s incredible speed?
Is your tactic any good? They’re already leading by ten points!
It actually kept up with me
Doesn’t it get tiring to keep wearing protective patches?
It seems that after rounds of marking at the beginning
The Team Sonic members are starting to show signs of fatigue.
But Team Defenders are still in high spirits!
Is this Team Defenders’ purpose?
Team Sonic is fast and has explosive power!
We cannot reach it
However, this state will not last forever.
Therefore, we need to use this characteristic to force them to expend their physical strength.
No wonder you used to push the children so hard to improve their physical fitness.
It turned out that this was to ensure they had enough stamina to wear down Team Sonic.
Once they’re all exhausted, we’ll launch a full-scale attack.
Blazey, you’re really something!
A little better than you, right?
If you’re so capable, compete in invention!
Children, it’s your turn to perform.
not good
4. My legs are a little slow to keep up.
Leopardess (elder): I tried my best.
I didn’t see wrong, did I?
Team Sonic requests a pause
Team Defenders caught up by 14
Team Sonic seems to be struggling with physical issues.
How should they respond?
Our Goat Clan is also very good at basketball.
Keep up the good work, everyone!
SS
We can’t keep rushing in blindly.
Let’s use that tactic; that’ll cut off their attack.
yes
Thinking about me won’t be that easy.
Weslie’s shot was intercepted.
It appeared
Team Sonic’s signature move: Sonic steal.
The speed of the sonic steal is much faster than Weslie’s.
This will be a fierce battle.
om
Don’t think you can beat us.
Weslie, over here
The point difference has widened again.
It seems the pause just now helped Team Sonic regain a lot of energy.
We have no way to attack like this.
what to do
Dodged
Wow, that’s fast!
She’s here again. Can I escape her?
out of bounds
Request to pause
Tibbie, it’s your turn to break the deadlock for the team.
Can I?
You have a stable sense of ball control and passing skills
You must believe in yourself
I…
Tibbie, believe in yourself.
We’re waiting for your pass.
come on
Everyone
I will try my best.
The timeout has ended, and Team Defenders are kicking off.
Facing Team Sonic’s lightning-fast steal
How can Team Defenders resolve this predicament?
It’s up to you, Tibbie.
Can I… do it?
Must be done
I will carry Leopardess (elder)’s belief and play my best in basketball.
SS
I can control the ball well.
Go Tibbie!
I want to be with everyone
S
Continue to race on this field
Let’s talk after the goal is scored.
Don’t even think about scoring.
That was amazing, that beautiful turn!
Brilliant ball control, stunning passes
I can’t think of any words to express the excitement I feel.
Tibbie, you’re the best point guard!
I…I did it.
You’re amazing, Tibbie!
We need to keep chasing points.
good
They tied it.
The first half has ended, and both sides are now in a break.
I will beat you in the second half.
I’m waiting.