Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Chapter of Way Out
As mentioned in the previous episode, Team Defenders utilize physical strength and defense.
They were evenly matched against Team Sonic, who excelled at fast breaks but lacked stamina.
Team Sonic frequently stole the ball.
Interrupting Team Defenders’ attack
At this moment, Tibbie stepped up, using his skillful ball control…
Protecting possession of the ball and helping teammates break the deadlock
Team Defenders will win!
Excellent, children!
In the second half, just keep an eye on Team Sonic.
Their stamina definitely can’t keep up.
Don’t let your guard down, they definitely have a way to deal with this.
SS
They will definitely continue to use this tactic to wear us down in the second half.
Tibbie, your opponent might adjust their formation to counter you in the next match.
To reduce energy consumption, let’s use that move.
Second half start
Team Sonic wanted to prevent Tibbie from using her fancy ball control to attack the penalty area again.
A strategy of shrinking the defensive zone was adopted.
Watch me
The defense is too tight; we can’t force our way through.
Let’s pass the ball out first.
They tightened their defense on the perimeter, giving Paddi an opportunity.
It’s probably not that easy.
Things you can think of
Do you think we wouldn’t think of that?
Don’t panic, everyone, hurry back!
Defend
CVC
What just happened? How did Team Sonic score?
Just now… what was that?
After the opponent’s small forward intercepted the ball
Throw the ball directly into the undefended attacking third.
It’s impossible for an average person to keep up with the speed of a ball.
But Team Sonic can
So that’s how it is.
Leopardess (elder)
Team Defenders will win!
SS
Jonie
Oh no!
CVC
Team Sonic continuously unleashed long, cannon-like passes from extremely long distances.
Team Defenders suffers a series of defeats.
Team Defenders has requested a pause.
What’s going on? They’re withstanding our tight defense.
It seems like I’m not expending as much energy as before.
Constantly rotating players makes fast breaks less tiring.
Their tactic was a supersonic fast attack.
The Sonic Fast Break only has one player on offense at a time.
Other players will get a proper rest.
In other words, Team Sonic’s physical weakness has been overcome.
What should we do then?
The game restarted
Quickly return to defense
Tibbie
The only way to break the sonic attack
It depends on you first anticipating who your opponent will pass to.
This is how you can prevent it.
To anticipate… to anticipate
Who will this ball be passed to?
No… the players who pass and receive the ball are not fixed at all.
No… I can’t do it.
Believe in yourself
Leopardess (elder)
Losing isn’t scary; what’s scary is when you think you’re not good enough.
Believe in yourself
That’s right, you have to believe in yourself.
It’s time to put your fishing training to good use!
It is small forward
Wait a bit longer, let’s observe a little more.
It is power forward
Do you want to pass the ball there?
You have no chance of catching up with us.
What
Offensive foul
Tibbie intercepted them, surprisingly seeing through the opponent’s tactics first.
Block the opponent’s attack route first.
Team Sonic’s sonic offensive was brought to an end.
come on
Great, Tibbie succeeded!
I had expected this.
Tibbie, are you okay?
I’m fine.
Tibbie, you’re amazing!
SS
They played really well.
but.
SS
That’s all.
Let’s see how you see through me this time.
Team Sonic’s four players simultaneously coordinated a fast break.
Team Defenders probably had no other choice this time.
pretty
Go Team Sonic!
No, the gap we finally managed to close…
It absolutely cannot be widened any further.
Kids, stay calm!
Team Sonic seized another opportunity to attack.
Who will Leopardess (elder) pass to this time?
I need to calm down.
Their movements and expressions
They’re all the same, so which one is the main attacker?
I can’t figure it out… what should I do…?
Don’t forget
And us
Yes, and everyone else too.
Although you saved some energy
But you’re not as fast as you used to be.
Team Defenders went out of bounds.
However, this also interrupted Team Sonic’s attack.
Team Sonic was constantly disrupted, leading to frequent mistakes.
Team Defenders seized the opportunity to close the gap.
Goat, are you alright?
I’m fine.
Why, why play ball without regard for your physical condition?
Is it worth it?
Worth it
I will let you know
That’s not worth it…
Leopardess (elder)’s shot was faster and more powerful than before.
I want to become
A person as strong as Leopardess (elder)
Tibbie
Oh my god
Tibbie risked his life to receive this high-strength pass.
To be continued…