Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Because of Passion
In the previous episode,
Second half begins
Team Sonic unleashed their signature cannonball pass.
Tibbie spotted the opening and interrupted the attack.
This enraged Leopardess (younger), who unleashed an upgraded version of his ultimate move.
To prevent the score from widening further, Tibbie…
He bravely blocked the ball, even shattering his goggles in the process.
Tibbie…
Tibbie
Tibbie, can you still go on?
I’m fine, I must continue the competition.
Tibbie
Are you alright?
I’m fine, even if you throw a faster pass.
I will do everything in my power to stop you, just like you.
You were clearly injured, so why?
Why keep putting on a brave face?
Because of giving it your all
That’s the charm of sports competitions…
In short, I will definitely defeat you.
What tactics are they planning to use this time?
Pass the ball?
To whom should it be sent?
he?
He actually broke through on his own?
I must win.
Leopardess (elder) actually made a layup himself this time.
Surprisingly, she didn’t pass the ball to her teammate.
Even Tibbie was fooled.
Tibbie, it’s okay, keep it up!
Pass the ball to me, I’ll score.
Then all the pressure will be concentrated on you.
You might not be able to hold on.
You don’t need to say anything more. I know what I’m doing.
Do as I say
Leopardess (elder) scored another goal.
The competition is getting more and more exciting.
Don’t worry, let’s keep going!
Leopardess (elder) scored again this time.
She used her speed to score continuously.
Her stamina seems inexhaustible.
Victory will surely belong to us.
Only five minutes left
Team Defenders requests a pause.
Next, I’d like to switch Weslie to defend Leopardess (younger).
I understand, Coach.
Tibbie
Your current abilities are not yet sufficient.
Fighting against Leopardess (younger) in her burst state
I really am…
But you’ve already done a great job.
Do you remember what I said?
Basketball is a team sport
Since I can’t handle it by myself
Let’s work together to figure out a way to deal with it.
Even if you’re not the one defending Leopardess (younger)
You can also defeat her
You need to use your observation skills
Protect your ball
At the same time, create scoring opportunities for your teammates.
This is what makes a great point guard.
Defeat her in your own way.
I understand, Coach.
The game continued with only five minutes remaining.
bring it on…
Stop her quickly!
Oh no!
Very good…
I will definitely defeat you.
We must keep going and not give up.
You’re really troublesome, just like me.
Team Defenders have pulled the score back.
Team Sonic is in a bit of trouble.
Sister… I will help you win the championship.
Don’t give up any opportunity.
You guys… pass the ball to me.
Isn’t Leopardess (elder) nearing his physical limit?
Why does she seem to have inexhaustible energy?
That’s terrifying.
For my sister’s sake, I will not lose.
elder sister
Sister, please stop forcing it.
No, I can continue.
I must lead everyone to victory in place of my sister!
Your stamina is almost at its limit.
Don’t force it anymore; it’s very dangerous.
No, I will do my best to keep fighting.
Sister, please stop playing basketball.
This is dangerous.
No, I will do my best to keep fighting.
Go all out…
I actually said the same thing as my sister.
Everyone do their best to defend this ball.
We can win.
I absolutely will not let you score.
You’re too slow.
elder sister
Team Defenders wins.
We won…
We actually lost.
I’m sorry, sister, I still lost.
If I had devoted myself to it earlier
perhaps…
Perhaps the outcome would be different.
You’ve arrived?
I brought flowers.
It is Leopardess (elder’s) favorite flower.
How did you know?
Of course
I’m a huge fan of Leopardess (Elder)!
Although I lost this game
But I think I’m starting to understand.
Why does my sister like basketball so much?
These are my sister’s goggles.
I broke yours, so I’m giving this to you.
These are Leopardess (elder) goggles, really given to me?
I think I’m starting to understand.
Why are you working so hard for one thing?
I hope you’re wearing my sister’s goggles.
Continue to advance
I will definitely win the championship.
And I’ve already discussed it with my other teammates.
We decided to use the wish given by the champion.
Wake up Leopardess (elder)
Are you serious? Wait until my sister wakes up.
I will definitely tell her.
I will no longer object to her playing basketball.
Tibbie, we’ve been waiting for you for so long!
Let’s go back and have dinner together.
Here
Isn’t this Leopardess (elder) goggles?
So cool
I need to wear Leopardess (elder) goggles.
Win the championship
And us…
To be continued…