Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Hide-and-Seek Party
In the previous episode,
Tibbie consistently used passing to help his team score.
Leopardess (younger) also pushed his physical limits to the limit, pushing himself beyond his limits.
Both teams gave it their all.
Team Defenders ultimately won a hard-fought victory.
Leopardess (younger) lost the game
But she understood her sister and Tibbie’s love for basketball.
I’ve finally gotten rid of the substitute jersey!
Congratulations, Wolffy!
Thanks
Wolffy, come and cut the cake!
good
bring it on
Where’s the knife I prepared?
Why use a knife? Just eat it!
Don’t be so stingy on such a happy day!
Wish us success in winning the basketball championship!
This juice is so delicious!
It would be even better if we could have a leg of goat at this time.
No problem, arrangements will be made.
Lamb leg
It’s me
Congratulations on becoming a regular player, Wolffy!
We’ve come to celebrate with you.
OK
I’ve forgotten how long it’s been since I’ve had goat meat.
I really want to eat a couple of bites
No… wait a minute
Get ready for a feast!
See you later
Don’t come yet.
What’s wrong? Are any friends coming over?
No one came. Wolnie asked me what else I wanted to eat.
Could you ask your sister-in-law to bring back some goat meat?
Eat some fruit, eat more!
Goat meat is so delicious… We want to eat goat meat!
Just wait, Wolffy
The victory in the finals will definitely belong to our Goat Clan.
It seems Weslie is genuinely happy for Wolffy.
Why are you walking so slowly?
I’m going first, you guys hurry up!
Being happy is fine, but can’t I be happy if I walk slower?
OK
You’re lucky today.
I don’t usually sign my name easily, but I’ll make an exception for you today.
No need for thanks.
You drew something on my ball.
Don’t be ungrateful, we’re the reigning champions, Team Gliders!
I don’t know you
Okay, here you go.
My hand slipped
D
Give me back my ball
You’ve gone too far.
Don’t worry, I’ll get it back for you.
Who are you to mess with me?
If you can take it, then take it.
Answer the phone quickly, Weslie!
They arrived so quickly!
You…you ate him.
Of course I ate it.
Why is it taking so long to arrive?
Want to swallow it all by yourself?
I’ve only ever taken a sip in my entire life, and I wish I could swallow it whole!
He also took it all for himself
Seriously? I’ve never even tried dragon fruit.
pitaya
Here’s an extra treat! This dragon fruit is quite delicious.
Really? Actually, I also think fruit tastes better than goat meat.
It seems like it would be nice to get along peacefully with goats; they’re so cute.
Adorable, hateful
To live peacefully with a goat is the greatest disgrace a wolf can bear.
If wolves and goats could live peacefully together, I would be the first to despise them.
To despise him
I…I’m going to make a phone call.
Eat more
Answer the phone quickly
Wolffy
You finally answered the phone.
Surprised? Unexpected?
Where did you come from?
Wolffy, who are you talking to?
No, you misheard.
What are you doing, Wolffy?
Where is Wolffy?
Who is he, Wolffy?
My teammate
Teammates, that’s a good opportunity to get to know each other!
Do you know what my team’s name is?
Isn’t it called Team Wolves?
Good to know. Do you think all wolves are like me, not eating goats?
So you were here.
Wolffy, you
Me, this
I am
Don’t pluck long hairs. Otherwise, they’ll just grow back thicker.
Bai…yes, thank you for reminding me.
Let’s go play games!
Do you think the captain’s white fur is from plucking too many of his own hairs?
Jonie, are you really going to use this method?
bring it on
If you can’t do it, don’t force it.
I will definitely get it.
Squad Leader
I just want to get the ball.
How about it
Or, you could ask me to sign my name.
I’ll reluctantly help you get the ball.
Come on, ask me for help.
Here, your ball.
Take it
Thank you, sister.
Go home quickly
Okay, very good
We’ll see.
Squad leader, are you alright?
I’m fine, let’s hurry to Wolf Fortress.
By the way, Jonie, you’re really amazing!
They managed to get the ball back that way.
I just happened to hit the ball when I fell…
Squad leader, you’re too modest.
Don’t worry, they’re all in their rooms.
You can just go out through the main gate in a bit.
You think you can just leave? No way!
sorry
You’re really pathetic.
What did you say
To shoot him
Whoever loses has to cover the cleaning duties of the stadium for a month.
Didn’t you say they were in the room?
Hide quickly
Wolffy
There are no goats here.
Where is the toilet?
My stomach suddenly felt uncomfortable.
So it was just an upset stomach.
Oh no, I forgot Weslie was in there!
Wolffy, what’s going on?
You…you listen to my explanation.
It wasn’t a toilet seat.
Go straight and turn right to find the toilet.
Your dragon fruit must be dirty.
Sorry Weslie, let’s go now!
Go out through that window.
I’ll definitely beat you next time.
impossible
Run
Sitting on the toilet is still more comfortable.
Why not just knock him out?
Let’s go watch them play games.
15. He finished pooping so quickly!
What should we do?
So you’re here, Ning Tailang
Can you smell the aroma of goat meat?
Is the smell really that strong?
Never mind that for now, where did Wolffy go?
He’s the star of the banquet!
Why don’t we wait for Wolffy in the lobby?
What is that sound?
Hi everyone, just playing hide-and-seek with you guys…
Let’s go get some juice.
Look, the juice is here!
Who is it?
Us
What do you mean “us”?
I went to open the door.
No need… I’ll go.
let me
Even opening a door can take forever.
Let me do this tiring work.
Nobody
It must be a prank.
They’re so full they have nothing better to do.
Okay, you’re not coming to training for a whole day.
Watch how I deal with you all
Goat
It’s so windy outside, I need to close the door.
I’m so sorry, I can’t entertain you.
Wolffy, wishing you a happy probationary period!
Thank you for coming to celebrate with me today.
No need to thank me, we’re best friends.
Thank you so much, I’m so touched.
Who knew Wolffy was friends with a goat?
Team Wolves cannot tolerate the existence of such a traitor.
To be continued…