Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories
“Eagle vs. Wolf”
In the previous episode,
Weslie unexpectedly stumbles into Team Wolves’ party
Wolffy helps Weslie
Playing hide-and-seek with Team Wolves all over the place
They escaped in a thrilling way.
On the other side
The other four goats, seeing the injustice, stepped in to help.
They had a grudge against the Hawks.
Good morning, everyone.
How come it’s so clean?
Why are you so enthusiastic today? Have you lost your mind?
Or did you get punished by the captain again?
No, I’m a starter for the team now.
Therefore, we need to work even harder.
very good
Good morning
team leader…
Captain, thank you so much for making me a regular player.
Let’s work hard together from now on.
boring
By the way, Wolffy
This gift is for you.
Gift?
Finally, I’m not No. 99 anymore.
congratulations
I finally got my starting player jersey!
Wait a minute.
Wolffy, do you want to become the starting player?
And then sell our intelligence to Team Defenders?
Zi Tailang, what are you saying?
See for yourselves
Did you see it clearly?
Wolffy is friends with the goats.
Find an opportunity to betray our intelligence.
If I hadn’t discovered it early…
You’ve already betrayed us, haven’t you?
Is this true, Wolffy?
I didn’t betray Team Wolves’ information.
But I am indeed friends with them.
What?
You actually made friends with other teams?
You’ve misunderstood, I just…
We are so disappointed
You can leave.
From today onwards, you are no longer a Team Wolves player.
Dear friends
train…
I didn’t know we were friends with Wolffy.
Has it been discovered?
Whose prank was it?
Why is everything around me so messy?
Come and take a look.
There is an eagle pattern here.
eagle?
Who do you think you are? How dare you oppose me?
It must be that eagle from last time.
Is he doing this to retaliate against us?
Are there any other pranks planned?
Mr. Slowy…
Why is this happening?
Why is there so much trash on the stadium?
It was the eagle’s prank.
eagle?
How could there be your opponent in the next match?
What is the Team Gliders’ logo?
Who will be the opponent in the next match?
Yes, this opponent is no ordinary opponent.
They are the defending champions.
Do you know them?
Why did you react so strongly just now?
Actually, the thing is this:
I see
That’s really going too far.
They probably just wanted to play a prank on you.
There probably won’t be a next time, right?
Goats
What do you think? My surprise gift
Do you like it?
It really was you who did it.
That’s right, are you not convinced?
Go to the street court and have a match with me!
You won, everything is wiped clean.
I’m sorry, it’s all my fault.
You did nothing wrong, Jonie.
That’s right, he was the one who was unreasonable first.
Okay, let’s go find him and settle the score.
What should I do? Nobody believes me.
I promised my wife and son.
To become the team’s main player
Now it’s turned out like this.
A flock of silly goat
Just wait and see how I teach you a lesson.
He said he wanted to teach the goat a lesson?
What exactly happened?
We started practicing defense.
Where’s Wolffy? Wolffy, you go first.
What did you say?
Wolffy has already left.
yes
When I didn’t say
Everyone perked up
team leader…
Come with me to train for long-distance running.
yes…
Sky Hawk, we’ve arrived as promised.
Why are there always some overconfident little lambs (goats)?
Are you going to challenge me?
You challenged us first!
Sparky, calm down.
Okay, then I’ll give you a chance to challenge for the championship.
You guys take turns playing, one at a time.
You win if you score the first goal.
They are goats
good
Let you attack first
Want to back down and play one-on-one?
It flew…it took off!
You?
Don’t be so smug, we haven’t lost yet.
Then you should give it a try too!
Really? Is this all you’ve got?
Captain, there’s a sound coming from over there on the field.
Why don’t we go over and take a look?
Who else wants to challenge me?
I…
you?
Didn’t you like to show off last time?
Why don’t you dare to stand up today?
I’ll come.
I’ll challenge you to a duel.
Wolffy
Who are you? Meddling in other people’s business again?
I am a member of Team Wolves
I won’t allow you to bully my friend.
Friends? Goats and wolves are friends?
Make friends with weak teams
It seems Team Wolves are nothing special after all.
Don’t slander them.
They are very strong players
How can you say nice things about both a goat and a wolf at the same time?
Are you their traitor?
What?
You actually made friends with other teams?
You can leave.
From today onwards, you are no longer a Team Wolves player.
That’s not how it is.
Although I am friends with the goats
But that doesn’t mean I’ll betray Team Wolves.
So complicated
I’m not interested in your friendship.
Who wants to challenge me?
Let me do it.
Wait a minute.
Let me be your opponent
team leader?
Wolffy
When did you arrive?
We arrived a long time ago.
We heard what you just said.
With your current skills
It will only embarrass our Team Wolves.
team leader
Who exactly are you?
This year’s Basketball Game champion
Victor
I don’t know you
Let you attack first
Is this all the skill you have?
How can it be so amazing?
We’re not even playing the same sport.
You are definitely different from those little lambs (goats).
That’s interesting.
It’s a pity this basketball hoop is so bad.
Never mind, I’ll win against you next time.
Let’s go
Wolffy
I’ll punish you by making you run 100 laps.
We misunderstood you before.
Welcome back to the team
Let’s go back to training together…
Captain, this…
Needless to say
Team Defenders is so weak
Even if Wolffy really did give them intelligence
It doesn’t affect us either.
All right
Thank you, Captain.
It seems our strength is still insufficient.
Let’s start training twice as hard today!
good…
(to be continued)