In the previous episode,
Zi Tailang exposes Wolffy’s relationship with the goat and kicks him out of Team Wolves.
On the other side, Ying Aotian forced Goat to fight him one-on-one.
Wolffy lends a helping hand
Team Wolves were touched by his bond with the goat.
Victor steps in to fight Sky Hawk and brings Wolffy back to the team.
98… 99 …Completed
Wolffy, how much did you do?
4 no, 5
No way, there really isn’t anyone who can’t do 100 sit-ups, right?
101, 102, 103, 104, 105…
They’re still practicing!
Wolffy, aren’t you on holiday today?
How can you be so diligent?
Captain, please let me stay.
And he was a regular pick.
Therefore, I must train hard to repay the captain.
Win the championship for Team Wolves
The championship will definitely belong to our Team Wolves!
Training time ended
It’s finally stopped.
The next step is the strategic preparation phase.
Strategic preparation phase
Jonie
Are you alright?
Jonie, what’s wrong with you lately?
Why do I often get distracted?
It’s okay, I probably just didn’t sleep well.
I’m going to take a break.
I’m so terrible.
When faced with a formidable opponent, they don’t even have the courage to accept the challenge.
I’ll definitely drag everyone down during the competition.
The coaches must have a solution; I’ll go ask them.
Blazey, Team Gliders should be our best team to date!
The strongest team I’ve ever encountered
As the previous champion
They are top players in every position.
Especially their center, Sky Hawk, whose strength is extraordinary.
If Jonie, who is also a center, were to be matched up against him…
Now we’re probably going to lose badly.
To win the championship, you need to know yourself and your enemy.
As long as I figure out everyone’s tactics, I will definitely be able to win every battle.
Although it’s a bit too much.
But I, King Wolffy, am so energetic
He watched all the videos without blinking.
Next up is the Blazing Fire team.
Their captain, Blazey, is a legendary player.
This is Blazey when he was young, what a handsome young man!
The Blazing Fire team truly lives up to its reputation as a representative of team basketball.
They once again won the game through teamwork.
Mutual cooperation and teamwork
I wish our team could play like that.
Wolffy, catch the ball
Let’s go with our dreams.
Leave it to me.
Team basketball
As long as you have the ability
One person is enough
Actually, the team’s winning percentage is still quite high.
With such a strong captain, is it necessary to play team basketball?
If Jonie were to face him…
I’m afraid we’ll lose badly.
What should I do? If this continues, I’ll definitely hold everyone back.
So you were here.
Mr. Slowy.
Jonie, what’s wrong?
He looks really bad.
Mr. Slowy, I’m so worried.
What are you worried about?
I’m currently the least skilled player on the team.
I’m sure we’ll lose to Team Gliders because of me.
I’m afraid of holding everyone back.
Jonie
You definitely didn’t hold everyone back.
Since we started participating in the Basketball Game, we’ve faced so many strong opponents along the way.
At the time, I thought this was an opponent that was impossible to defeat.
But we made it through.
What do we rely on? Technology, experience, and tactics.
We don’t depend on each other.
We depend on each other.
You’re the teammate everyone relies on.
So you must believe in yourself and know that you can do it.
You haven’t shown your true strength yet.
But…didn’t my senior say I would lose badly?
I did say you would lose badly now.
However, as long as you keep practicing according to my method
There will definitely be progress.
You are about to face very tough training.
It might be several times harder than it is now.
Are you scared?
Can I really do it?
You can definitely do it! Our Jonie is our strongest support!
Why are you here?
We don’t trust our Jonie.
Jonie is the most reliable.
Most diligent
strongest
Most stable
Everyone
Why didn’t Jonie tell us what was wrong?
We’re on the same team. We agreed to stand together through thick and thin.
Yeah, don’t keep it all bottled up inside.
We depend on each other.
Sorry, we had a little disagreement.
Even if it’s several times harder, no
For our team, even if it’s a thousand times harder…
I’m not afraid
Thank you all, I will do my best.
With such a great captain, the team has been on a winning streak.
Is it really necessary to play team basketball?
After being elected as the official candidate, I finally had a day off.
Could you spend more time with Wilie?
yes
Wilie, let Daddy take you out to play!
Dad, let’s go play basketball together!
Basketball – that’s Dad’s forte, come on!
Son, isn’t Daddy handsome?
I’m not playing with you anymore, I’m playing with my little silver goat brother.
No, are you having a bad time?
Dad is so good at basketball, I can’t even touch the ball.
Sorry, I get obsessed with basketball.
When I played ball with my brother Goat
My brothers would pass the ball to me.
I even made several shots!
Have you ever won?
Of course, although I’m not tall.
But through passing and teamwork, we won several times.
Son, do you think team basketball is better or individual basketball?
Of course, a good team is better!
One person’s strength is definitely not as great as five people’s.
That’s right, basketball is a team sport.
Cooperate with each other and pass the ball to each other.
One person’s strength is definitely not as great as five people’s.
This is the best way to win the championship.
Thank you, son.
Jonie, do push-ups after you finish running 100 laps.
What
yes
99…100…I can’t take it anymore.
1000, 1001, 1002, 1003, …
500, 501, 502.
Jonie is amazing!
Yes, her training volume is several times that of mine.
Wouldn’t that be too intense?
Jonie, today’s training session was only halfway done.
Speed up
Only half
Is Jonie’s high-intensity training really effective?
Jonie is weak-willed and lacks confidence on the court.
Only through extensive and intensive training can she build confidence.
Become stronger
Even training is done individually.
Everyone, please stop for a moment.
I have a question for everyone.
You guys like one-on-one basketball.
I still prefer basketball where teammates cooperate and pass the ball around.
Why did you suddenly ask this?
Answer me first, which one do you think is better?
If I absolutely had to choose one
I think team basketball is better.
It is easier to win
And even more…happy
Actually, I also think team basketball is pretty good.
I think so too.
Me too
But the captain… he wouldn’t like it.
Leave it to me, I’ll go talk to the captain.
Let him understand the meaning of team basketball, and understand our thoughts.
Wolffy
But will the captain accept the advice?
I have to try.
Mutual cooperation and mutual trust
As long as you play true team basketball
I believe our team will definitely become stronger.
champion
It will definitely be ours.