In the previous episode, we talked about
After Wolffy watched Blazey’s old match footage…
He fell in love with Blazey’s team playstyle
With the support of his son and teammates
Wolffy decided to find an opportunity to share his thoughts with Victor.
On the other hand, Jonie overcame her lack of confidence.
Determined to face the competition
I must have a serious talk with the captain about the team’s problems.
Team… Captain
What’s wrong?
Our team
The court floor was exceptionally clean.
No…no, I meant to say
I cleaned the floor.
Practice more whenever you have time.
I asked you to stay, not to mop the floor.
Wolffy, how can you be such a coward?
What is Wolffy up to now?
Jonie has been working really hard lately!
Not just her
Keep it up, everyone!
good
Slowy may not be good at much else, but he’s certainly raised a group of decent kids.
That goes without saying.
No, what do you mean I can’t?
I’m pretty good at inventing.
It’s raining, kids, let’s go to the lounge.
Let’s play one more ball.
I didn’t know what to say when I saw the captain.
Wolffy, what are you doing?
Is he planning to take over the team again?
No, I just felt
The team should unite, instead of each player acting alone.
We should be more inclined towards team basketball.
I didn’t expect you to consider so much for the team.
But I didn’t dare tell the captain.
I have considered what you said, but the captain has too many ideas of his own.
But you and the captain seem to have a good relationship.
He might listen to what you say.
You support me
Go ahead, as long as it’s for the good of the team.
I will support you.
I also hope the team wins the championship!
eight
Come in quickly!
Coach, playing ball in the rain is a lot of fun!
Paddi
sorry
It was very interesting to see my master playing basketball in the rain.
It’s rare to see a coach smile.
I just remembered someone
Is it Victor?
Slowy
I told them before.
coach
Tell us something about Victor.
When I first met Victor
I knew he was good at playing basketball.
come on.
Come on, let’s continue.
What
Amazing!
Please teach me how to play basketball.
I want to participate in the basketball cup and win the championship.
He is very talented and hardworking.
I used to have a lot of faith in him.
How did you all end up like this?
He felt that he had placed too much faith in team basketball back then.
That’s why they lost an important game.
I have an idea for the team
It can improve our team’s overall strength.
I think what our team lacks most is team unity and cooperation.
I think you might want to pay a little more attention to collaborating with others.
This will also improve the atmosphere within our team.
Then our team will unite into an invincible force.
Basketball is a team sport
As long as we unite, our team’s strength will definitely increase.
enough
Forget about teamwork, as long as I’m strong enough, that’s all that matters.
A victory that can be won on one’s own
There is absolutely no need to rely on a team.
You should focus on improving your own skills.
Teamwork doesn’t mean you don’t need to hone your individual skills.
Wolffy should have a match with the captain.
Can’t we prove who’s right by our own strength?
Sure, Chang Tailang and Yu Tailang can be in your group.
Play a match with me, the first player to score ten goals wins.
good
Since then, Victor’s playing style has become increasingly autocratic.
On the field, he only believes in himself.
Your kind of autocratic basketball style won’t go far.
If I’m strong enough, I can win even carrying four opponents.
Your individual skills are strong, but basketball is a team sport.
I’m tired of hearing it, Master.
I will show you with my strength.
Your idea… is wrong.
This Victor is so stubborn!
I never expected him to view basketball this way.
The captain is very powerful
But there are three of us, so it’s hard to say who will win.
We’ll do our best.
good
Fast defense
The captain is still the captain.
No one can change his mind about basketball.
No one can change his mind about individual basketball.
For him, the team was just a tool to participate in games.
After many years, his skills have indeed improved considerably.
However, individual basketball remains his weak point.
Then he is not invincible.
Wait a minute, our next match is against Team Gliders.
They’re the reigning champions, their strength shouldn’t be below Team Wolves, right?
Should we worry about this first?
Practice well
Let’s consider the upcoming Team Gliders match as a warm-up before the game against Team Wolves.
So, do you still think I’m not strong enough to carry the whole team?
10-0, captain wins
I
I can still fight
Individual ability is everything in basketball, since you don’t agree with my idea…
Then this team no longer needs you.