Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
The Gale’s Breath
In the previous episode,
Wolffy suggested to Victor that they play Blazey’s team basketball.
Who knew Victor would be so resistant?
He proved his individual basketball skills with a one-on-three game.
More powerful than team basketball
When she found that her differences with Victor were irreconcilable
Wolffy had no choice but to accept his fate of leaving the team.
I’m sorry, are you alright?
I’m fine.
Squad leader, your fighting spirit seems to have increased.
That’s amazing!
This is called hooking the hand.
Coach, can you teach me the hook shot?
Any skill takes time to hone.
It’s impossible to learn it in a day or two.
This advanced offensive technique requires at least ten thousand repetitions to master.
10,000 times
However, your primary task now is to continue strengthening your body.
Jonie’s performance was already quite strong.
However, compared to Team Gliders, they are still considerably weaker.
According to statistics, their center Sky Hawk
The success rate in close-range battles can reach 90%.
Ninety percent
Coach, what should I do?
You need special training
This special training will be much more rigorous than previous training sessions.
Are you willing to speak?
I do
Great, the rest of you continue training here.
yes
Coach, where is this place?
Storm Valley
That’s right
Stand still, Jonie
It’s coming!
What’s coming?
Coach, are you alright?
Strong gusts of wind blow in from time to time at the windy spot.
When you can stand firm in this wind like a boulder
That is, when the special training ends
How can I stand firm in a strong wind?
When you are able to pull this boulder here
You’ll be able to stand firm in this strong wind.
Just focus on strength training.
good
How did I get here?
Wolffy, wake up!
You have nothing to do with basketball anymore.
If we win, will we face Team Wolves in the next game?
Wait a minute, why am I hiding?
Go out and say hello.
Isn’t Wolffy on Team Wolves?
Let’s compare
I really look forward to playing against him!
That will definitely be a very exciting match.
But the championship is definitely ours.
Weslie
We can no longer meet on the field.
basketball
This is my ball.
No. I can’t think about basketball anymore.
Hurry to the stadium, the game is about to start.
There’s a Team Wolves game today.
Victor is so handsome
Why is it Victor again?
Oh no, it’s raining!
Go back and collect the laundry.
It was raining just as hard the day the team left.
Stand firm like a boulder
I won’t give up easily.
Captain, what is that goat doing in Storm Valley?
How should I know? Who cares?
Again
It moved
you…
Do you still want to go back to Team Wolves to play basketball?
Can I still go back to the team and play basketball?
If you agree with my approach, please come back for training tomorrow morning.
Keep up the good work, Tian!
She’s still practicing? Why don’t we go help her?
Let’s begin.
Why do I feel like I’ve gotten heavier?
What’s wrong, little goat? Can’t you pull it anymore?
It’s you guys
Will it open? Will you be surprised? Will you be unexpected?
You are interfering with my training, please come down immediately.
How is this hindering your training? It’s helping you increase the weight.
Don’t go too far, get down here right now.
Don’t waste your energy; you can’t possibly move it.
With that kind of strength, you might as well go home and play house.
What
effort
I want to succeed
I will succeed.
You’re so happy about such a small thing, don’t get cocky.
You still can’t beat me in a match.
I wonder how Jonie’s training is going.
With Jonie working so hard, there’s definitely no problem.
That is
Jonie
This is
What a strong wind!
Jonie
They actually stood in the wind and withstood it! That’s amazing!
How did you do that?
Nothing much, just constant training.
I knew Jonie could do it.
nice shot
Why hasn’t the captain started training yet?
Wolffy, are you back?
Have you thought it through?
Thank you for giving me this opportunity
but.
I still think team basketball suits me better.
Wolffy
The captain has gone to great lengths to give you this opportunity, so please stay.
Keep up the good work, everyone!
I hope we’ll have another chance to play basketball together in the future.
Thank you
Let’s start training.
To be continued…