In the previous episode, how Jonie wanted to improve her physical fitness.
Blazey took him to Storm Valley for special training.
Although they encountered interference and ridicule from Ying Aotian along the way.
But Jonie persisted.
Successfully withstood strong winds and completed the training.
The match is about to begin
The winner of this competition will qualify for the semifinals.
Tonight’s performer is…
The formidable defending champions, Team Gliders
And then there’s this year’s dark horse, Team Defenders.
Go Team Defenders!
You’d better watch out, Team Gliders are your opponents in the finals.
Team Defenders, they seem to have never lost.
But their opponent in this match is Team Gliders, and Team Defenders are bound to lose.
Team Defenders will win!
Why aren’t you sitting with your teammates?
Since I rarely have time, I’ll watch it with you.
I want to see Dad perform live this time too.
Next, I’ll show you what a true powerhouse is.
So high!
We are the rulers of the skies, not like you little lambs (goats).
Fast defense
Before Team Defenders could react, Team Gliders had already scored the first goal.
Speed! So fast!
It’s alright.
Next ball, we’ll take it back.
Such strong willpower
team leader
I won’t give you the past.
Do you think you can stop me?
I must
Stop you
My God, Jonie is completely outmatched by Sky Hawk.
Is this the strength of the previous champion?
You… are absolutely pathetic.
What gives you the right to say that about Jonie?
Don’t get me wrong, I’m not targeting Jonie.
To be precise, it should be said that Team Defenders is absolutely terrible.
Squad leader 1, hurry back to defense
The score suddenly widened to 20 points.
This is practically a Team Gliders exhibition match!
Request to pause
Game paused
Our
The gap in strength is too big.
It’s impossible to defend against.
It’s all my fault
Jonie
We’re still a bit short of breaking up with him.
Why are you suddenly saying such discouraging things?
If we’re talking about effort, you’re definitely not inferior to them.
All that hard training you guys put in was for this day, wasn’t it?
You guys worked so hard, you’re no worse than Team Gliders.
We must have confidence
We’ve come this far.
Don’t be discouraged. Believe in yourself.
Jonie, you’re our guardian angel under the basket!
Believe in yourself
Team Defenders are the best! Go for it!
Go Team Defenders!
We’ll do our best.
Everyone trusts you, so don’t let them down!
I need to believe in myself
Let’s go
good…
Team Gliders is completely useless for this kind of team; I really want to go back!
Then let’s go back.
Auntie, who are you?
Team Defenders’ beautiful cheerleading captain
It’s so noisy
Team Defenders will definitely catch up.
How can they possibly catch up when they’re so weak?
Keep reading and you’ll find out.
Weslie, we can’t lose!
That’s so boring.
Too easy
What
They blocked my shot!
I won’t let you score so easily again.
Conquer those who doubt you with your abilities!
That’s right, we
You need to prove yourself with your own abilities.
Jonie, well done!
Quickly return to defense
Team Defenders finally broke their scoring drought.
Well done!
marvelous
Not bad luck!
This is not luck; it is the result of our collective efforts.
Team Defenders’ center exploded, and Team Gliders couldn’t score a single point.
Your defense is indeed quite good; you were able to stop us.
That’s something to praise you for.
But you’re still a bit short of being able to defend against me.
He’s so strong!
She can’t stop our captain; our captain is finally getting serious.
You are our guardian angel under the basket, believe in yourself.
I want
Keep an eye on you
What
It’s impossible to squeeze through.
I can’t believe it!
Jonie actually managed to stop the strongest center, Sky Hawk.
Impressive… Keep him in check.
Can you defend against me?
Good heavens, even Sky Hawk got blocked by Jonie!
Team Defenders scored again.
Give me the ball, I’ll deal with her.
Don’t get too cocky after scoring one or two goals.
We are the defending champions.
That’s where you stop.
X
Sky Hawk actually fell to the ground.
Good shot! Jonie actually figured that out.
Sky Hawk actually fell down.
I really can’t believe it.
How embarrassing!
What a disgrace, the championship team is now in decline.
Are they capable? Seriously, are they capable?
Ying Aotian, are you alright?
No matter what, I will protect myself from you.
It’s a tie.
How can Team Gliders break this deadlock?
I admit you have some talent.
but
Not enough to defeat me
Wow, so fast!
This is terrifying! Sky Hawk is finally getting serious.
Is this the true strength of the previous champion?