In the previous episode, we discussed how Team Gliders overwhelmingly possessed superior talent.
The goats are facing a critical situation in their inside defense.
Under Blazey’s guidance
Jonie finally resolved her inner conflict and gave it her all.
Team Defenders launched a counterattack.
While everyone was celebrating the comeback…
It turned out that Team Gliders hadn’t even used their full strength.
come on
I’ll protect Team Defenders’ rim.
By your
So fast…
This is the difference between us.
I am at a height that ordinary people like you can never reach.
Team Gliders are just too strong!
Look, everyone, he’s about to attack again.
Sky Hawk quickly broke through Team Defenders’ layers of defense.
He also hit a beautiful three-pointer.
Entered
Awesome! Sky Hawk is so cool!
I think Sky Hawk alone could easily crush them.
Basketball is about teamwork and tactics.
The Goat team called another timeout.
I’m sorry, I still can’t defend against my opponent.
It’s okay, you’ve done very well.
So how can we defend against them?
Since we can’t defend, let’s intensify our offense.
yes…
12 points behind, keep going!
I think Team Gliders are destined to win.
Yes, the goat is too weak.
The whole team couldn’t stop our Ying Aotian.
The goats are very strong too; they won’t lose!
The goats will definitely win!
You need to disrupt Team Gliders’ rhythm with your passing.
I saw through it long ago; you were going to pass it on to Weslie.
nice shot
It seems Team Defenders have intensified their offensive efforts.
It’s Team Gliders’ turn to attack.
You think you can get my ball?
You won’t have a chance.
What
You will increase the intensity of your attack.
Won’t we step up our defense? Naive.
Tibbie didn’t even dare to pass the ball.
Are you playing Eagle Catches Chickens?
We don’t have time for that.
Where’s the ball?
Team Gliders are extremely adaptable.
Tibbie, you need to be more discreet with your passes.
Sparky needs to be ready to provide support at any time.
After receiving the ball, he quickly drove in and used a back-to-the-basket move to break through to the inside.
Sparky scored!
Sparky, you’re awesome! Keep it up!
These are just trivial tricks; victory will surely be ours.
yes…
Team Gliders actually started a two-man attack.
This is
Team Gliders score another goal.
Oh no!
I won’t let you pass.
Team Gliders intercepted the ball again and passed it to their teammate.
Oops
Hey little guy, if you dare to shoot, I’ll dare to block you.
I’m not afraid of you.
My goodness, that was an incredibly difficult shot by Paddi!
Team Defenders take another three points.
Don’t underestimate us, we won’t lose.
Based on you guys
Well done, keep it up, little sheep (goats)!
Minato only made one shot, is it really necessary to get so excited?
Go Team Defenders!
That was brilliant! Team Defenders’ ingenious tactical deployment!
Their adaptability is on par with Team Gliders.
Team Gliders were unable to pull away from the score.
This is Team Gliders’ first appearance in this competition.
An unprecedented crisis!
See? I told you so.
Basketball is about teamwork and tactics.
Dama is amazing! She got everything right.
In a real match, it all comes down to the ability of the star players.
With just one minute left in the first half, let’s use that move to completely crush them!
What
Full of loopholes
You’re all just so-so.
You guys have only gotten this far thanks to luck, right?
It seems Tibbie has become more cautious after the previous round of matches.
Sparky passed the ball to Weslie
Sky Hawk executed a free interception, passing the shuttlecock to his teammate.
Team Gliders team up again to score.
Go Team Defenders!
Finished
You need to think of a solution quickly!
Team Gliders used White Feather Intercept.
If Team Defenders can’t come up with a way to check and balance things…
Then the outcome of the match will likely be a foregone conclusion.
How can we play like this? We get intercepted every time we attack.
Little goats, you won’t fall down so easily.
Wolffy
Quickly show your usual spirit!
I will not allow you to lose any game.
Wolffy
Did I say we would lose?
Do you really want to study overload?
Yes, I want to help the team win.
Overloading requires forcing all your organs, muscles, and bones to work harder.
Nerves, and even all cells, participate in breathing together.
This is the only way to unleash the body’s potential in a short period of time.
Maximize efficiency and increase speed
Too fast
Overload
How could he know Leopardess (elder)’s special move?
This is Leopardess (elder)’s famous move, Overload.
Unexpectedly, Weslie actually used Leopardess (elder)’s signature move.
Weslie
Stay calm, we can
Win
16 points remaining
Don’t even think about the past.
Weslie’s overload was unstoppable.
His speed increased faster and faster, seemingly without limit.
Be careful when using overload; do not use for extended periods.
Otherwise, it will cause irreversible damage to the body.
As long as it helps the team win
Everything, all of it.
not give a darn about
That was amazing! Weslie scored 16 points in just one minute!
Now, the gap is only five points.
Weslie, you’re amazing!
Are you alright, Weslie?
It’s okay, we’ve caught up.
a 18
Great, you’ve got the chance to witness the strongest Team Gliders!