Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
One Guarding the Hoop
In the previous episode,
The goats gradually adapted to the game and began to catch up.
But Team Gliders used their superior wingspan to suppress the goats.
The score widened again.
Weslie had to resort to the overload dribbling technique he learned from Leopardess (younger) to tie the score.
Shocking the entire audience
The two sides clashed fiercely in the second half.
Several minutes had passed, and the two sides continued to chase each other.
The match was absolutely amazing!
Weslie, conserve your energy first.
Weslie was also very tired.
Weslie probably won’t use that overload again.
Next comes our counterattack.
Let’s all recover our strength first.
yes
We are still in the lead and looking for opportunities to widen the gap.
Oh no!
Don’t let your guard down, get back on defense quickly!
Don’t be scared by him, keep the counterattack!
Watch me
Their defense was too tight; we couldn’t score at all.
How can we fight like this?
What should I do?
Blazey, hurry up and think of a way to turn things around!
The Hawks’ defense was like an impenetrable iron wall, almost impossible to break through.
unless…
Unless something
Give me the ball.
Squad Leader
Believe me
With your talent
Even if you throw a hundred times, you still won’t be able to make it.
With effort, nothing is impossible.
Unless she can hook her hand
Only a hook shot can get over that high defensive wall.
1002, 1003, 1004, 1005, 1006…
10000. .
Still not proficient
Why is the hit rate so low?
No, I can’t give up yet.
10001, 10002.
10,000…03
Jonie actually broke through Sky Hawk’s defense.
I didn’t expect you to have a trick up your sleeve.
Jonie, you’re amazing!
Squad leader, I want to learn your move too!
To have mastered the hook hand in such a short time
Jonie is such a hardworking kid.
Sometimes hard work is more important than talent.
CV CV CV CV CV CV CV CV CV
The goats cooperated really well!
Stop her quickly!
Jonie’s hook shot opened up the game, and the score was finally caught up.
The show is about to begin.
This tactic was originally intended for the finals.
Now I can only show you in advance.
I said, how can we fight like this?
This is indeed impossible to fight.
Quickly return to defense
Luckily, I held back, otherwise I would have smashed the rim.
See? That’s the difference between you and me.
Who would dare to block Sky Hawk’s attack?
team leader
I can definitely do it.
Keep an eye on you
No matter how many people come, the result will be the same.
Unable to defend
Blazey, Jonie is injured again.
Call a timeout!
Wait a minute.
I promised everyone I would protect the basket.
so
I will protect myself from you no matter what.
Squad Leader
Overestimating one’s abilities
Jonie
Squad Leader
Even so, I will not give up.
Okay, then I won’t hold back either.
That was brutal! Team Gliders’ dunks were like cannonballs!
It looks painful!
Squad leader, are you alright?
It’s okay, I can still block it.
I, as center
You must protect the team’s defense until the very last second.
Knowing you can’t beat me, why are you still making these futile struggles?
Because I believe that even the weakest person can create a miracle of their own.
Although Team Gliders were leading by a large margin
But Team Defenders showed no signs of giving up.
Who will emerge victorious in this match?
How ridiculous! I’ll prove you wrong.
The weak are always weak; they can never turn their lives around.
No, even for an ordinary person like me.
They also have the right to touch the sky.
It was blocked.
impossible
Based on you
What
My goodness, Jonie is even weaker than Sky Hawk!
They actually managed to stop Ying Aotian’s domineering and invincible dunk.
Keep it up!
It’s simply a miracle on the field.
However, Team Defenders doesn’t have much time left.
There is still a ten-point difference.
Weslie, it’s all up to you.
To be continued…