Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Buzzer Beating Overload
In the previous episode, Jonie using a hook hand.
Forcing Sky Hawk to use his strongest killing move
Eagle Soars Through the Sky and Dunks
None of Team Defenders were able to intercept it.
The score was quickly widened
In the end, Jonie stepped forward.
He used perseverance to block Sky Hawk’s ultimate move.
But there was only one minute left in the game.
Give up, you’re destined to lose.
It appeared again.
Weslie once again unleashed a high-risk overload.
This move is simply invincible.
This kind of overload will lead to physical exhaustion.
If you continue using it, you will definitely get hurt.
Weslie, be careful, don’t get hurt.
Pause, Pause
Blazey, we’ve used up all our timeouts.
Weslie
Don’t use overload again.
Did you hear me?
incredible
Weslie under overload conditions
10 points in 30 seconds
A single player equalized the score.
Team Gliders were caught off guard
Weslie, are you okay?
No problem, this match
We will definitely win.
good…
We actually ended up playing against such a weak Goat Clan.
To this extent
It’s a disgrace!
Captain, are we going to lose this time?
What did you say?
Remember this: we are the reigning champions.
We must uphold the dignity of the champion.
After all, they were the previous champions.
How could they willingly let Team Defenders overpower them and launch a counterattack?
Stop them!
Sky Hawk unleashed his most powerful move once again.
Eagle Soars Through the Sky and Dunks
Does Team Defenders still have a chance to turn things around?
This is infuriating! They’re using this trick again!
There’s simply no way to defend against it.
Team Gliders actually ganged up on Weslie!
Only 15 seconds left, give up.
Can Weslie break through?
Weslie, Weslie
Never give up
Weslie
Want to pass the ball?
Hurry, stop him!
Wait a moment
overload
Overloaded, overloaded again.
Weslie scores another crucial goal
The two sides tied again.
With only 10 seconds left in the game…
We can’t let him use the Eagle Soaring Through the Sky…
Oh no…
The championship is ours
Two points, leading by two points again.
There are only 6 seconds left.
How should Team Defenders respond?
With only 6 seconds left, did they win the final blow?
Weslie’s three-point shooting was inconsistent.
So even if this ball goes in…
The score can only be tied at best, leading to overtime.
If it goes into overtime
Weslie certainly didn’t have the strength to exert himself beyond his limits.
It seems the scales of victory are in play.
I’m slowly leaning towards Team Gliders
Team Defenders will win.
Start of timer
Only 5 seconds left
Which team will win?
I vouch for this with the honor of Team Gliders.
This time I will definitely stop you.
Foul, now it’s a tie.
Team Defenders take the free throw.
The final goal decided the game; who would have thought?
Weslie
Weslie, how’s your foot?
I’m fine.
stretcher, stretcher
I…
You can also take this free throw.
But you now… I think…
I want to persevere to the end.
All right
We must get in
Go in…
You absolutely must get in…
We won…
Awesome…
Awesome… Amazing…
Team Defenders is truly remarkable.
I never expected these goats.
Such a wonderful match can be played.
No one will ever say we Goat Clan again.
I can’t play basketball anymore.
Surprisingly, the goats were the ones who ultimately won.
You were right before.
Your next opponent is here.
But not Team Gliders
Our Green Green Grassland Team Defenders
Team Defenders
Awesome… Great…
So what if we win now?
Let’s see how long they can be happy.
Everyone hurry back and continue practicing.
Well done, Team Defenders played well…
team leader
What a disgrace!
I, the king, actually lost to those little sheep (goats)!
Awesome…
let’s go
The next championship will definitely belong to us.
Weslie…
We won…we won!
I never expected we could beat the defending champions.
Beautiful pitch, Weslie
Everyone played very well.
By the way, Weslie, is your foot alright?
Should we have Mr. Slowy check it?
I’m fine.
A rest should fix it.
Let’s go find the coach.
Coach, Mr. Slowy, we won…
Our Team Defenders is truly amazing!
What’s the point of winning?
If you don’t listen to the coach’s instructions next time
Don’t even think about playing.
knew
But Weslie
I also want to say sorry to you.
I’m such a bad coach.
Actually, I know perfectly well that you’re in danger if you continue like this.
But deep down I still don’t want to replace you.
because…
I’m so eager to see you win this game.
coach
Thank you
Now that you’ve won the game, stop wearing that long face.
Weslie, how’s your foot?
It seems like nothing serious, just need some rest.
Congratulations, Team Defenders!
Wolffy, you’ve arrived? How are you?
Goat brother and goat sister are so amazing!
Weslie, are you sure your foot is okay?
I saw you were working really hard just now.
Because we said we’d meet in the finals, right?
Actually, I…
Weslie, please sign your name…
I’m your fan, can I get an autograph?
Let’s go first and get our autographs.
Weslie Wolffy, etc.
Please sign your name.
Weslie
let me see
It must be due to overloading, resulting in excessive burden.
This resulted in a foot injury.
To be continued…