Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
The Disappearance of Wolffy
In the previous episode,
Despite the physical strain and Blazey’s objections, Weslie disregarded the pressure his body could withstand.
Using an overloaded finishing move to defeat the defending champion
Weslie’s foot injury worsened as a result.
Wolffy sent his congratulations on advancing to the next round.
He also never managed to tell Weslie and his family about his departure from the team.
Wolffy, why aren’t you at team practice yet?
I’ll help you clean.
I cleaned it yesterday.
I’ll go make you breakfast.
It’s cooking, it’ll be ready to eat in a bit.
Oh right, clothes
Didn’t you see me coming down with the basket of clothes?
What’s wrong with you, Wolffy?
Actually, I
I’ve been kicked out of Team Wolves.
What
What happened?
So… I no longer have the chance to participate in basketball games.
I knew a long time ago that there was no point in staying on that lousy team.
It’s better this way.
Wolnie, you’re so kind.
This way you’ll have more time to do housework.
Didn’t you finish everything?
I haven’t bought my lunch groceries yet.
dad
What are you doing here?
Don’t we have to train today?
Even the team’s star players need rest.
Wilie, how can you be so dirty?
This is a secret; I want to give Dad a surprise.
My dad is the best basketball player.
Even with a leg injury, I can still practice shooting.
Sparky
Didn’t Mr. Slowy and the others tell you to get some rest?
You need to rest well and avoid strenuous exercise.
Otherwise, if the injury worsens, he won’t be able to play anymore.
It’s fine
I just need to be careful.
Doing some simple exercises is not a problem.
No, I really
Wait a minute, can’t I even drink juice because of a leg injury?
I just really wanted a drink.
How come you guys don’t have time to train?
Yes, I want to, but I know you definitely won’t obediently rest.
That’s why we came to see you.
You’re worrying too much.
See how perfectly fine I am? I’m so agile!
Are you alright?
Nothing’s wrong, I was just kidding.
Alright, you guys go train now.
I’ll be able to rejoin the team soon.
Then don’t push yourself too hard, get some rest.
Got it. You guys keep it up too!
Don’t worry, we know you’ll be bored.
We’ll come back and play with you after training.
We’re leaving now.
Thank you
Wolffy
Weslie, what brings you to call me?
No training today?
Actually, I
I want to ask you about what you said to me after the game yesterday.
I
Why are you taking things from other people’s baskets?
You haven’t even paid yet!
Stealing the ball is one of my strengths.
Broccoli Special Price
Sorry Weslie, I’m busy right now.
Let’s talk later.
Positioning is also one of my strengths.
This wolf is behaving strangely, trying to steal the ball and block positions.
I thought this was a basketball court.
I also need to buy canned grass and paper towels.
Don’t even think about scoring.
Get out!
People are so excited right now!
I still want to play basketball.
We need people like you who are interested in basketball.
Why is there a hand here?
Hello, I’m the robot scout from the Cosmic Carnival.
I see you have extraordinary talent; you must be a basketball prodigy.
Machine Scout
0-1
That’s right
Do scouts still use machines?
0-1
I just saw it.
What did you see?
I saw you snatch a Dama apple with one hand in the store.
Block Dama’s position and take the last broccoli.
The shop assistant is arranging the merchandise while wearing a hat.
I’d like to invite you to our Super Universe Cup.
Super Universe Cup
Our Super Universe Cup is even better than the Grassland Basketball Game!
People from all over the universe are vying to participate.
Come and become a dazzling basketball star!
Basketball captain
Where are you? Come back soon!
Wilie is looking for you.
Okay… I’ll be right back.
Excuse me, I have to go home now.
Handsome guy, think about it.
It’s free!
Just go to the address on the flyer to register.
Okay, I’ll think about it.
8-1
Dad, you’re back.
Look what I did for you
Why did Wilie make a flag?
When Dad becomes the team’s star player
I’ll wave this flag and cheer you on.
Go Dad!
It’s broken, what should I do?
It’s okay, Wilie, Daddy is already very happy.
No, I want to use it to cheer up my dad.
It’s alright, Wilie.
Dad will no longer be a star basketball player.
Why? Dad is working so hard, he can definitely do it!
I’m sorry, Dad lied to you.
Dad is no longer a star basketball player.
There’s no way I can participate in this year’s Basketball Game.
My dad is a big liar.
It’s okay, Wilie will understand.
I’m fine, you should go check on Wilie.
Dad is a big liar
flyers
If you lead your team to victory in front of the whole world
What an exciting scene!
By the way, as long as you participate in the Super Universe Cup
I can stand in front of everyone again and lead the team.
Why is the training camp so difficult to navigate?
Dad is a big liar
I can’t give up like this.
I must become no matter what.
Basketball star
Is this… the training base for the Super Universe Cup?
This isn’t luxurious at all; this is just a scam!
I want to go back
Don’t go, I didn’t lie to you.
You can have anything in your dreams.
To be continued…