In the previous episode,
Although Wolffy has left Team Wolves and no longer plays basketball
In his personal life, Wolffy never forgets basketball.
And he inadvertently let Wilie know about his departure from the team.
To avoid disappointing Wilie
Wolffy decides to risk joining a bizarre basketball training session.
Why isn’t Wolffy answering the phone?
Wolffy, you finally answered the phone.
The grassland hobby class is now recruiting!
Music, chess, calligraphy, painting, swimming, and fitness – learn more!
No need, thank you.
Where did Wolffy go?
Players confirmed to be missing include San Shu, Point Guard (Rabbit Team), and Small Forward (Cheetah Team).
Big Humphrey is conducting a thorough investigation; all players are advised to take precautions to protect themselves.
Missing
Who ambushed me?
Where am I?
combination lock
Incorrect password
Is anyone there?
Experimental subject enters program start
What sound?
Welcome to the Super Shooting Room
You can pass the level by hitting 50 balls within 5 minutes.
Is passing this enough to complete the training?
Yes, then let the training begin.
I’m not ready yet.
A penalty will be imposed for failing the challenge.
CU
There are also punishments
The challenge continues
Why are we still fighting wolves?
UCCU
CUUUU
C
UCCU
Increase difficulty
You’ve passed the test now, right?
CCCCC
Congratulations on advancing to the second level!
Are you kidding me? And…
You can pass the level by hitting 50 balls within 5 minutes.
The basket is moving, right? Okay.
Wolffy
Surprised? Unexpected?
It’s me again. The grassland hobby class is now recruiting!
Learn about music, chess, calligraphy, painting, swimming, and fitness.
No need, thank you.
Weslie’s brother
What’s wrong with you? You all look so worried.
Wolffy hasn’t been home since yesterday.
Have you seen him?
No, I can’t find him either.
You’ve never seen him
Repeat broadcast
There have been several cases of players going missing since then.
Please try to avoid going out.
Could it be…?
Could Wolffy have disappeared too?
No, I have to go find him.
But everyone says your foot is injured.
It’s all better now. As long as you don’t do anything too strenuous, it’ll be fine.
Is Dad angry with me and doesn’t want to see me?
No, something must have delayed it.
Let’s go look for it together.
Have you ever seen Wolffy?
I’ll go look over there.
What’s wrong, Wilie?
Brother Weslie, can I ask you a question?
Go ahead and ask.
What kind of wolf do you think my dad is?
Your father is a very, very powerful wolf.
Is it really that amazing?
certainly
He put in a lot of effort to play basketball well.
The first to arrive at the basketball training court each day, and the last to leave.
real
Team Wolves used to recruit so many reserve players.
But only your father can become a regular player.
That’s not impressive enough!
Wow, my dad is so amazing!
What’s wrong
But that’s what I said about him.
Dad is a big liar
Dad must be angry with me, that’s why he’s not coming back.
Dad won’t be angry with you.
Because you are the driving force behind his lifelong efforts and struggles.
Um… Brother Weslie, could you do me a favor?
What’s going on?
I think… if you find my dad
Could you apologize to me?
I will help you find your father.
But you have to apologize to your father yourself.
But
Wilie, you should be like your father.
Be a man. You know that?
There isn’t one there either.
Let’s look in the next place.
Be careful!
Thanks
Let’s go
Hey kid, I’m the robot scout from the Cosmic Basketball Carnival.
I see you have extraordinary talent; you must be a basketball prodigy.
Come join the Super Universe Cup!
No…we have urgent business.
By the way
Have you seen this wolf?
this…
have
No
What should we do? We even made plans to participate in the Cosmic Cup together!
I can’t find him now, so I can’t participate.
He has already registered.
Sure enough, Wolffy is with you.
Where did you take Wolffy?
Hand it over quickly
stop
Can’t you give me some robots that are a little smarter?
Congratulations on reaching level 5!
How many levels are left?
While avoiding basketball interference
You can pass the level by hitting 50 balls within 5 minutes.
Only now are you saying this?
Do you think I’m afraid?
Don’t underestimate me, I’m serious now.
This is going too far, I’m getting serious.
As expected of me
It’s alright.
Faster
That’s it.
This King/Majety is so amazing, this training is nothing special.
Let me out!
Congratulations on passing level 5! The final level is coming up.
We’ve reached the final hurdle; we can finally leave!
Where is the basketball hoop?
stop
Activate emergency procedures
He was right ahead, chase after him.
Weslie Weslie’s brother
Fortunately, I have experience.
How could there be a trap here?
It must have been a setup by those who arrested Wolffy.
Is Dad in danger? I need to save Dad.
Danger
This place is too dangerous.
I’ll handle the rest of the journey; you all wait for me here.
But I also want to save my dad.
Wolffy will be even more worried if you get injured again.
Thank you, Weslie
Let’s leave this to the handsome Goat (or Happy Sheep)!
But
I promise you, I will definitely bring your father back.
Then I’ll leave it to you.
Where is the strange person?
You just ran here!