Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
The Black Training Base
In the previous episode, Wolffy went missing.
Weslie, along with Wolfie and her son, set off to search for Wolffy.
During this time, I encountered a person with strange behavior.
Upon further investigation, Weslie suspected that this person was connected to Wolffy’s disappearance.
Weslie single-handedly ventured into the heart of the enemy’s den.
UH
Welcome!
What are you doing?
No, nothing.
Why were you running so fast?
I’m in a hurry to get back and charge my phone.
Tell me quickly, where is Wolffy?
Since he’s found out, let him in.
He’s inside, come with me.
There’s even a basement!
Being so secretive, there’s definitely something wrong.
Why make such a fuss about something as simple as training?
Our training content is all classified.
Therefore, the confidentiality work was done very well.
All right
Come on, I’ll take you down to see.
Where is the basketball hoop?
This is the final level, so please don’t cheat!
Can’t you see me anymore?
You’re so weak.
You come out here right now!
I’ve always been here.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Please look more carefully.
No way!
So fast!
You need to make 50 shots within 5 minutes to pass the level.
Challenge begins
Is this still basketball training?
This is never going to end! It’s impossible to finish!
When Dad becomes a star basketball player, I’ll wave the flag and cheer for you like this.
How could I give up so easily?
Bring it on!
I’ve got you!
That Wolffy is really cunning.
Weslie, we’ve come to see you.
Weslie
It seems like he’s not here.
The TV is still on, where did he go?
They must have gone to buy food; it’s time to eat by now.
You think it’s you?
It would be terrible if his leg injury flared up again while he was away. We should go find him.
I couldn’t find Weslie.
Me too
Where to go?
broadcast again
Recently, several basketball players from Green Green Grassland have mysteriously disappeared.
The players who have been confirmed missing are:
San Shu, Rabbit Team Point Guard, Leopard Team Small Forward, etc.
Big Humphrey has launched an investigation; all players are advised to take precautions to protect themselves.
They are all missing.
how so
Weslie suddenly disappeared, could it be…?
Let’s go tell the coach!
Can I train with Wolffy?
no
Can I say hello to him?
All right
There’s definitely a problem.
Help!
What is that sound?
It’s normal to hear some screams at the training base.
Everyone is training hard.
Are these… cameras?
Please enter your password.
What happened?
Is there anything wrong?
You can train here first.
You’ll be allowed to leave after training.
CC clc
C Okay C c
We need to leave here as soon as possible to find Wolffy.
I just saw the password is 052, what’s the other one?
Never mind, let’s give it a try.
Incorrect password
Reaction test begins
What’s going on? Is this what the robot meant by training?
C 010 C
Incorrect password
What is this?
7 or 5…
Never mind
That was close!
Alarm - Experimental Subject Escape
Now you know how powerful I am!
Violation…
The basket broke the rule first.
The challenger failed to pass the challenge due to using illegal methods.
Accept Hell Mode Punishment
Punishment and Hell Mode
I don’t want to train anymore, and I don’t want to participate in any more Cosmic Cups.
Let me out
This password… could it be my birthday?
Incorrect password
Seriously? It’s not even the protagonist’s birthday.
What is the password?
Alarm - Experimental Subject Escape
What? You can escape without even opening the door?
The machine suddenly stopped.
Training Conclusion
Wasn’t the training all over?
The experimental subject has escaped; the destruction operation is now underway.
What
That’s too cruel!
Can’t fall here
Wolnie and Wilie are still waiting for me.
What
You must hang in there!
Wolffy, where are you?
Weslie, I’m here.
Experimental subject escapes, triggering destruction procedure.
These weren’t cameras, they were laser pointers.
Weslie, I’m here.
Wolffy
Wolffy, hang in there!
I’m coming to save you right away.
Wolffy
guard
not good
Weslie
I knew you would come to save me
Wilie and Wolnie are also very worried about you.
They were the ones who told me you were missing.
Wilie
How are your feet?
I was injured in the last game.
Therefore, strenuous running is not allowed now.
Then why did you come to save me?
We’re friends, right?
To be continued…