In the previous episode, we talked about
Wolffy undergoes all sorts of strange special training at the robot training base.
Even left him covered in wounds
Wolffy realized this was no longer training.
Weslie arrived at the moment of danger.
Wolffy was rescued in time
Weslie
I’m fine, let’s go.
No, what if you get hurt again?
What are you going to do about your next match?
You call for me
How can a wolf fight for a goat? Don’t be ridiculous.
Come on, I’ll run for you.
But please, whatever you do, don’t get hurt again.
Once you go through that door, those annoying lasers will be gone.
Oh no, the door is about to close!
What should we do now?
That’s all we can do.
Are you sure you can get through like this?
Dingxing
Are you ready?
3 jumps
My back!
At your age, what are you doing?
Weslie’s foot was injured, and so was yours.
I’ll have to step in for the next game.
You can’t do it.
Then I’ll find someone who can replace me.
I’m looking for someone who can replace Weslie.
The final piece of the puzzle for the championship team
Must possess technical skills, perseverance, and a spirit of teamwork.
Can you find it?
this
There doesn’t seem to be anyone like that in the Goat Clan.
Goat Clan
Now we can only hope that Weslie recovers quickly.
village head
Weslie is missing.
The exit is on the left.
Is anyone outside? Help!
Help!
Great, we’re finally saved!
You are a member of the Wild Boar team.
He was the person who went missing in the television reports.
Let’s get out of here quickly.
But there are still people trapped in other rooms.
We need to hurry and rescue them!
Everyone, keep up!
We haven’t collaborated like this in a long time.
Yes, it feels great to fight alongside you.
The exit is just ahead.
Oh no!
this
We are trapped
Open the door! Open the door!
Let me out
Let me out, help!
It seems we won’t be able to get out anytime soon.
It’s better not to go, anyway, I don’t have the courage to face Wolnie and Willie.
Wolffy
I’ve never accomplished anything significant.
This Basketball Game
I truly feel proud to be the captain of the team and make my family proud.
But I still disappointed them.
If you find my dad
Could you apologize to me?
No, Willie asked me to pass on a message to you.
What did he say?
You should go out and ask him yourself.
This is terrible.
Are you alright?
I have a solution.
Darn it, they’ve figured out our plan.
It’s okay, the iron plate is already bent.
Everyone, if you want to get out, let’s work together!
good…
S SSL
twenty three
12, 3
1, 2, 3
Free
Our turn
Here we go again.
Mom, be careful.
I never imagined picking apples could be so difficult.
Come, give it to me
Dad usually picks them.
Don’t worry, Weslie will definitely find Dad.
You can apologize to him then.
Wolffy’s father
It’s you guys
It turns out Weslie was helping to find the missing Wolffy.
This is too reckless. Couldn’t you have told us first if there was anything wrong?
What if he injures his foot again and suffers any long-term effects?
Let’s find them first.
But where would they be?
Everyone run!
They are people from the missing persons list.
Have you ever seen Wolffy and Weslie?
They were the two who saved us.
What about them?
It’s in the back.
Strange, they should have followed.
Could he still be inside?
The basketball turned into a bomb.
We can’t hold out for long if things continue like this.
here we go again
Weslie, throw the basketball away!
It turns out that these basketballs explode with a delayed effect after being caught.
Also, before each attack
This monitor will move slightly.
Based on my many years of invention experience
This monitor is likely its switch.
As long as we destroy it
It seems you were right.
How about we play a game of basketball right now?
good
It’s all blocked inside.
Everyone, push it away!
Wait, let’s use the X-ray vision device to check the situation inside first.
Weslie
It’s Dad
nice shot
Dad Wolffy
how
Wilie, Wolnie
finally found you
dad
Wilie, I’m sorry
Your father lied to you.
No, it’s my fault for being angry with you.
Actually, from the very beginning, my dad has always been the best basketball player in my heart.
Wilie
Never get proper rest
If your foot injury gets worse, who will replace you in the next game?
I have found the most suitable substitute.
who
Wolffy
I
Wolnie told me you’ve left Team Wolves.
Would you like to come and be the star basketball player for the Goat Team?
But I am a wolf.
Can I play for the Goat Team?
I don’t remember the Basketball Game rules saying anything about not being able to.
dad
As the captain of Team Goat, I welcome you on behalf of Team Goat.
Everyone
Okay, let’s work together!
We’ll see each other on the field again.
Go back