As mentioned in the previous episode, because Weslie was injured…
Blazey is looking for a new player for the Goat team but can’t find a suitable candidate.
On the other side, Weslie and Wolffy worked together seamlessly.
The puzzle was solved using a basketball.
Blazey witnessed this and confirmed Wolffy as the new member of Team Goat.
The highly anticipated semi-finals are about to begin.
The athletes are making their final preparations for the competition.
Please wait and see.
Why can’t I play?
In the last game you didn’t listen to the coach’s instructions
Insisting on using excessive force and causing injury to oneself
The suspension is your punishment
Weslie
Weslie, you almost aggravated your foot injury while trying to save me.
Just think of it as taking a break.
Both teams that are about to play have finished warming up.
The winner will compete for this year’s championship throne.
Team Defenders’ Weslie was surprisingly on the bench.
Which goat will take his place?
It’s not a goat, it’s King Wolffy.
Dad, keep going!
What’s going on?
A wolf joining the sheep (goat) team? That’s unheard of!
Could that wolf have joined the sheep (goat) team because it couldn’t find a team?
You guys are talking too much. Focus on watching the game.
It seems Wolffy has chosen to betray Team Wolves after all.
It seems that having wolves and goats on the same team has caused quite a bit of controversy.
But without further ado, let’s welcome…
The robot team makes its appearance
really
This…this isn’t the place that arrested me.
Ball scout?
They turned out to be our opponents in the semifinals.
Both teams are in position, and the match is about to begin.
What was your purpose in arresting people before?
The purpose, of course, is to collect data.
Create a powerful machine team
No matter what your purpose is, I will use basketball to completely defeat you.
Two people trying to stop me? Try it if you can.
A piece of cake
Great! Wolffy got off to a winning start right from the start.
Team Defenders took the lead with two points.
nice shot
Dad is amazing! Dad is a true basketball star!
I’ve been dreaming of this day, and it’s finally come true!
Okay, for Wolnie and Willie
I must win this game.
Although captain Weslie did not play.
However, Team Defenders’ foreign player has quite comprehensive skills.
They are currently leading by thirteen points.
This is my strength.
Did you see that?… Did you see that?
It’s just a few points.
Exactly, what’s there to be proud of?
He’s never scored a goal, has he? Look how smug he is.
Really
D
You guys are talking too much. Focus on watching the game.
Wolffy, let’s prove our strength with this victory!
Give it to me.
I didn’t expect you to have some skills.
But do you think you can win like this?
The real show is just beginning.
Now it’s time to cheer up!
With me here, you can forget about getting past me.
It’s time to show you what I’ve got.
What, a half-court shot?
No, if it’s a machine’s precise calculation…
How could I possibly let you make a move so easily?
OH IE
It flew out
V
Referee, that should be considered a foul.
Let me see.
In fact, the robot team did not violate the rules.
What
The machine team scored two points.
etc.
It seems they themselves felt it was outrageous and were embarrassed to ask for a share.
When I shot, my foot was outside the three-point line, so it should count as a three-pointer, right?
It definitely counts as three points.
Do you even have feet?
It was clearly suspended in mid-air the whole time.
Why not just play it like rugby?
Referee, stop them from playing immediately!
That’s enough, let’s continue the game.
It seems the machine team is no longer holding back and is about to show their true strength.
The machine team repeatedly scored using unorthodox split-push tactics.
The score has been reversed and Team Defenders has been overtaken.
They’ve fallen behind so quickly.
I knew it! How could the Goat-Wolves team possibly win?
If you’re so good, you do it!
Does this even look like a proper basketball game?
What’s the connection between being on the same team as wolves and sheep (GOAT)?
Team Defenders’ morale has been affected.
Win rate prediction: 80%
0-1 receiving the ball
Where are my hands?
It seems Team Defenders are furious.
They hid the robot team’s hands.
They can show off their skills. Why can’t I keep mine to myself?
No, I don’t want it.
Team Defenders also attacked the referee.
That technical foul was really unfair.
Team Defenders requests a pause.
How can these robots score points like that?
How are you all?
No problem, we only used Yan Cheng’s power.
Don’t worry, leave it to us.
You should get some rest.
Coach, I know I was wrong.
Please, please let me play.
You stay seated. Everyone else, come over here.
Coaching
Every time the machine team attacks, they score a layup by sending out a flying hand into the paint.
Since we can’t defend the outer perimeter, we should tighten our defense.
Defend the basket
We will definitely prevent it.
Go
Coach
I really want to
I really want to play and contribute to the team.
Even if you’re on the bench, there’s always something you can do.
bring it on
Team Defenders used a collapsed defense tactic.
Watch me
Stop struggling in vain.
And me
10 Good opportunities to quickly counterattack
Team Defenders actually managed to defend against it.
Are they about to sound the horn of retaliation?
What about the robotic arm?
Tibbie
It’s okay, we’ll definitely have another chance to fight back.
The machine team’s flying arm technique is good at both defense and offense.
Team Defenders were completely overwhelmed and unable to mount any resistance.
Is the competition about to end here?
Different races on the same team is simply not going to work.
If you’re so capable, then give me 99.
You will definitely have things you can do.
How can I help the team?
Could it be…?
I see
Listen to me, everyone.
Their robotic arms have limited flight time.
Each launch and recovery requires charging to maintain power.
This is the key to our victory.
Are you guys going to kick off or not?
It’s time for us to fight back.
First, focus on dribbling and passing to delay the attack.
Here
All you do is hide and run; your attack time is almost over.
Not good yet
Right now
Oh no, we’re running out of energy and the speed is slowing down.
Goal! Team Defenders finally broke the deadlock and scored!
It’s time for us to fight back.
That’s quite capable, but can you handle what’s to come?
Data update complete – successful upgrade to Universe System version 2.0.