Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Surpassing Yourself
In the previous episode, we saw the Goat Team compete against the suspicious Machine team.
Wolffy performed brilliantly in his first match.
Unexpectedly, the robot team gained the upper hand using a rule-breaking tactic.
Despite being sidelined due to injury, Weslie found a way to help the team break through.
But the machine team’s approach is not limited to this.
The competition has entered its climax.
Team Defenders gradually caught up in the score.
11 Good
Upgrade complete. Welcome to the new system version 2.0.
They seem to have changed again.
0-3
Is this the status after the system upgrade?
The game continues
Calculating the optimal breakthrough route
The route has been determined.
Here we go
Optimal three-point shot trajectory set complete
Incredible! The robot broke through the entire Team Defenders team in just 2 seconds!
He made a precise three-pointer.
99 10
99 No. Didn’t see it clearly
They passed us in an instant!
He had anticipated our actions.
I’d like to see if you can even read my movements.
According to big data analysis, these are all feints.
Another 3-pointer
According to big data analysis, Sparky is about to break through to the right.
Success
Based on the basketball’s trajectory, its final landing point has been calculated.
The opposing player is preparing to grab the rebound.
It’s over, there’s no chance anymore.
3 points again
Another 3 points
The machine team scored three consecutive points, completely dominating the game.
The score is now 61:32.
On the other hand, Team Defenders seem to be suffering from severe physical exhaustion.
Do they still have a chance to turn things around?
Please rest assured.
Our final wish must be
Team Defenders has all the information on everyone.
My Team Robot
I’ve already played against them in simulated matches on the computer hundreds of times.
I can’t possibly lose.
Okay, let’s get back to the game.
It seems the situation is very bad for Team Defenders now.
Team Robot is really amazing!
He got so many points all at once.
I think Team Defenders is going to lose.
How can people of different races play ball together?
Their habits and body types are different.
that is
It seems they have tracked all our actions.
This is going to be a tough battle.
Basketball is not a game where you can win by calculating alone.
The first half ended with a score of 67:32.
Team Robot Leads
How can we fight like this? All our actions are within their calculations.
They always know who I want to send it to.
I couldn’t find an open shot at all.
So, are we just going to give up like this?
coach
Although it’s difficult, there’s only one way to turn things around.
Keep going, we can do it!
Here
The target of the attack, Tibbie, is attempting to break through and has initiated a siege mode.
HIO
Shooting route blocked
Switch ball protection mode
Wolffy’s stamina is rapidly depleting, and it’s clear the opponent cannot steal possession of the ball.
Are you kidding me?
Don’t underestimate me
Wolffy has lost his balance.
Calculation error, data anomaly
The data they collected is just your past.
Therefore, the only way to win is…
Make yourself stronger every second than the last.
Go and surpass yourself!
Surpass yourself
Catch
The detection indicates the other party is powerless to stop it; a forced breakthrough is possible.
Come on everyone, we’ll definitely score!
good.
good…
We’ve already arrived here.
We cannot lose
Calculation error, data anomaly
Oh no, I can’t reach it.
Is this… my limit?
No matter how difficult, I will
Chasing after
Calculation error
I want one too.
Surpass yourself
The ball…the ball changed direction
The ball is in Paddi’s hands; this is Team Defenders’ chance.
Data shows normal, predicted 3-point shot
Block pitching
Believe in yourself
It is definitely possible.
Step-back 3-pointer
Team Defenders finally scored! That’s so exciting!
They haven’t given up on the game.
nice shot
Will they retaliate next?
It was a success…
Data error, unable to calculate
how so
The program cannot possibly have a problem.
Do you still have the strength?
Of course.
Alright, time to start the counterattack.
Okay, let’s go!
0-3
What kind of monsters are Team Defenders?
That way they can recover the score.
It seems we underestimated them.
Team Defenders requests a pause.
Sparky, are you alright?
I’m fine, this little injury is nothing.
Sparky, you should rest now.
Coach, I can still play.
no
I can’t risk aggravating your injury by letting you play.
For the next match, Weslie will take your place.
That’s great, Weslie.
The rest is up to you.
Bring victory back!
Unforgivable
I never expected those goats to fight like that.
I must win this game.
The most powerful version 3.0 starts up.
To be continued…