In the previous episode,
The machine team uses a computational analysis system
Master all of Team Defenders’ next moves
But inspired by Wolffy’s never-give-up spirit
The goats also pushed their limits, causing the machine team’s computer to temporarily crash.
However, the machine team upgraded the system again.
What other new tricks do they have up their sleeves?
Hopefully nothing goes wrong.
pretty
Weslie made a lightning-fast breakthrough and scored two points in an instant.
Weslie, is your foot alright?
As long as you don’t use overload mode, it should be fine.
The robot Small Forward unleashed… Lightning Breakthrough
Isn’t this Weslie’s signature move?
How come?
What
Unbelievable!
The robot Small Forward seemed to mimic all of Weslie’s movements.
CC
0-5
CVCV
Team Defenders requests a pause.
Exactly the same; these robots have probably upgraded their systems.
It can replicate your every move, which means
Standing before you now is equivalent to five versions of yourself.
This is cheating!
There are no rules in the competition prohibiting the use of the opponent’s techniques.
Coach, what should we do?
We’ll try out some coordinated tactics in a bit; they might not be able to replicate them.
Let me play, my injury is fine.
no
However, Wolffy hadn’t practiced teamwork.
Let me give it a try, I know all your tactics.
When did you learn it?
actually
When I was on Team Wolves, I used to watch a lot of your basketball videos.
Firstly, it’s to defeat you.
Secondly, because I really like your style of play.
So I’ve written down all your tactics.
That’s interesting.
Then it’s up to you, Wolffy.
Master, why don’t you use the same technique as me?
Hurry up and use your own tricks!
I will defeat you and become the number one in the world.
The one who can defeat himself is the greatest fool in the world.
Can Team Defenders create a breakthrough after the pause?
How to counter Team Robot’s copy tactics?
The squad leader and I held off the opponent.
Tibbie and Paddi pass the ball to Wolffy, who is responsible for the score.
good
Oh no!
Don’t rush, take your time.
Wolffy tried very hard
But it’s too much of a stretch to have practiced it in actual combat without any prior experience.
I believe that those who work hard will definitely reap the rewards.
Don’t worry, I definitely won’t.
again…
Disappointing everyone
CV
Goal!
good
Very good
They can’t replicate our teamwork, so let’s try again.
What
Just now
Even teamwork can be replicated.
How can we fight like this?
No, we can’t let them waste any more time like this.
Could they even anticipate their opponents’ thoughts?
It seems the only option is to use overload again.
What are you doing, you little goat? Are you out of your mind?
But they
That won’t work either.
If you use overload again
Even if we win this game, what about the next one?
Calm down, Weslie
There must be a way.
0-1
You are Zi Tailang
That’s right
Why would you
I heard you’re very smart, how come you couldn’t think of this?
Because this is my team too.
What?! Aren’t you the manager of Team Wolves?
Of course, this is for double protection after we win against you.
Both teams in the finals were my teams.
Regardless of winning or losing, I will be the one who ultimately triumphs.
Zi Tailang, you’re so despicable!
Everyone on Team Wolves is playing so hard.
You…you treat them like this.
This world only has winners and losers.
It’s obvious you’re on the loser’s side.
And I… will definitely be the one who wins in the end and gets my wish.
We will lose
With your current technology, what makes you think you can beat me?
Enjoy these last moments.
An ant is still an ant.
Is it really impossible to defeat them?
Could we have been friends before?
We’ve achieved peace with wolves and sheep (goats), what can’t we do?
This is how we’ve always come to be.
I believe our teamwork will definitely defeat them.
You absolutely must not let his words sway you.
Big Grey Wolf O
Wolffy is right, nothing is impossible.
Let them see how powerful Team Defenders are.
good
It seems the tide has turned: facing Team Robot’s replication capabilities.
How can Team Defenders turn the tide?
Wait, what’s that?
What.
Stop struggling
I can replicate your movements, skills, and even your thoughts.
Some things you can never replicate.
What did you say
Your copying skills are indeed impressive.
But… can you replicate our tacit understanding?
Is it keeping pace with our evolutionary speed?
Why is this happening?
Why is my machine always one step behind them?
Every second of progress we make is different from every bit of progress in our data.
Don’t even think about it.
What are you talking big about? I see through you.
Win
What
Don’t underestimate our teamwork.
good
nice shot
They did it, they really did it.
The goats actually defeated Team Robot!
I never expected that wolves and goats could put on such a spectacular match together!
It seems we underestimated them.
I told you, wolves and goats teaming up are incredibly powerful.
nothing is impossible
Basketball has no boundaries.
Let’s cheer for Team Defenders!
Go Team Defenders!