In the previous episode, we mentioned that the robot team copied Team Defenders’ every move.
At the same time, everyone learned
The machine team was also the team Zi Tailang used to deal with Goat Clan.
anxious
Facing a stalemate
Weslie and Wolffy ultimately achieved a tacit understanding that machines could not replicate.
Successfully defeated the opponent
To celebrate our ticket to the finals
Let’s have a big meal!
Weslie, what’s wrong?
Yeah, why are you looking so gloomy?
nothing
I was just thinking… Zi Tailang
Do you remember?
She communicated with us via robot on the court.
She’s so lowly.
He wanted to use this method to win the championship.
I always felt she had some kind of conspiracy.
Why is she so obsessed with victory?
So much so that she had to use two teams simultaneously to win the championship.
Perhaps she also wanted to have her wish granted, to wish for an endless supply of cakes.
You think everyone is like you?
Perhaps you’re overthinking it.
She just really wanted that wish.
What danger haven’t we encountered?
As long as we work together, there is no difficulty we cannot overcome.
That’s right, as long as we work together…
There is no difficulty that cannot be overcome.
That’s right, and besides, I’m here too.
I will definitely not let those wolves act recklessly.
If you were here, you would definitely be able to help us.
Coach, when will you lead us in training?
The more we practice, the greater our chances of winning will be.
You’ve done all the practice you needed to do, now you should go eat.
Go have fun, go to sleep, and relax.
Alright, let’s disband.
They actually made it to the finals!
Wolffy, I didn’t realize that!
So much potential!
My plan absolutely cannot fail.
It’s okay, Wolffy
So what if you’re amazing?
You just need to be outside the sheep (goat) team.
After training for so long, I finally have a chance to rest.
By the way, my performance in the semifinals was so cool!
Why haven’t any fans asked me for autographs yet?
Did the fans follow us here?
What hairstyle is good?
Let’s get some bangs.
handsome
Wolffy
Here
Traitor Wolffy
When did I become a traitor?
If you help the goats fight the Wolf Clan, you are a traitor to the Wolf Clan.
When did I betray Wolf Clan? Don’t you dare hurt my family.
As long as you’re still in the goat’s team, we won’t give up.
That’s too much! I was just playing ball with a goat.
Where is there any betrayal of Wolf Clan?
It doesn’t matter even if the whole world doesn’t understand you.
We understand you.
Yes, Dad is the best.
You guys are so nice
I believe that one day they will change their minds.
Let’s clean it up together.
Wolnie, are you alright?
My toy got smashed.
The final training you mentioned is this.
That’s right
What if they really choose to play?
Athletes who only care about having fun will never win a championship.
Let’s not bother them then.
Weslie, you call me as soon as you’re resting.
Who should I call?
I plan to ask Lion Jay and his team to help us with training.
But the phone call couldn’t get through.
Forget it, let’s go find Wolffy and train together.
I’ll also go to Wolf Fortress to freeload some food and drinks.
Sorry, I thought someone else was causing trouble.
Who are you?
I am from the Department of Science
Our chief inventor has stepped down; someone has recommended you to succeed him.
The Science Department, the department that controls all of Wolf Clan’s inventions.
Yes, this is an appointment notice.
From now on, you will be our chief inventor.
Is this real? That’s amazing!
Great, Wolffy
Dad is amazing
But I heard you’re playing for the Goat team now.
This is unacceptable to Wolf Clan.
You must leave the goat team to become our chief scientist.
No, how could I possibly leave the Goat team?
So you’re going to become a traitor to Wolf Clan and continue to cause your family fear?
Or become the pride of the Wolf Clan and live the life of a wolf-waiting.
Have you thought it through?
No, I can’t let Goat down.
But what about Wolnie and Willie?
traitor
Shameless traitor
They’re here again.
Don’t be afraid, Dad will protect us.
What are you going to do?
We must teach the traitors a lesson.
Wait, everyone calm down.
As long as Wolffy signs this contract and leaves the Goat team
He is not a traitor
Then sign it, sign it!
Sign quickly!
this
Wolffy, don’t listen to them.
Willie and I both support you.
This is just a basketball trophy.
Why put your family in danger because of this sport?
I can’t let the goat down!
They don’t need you, so please don’t make the wrong choice.
I’m afraid I won’t be able to stop them.
It’s not good if anyone gets hurt in the end.
Wolffy, Team Defenders can’t do without you.
goat
You said that as long as we work together…
There’s nothing you can’t ask.
you.
That’s right.
See, he really is good friends with the goat.
We need to teach them a lesson.
Who, who dares to stop me?
Let’s see who dares.
Paddi, we’re here to help.
I heard you forced Wolffy to leave the team.
Why are you here?
We heard you made it to the finals, so the four of us are planning to come and celebrate with you.
However, it seems now…
Someone wants to cause trouble.
What should we do? The mighty and ferocious leopard clan, lion clan, and eagle clan…
There are also rabbits.
We just slightly felt that Wolffy joining the GOAT team was a bit of a bad idea.
I wanted to persuade him to leave the team.
Basketball has no racial distinctions, and no one has the right to stop others from playing together.
We all support everyone playing basketball together.
Do you think we are all traitors to our race?
Don’t be afraid, everyone, let’s push this up.
So it was you.
Zi Tailang
You all need to remember this.
They were so incapable of distinguishing right from wrong that they aided and abetted the wicked.
We won’t do it again.
Slowy, thank you.
This is the first time in my life that you’ve said thank you to me. Why are you doing this so suddenly?
Basketball has been my obsession since I was a child.
Without your help, I wouldn’t have been able to lead the team to the finals.
Thank you
Really? It’s alright.
I only put in one-tenth of the effort.
I didn’t even use one-tenth of it.
What, you’re just bragging.