Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Zi Tailang’s Conspiracy
In the previous episode, Wolffy was very excited to help the goats win.
But the truth is that the Wolf Clan members considered Wolffy a traitor.
He was extremely angry with the Wolffy family.
At the crucial moment, the goats and other basketball team captains showed up to support them.
Solving the Wolffy family’s crisis
The match time is getting closer and closer
Fortunately, you were all there; you were all happy to accompany us for the final training session.
The finals are the day after tomorrow, good luck to you guys!
Thank you for your help.
We will definitely come to support you then.
Okay, thank you everyone for your support.
Let’s head back to Goats’ Village now.
goodbye
Wait a moment
Please be careful on the road.
What danger could there be?
A few days ago, I was attacked by a mysterious person at the stadium.
What, you encountered this too?
Give me back the ball
And just like that, that mysterious figure unleashed my Super Slam Dunk.
I was defeated
What
How could he use your moves?
I too was defeated by my own overload acceleration.
She used my Eagle Soaring Through the Sky technique.
It startled me, which gave her an opportunity to take advantage.
Even you, the reigning champion, got defeated.
So, you were also defeated by your own three-point dunk?
That’s right
Do you still remember the mysterious person who attacked you?
What does she look like?
She was wearing a hat at the time, so I couldn’t see her face clearly.
However, judging from her figure, “it should be a woman.”
She also has a wolf tail
A wolf
Weslie, you mentioned the wolves that attacked the captains.
Could it be Zi Tailang?
It is indeed possible
After all, she had hurt us time and time again before.
But I’ve been with Team Wolves for so long, and I’ve never seen her play basketball.
Not to mention she’ll learn all the captains’ special moves.
Could this be another of her schemes?
Don’t think too much about it.
The most important thing now is to prepare for the finals.
Mr. Slowy, coach, we’re back!
That’s strange.
Why is no one here?
Something terrible has happened!
What happened?
Blazey and Slowy have been arrested.
What
I was just hanging my blankets out to dry by the river.
Suddenly a robot appeared behind them
They took them away, and I can’t catch up at all!
Another robot
Let’s hurry and save them!
Dama, you can leave it to us without worry.
I wonder if I’ll encounter any danger.
Go home and wait for my message.
You must be careful!
The place Dama mentioned should be here.
Look, this is the coach’s notes.
Why is a page missing?
Look, these should be pages from the coach’s notes.
This must be a clue he left for us when he was taken away.
Let’s hurry over and take a look.
The paper is gone, how are we going to find Mr. Slowy and the others now?
There
These Zi Tailang robots are guarding this place.
What is she plotting now?
Mr. Slowy and the others must be inside.
Let’s hurry and rescue Mr. Slowy and the others!
Little Ba ah
Rushing out like that is too dangerous.
Yes, Zi Tailang must be plotting something again.
There must have been many traps and mechanisms inside.
Used to catch us
We can’t handle so many robots.
I think we can ask Victor for help.
Victor
Can he handle these robots?
No, he probably couldn’t handle so many robots either.
However, he can stop Zi Tailang
He’s very committed to fairness in competitions.
You’re right, Victor is the captain of Team Wolves.
He should be able to stop her.
You’re hiding here keeping watch.
Wolffy and I will go find Victor for help right away.
We will keep a close watch here.
But by the time you found Victor…
Could Mr. Slowy and the others have already encountered danger?
We will definitely come back as soon as possible.
Please don’t act impulsively!
Sparky?
Sparky
Sparky, why did you run off again?
I need to go save Mr. Slowy and the others; they might be in danger if I’m too late.
Sparky
It would be dangerous for Sparky to go alone.
Let’s go help him!
What happened to the surveillance…? Wait for me!
000.
Not a Wolf Clan member, no entry.
What should I do? I can’t get in!
I’m here.
Am I not from Wolf Clan? I used to be a member of Team Wolves!
Identity verification successful, Wolffy
Success
Wolf Clan traitor, expelled
I’m not a traitor!
How can I find Victor?
I don’t know either.
Please move aside
Captain Victor
Team
You’re no longer a member of Team Wolves, so don’t call me captain.
I’m used to saying sorry.
Victor, we need your help!
Here’s the thing: our Mr. Slowy and coach have disappeared.
He was probably arrested by Zi Tailang.
This time, I wonder what new tricks she’ll pull to sabotage the competition?
Please help us.
Victor, didn’t you say you wanted a fair and just competition?
Is it just talk?
Do you have any evidence to prove that Zi Tailang did it?
No/No
But
Without even any evidence, how can you be so sure that Zi Tailang did it?
The final is almost here, don’t waste any time.
Go practice hard.
That’s your master!
How could this mechanism be activated so easily?
What happened?
Thank you
We are all a team
That’s how it should be.
Oh no, the robot has been attracted!
See my
Why is there no response?
Who said there isn’t?
Success
Paddi, you’re something else!
It is a suspension bridge
What are you all standing there for? Run!
Grab my hand
I won’t let you fall.
Sparky, thank you
No problem, we’re teammates.
That’s right, as long as we unite
No matter how great the difficulties, they cannot stop us.
We will definitely be able to rescue Mr. Slowy and the others.
come on
Mr. Slowy & Coach
Don’t be afraid, we will rescue you.
Oh no, the door has been closed.
We can’t get out.
It’s a trap.
Oh no, this smoke is poisonous!
Everyone, quickly cover your noses!
Xi Weslie
Both the opponents and the audience are ready.
Now all that’s missing are you two main characters.
Hurry up and step onto the stage I’ve prepared for you!
To be continued…