In the previous episode, Blazey and Slowy were arrested.
The group tracked down to a suspicious cave.
The incident appears to be related to Zi Tailang.
Weslie and Wolffy decide to ask Victor for help.
But he refused.
The other goats couldn’t contain themselves and rushed into the cave.
However, they were trapped by Zi Tailang’s trap.
How long have I been asleep?
Where are the coach and the village chief?
There
It’s fake.
So what should we do now?
Let’s get out of here quickly!
The door won’t open!
The finals are tomorrow, we can’t let ourselves be stuck here.
Sparky
Brute force won’t work; we need to use our brains.
So what can you do?
We’ll eat and drink our fill, then we can just wait for Weslie to come and rescue us, right?
You’re joking around during such a crisis?
I swear on my experience of being caught over 800 times.
Weslie will definitely come to save us.
What’s so great about being arrested over 800 times?
Even if Weslie and the others come to rescue us
We have to figure out a way to get out ourselves.
Then you should keep banging on the door.
You need to eat your fill to have the energy to continue.
We must continue!
= N
Captain, what brings you here?
You played well!
No, those are all the results of training.
but
Team Captain
It seems like there’s something interesting behind you.
No…we
This is the reason for your progress, isn’t it?
Who gave it to you?
CI
My team doesn’t need people like you who cheat and deceive.
They’ve all disappeared.
They must have gone inside already, let’s hurry and catch up!
Wait a minute.
The footprints on the ground were so messy
And Paddi left behind all his favorite snacks.
Something must have happened here.
Hurry up
Hurry up, Wolffy
They may be in danger.
Be careful, there’s something wrong with that stone.
Lie down quickly
Why did you move away?
It looks like a fierce battle took place here.
The traps have all been destroyed.
I speculate
The goats must have won.
That is
Village Chief & Coach
We need to catch up quickly.
Wait a minute, village chief!
coach
Village chief, I’m so glad you’re all alright.
Coach, don’t be afraid, we’re here to rescue you.
Village chief, what did you stick on my back?
What is that? I can’t reach it.
What happened?
My eyes!
What exactly is this place?
basketball court
Weslie, look!
C
Weslie, Wolffy
How did you end up locked up here? I’m coming to rescue you right now!
That is
Weslie, you’re carrying a bomb!
What
Let me see how I disassembled it.
Village chief, coach
Why
Even the village chief and his men had bombs on them.
I advise you not to make any rash moves.
The bomb I set will explode as soon as it’s detonated.
What
Is that sound… Zi Tailang?
What trick are you up to now?
Wolffy
The village chief and the coach seem to be behaving strangely; they haven’t reacted at all.
No way, coach
coach
They seem to be under control.
That’s right
As a reward for you, the following…
You and the two elderly people will have a 20-minute, 2-2 match.
Why should we listen to you?
You’ll find out soon enough.
The coach is still so amazing!
How did the number decrease?
Mine seems to be the same.
The points you have are your life points.
Each time a goal is scored, the penalty decreases; if it reaches 0…
You will die
How could Weslie possibly beat the coach?
Don’t panic, their team has the village chief with them.
We try our best to keep the ball in our hands and drag it out as long as possible.
Leave Slowy to me with confidence.
Slowy, what’s going on?
Didn’t you say that with the village chief around, they’d be fine?
In addition to controlling movement, chips can also enhance the user’s physical fitness.
Even Slowy can become quite powerful with a chip installed.
This is cheating. I strongly demand a fair match against Slowy.
Wolffy
Since there are no referees, who wants to compete with them?
Let’s remove the control chip first.
Coach, I’m sorry.
Slowy, wake up!
come on
The audience’s time is also life.
The bombs they planted above them were counting down.
If they keep dragging things out, the audience will suffer.
not good
If you want to win, then trap us.
Why plant a bomb?
Because I hate Goat Clan
I had everything planned out long ago.
First place was originally my for the taking.
And you guys just had to come and cause trouble, especially since you’re all talentless Goat Clan members.
Then I
You traitor to Wolf Clan, you deserve it!
To make sure you get a proper welcome, I’ve even added extra bombs.
This can’t go on.
Wolffy, catch!
Hang in there!
Don’t worry, leave it to me.
Don’t worry, I’ll try to get you out first.
They’re in a confined space; how can we get them out?
Weslie
Wait, I’m thinking of a way.
Hurry back, the points are almost gone!
Please come back soon, I can’t handle this alone.
Go back quickly, go back quickly!
Village chief/coach, please stop hitting him.
Wake up!
And me too, don’t even think about getting past me.
I won’t let you score again.
Human wall defense technique
What?! This way you can still move forward?
It’s impossible to defend against!
This is a step back.
Oh no, you can forget about scoring again.
No, our strength is far too inferior.
If this continues…
We mustn’t give up; there must be another way.
Weslie, we can’t just sit here and wait to die.
You should give up; these glasses are specially made.
You can’t possibly break it open.
Why are you treating us like this?
Is your desire to win first place really that strong?
I have absolutely no interest in wishes or anything like that.
I’m determined to get first place.
What’s the point of getting first place like this?
No matter how much you’ve sacrificed or how long you’ve persevered.
Ultimately, people still only look at the results.
Who else cares?
In short, I’m determined to get first place.