Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Escaping to Safety
In the previous episode,
Blazey, Slowy, and the four little goats
Controlled by wolves
This was used to threaten Weslie and Wolffy.
The two of them faced a fateful choice.
Whether it’s winning the game or stalling for time
None of them worked
The bomb was about to explode
What will become of them?
What should we do now?
Since there is no way out
Let’s try this method.
The bomb is about to explode
Our Mr. Slowy and coach have both disappeared.
He was probably captured by Zi Tailang.
Please help us.
Who gave it to you?
That’s more like it!
Weslie, what do you want to do?
Coach, do you remember this move?
Haste makes waste; relax your mindset.
The opportunity will come naturally…
If I hadn’t heard what you said…
I definitely can’t master this move.
It’s a lightning breakthrough.
Weslie is using the basketball skills taught by his coach.
Could it be that he’s trying to wake up Mr. Slowy and coach?
My specially made device
It’s not that easy for you to crack it.
Single-gear, that was the first tactic you taught us.
I have a trick
I’ll help you get a point…
Why are you standing there like that? Get back at me and launch a counterattack!
Do you think they can really hear what you’re saying?
I believe in Mr. Slowy and coach
I’ll bet on these two points.
We must make you wake up.
Okay, we’ll help too.
Can they really hear us?
Can be heard
As long as you pass it on with your heart
It can break any distance
Coach, Mr. Slowy…
Thank you for always being there at the stadium during every game…
They cheered us on with all their might…
Coach, it’s because you recognize my abilities.
Only then can I play on the court again.
Yes, Coach
You also told us before
We must use our strength to conquer those who doubt us.
Give it your all on the court.
Trust your teammates and care for your teammates
Always have confidence
Coach, Mr. Slowy, do you remember?
Senior, please don’t go.
So you’re agreeing to be our coach?
yes…
Coach, Mr. Slowy, we…
Let’s go to the finals together…
What are you two doing?
Attack now!
Go shoot the ball right now!
coach
don’t want
Let’s end it here.
How did the door open?
Who is it?
Luckily, I made it in time.
He actually removed all my surveillance cameras.
Victor, do you really prefer to go against Wolf Clan?
Should we also rescue those goats?
I just want to work with Team Defenders
To play a fair and just final match
A fair and just final?
Isn’t winning all that matters? The process is completely unimportant.
That’s enough.
Your plan has completely failed.
I removed the chip you implanted in your teammate.
What?
I shouldn’t have expected anything from you in the first place.
Tell you
You are now completely useless.
Without me, who else can compete in the finals?
Of course it is…
Me
What?
I have plenty of these.
Let me regain control of Zhuang Tailang and them
A new Team Wolves will be born.
You are despicable
Anyway, you don’t need teammates when you play basketball.
And I will bring out their greatest value.
Mechanical Team
Catching the Team Defenders players
Don’t let them participate in the finals
Wolffy
Great, we’re all alright now.
Why were we eventually released?
And the bomb didn’t explode.
Could it be that someone saved us?
Let’s remove the chip as soon as possible.
My feet hurt so much!
Mr. Slowy seemed to have aged several years suddenly.
But the coach doesn’t seem to be any different.
So sour
There’s no time to explain, let’s leave first.
Target them, capture them.
Oh no, run!
We need to run!
You should leave as soon as possible.
Don’t worry about the two of us.
Even if you take us with you, you won’t be able to escape.
You guys hurry up and go to the competition.
Without you
Can we still be considered Team Defenders?
Run
There are rooms over there, let’s go in and hide.
Who is it?
And who are you?
So it was you guys? The guardians of Goats’ Village
Do you know us?
Enjoy the happy moments right now!
Wait until I get my wish
I will rule this world.
Wait a minute, what do you mean by that?
Disappeared
That was a 3D projection, so advanced!
Hurry up, the match is about to start.
yes…
This time it’s an enhanced version of the chip.
What do you want to do? Zi Tailang
This time you will obey my orders completely.
Team Wolves was born.
The Team Defenders members haven’t reported for duty yet.
Did they give up before even fighting?
They were late for the final?
Don’t worry, they will definitely come.
What are these goats doing?
Ten minutes left
Team Defenders will be disqualified if they don’t come soon.
Wolffy
At our current speed
They’ll catch him sooner or later.
And there are so many of them.
Mr. Slowy, coach, keep up!
Mr. Slowy Coach
Don’t come any closer
Let’s stop them.
You guys hurry up and go to the competition.
You all have to go too.
I never thought we’d finally have a moment where we thought alike.
right
Mr. Slowy Coach
Run!
Your most important task now is to make it to the finals.
We’ll see.
We absolutely cannot let Zi Tailang and his group get away with this.
That wish to win the basketball trophy
That mysterious person must have done something.
Things that are bad for the world are…
But…
Are you disobedient?
Run!
Walk…
You absolutely have to win…
To be continued…