Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories
“Dilemma”
In the previous episode, we discussed their bomb trap.
Entering the countdown phase
Victor saved them
However, he was captured by Zi Tailang.
Zi Tailang sent robots to chase them.
He rushed off to participate in the finals.
The final is about to begin.
The two elderly people wanted them to arrive in time
Decide to sacrifice yourself
My brother is amazing!
It’s you, Zi Tailang
Why don’t you rest for a while, brother?
Thank you
but
I want to practice a little longer.
Brother, you are so diligent and talented.
We will definitely win this Basketball Game.
To continue this family honor
By the way, Zi Tailang
This wristband is for you.
You and I each have one
I will be wearing this wristband then.
Go and win the Basketball Game championship.
Go, brother!
Sky Hawks scored!
This year’s champion is… Team Gliders
Really
Seriously? Losing is outrageous!
They couldn’t win even if they were just one goal away.
Absolutely terrible, absolutely terrible.
They couldn’t even stop Sky Hawk!
It was all because of him that we lost.
You can tell how incompetent he is just by looking at him.
Let’s go, this is a waste of time.
After he left, he stopped looking at anything related to him.
Yeah, I’m not watching anymore.
Why do you say that?
Weren’t you all very supportive of my brother before?
elder brother…
Go away, don’t embarrass yourself anymore.
Don’t embarrass yourself, just leave.
I really hate him and can’t stand the sight of him.
What are you looking at?
I don’t want to see you again.
I don’t want to see you…
Let’s go
Do you think you’ve done right by the fans? It’s just…
If you’re this bad, you shouldn’t play ball.
You have a lot of talent for it, but you still lost?
You are terrible.
It’s possible that I would be better at playing.
Lü Tailang faltered, and Team Wolves suffered a crushing defeat.
It was a really ugly loss, it’s all his fault…
He dragged the whole team down; he doesn’t deserve to be captain.
Not worthy at all
Let’s change the captain.
What’s the point of only getting second place?
He has completely disgraced the Wolf Clan!
We, the Wolf Clan, lost face; it’s all his fault.
It’s all his fault, it’s all his fault.
It’s all his fault…
Brother, come out and get something to eat.
You haven’t eaten for many days.
elder brother…
The glory we lost back then
I’ll go get it.
Report
Only two goats were caught; the rest escaped.
It’s no use coming here.
The championship has always belonged to me.
Today has finally arrived.
The final game of the Grassland Basketball Game
First up is…
Team Wolves
Victor…
What exactly happened?
Just received the latest list of participants.
Victor will not be attending the finals.
He was replaced by the team manager… Zi Tailang?
Why her?
Team Wolves truly deserve to be called the strongest among the strong.
Even the manager can play ball.
What came out from the other side was…
Team Defenders
Where are they? I can’t see them.
Why haven’t they arrived yet?
The final match is about to begin in one minute.
What exactly happened today?
And Yang Dama
She usually arrives earlier than the referees.
Their coaching team hasn’t arrived yet.
Why haven’t they arrived yet, so late?
Wolffy, answer the phone!
Why is the Goat Team still not here?
Not because I’m afraid of losing too badly
So you don’t dare to come, right?
What a pity
It seems Team Defenders
Will miss this important final
I hereby declare that, due to…
The contestant failed to arrive on time, so…
The winner of this match is…
Wolf…
I’m so sorry we’re a little late.
That’s great… Keep it up…
They finally appeared.
Team Defenders managed to pull off a last-second…
Enter the competition venue in time
Where is Dad?
Unexpected…
You ultimately chose to compete.
They even abandoned their own coach.
What exactly is the difference between you and me?
We are completely different from you.
I will definitely save Slowy and the coach.
Weslie, remember, you absolutely cannot lose.
They’ll both be fine, just wait and see.
This is the venue for the finals.
The players from both teams are ready.
Which team will ultimately win?
What qualifications does Zi Tailang have to replace Victor?
You can tell from her appearance that she has no ability.
Jumped so high
Wow, that’s so high…
So tall…
She seems to have some skill.
Weslie unleashed a lightning breakthrough.
He has already dribbled past midfield.
I told you long ago, this wolf is no good.
Very oppressive
Team Wolves score again.
Team Wolves’ four players have shown amazing strength.
Team Wolves have pulled ahead of their opponents by 18 points.
Why did they suddenly turn into another wolf?
Team Defenders were completely outmatched by Team Wolves.
The four of them should have been taken by Zi Tailang.
Controlled by that device
Losing by 18 points so quickly
It looks like these goats are doomed to lose today.
It seems we need to resolve these issues before we can get in.
I advise you to give up.
You can’t possibly beat the upgraded Team Wolves.
I look forward to a basketball game with you.
I definitely won’t lose.
Will not lose
It seems Team Defenders have finally started to fight back.
Now all we need to do is cross Zi Tailang
Team Defenders should be able to score a layup.
Don’t underestimate me
Let me show you my true strength!
Such immense power, it’s almost unstoppable!
Go Team Wolves!
That move just now…
You are before my mighty power
We’re doomed to lose.
She…she just now…
That move just now, soaring through the air
And such a cool pose
It’s exactly the same as my special move!
She just used those that seemed to be all of them
Our secret weapon
She doesn’t even know my special move, does she?
You’re too late.
Unexpectedly, Zi Tailang
He had been hiding his strength all along.
It turns out she had already mastered the four captains’ ultimate techniques.
He’s simply the best player on the field.
An accident occurred
It seems Weslie’s leg injury is quite serious.
Blazey…
Blazey, wake up!
Help! Is anyone there?
Be quiet
Slowy, Coach, hang in there!
I’ll be there right away.
Why are there still so many robots?
(to be continued)