Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Wholeheartedly
In the previous episode,
The goats arrived at the scene at the last second.
A showdown with Zi Tailang
Zi Tailang copied the four captains’ special moves.
Several goats got into a fierce battle
Meanwhile, Wolffy secretly went to rescue the two elderly people.
But he was knocked unconscious by the ambushing robots.
Weslie, are you alright?
Weslie, how are you? Are you alright?
Do you really think you can stop me?
Don’t worry, everyone, I’m fine.
Still being so stubborn, huh?
Zi Tailang…
Let’s continue then.
I will reclaim the glory my family has lost.
From now on, you won’t get a single penny.
No goat could withstand Zi Tailang’s fierce attack.
Team Defenders is in dire straits.
This is bad; the goats are completely unable to fight back.
It would be great if their coach were there.
These robots actually ambushed me?
Captain, you’re here too?
What are you doing?
Nonsense, of course we need to find a way out.
You want to go out through the vent?
The captain is indeed clever.
Let me help you.
Success
I wonder if we can get out of here?
Exit with a low volume
Help! Is anyone there?
Help! Is anyone outside?
Stop shouting, there are many robots outside.
How are your feet?
It’s possible that they were controlling it.
Relapse of old illness
How exactly did you hurt your foot?
Why has it not been cured?
We’ve been friends for decades, after all.
What can’t be said?
Don’t keep it to yourself, it’ll make you feel better.
It all started with Victor.
Victor takes his first official match very seriously.
But in the end, because his teammates didn’t perform well…
He lost that game
From then on, he no longer trusted his teammates.
On the field, he only believes in himself.
Increasingly autocratic
One day, he went out for special training by himself.
I was a little worried, so I secretly followed him.
It was raining heavily that day, and it was very dangerous.
He happened to encounter a landslide.
Luckily I was nearby at the time.
Rescue him in time
At that moment, a large rock rolled down the mountain.
My leg was pinned down.
I left after taking Victor to the hospital.
I never expected that when I saw him again
He actually came to challenge me.
Because of that one-on-one match
It made my foot injury worse.
It turns out he saved me.
Do you hate Victor?
How could I possibly hate him?
Although he later stopped acknowledging me as his master
But in my heart
He has always been my proudest disciple.
I just don’t have the ability to teach him well.
From that moment on, I dared not teach anyone to play basketball anymore.
Because I am a failed basketball coach
No, Blazey
I think you are definitely a
Excellent basketball coach
He is better than you
Traveling foul
Zi Tailang is really too intimidating.
This forced Team Defenders to repeatedly make basic mistakes.
It seems Team Defenders are doomed to lose.
The two teams are too mismatched; Team Wolves are truly terrifying.
Team Defenders has done its best.
Team Defenders
come on
It’s Leopardess (elder).
She… woke up?
Remember, you are the formidable team that defeated Team Sonic.
Get back on your feet quickly
That’s right, when you competed against us
It’s not like this now.
I forbid you from holding back your strength any longer.
Go Team Defenders! Go Team Defenders!
come on…
You can’t really be that naive.
You think they’re genuinely trying to cheer you on?
If you don’t win the championship
They will despise you.
Go Team Defenders!
Go Team Wolves!
Is that all?
The most important technique of power forward
It’s about predicting where the ball will land after it bounces off the rim.
Take action one step ahead of others
Who can control the rebounds?
You can then dominate the game…
What?
Now I’ll show you.
This is the result of my hard work and special training.
Sparky…
When did you learn to dunk?
Surprised?
I knew it all along.
You’ll definitely learn to dunk someday.
come on…
Tibbie…
You need to stop her…
well done…
Weslie
Awesome…
Well said
Here it comes… the counterattack!
Team Defenders caught up.
Do you think this will allow you to overtake them?
That’s more like it!
So you have a story like this?
Wait, Captain
Enemy invasion, quickly eliminate.
What’s happening outside?
Wolffy, do you know kung fu?
Haven’t you seen Goats’ Village 3?
Enemy invasion, quickly eliminate.
Coach, Slowy, here we come!
So it was you guys.
Victor
you…
This time it’s my turn to save you.
We need to hurry.
This is bad, it looks like this place is about to collapse.
Hurry up and get out of there!
Thanks to the encouragement of supporters
Team Defenders are on a roll!
The score gap has gradually narrowed.
So how will Team Wolves handle this?
come on
That’s right, catch up slowly.
good…
You guys don’t actually think…
Can you beat me?
What?
This move is…
After using the sonic attack
It’s time for the eagle to soar through the sky.
If this ball goes in
Team Defenders’ hard-earned momentum
It will be destroyed instantly.
So this ball
It can be said to be the ball that decided the entire situation.
As the future star player of Team Wolves
I look forward to a basketball game with you.
Because we said we’d meet in the finals, right?
Okay, let’s work together!
We can meet again at the stadium.
We are carrying everyone’s hopes.
Only then could we get here step by step.
Therefore, we will not lose.
The championship is mine
Hold on
Facing Zi Tailang’s overwhelming offensive
Team Defenders actually managed to hold on.
Weslie, how are you? Are you alright?
I’m fine.
You can hold on
That block was really cool!
well done
It’s infuriating!
To be continued…