Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories
“Obsession”
In the previous episode, we talked about
Wolffy encounters Victor, who is also trapped.
I accidentally found out about Blazey’s foot injury.
How did it come about?
Two wolves worked together to rescue two old goats.
On the other side, although Zi Tailang was advancing step by step…
But the Goat Team rallied with everyone’s encouragement.
Break the deadlock
Press on our advantage, let’s quickly catch up!
good…
Given this situation, they will definitely be able to catch up.
Wolffy, we will keep our promise.
Waiting for you to bring Mr. Slowy and the others back
Report: Detonation successful
The base was destroyed, and all enemies were eliminated.
The base was destroyed.
Your coach and Mr. Slowy are buried inside.
Mr. Slowy, coach…
Quit the game now
Maybe they can still come and rescue them.
Have they lost interest in the game? Goat Clan is so fragile.
I will definitely come back.
They’ll be fine.
Wolffy never gives up no matter what difficulties he encounters.
He said he would do it.
We believe in Wolffy
What?
Are you really that heartless?
Wolffy, he…
I will definitely bring Mr. Slowy and coach back.
Team Defenders finally caught up
The difference is less than ten points.
Look at those little goats, they’re amazing!
This is what a team that can beat us should look like!
We will definitely keep our promise.
Are you all alright?
Hang in there, everyone, let’s hurry…
Don’t go
There are even robots?
No…no…no leaving
Great, I’ve finally found you!
Yang Dama?
Why did you know to come here to find us?
Enough talk, let’s get to the court!
Report: The enemy has escaped.
Set all to the highest level
soon
What exactly happened?
Team Wolves’ technology seems to have suddenly upgraded.
Could they evolve during the competition?
We must not let him succeed.
They actually failed?
Useless
Jonie, ball
fast attack
no
I won’t let you score.
A fadeaway jump shot?
Brother, come out.
You open the door first.
elder brother
Don’t step on our team flag.
It is the pride of our family.
So this is the Team Wolves’ team flag?
I thought it was a tattered carpet.
Go immediately
I heard that their captain lost the game.
He just kept himself locked in the house.
I’m too ashamed to face the wolf
Truly vulnerable
If you don’t even have the ability to win a championship, what’s the point of talking about glory?
They’ve completely disgraced Wolf Clan.
From this moment on, I will spare no effort.
Reclaim the family’s glory
Sorry, I accidentally committed a foul.
I didn’t mean to.
Paddi…
How are your eyes?
You deliberately hurt him.
I…I’m fine.
You’re injured like this and you still say you’re fine?
I can continue playing.
Because we promised Wolffy we would wait for him to come back.
Zi Tailang, you are truly despicable.
mean?
To win the championship, I’ve tried even more despicable methods.
Every team that poses even the slightest threat
I was on guard.
I just didn’t expect it.
Our final opponent turned out to be a bunch of pathetic goat.
Zi Tailang
No matter what, we will defeat you.
Weslie
Paddi, catch the ball
Your eyes are so badly injured.
It would be strange if he could still make the shot.
It seems Paddi has no choice but to pass the ball.
Don’t worry, I’ve practiced three-pointers countless times.
Even if only one eye is aiming…
how so?
no
I’m sure I can make them.
Three points
Paddi’s shooting accuracy is amazing, even when he’s injured.
The score has surpassed
Great… Team Defenders in this match
Finally taking the lead for the first time
Wow, Paddi played great…
Well done
how so?
Team Defenders overtake
It seems Zi Tailang is still not quite up to par.
Really lame
that is
Look at her.
So lame and yet he says he wants to win the championship
Her brother never won a championship back then.
They even claim to be from a basketball family.
They really made Wolf Clan lose all face.
I must help my brother win the championship.
To reclaim our family’s glory
Why?
Why is it still not working no matter how much I practice?
Zi Tailang
coach
Let’s just leave it at that.
I understand, I’ll rest for a bit before practicing again.
I mean, with your talent
No matter how hard you try, you won’t play well.
Maybe we should give up.
Give up…
Give up, it’s no use.
Give up
It’s shameful that you can’t do it.
Give up…
Why? Why? Why, really?
I’ve clearly tried so hard
Why can’t we still win?
I will not give up, even if I can’t play on the court.
Even if it means any means
I must do it for my family.
Win the basketball championship
No matter what, I will definitely make this shot.
This game
No matter what, I must…
win
Stop her
I want those animals that look down on my brother.
Shut up!
I played this shot with everything I had.
Do you think you can stop me?
It ended in a draw.
Team Wolves have tied the score.
Zi Tailang
Is there a paramedic?
I’ve done so much to get to where I am today.
It still ended like this.
That ball just now
I can completely sense just how much you want to win.
But what you’re doing is wrong.
You should work hard with your teammates.
Defeat your opponent fair and square.
Shut up!
Do you think we haven’t tried?
If you work hard, you can win.
Why should I go to such lengths?
Trying your best doesn’t guarantee a win.
But there are many things more important than winning.
We have also been questioned by everyone.
But we still relied on our own efforts
Step by step, we’ve come this far.
Even in the face of many difficulties
We must also strive to overcome them.
Because that’s what makes sports so appealing.
The latest situation is…
Zi Tailang left the field due to injury.
Team Wolves have no backup players.
What about Victor?
No backup players?
So this year’s champion is…
According to the competition rules, I hereby announce
The champion of this year’s Basketball Game is…
Could it be…?
It’s Victor
Victor is here
Victor…
King/Majety is back, keeping her promise.
Mr. Slowy and coach
dad
Wolffy
It was really thrilling.
Team Wolves captain Victor stepped up to lead the team in time.
Victor…
Keep the game going!
Which team will ultimately win the championship?
Can Goat Clan defeat their nemesis Wolf Clan?
(to be continued)