Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Fighting Alone against Many
In the previous episode,
Weslie boosted the morale of Team Defenders.
Paddi was injured
Still desperately trying to score for the team
The Goats’ Fighting Spirit
Zi Tailang was driven to a state of madness.
The two teams eventually tied.
Wolffy and Victor finally arrived at the scene.
What kind of performance will they deliver?
team leader
I’m so sorry, Captain.
Okay
Now is not the time to apologize.
There’s still half a game left.
Listen up, everyone.
Let me tell you how to deploy next.
yes…
Thank you for your hard work just now, Paddi
Wolffy will then take your place.
Don’t worry, Paddi
Leave the rest to me, you can take a rest.
I hope you will listen carefully to what I am about to say.
You have always been looked down upon and questioned by everyone.
We’ve come this far amidst a barrage of insults.
It’s really not easy.
But you managed to get through such difficulties.
It also lets all the animals see
Ordinary steps can complete a great journey.
This moment
To be able to stand on this final stage
It’s about your efforts and mutual trust.
Affirmation of unity and perseverance
The final match
I hope you remember
Believe in yourself
Each and every one of you is a strong person.
Don’t let yourself have regrets.
Enjoy the game!
From this second onwards
That’s your most shining moment.
Timeout complete. All players, please return to the field.
The real competition is finally about to begin.
Team Defenders are getting really impressive!
Which team will win the championship?
Of course, it’s our Team Defenders.
When did you get back?
A very powerful aura
Victor scored immediately upon entering the game.
His personal abilities are simply outstanding.
There was absolutely no way to stop him.
His method was very simple.
However, the timing of its use was very precise.
Achieving the optimal state of offense and defense
So fast
That was amazing!
That shot is going to be historic.
One against many, a god descended to earth, unstoppable.
This is the only way to describe Victor’s father.
Don’t worry, Dad will definitely win.
I think Victor seems even more amazing than before.
Weslie, your feet…
Don’t worry, I can handle it.
Wolffy, listen up!
Victor is so amazing solely because of his personal abilities.
So it’s not entirely impossible to defeat him.
Okay, I understand what you’re trying to say.
The ball is back in Victor’s hands.
Team Defenders switched to a double-team strategy against Victor.
Weslie, let’s go.
Just a little bit short
A two-person pincer attack requires a high degree of teamwork.
It seems they have found a way to counter it.
Wow, Team Defenders finally broke the spell!
Victor’s offensive
Stop him
Oh no!
come on
Entered
In this competition, individual skill was unmatched.
Victor, who never misses a shot
Team Defenders
The team’s cooperative approach defeated them.
There is no law in the world that the strong will always prevail.
No matter how strong a person is
It’s not even as good as the strength of the whole team.
Awesome…
Go, Captain!
Score the ball quickly and get back into the game!
Keep it up… Great job…
The power of team
Come on, let’s score another goal!
I have a question for everyone.
Do you guys prefer one-on-one basketball?
I still prefer to cooperate with each other.
Basketball where players pass the ball around?
If I absolutely had to choose one
I think team basketball is better.
It will be easier to win the game and be happier.
Actually, I also think team basketball is pretty good.
I feel the same way.
That’s what I think too.
I think you might want to try
Cooperate more with other teammates
This will also improve the atmosphere in our team.
Then it will condense into a force
An invincible force
You have indeed become stronger.
Passing
Victor received the ball and launched another solo attack.
Team Defenders saw
Immediately launch a team encirclement tactic
As expected, it happened again.
Victor decided to rely on his own attack.
Jonie
Jonie blocked Victor’s attack.
Trying to block me?
I…don’t want to lose anymore.
Since that incident, I’ve believed…
Only by becoming a king with outstanding personal abilities
Only then can you stand on this field forever.
If you can’t beat everyone on the field
It’s completely meaningless.
But now…
On my own
Even standing at the very top
You still can’t see what’s ahead.
If I wasn’t the only one
Maybe we can see further.
Goal!
team leader
Great shot… Great shot!
Victor’s assist led Team Wolves
Victor actually passed the ball after scoring another goal?
Win the championship together
good…
Welcome back
Weslie
To be continued…