Legends of Sports Heroes: Dunk for Victories.
Champion
In the previous episode,
Victor single-handedly broke away from Team Defenders
But slowly Team Defenders
Use team tactics to counter
Victor, who was at a disadvantage
Seeing my teammates who have been working so hard
They actually handed over the offensive command to them.
Your old injury has recurred.
He can no longer play.
Otherwise, they won’t even be able to walk normally in the future.
What?
It seems they can only do so now.
Paddi came on next.
You can substitute me in anytime.
no
I can still compete.
You can’t be stubborn and keep pushing your luck.
Your foot injury is too serious.
You need to listen to Mr. Slowy and get some rest.
We will definitely help you win the championship.
As long as I can walk at this moment
I can still play, Weslie.
coach
Without my approval
No one can go on the field without permission.
coach
I don’t want you in the future
I regret this impulsive act.
I will never regret it.
Even if he can’t walk normally in the future
Do you still want to keep playing?
coach
I believe if it were you…
You will make the same decision as me.
I want to keep playing
Not just for winning
More importantly, it can be done on the field…
Fighting alongside my teammates until the very last second…
Because I don’t want to have any regrets…
What a stubborn coach
Okay, referee.
No need to switch goats, let’s continue the game.
Go, don’t leave any regrets.
The game continues
Weslie
You’ll have to work hard for my points too later.
Otherwise, I can replace you anytime.
When you feel like you can’t go on
You can rely on us…
Don’t forget we are a team
Don’t worry, I will definitely work hard.
come on…
The rest is up to you. Good luck!
With them marking so closely, it’s difficult to pass the ball out.
Not long after the serve
Team Defenders’ shot was intercepted by the opponent.
Team Wolves’ responsiveness is amazing.
Awesome…
Team Wolves…
nice shot
It’s okay, keep trying!
Both sides have entered the point-scoring phase.
Team Wolves’ offense was strong and swift.
Team Defenders were not to be outdone.
They’re now only 3 points behind.
cut…
Weslie tried to stand up.
This tenacious willpower is truly admirable.
Are you going to try to tough it out on your own again?
Of course not
The game was about to end with less than a minute remaining.
If Team Defenders
Unable to stop Team Wolves’ attack
They were out of contention for the championship.
So fast
I must…
They stopped it
rebound
That’s all…
What?
Don’t underestimate us
Good job!
Jonie, Sparky…
Go for it!
Weslie
When exactly did he…?
anyway
We will definitely…
Go for it! Keep going!
Seize the opportunity…
It will definitely happen…
That’s it, that’s it, that’s all for now…
You can’t catch up.
Hurry up and…
Give me back the ball
nice shot
That was a brilliant grab!
So stylish…
They will definitely pass the ball to you.
Trust us…
Needless to say
Of course I believe you.
Is this another one?
You’ve got some skills.
Let me see just how amazing you are!
Come on
Stop him…
Don’t even think about scoring.
Score the ball quickly, Weslie…
I will definitely not let you down.
Weslie actually dunked over Victor
The match reached a fever pitch.
The two teams were locked in a fierce battle for points.
With only 30 seconds left, the difference is now just 1 minute.
Regardless of the outcome
They’ve already won in my heart.
Look how happy they are!
This match was absolutely amazing!
Go Team Defenders!
Go Team Wolves!
I never imagined playing basketball could be so much fun!
Let’s practice hard together!
I want to prove that the Goat Clan can be very good at basketball.
I want to participate in the Grassland Basketball Game, I want to play basketball.
Basketball is truly a magical sport.
I also believe
He will definitely become the strongest basketball team captain.
I will definitely become
Your favorite basketball team captain
Yes, it makes us more confident.
Go Dad! Go Wolffy!
I’m going to use this shot – this is a back-to-the-basket move.
Make the audience open their eyes wide and see clearly
This is our true strength.
Drive us forward
I want to be a strong girl like Leopardess (elder).
Because giving it your all is the charm of sports competitions.
Makes us stronger
I don’t want to leave the team
I want to play basketball with everyone.
As long as I feel confident and dare to throw the ball, that’s fine.
I can do it.
Make us no longer lazy
I’d love to give it a try, always protecting everyone.
As the center
We must hold the line until the very last second.
It brings us the joy of striving and growing together.
Please teach me how to play basketball.
Because I want to participate in the Basketball Game and win the championship.
See you next time, my name is Leopardess (elder) and my name is Victor.
I almost forgot
Playing basketball is such a fun thing!
Charge! Go for it!
bring it on
Let’s go
Since the Basketball Game
Goats’ Village has become different.
Watch me make a three-pointer!
come on…
Weslie, that kid
I went back to play as soon as my foot got a little better.
nice shot
Master
You’ve trained Team Defenders very well.
I didn’t teach them anything.
They were the ones who taught me.
Rekindle my fire
This makes me firmly believe that team basketball is the strongest.
And prove it to me.
Basketball is more than just a sport
It is also a kind of creation
The spirit of infinite possibilities
That’s right
I believe they will create even more miracles in the future.
Wolffy, we’re rivals again.
bring it on
(Fiery passion ignites like sparks)
(Boldly charging towards the final victory)
(Friends cheer us on, fueling our spirit)
(Continuously moving forward, staying true to ourselves)
(Flying towards that miracle that belongs to us)
(Sweat pouring on this court)
(Step forward and rush towards the basket of hope)
(Leaping vigorously on the stage of youth)
(Running with speed)
(Proud and brave)
Congratulations to Team Wolves on winning the championship!
Their fierce battle with Team Defenders
This marks a perfect end to this year’s Basketball Game.
What is your wish?
(Proud and brave)
(Step forward and rush towards the basket of hope)
(Dreams relentlessly breaking through the soil)
My wish is…
It is our hope that our basketball journey
Can go further
good…
Why can’t I find that Doctor?
We should go.
Who exactly is that Doctor?
Actually, I don’t know either.
He was in this Grassland Basketball Game
They suddenly came to see me about a month ago.
He said he wanted to make a deal with me.
He said he could help me win the championship.
But I had to grant him a wish.
Based on my analysis
These robots
It shouldn’t belong to our era.
End…